Next up, an original way for kids to
express
[Music]
themselves. Hi, Sharks. My name is
Jennifer Stein Bishoff and I'm from
Brooklyn, New York. I'm seeking
$250,000 in exchange for 10% equity of
my company, Supermix Studio. Sharks. As
a mom, I've witnessed the self-esteem
boost that kids get when they pick out
their own outfit. As a designer, I
wondered how I could enable kids to
create something that's a true
reflection of who they are. Introducing
Supermix Studio, the world's first
interactive custom kids clothing brand.
Our innovative platform empowers kids to
celebrate their individuality by
designing their own clothes. If a video
game and a clothing brand had a baby, it
would be Supermix Studio. Users can
hyperpersonalize our clothing and
accessories and create something that's
100% original. Just like Jake, who loves
soccer and skating, nice, and Jasmine
who loves tennis and dance.
But Supermix is really all about the
design experience. Let me show you.
First, visit our website and choose a
style. We have sweats, denim jackets,
backpacks, and accessories, all made of
sustainable materials. Then click
customize now. Our design platform opens
up and you'll find over 500 premium
patches to choose from. Just drag and
drop and place them anywhere you want on
the style, the front, back, sleeves, and
even the hood. Step three is our job. In
our studio, we bring your child's
masterpiece to life. As you can see, May
is wearing the final product, just like
the one designed on screen. Nice. Nice.
And the best part, your kid won't want
to take Supermix off because they're
proud of it. That's the Supermix magic.
Sharks, who wants to join me in
empowering kids to express themselves by
literally wearing their hearts on their
sleeves? Ready, set, patch.
Good job, guys. Good job, guys. Thank
you guys. You're amazing. Thank you.
Good job, guys. Thank you, guys.
Excellent. Excellent.
Sharks, in front of you, you'll find
Super Mix that I took the liberty of
designing for you. Oh my goodness. Look
at this.
Of course. All right, I'm in. It's
really cute. Sniffle. Robert, you have
our classic denim jacket. And what
you're seeing there are our superized
patches. As I mentioned, we have over
500 patches and we have over 30 of these
large superized patches, which is really
what everybody gets super excited about.
It's really a cute idea. Very cute. This
is really well made. It is thick. This
is a jean jacket, but it's soft. Yes.
And how much is it? What would this jean
jacket cost? Sure. So, that jean jacket
is $69. That's the base price. We're
seeing an additional 15
to20 upsell in all of the patches per
design. It comes that's an amazingly
good price. It is an amazing price. What
does it cost you to make? So that denim
jacket is $1375 and as I mentioned it
retails for 69. So the margins on denim
are in the high7s. What about in the
sweatshirts? The sweatshirt. So Damon,
the sweatshirt that you have there is
705 and retails for 55. It appears that
you're actually manufacturing the
patches yourself. All of them. All of
the patches are 100% proprietary
artwork. I'm a designer. I've been in
the industry for two decades. I'm
responsible for generating billions of
dollars in What companies were you with?
Well, my first big job was for Gloria
Vanderbilt. I was hired to launch their
first ever junior brand. I would create
a gene there that ultimately was written
up as the hundred million dollar fit.
Tommy Hilfiger saw that article and the
next thing I knew I was sitting in his
office and at 28 he hired me to be the
vice president of design for Tommy Jeans
to breathe some new energy into the
brand. Wow. Jennifer, you're a real
loser. Yeah. So, you have no experience
going at all. My last role was as chief
merchandising officer for a large scale
private children's wear manufacturer. It
took my entire career to finally figure
out that kids is what I love doing the
most. This is definitely the most fun
I've had in in my whole career. What
inspired you to say enough of the
corporate world? It was the pandemic and
my kids were home and I was just looking
for things to keep them busy. We started
tie dying and putting patches on things.
I was like, "This is so much fun. This
is the white space idea that I'm keeping
for myself. I love this." So, you're
rolling out kiosks. Where would the
kiosk be going? So, we're looking at
taking these kiosks to all kinds of
physical locations. The first people
that we're testing the kiosk with is
actually with Claire's. They're the
premier destination of all things tween.
Smart, but we're also looking at putting
them in kids clubs at resorts and on
cruise ships and of course department
stores and boutiques. Okay. So, when you
came in, I thought that this was you do
this online, direct to consumer. I go to
your website. That's correct. Yeah, me
too. Is this now an expansion? Yes. But
Jennifer, why? Well, because I'm a trend
forecaster and that's how I've been
successful in my career by doing things
that haven't been done before. And this
is an incredible instore experience.
Everything's about retail tamement. What
are your sales? I launched in October of
22. My first holiday season was $60,000.
Okay. And year to date, we've done 110.
So, it's 170 lifetime sales. You're not
making any money yet, are you? Not yet.
You're not selling the kiosk at all.
You're putting them in stores, right?
It's a very interesting relationship
with our retail and venue partners. I
hate this kiosk idea. Take your retail
shackles off. Set yourself free. I am be
reborn. I am reborn and I'm very happy
to go into this from a DTC perspective,
but we all know that customer
acquisition costs are very expensive and
they're rising and they're getting more
and more difficult. This is customer
acquisition. Yeah, but it's not. This is
It's not. And here's why. Because we've
gotten to the point now with direct to
consumer where there's online and
there's instore. And typically when you
make the decision to go in store, it's
the immediiacy of the product, right? I
can grab it and get it right there. That
doesn't happen with your kiosk. I think
you're going to have people walk up to
it and maybe put in some information
which is great for customer acquisition
and then expect it to pop out and you're
going to get a lot of canceled cards
because that product isn't right there.
So, for those reasons, I'm out.
Damon, what are you doing? I'm
struggling. I I like I like this thing a
lot. You know, this kiosk thing can
either be a massive hit or a real
problem. It's just too risky for me. So,
I'm out. Jennifer, incredible quality,
great price point. The sales are so low
and now we're going into
kiosks, but I still love
it. I I hear your feedback about the
kiosk, and it's certainly giving me a
lot to think about. The people in the
space that I've shown it to have been
very, very excited about it. It's an
incredible instore experience, keeping
people in the store longer. Why do you
pay the retailer? And the arrangement
here as we're discussing going into
Claire's is that they will receive 30%
of the revenue driven from the machine.
That's fine. It's a win-win. Ultimately,
I'm holding the inventory and
fulfilling. So, all they have to do is
put this kiosk in their store and then
it's it's 100% incremental volume. I'm
telling you, this is the next massive
children's brand. Imagine it as the
Build-A-Bear of apparel. Let me take a
stab at it. Okay. You're very impressive
and I really believe in the demand and
it all came to you during CO 19. But
before CO 19, you got a different virus.
It's called retail 19 and it's it's
running through your veins even now. You
can't let it go. It's 30 to 40% of your
margin forever. It's a curse. But she's
selling online. She's about to do
retail, which I hate. I'm sorry. I'm
out. And and don't come too close to me
with that retail 19. I mean, that's just
me.
Listen, I actually think you're pretty
brilliant. Thank you. I think that you
think out of the box. You're an
innovator. You've done something
completely unique and different. And I
think it's super smart. I see this for
Disney. I see this as in places where
you have the mom and the kid. They're a
captive audience, right? It's empowering
and it feels empowering to me. All
right. So, okay. We're going to make you
an offer. I don't know. We're going to
figure it out. I mean, honestly, I've
never done a kids clothing line. Oh,
we're going to do a kids clothing line.
So, at this point, yeah, while you're on
to a great thing, it's still pretty
early. We're going to offer you
250,000. We want 25%.
We'd also like a royalty because we
think a cash flow of 5%. Until we make
back the initial 250,000. After that, it
goes away. 5%. And then it goes away.
What a bad deal. Well, you can
negotiate. I mean, Mark, you're not
putting up any money. Mark is not in
this deal. I do not find that a bad deal
in today's market. Capital is completely
dried up, particularly in your space.
The fact you have an offer goes to your
credibility in your past. Even though
you are infected with retail 19,
obviously, it's really important for me
to remain liquid and to be able to grow
this company. So, I'd like to counter at
20%
and 2% royalty.
I'm sorry. I just can't.
All right, Jennifer.
250,000, 20% equity, 3.5% royalty.
Lori, I'm good with that. Are you? The
royalty goes away after you're paid
back. Correct.
You have a deal. Amazing.
Thank you so much, Lori.
Congrats. Well done. Great presentation.
Thank you so much.