is today Tuesday yes you have to edit
this tonight as well [ __ ] okay no
problem Rush no problem
problem are you serious like God for I'm
going to do I have to switch seats to
Chris again I'd love for that the amount
of times I sit in the middle you need
some space camp right now I know guys I
know is that am I saying that wrong I
don't like the way you said my lips are
super irritated but my space camp
Wellness is helping so much okay today
we're filming a video that Nick and Matt
planned and I don't know what it is I
don't know what it it is either to be
honest yeah Matt it was Matt's idea but
it was like a halfway idea and me and
him kind of just like immediately acted
on it so F little 30 second story time
me and Matt built Lego sets and you
built a Lego set and we were like all
legoed up and then Chris was like yo if
you go to Target get me another Lego set
so we were going to go surprise Chris
with a Lego set we were in the Lego
aisle of a small Target which also is
the Kitty toy aisle like super kitty
kitties like little babies Toddlers and
such
so Matt it struck Matt he was like
playing with the kids toys he goes I
think it'd be funny if we like played
with these for a video so we bought a
bunch of we bought a bunch of children's
like like baby children's toys and
you're happy about it Matt not mad about
it okay F we also met um two girls that
watched our YouTube videos and she was
so nice yeah we picked their Lego set
it's their first Lego as a couple so it
was pretty pretty they were so cute it
was these two two girls and they were
adorable and they were about to play
Legos they were so nice so if that was
you she said she going to watch the
video so it was nice to meet you and
talk this is what this is this yeah this
is what we were doing she asked me what
was going to happen I said I have no
[ __ ] idea but we're buying it yeah
you said who knows could to tell you egg
with a horn this is the rainbow corns
fairy corn princess surprise um I didn't
think we needed this this was like one
of the last things we grabbed but Matt
thought we needed it because it has over
35 princess surprises inside wow that's
a good so it's for babies let's open it
stop oh it's a it's like a egg split in
half I'm going to give the kid a I just
like I never saw I never saw the appeal
to little kids
who holy [ __ ] there's like one unicorn
surprise where's the other there going
to be like a smaller thing I hate this
texture how much did you guys just pay
for this my total at Target was like 200
you can wear the wings okay hold on this
is important so if you this is super
cute like the sparkles on the back and
stuff you can keep it this is the most
uncomfortable stuff wait how do we get
the Wings off hold on well I don't like
this I hate it I like these little
silver off what should we name it ew
it's getting glitter on me already throw
this thing away wo oh it's a stupid
little thing oh my goodness are you
going to wear it oh
yes what is that frencher bracelets the
wings wow I feel like they're just not
creative with kids toys at all anymore
can I get something else on this well
yeah I feel like there's supposed to be
more additions what the [ __ ] is that
there's supposed to be hold up a mini
egg in the egg there's supposed to be 35
surprises inside and I think that it's
the I think there's five surprises and
the other 30 are surprises of
disappointment how much you
paid this is like real this is a charm
bra stand than do what is this what is
this turn around turn around yeah arms
up oh my God I don't think it's supposed
to tie behind me is it Nick wings dude
this is [ __ ] stupid let me see I
definitely didn't do it right Nick hold
on you flip it yeah hold on yes Nick
this is cool actually you look nice do I
look like I'm going to you look like
this dude twin and um oh wait who did we
get is that oh that's um gimi Jimi
that's Ruby that's clearly it's Ruby
it's clearly Ruby is it Ruby it's
definitely Ruby oh it is Ruby cuz oh
then they want you to collect them all
so it's a scam they want you to waste
oh wait what happens to the stomach I'm
like pissed
off each bead is one surprise yeah
that's hon one surprise two surpris the
only thing surprising is how mid this
toy is I feel like too many kids toys
recently have had to do with like eggs
and like hatching them like where can I
just get my [ __ ] toy if we had a kid
and I was trying to be like a cool puy
corn bear corn yeah they should add uni
in front of each oh we just got unicorn
that's all we got that's so boring we
didn't oh we could have got Kitty corn
yeah I would have been 10 times more
interested if we got a different animal
in a unn did we know we were getting
this [ __ ] no I would have bought
it no yeah you just buy the egg what if
you buy the egg trying to get all of
them and you just get the same
[ __ ] yeah I can't believe we
just got that's probably why I don't
like it that much cuz we just got
unicorn when there were so many yeah we
got puppy corn I would have been turn
with Kitty corn dude Kitty corn the tail
sticking out if I was trying to be like
a cool put this thing back put this
thing that doesn't go in the egg that
that one around it remember well did you
guys see this egg no all right what do
you rate that toy out of 10 zero if I
was trying to be a cool uncle and this
is how I'm rating it I would not get
this for your kids I think they'd laugh
at me yeah I agree I would get this like
if I was try You' get this man no I
wouldn't get it like come on put that
away boring all right we have this is
fashion we got mini we got oh mini
brands are actually cool yeah mini
Brands I saw this girl on Tik Tok get
arrested cuz she stole a ton of these
what a [ __ ] psychopath Let each get
one okay oh it's like checklist wait we
might actually be we might have to do
this what do you guys want the most stop
stop stop stop stop what do you guys
want the mostop hold on what do you want
the most okay oh I want the 7-Eleven
Double Cup you get the double G cup
slurpy oh my God Nick there's a glue gun
sour jelly beans wa wait These are nice
that one's not on here check really rare
check the back check the back check the
back and bean boozled as well oh no it's
here it's here it's here how we getting
oh no it's not I don't see it yet
oh yeah they're both right here okay
nice how wait there's Mentos we can get
Mentos wait these are kind of cool this
is like cute but like now what I know
one of these are rare like oh who opened
this I did a shitel Smith Smiths what is
that mints I don't know sugar-free gum I
think boring this is boring that one's
oh my God a girod deli chocolate cake
wait that's fire
I love that wait does it actually have
all the mini
Coke mini
Coke hold on how much sugar this as this
has zero sugar this makes me really want
to have like an attic that I can go up
to a I want like a little like a little
Smurf Village and I can little store
like yeah like I want to like well no
it's still not in comparison is it well
no if you took a can of Coke and then a
bean boozled and put them side by side
this would probably be a little accurate
so we get like a character nuh-uh yeah
and our character is themed off of a
candy and we make the character good God
this dude the [ __ ] is this is it naked
that's not good what is happening let me
see let me see let me see what is
happening what's happening in the toys
nowadays dude what is going on look you
know how it comes to this Haribo cup I
saw on the thing you can fill this with
water I'm stunned I love [ __ ] like this
the water's turning yellow and then you
can like give it the water I
think it's like bubbles it's spitting up
it's okay we had his
back if that thing squirts water out of
its mouth I'm freaked out Nick Nick it's
like if
you nick are you [ __ ] kidding me that
like why what
is yeah the water's out of it buddy I
just spit up stupid toyi all right kids
toys not we going downhill the mini ones
are the coolest so far yeah those are
the coolest that those are like way up
there and then that was number two the
egg still third in my opinion no yeah
cuz the spit up I don't know stop
calling it spit up dude that's what it
was it spit up dude it like get the next
toy like projectile it's like who wants
a little dolly that you can dress up and
then make projectile vomit okay so this
is my pet lamb snowy love him I actually
love it hold on hold
on oh I walk on a leash okay walk him
like a dog first things first let's hit
the try me
[Music]
button yes that was cute that was cute I
like that a lot that was a nice dance
this is like a toy I'd like
yeah I agree now we're
moving do you like
it I can't
look wait wait what happens if you do it
on the table wait no it says wait wait
wait it says walking watch your lamb
walk by giving her a hatat on the back
hold on to the leash and see where she
takes you let me wait let
me you're going to drop snowy oh you got
to turn her
[Laughter]
on I me like on the bottom dude the
actual power button you guys are sick
okay snowy hold
on yeah you just got to hit it was in
tryy mode and you have to turn it
on oh God you got to turn her off did
you name it snowy or is this
thought's thing oh my God I thought
he wait can I have it can I have it hold
on hold on hold on ready I want to play
you got to turn it on let me see no so
the first I want to put the leash on
first can I do it can I put the leash on
you've had this thing for an
hour I think this Tes the cake literally
fighting yeah we're two 20-year-olds
fighting over the lamb snowy the
like this clearly is the best toy you
guys are fighting over snowy mat stop
beting it with a [ __ ]
thing wait should
kill what else can snowy do at the tail
Mt stop ping it's really cute though
press the mode button let me see
this
oh she wanted this n wait wait no wants
this no hold on I don't like her bottle
oh she's dancing party
mode wait get over here get
back oh I like that little tail
Shake yes Queen
Dance Let her walk let her
walk that's cute I like that stop
pulling we're to go all the way to you
and then you can I I haven't wait pet
her yeah I like that I like the dancing
okay okay hold on give pats on the head
for nurturing it says I don't want to do
that nurture her no we have to great you
have to pretend it's you have to pretend
this isn't snowy the electronic toy it's
snowy the baby we have to okay wait
there's two more things Pat the head to
nurture it no you're feeding it patting
the head is the that's what no you also
have to feed it no one at a
time
I don't
like okay stop okay now you can feed
[Music]
it
oh bless
you you good sis okay okay feed it
actually thirsty don't make any of this
weird pretend it's
okay us
pretend I have a kid right and this is
my baby and I'm introducing you guys you
guys are uncles for the first time and
it's snowy this is all normal okay was
that a disclaimer or
something did she just fart excuse me
that was clearly a burp oh MOS did she
just fart no that was a
burp that's
cute Barbie cutie reveal okay Barbie
cutie
reveal six surprises this one only has
Beats that
2 hey get back here get back here bless
you
snore I think she's snoring now she is
snoring hey snowy wake
up time for
school okay okay you're so dramatic
you're so
shut up she like immediately singing and
dancing yeah you're just asleep dude
this is hard to open give me this thing
Matt like what is this is this another
[ __ ] thing
we I thought I just Ed it it's a furry
wait is it just it's a doll instructions
is to undress it and it's like a a a a
doll wait so it's playing pretend I
think like to be an animal I don't I
didn't you get a furry or a girl no it's
like both whatever you want be but you
get this one like the oh this one's cute
this little thing is supposed to change
it's supposed to change the way it looks
under temperature so right now it's this
and then let's put it in this water are
we pl maybe this thing changes if it
goes in water
Nick I mean water waterboard the
girl yeah that was a fit it was a little
teddy bear just making maybe that goes
underwater nick nick no she doesn't
change one of these things Chang is
underwater no it's not Nick why would it
be the little soft cushiony thing I
don't know oh maybe it's the heart on
the chest guys you're taking guesses
read the manual are going to care that
much I it is it her hair was this blue
yes that was blue no do this thing come
off does this thing
demask it does it's like the [ __ ]
it's like Rey Mysterio I think it's
supposed to be this thing Nick no you
wouldn't have to get that wet nothing is
changing
underwater that thing is it looks
exactly no it's one eye shut it's
winking now oh okay so this stupid
little thing changes the slightest bit
in water it Winks it it goes like this
it goes to bed if you if you waterboard
this little bear it goes to bed in an
hour time let's listen to the question
and use our tools to answer Matt we need
our tools to we use the hit press the
right button to answer Hammer Hammer
Hammer fantastic job thank you I wish my
waist is which button shows
thech wrench this is the wrench
wrench hey you're doing
great slow
[Music]
down all right no put it in work mode
get out of the question
drill drill hammer this button is red
yeah I
Goa woohoo music time press the tool
buttons to play some
songs
[Music]
Hammer can I have a
drill yeah drill drill drill
you got to change it so if you want to
put it in you got to go that way I got
you take out you that way I got you I
got to go in right
[Applause]
now
nice nice I'm quick with it let me get
this out time the wrench I'll be out of
here by 330 wrench please
nice drench please don't you worry I've
been doing this for quite some time
no the wrench is for this yeah dude the
wrench is for those this is the hammer
that one you you hammer in
oh so it's a wrench and a Dr tool and
let's get to work shut up I have the
tool bels on I think we're done let me
see
stop let him keep going Let's do an
outro yeah well guys that I think this
one was really fun like I was clearly
entertained for a
bit there you go that's for the L lamby
wins Lambie wins and then I think this
box the
second what are you tell any
more hard it's hard to dude this kid's
like loving it like actually this is
really fun I think that yeah Lambie wins
and the toolbox is
sick oh my God also just in case you
guys were wondering we're not throwing
this all away my mom's going to donate
it to some little kids she knows so kids
kids will have fun with these toys this
just giggle yeah yeah I don't know it's
a little ridiculous press the tool
button we had fun and then some kids are
going to have fun with these toys as
well um let us know what you guys think
what toy here would you buy if you were
a little
kid I can't get that one we're going to
go anyway we need to go nice to see you
guys thank you guys so much for tuning
in and see you on
[Music]
Friday and then
you