But I've been investing and working in
technology companies since 1999. I've
seen a bunch of technologies come and
go. I saw the first crash. I was working
in the mobile phone industry when all of
a sudden the world discovered mobile
phones. What I think that does is it
changes the lens under which you look at
new technologies and new developments.
When I was investing in 2022, I was not
investing in what everybody else was
investing in because I felt like we were
going straight up the hype curve. You
want to invest when nobody else is
investing. And if everybody's investing
in the same thing, you probably
shouldn't be in there. You should
wait. Hi, my name is Terry Doyle. I'm
the managing partner of Telus Global
Ventures. We're the corporate venturing
arm of Telus, which is a Canadian
headquartered global technology and
services business. So, we have about 90
companies in our portfolio. 60% of them
have a commercial deal with Telus. Last
year we did about $34 million of
business with our portfolio
companies. Age is not a determination of
intelligence. And in fact, some of the
best founders I meet are great because
they don't have preformed ideas.
Sometimes you meet people and they've
got lots of experience and because of
that experience something that hasn't
worked they sort of shut their minds off
that doesn't work I can't do this I
can't solve this problem this way
whereas I think sometimes people who
maybe don't have that experience they
bring a very new perspective to solving
a problem and say they don't make
assumptions if you talk to people in in
great companies like uh Google they
spend a lot of time trying to prevent
people from making those assumptions
Your response to this question is X. Do
you realize that there's two assumptions
that are part of that? Why have you made
those assumptions? Oh, that's always how
it's always been. Removing that bias
almost is where you get some real
breakthroughs. We've invested in
companies like Clinia, which has really
developed an AIdriven optimized search
for enterprise customers and that helps
providers give better outcomes to
patients. We knew we had a lot of data,
but again, data is only as good as how
it's presented, how it's accessed.
Lineia has really changed the way we
think about what we can do with that
data and that business. It's changed how
our customers think about their own
data, but also how they they run their
businesses. Creating that shift in the
way we think and how our customers think
was really one of the important outcomes
that we got in making that investment.
But I've been investing and working in
technology companies since 1999. I've
seen a bunch of technologies come and
go. I saw the first dot crash when web
van got hundreds of millions of dollars
investment and then went bankrupt. You
know, I was working in the mobile phone
industry when all of a sudden the world
discovered mobile phones. What I think
that does is it changes the lens under
which you look at new technologies and
new developments.
2014 I was spending time with a whole
bunch of some of the best people in the
world in artificial intelligence. This
is great. You know, it's going to be a
good development. Maybe I won't be as
excited about the changes in the
marketplace as if I'd never seen those
previous cycles. It means that when I
was investing in 2022, I was not
investing in what everybody else was
investing in because I felt like we were
going straight up the hype curve. You
want to invest when nobody else is
investing. And if everybody's investing
in the same thing, you probably
shouldn't be in there. You should wait.
When a good investor is able to see a
fundamental shift in society, you know,
the consulting firm McKenzie has a
language which is horizon 1, horizon 2,
horizon 3. Horizon 1 is something that
we can use now. It's getting to the
beginning parts of the use of its life
in as a technology. Horizon 3 is well
into the future, very far away from
being commercialized. More like
fundamental science. We will sometimes
want to make an investment in a Horizon
3 company and the business just doesn't
see the opportunity for it. The area of
quantum security is a good example of
this. We know that at some point in the
future quantum will change how people
can they will create tools where people
can do harm just as we start to see in
AI. We've done some investing in quantum
security and we're not quite at that
point where we can use it. We have to
make a an educated guess. Okay, we think
this is going to be problem in the
future. So we we should probably invest
early and learn get we'll call it
tuition value about how this particular
space is evolving and as a result we'll
wait five or 6 years before we have any
commercial deal with the company. Being
able to spot the large shifts make you
better able to invest in the right
things. I think if you jump at every new
development I think you're probably
going to have a hard time. You're
probably going to make a lot of
mistakes.
You know, I talk to my team all the time
about this idea that we will make
mistakes. As soon as you say that, that
changes the way people do things because
they don't freeze up. They're not
nervous about making a mistake. So, one,
we're going to make mistakes. Most
important thing is acknowledge that
you've made a mistake. Second is fix the
mistake as best you can. And third is
obviously the most important thing.
Don't make the same mistake twice. I
think if you create that environment for
people, they feel more comfortable. They
explore options more. they don't freeze
up and be conservative in how they
think. And I think that's that's really
our job. Our job is to take risk on
behalf of the company and do that in a
way which is sensible, but to push the
company and to help get more technology
into the hands of our customers to make
their lives
better. You'll hear many investors talk
about are you investing in the
individual or are you investing in the
idea or the market. I think the
individual is really the most
determinative factor. Somebody's ability
to solve problems and continue to work
at problems even when they're not making
headway is the sign of a good
entrepreneur. There's a level of
stubbornness there which really is
important in taking on big problems.
That problem solving mentality and that
ability to continue to work even though
there's no progress. I think that's one
of the things that makes good founders.
And so our job is to really find great
founders who are solving significant
problems. And if you find those people,
generally you can usually find people
who want to give them money to solve
those problems. That's really what
you're doing as an investor. You're
finding money and you're finding smart
people and you're bringing them
together. Being a founder is a really
hard job. It's an exceptionally hard job
and you have to have that ability to
wake up every day and want to take on
and solve a difficult problem. And so I
think the thing that I find rewarding is
every time I work with a founder and I'm
able to help them go that little bit
farther on their journey, that's
rewarding for me.