baby grind on
me I like your
hat all right y'all welcome back to
another St Tri it's back I need a
haircut OG fortnite is back right now OG
fortnite brings tears to my eyes it can
make a grown man cry basically when me
and M Chris were growing up we never
ever played video games we got our first
gaming system freshman year when high
school started which is a lot of when
our mental health issues started so
Chris just bonded with fortnite in a
severe level so all throughout high
school fortnite was like our favorite
thing they brought back the fortnite
that used to be around when we were
freshman really really really briefly
for those of you that watch the stola
triplets and have no idea what the [ __ ]
is happening with fortnite I'm going to
explain the game to you so that you can
enjoy today's video very very briefly
and quick freshman YY maer started
playing fortnite this is what the map
looks like over time without all the
years fortnite was trying something new
and they did a bunch of different
updates across the screen right now well
They're bringing back the map with some
of the updates from the old game
basically fortnite is 100 people in a
Lobby and you guys all have to work
together to be the last one standing
okay you're fighting everybody else and
you're using material that you find on
the map to build so that you can survive
achieve and win basically me maners are
going to take turns every single time
that one of us kills somebody we're
going to swap the remote I'm going to
start then I'm going to pass to Matt
then I'm going to pass to Chris it's a
super fast-paced game so there's going
to be a really really it's going to be
really scary to transition from triplet
to Triplet mid game but we're going to
do it we're going to get a victory
Royale and you guys are coming along
let's go all right all right guys so we
are about to get started here but first
things first we're all going to have to
pick a pick a skin as a group no yeah
we're not picking your ugly that
Flamingo guy is kind of cool no he's
hideous Nick I'm not being a [ __ ] Tru
no that one's sick the baseball one yeah
that hard I'm with fast fast ball let's
go tilted Towers if you don't know is
the most popular place in the entire
game and the hardest to survive
so that's where we're going to land
every single round Nick just try to kill
someone off ri right now Nick kill him
that's H get him get him get him get him
go pick pickax him pix him
pickaxe yes give
me I need a headset I need a headset
come on nice I like good yeah yeah
yeah good [ __ ] here you know I I know I
know right
there SWAP SWAP SWAP SWAP okay okay M's
a bot you're trap and switch nade
launcher for Porta for Hold on shut up
there's a kid right here drink the mini
the mini shut up [ __ ] shut up once you
swap I got in my mouth tra me I'm sorry
Nick that's on this floor come on hold
on here here here that's me head at me
you're good you're good there's no one
nearby
okay we were doing so good how Nick you
got guys you [ __ ] [ __ ] get him get
him get him Nick run his [ __ ] get him
get him get him Nick go
Nick give me where was he give me where
was he when he shot me for so much
damage dud you suck at where was he when
he shot me for so much
damage kid nearby a bunch of kids Matt
like if I get a kill be ready basically
said we got to get
kill nice [ __ ]
work oh my God I to CH my pant come on
Matt what would you guys do if I poop
myself that's gross Nick I got really
nervous and I just like actually Nick
stop not looking good you have a chug
jug it's
over Nick Nick you're off rip pump
shotgun last game was what he say you
[ __ ]
[ __ ] I was a little shocked I got a
little angry you dumb [ __ ] you dumb
[ __ ] you dumb [ __ ] where are
you I'm done
for stupid
[ __ ] s and I have the worst Glide ever
so many people are going to beat me
[Music]
hi what are you doing it's Mr Sant CL
go
up Nick I just spit
everywhere did you say to me [ __ ] it's
never
over oh this is no good get there get
there Nick
what I saw I saw
oh
oh all
right oh
11 Nick what are you
doing where are they
all I'm going to find them right
now all right we're going greasy Grove
we're going to switch it up for this
next
attempt it's over he was not under that
floor if you weren't trying to Boogie
bomb for the whole [ __ ] 10 minutes it
would have been a different story guys
can we post for th really
quick we never do this [ __ ] okay ready
[Laughter]
set hold on taking fall damage
nice great great great fabulous
work there's another kid there you have
to be the one to get him stink them
shoot him with stink pug
grenades stink pug get this stink
pug I'm so excited M fatal FS right now
you already have the [ __ ] you need great
[ __ ] work
Nick threw up drinkie drink took a sip
of drinkie little drinkie a little
drinky for the brosi want a drinkies
let's drink brokies let's get beer let's
get drunk little BR drink up drink Dr
the alcohol maybe and go crazy little
big shieldy for the big drinkie big
drinkie big night out bar
time see you lights out is there another
person good night you're supposed to put
that on me guys we need to not yell we
live in a
neighborhood oh my God the camera camera
he going to die
oh my God it's okay guys I have two
batteries yes but I don't think the
other one's plugged in right now which
is not good Nick it's okay Nick build
Nick Nick build build build build what
the [ __ ] are you doing get on a gun
shoot him Nick give me the remote give
me the remote give me the remote give me
I have
to go charge the camera get a
camera no oh [ __ ] guys this kid's good
oh my
God no I hit him too motherfucker's at
what MCO murder
him from behind getting absolutely lit
up like that is something uncomp the
dude
wait Nick don't Nick I it literally
fully cringes me out when he does that I
have to like plug my ears Nick stop you
open 50 of these a day get all my teeth
you Gremlin okay just think of the sound
oh my God it freaks me out dud I just
think of your big tooth like falling out
my big teeth are strong I actually have
a fake Big Tooth I know that's why it
freaks me out one fake Big Tooth well
half of it
fake what are you going to die every
time okay stop yelling when we die as
well no cuz I'm probably going to die
right now no you're not Nick oh my God
there's a gajillion people
here Nick ah you're
done oh my God that was [ __ ]
up make your Daddy proud C that's a
crazy thing to say
yeah out of the sky you're not real
they killing [ __ ] out the sky
bro no get ammo ammo to the
left kill Nick he's fighting somebody
straight I know
I'm like the worst I can't you're the
best he's in a [ __ ] goddamn go the
bottom of it go in the bottom of it just
go to the bottom of the port
Fort what is this going to do just go in
it there's another person throwing aen
this kid's ass kill
him I'm shooting I you to God I was
lagging you have
to oh no no no grab the tag really yes
Nick you already suck with heavy
shotguns come on Nick stop standing
still I really want this Grappler grab
it for the SMG then SMG attack Nick you
don't need wait do you guys like this
one better no really yes I do dude come
on no yes
dude no it's fine I'll live without it
dude you don't need the SMG you have a
tack like that's what I don't get he
wants okay fine we'll get the grappler
yeah like you don't you have attack shot
shut up put the deagle in the last slot
please put your mother in the last slot
please eat that corn yeah I'm getting
there tell me what to do I'm jumping I'm
going to take ball damage and
die Nick don't use the deagle you're not
going to hit the
shot I wish you'd tell me less about
what I'm going to
do yeah edit on me
[ __ ] I can't even build that's why I got
this grappling hook little Doo I'm about
to be in your tea oh no Nick I'm so
awful guys I know just lay low you don't
have any backup Shields he Chop It Down
chop it down no don't chop it down wait
kind of a good idea no it's a terrible
idea oh he's throwing grenades at me
grabble the height grabble the height
grabble the
height now turn around shoot him where
is
he Nick I'm going to [ __ ] myself heck
you have to
win all right
sh Nick you are the what can I
do go
back don't panic I'm not panicking I
just want to get the kill as fast as I
can yeah you're
panicking he's
dead he atrocious
aort if if the P ch was a good
gun nice there's more people Nick
there's more people Far Side Far Side
Far Side far left far
left look with your AR with your
AR you need health so don't shut up
don't fight you need health yeah I'm
having a panic attack my headset's not
on fully okay Nick you need to use your
own hands like we don't know where your
[ __ ] head is yeah I didn't have a
moment to breathe thanks Matt genius
he's about to be
dead you're dead me closer to you
is nice [ __ ]
work that's actually golden Matt shoot
the wall shoot the wall shoot the wall
shoot it shoot it with an AR before the
rocket shoot
it you got him full damage oh my God put
it on my head put it on my head reload
your reload
Nick oh he ducked under it he ducked
under it that been awesome Nick that was
a great shot so good guys call me stupid
I don't care don't don't okay okay right
he's going to be yeah just build build
build you're not done
H rocket launch from low ground and I
just yeah it doesn't do anything though
you're just breaking his wall don't peek
him don't peek him what are you doing
Nick you're actually like [ __ ]
terrible at this game
really you I didn't do that did I last I
last I'm really worried oh my God we're
awful you're awful I you just
died it doesn't matter you no cuz we're
going to try our best if you you should
not get the ninth kill until there's
like four people left and then Chris
should avoid everyone till the last
person oh my God that's so good so
good nick nick it's oh it's me it's me
it's me it's me you're in my Matt's in
my way Matt's in my way may I say Matt's
in my way Nick this is huge that we have
this gun yeah I'm trying to find someone
you also need mats bad but you're
good awesome that was not
cool good
shot there's no one there he's he killed
the other kid right there right there he
so bad he went up he went up went
up oh my
God Nick Nick Nick sorry you I wasn't I
wasn't ready give it to me I just
hearded running car coming I know be
ready Nick it's okay I'm like ready for
f where did this idiot just
go uh-oh
give me it give me it give me it give me
it really is
like oh my God we're
good I'm very prepared to switch I have
to wait for him to kill cuz I can't kill
and then have the other kid kill while
we switch no Nick can kill the other kid
I could chis I know but it has to be
like I have to be
like maybe not oh they're good wait I
might be [ __ ] here right after Chris
just killed the better one our camera's
about to die again I have the batteries
been charging now what if I chop it
out yeah get them
both cuz then that counts toward
kills the other one's there Nick did I
get them both yeah you killed them both
who's the [ __ ] best I'm the [ __ ]
best I'm
f needed that needed that [ __ ] need
guys we need to reset that we need to
reset that it's going to die it's
plugged in behind me guys we're
resetting the camera I'm going to
literally sit and do nothing sniper
instead of what the rift Rift
yeah if Nick put the Bush on put the
Bush on and snipe someone SN shot to the
Nick shot on I'm putting the Bush on I
know I'm just making sure you
know what
oh that that ruin Nick he went to the
left he's shooting at me he's an
idiot I'm [ __ ] better snipe him in
the face I'm
trying thank
God
oh my God oh my God I did that Nick good
[ __ ] good [ __ ] I can't believe that
didn't hit him come on pretty up
though hold on Matt look to your right
look to your right a little bit more
sorry an illusion just happened but
you're good I thought I saw something
like my bad that was insane you don't
need to Lo them we're better at the game
chug jug kid kid kid oh let them drink
it wait for them to drink
it Matt Matt Matt we're that kid was so
good all do we take guys before I move
do we take dude our bush is with saving
us right
[Laughter]
now please don't shoot him out of the
sky cra cuz you'll blow your cover guys
I want to do it no don't don't think it
I need the bush think about it I need
the
bush did he see you
move I lost the bush it's okay you have
to kill this
kid not one [ __ ] piece of Health go
on you're good chill okay I'm going to
knock all down shut up you don't have to
knock it all down all right go to the
edge of Zone and kind of run to the
right you have to kill someone you guys
going to stop talking to me now toward
the right a little shut
up right there right there up there OMG
chill oh God he's going to be take your
time take your time I'm going yes take
your time Nick just do it oh he's up
there ni you can snipe the [ __ ] out of
him wait oh you could have pulled go go
on top of the house on top of the White
House him oh yes you can
Nick yes Nick [ __ ] let go let go
that's a cheat dude you can't I can
breathe forever I can
breathe kill the next two kids oh no one
just one you're kill number 10 you're
kill 10 Matt okay guys Matt we have
officially made it we've been swapping
kills every single time we're one kill
away with two people left from a 10 kill
Victory Royale swapping the entire
game oh they're both there I think are
they teaming on you if these guys are
teaming I give up no no if they're
teaming you would have got buried I'm
going to kill him with the Trap Matt up
there yeah I'm going to get him with the
Trap I'm going to get him with the Trap
I'm going to get him with the Trap you
have to be ready to rotate if he dies
though I
know well I don't think he'll die yes if
he if he's 150 Health he will well mat
your head's peeking out so yeah I know
I'm fine I might boot
myself I might Bo myself guys this is
everything we've been wanting oh my God
it's actually getting real like my heart
shut up it's getting real shut up dude
this is real life oh I got do look to
your right Nick Nick yeah if M kills
someone yank the chair away no I'm going
to take his headset off and pull the
chair away like I don't want I just
won't kill someone you have to just do
it in the storm in the storm kill
him no no he's got to kill him he's got
to kill yeah but just kill they're in
the trees build
build Dead one one ni [ __ ] Matt come on
you have to do
this don't try and hunt it rifle him
he's right in front of you I got
it Nick ni this is the moment of truth
it's the moment of everything not my
edit button by the
way yeah you're rotating the stairs dude
I think am I yeah no I'm not no it was
Chris cuz he had played last shoot the
trees yeah
yeah the [ __ ] above
you
yes we [ __ ] go mat we [ __ ] go yes
yes Victory Royale that's how we
doit put put
Tri go get R me 10 kills guys dude that
was I want to thank my mom I want to
thank OG fortnite coming back I want to
thank my freshman
yourself oh my gosh Dad Dad you said my
mom she just came to my mind really
quick dad oh my God guys we did it dude
that was amazing my God I'm so proud W
those are pretty good stats too I'm so
proud of us 50% accuracy really good oh
my God let us know if you guys want us
to try that challenge again I now have
to go edit for the next 13 hours of my
life I really hope you guys like
fortnite content cuz it's so fun it's so
fun I really want to stream
it just saying don't tell them that cuz
then they'll never hear the end of it
just
saying guys thanks for watching every
single Wednesday Friday and Monday video
that we post we wouldn't be able to do
anything without you and you better edit
me today please I want to brag about it
I want to tie and not oh my god well
there it is guys the ultimate OG
fortnite challenge 10 kill triplet
rotation every kill challenge I'm going
to go to
bed love you guys thanks for tuning in t
fantastic play fortnite for yourself
it's pretty fun it's so much fun