when is it time to call it? When is the
chapter closed? I think one big piece of
advice is I think we're often as
entrepreneurs, we have a lot of weight
on our shoulders and between Instagram
and Artifact, I did some angel
investment and it's never positive news
when an entrepreneur tells you that a
company doesn't work. But I've seen it
before, you know, and so it's not a
surprise that some companies don't work
out. That's baked into the model. And so
I guess the advice I would give is
really check in with your investors and
don't I've seen entrepreneurs get stuck
in this idea like I have to keep going
because my investor expects me to and I
think what they'll find is sometimes
investors are like you're trying you've
tried it all in this space. I think it's
time to to call it and that's okay. And
you know it's never it's never a
celebration but it doesn't have to be
you know a tragedy
either. I'm Mike Kger. I'm currently the
chief product officer um at Anthropic
which is an AI company based here in San
Francisco. I co-founded Instagram and
was its chief technology officer from
about 2010 to 2018. So nice crazy
journey that we had there too. Started
one other company with the same founder
as Instagram called Artifact which was a
AI news startup and then uh joined
Anthropic just under a year ago. So it's
been the kind of third chapter in my
professional career and it's been it's
been a lot of fun so far.
Credit my dad for a lot of this. He
brought home a computer for us when I
was about four. I remember it had it
around Microsoft Daws still. It didn't
even have Windows. But one of the things
that was very cool is you can just type
edit and you would be able to open up
the files and all the even the apps that
came with the computer. And so I think I
liked taking things apart and putting
them back together. And I think I really
liked seeing how things worked. So it
sparked very early for me when I was
just four. when it came time to decide
what my career was going to be. What was
interesting was in Brazil at the time,
there wasn't really the same kind of
technology industry as there is today.
And so I didn't have any friends or
parents friends who were working in
tech. And so I didn't really see it as a
career for me. I just thought it was a
thing other people did. And so it
actually only really took me until I
came to California that I realized that
this childhood interest that I had
actually was something that I could do
as a career and and make a whole living
off of.
When I got to Stanford, I discovered
that they had this degree program called
Symbolic Systems, which only Stanford
has, and it's kind of this little
strange program that when I was there, I
think per year they had about 40 or 50
students, and now I think it's more than
200. So, it's really grown, which is
great. What I loved about it is that it
wasn't just computer science which I was
interested in but it also included
design it included philosophy included
psychology and it was really you think
about the idea of the program it's not
just to study computing it's to study
the the whole context around why we
build software that was really powerful
for me because I knew I liked design and
I liked making things useful for people
but I also liked the actual building you
know of those things so I think a few of
the things I really came out of that
program with one was this idea that
everything you build should solve a
problem for somebody, right? It's like
kind of the core of design thinking that
you identify problems, you figure out
how you can best solve them after doing
the research and then you validate what
you've built to make sure you actually
solve those problems. I think that is
really important and that's a big piece
of what I what I came out with. The
other is the value of prototyping. So,
you know, instead of just working for 6
months on a project and then showing it
to somebody for the first time and then
it turns out you got something really
fundamentally wrong, willing to build
prototypes, show them along the way and
open up the design process a lot more.
And maybe the last one is the value of a
good team um and having the right
partners. So, person I co-founded
Instagram with is somebody I actually
met back at Stanford. At the time, we
didn't know we were going to start a
company together, but I knew that
partnering with the right person,
especially that somebody that has
similar skills in some ways, but
different skills in other ways, and they
can complement you, um, can make the
difference as well for the company
succeeding. For example, there's a brand
new built-in camera. Now, the camera is
another way that the iPhone 3G has
really changed how people use their cell
phones. The new iPhone 3GS, there's a
brand new 3 megapixel autofocus camera.
It takes pictures that are even larger,
even more beautiful.
You have to kind of rewind your uh time
machine back to 2009. Now we take for
granted that everybody uses a lot of
apps on their phone, that we take a lot
of photos on our phone and that we
network or we, you know, use social
media on our phones. But in 2009, that
wasn't the case quite yet. So the
cameras were getting better, but they
were still quite bad. Facebook had a
mobile app, but um it was kind of that
early one where it was kind of just
trying to recreate the website on the
mobile side and it wasn't quite as a
native and there were very few sort of
new social products coming out and the
context is important because the reason
I got really excited to collaborate with
Kevin who ended up being my co-founder
is that he wanted to change all three of
those things. So he was building time as
a location sharing site a little bit
like Foursquare if you remember
Foursquare but with photos and videos
attached as well and really creating a
social experience when you're out and
about. That was really exciting to me
because I saw the potential for mobile
device to create a much more personal
connecting experience. So first moment
was reconnecting with Kevin and seeing
that he was interested in these ideas.
Second important moment was me getting
my work visa so I could go work with
him. So I was first had to transfer my
work visa and that actually took four
months. And then the third important
moment was us realizing that product
that we were working on it was called
Bourbon Burbn which was a that sort of
location-based check-in location sharing
app was good but it was not product that
was really going to where we wanted to
go and so we had a moment where we had
to take a pause really peel back all of
what was not working about the product
and realized that at the core the piece
that was really working was this uh
aspect about taking photos sharing what
you were doing and connecting with
people that way. And that was really the
the moment where we took a lot of
distracting things, stripped them all
away and then focused on what would
eventually become
Instagram. I think a lot of the art and
it's a part both art and science of
building great products especially with
emerging technologies. So Instagram it
was the rise of the mobile phone.
finding the technologies that are ready
for broader adoption than they currently
have and then finding how do you build
the product around it to make it usable
for many many people that's a common
sort of through line and I think the
kinds of things you can look for in
terms of that early energy is are there
some people already starting to do
something interesting in the space but
it's all the early adopters that's an
interesting kind of area um the other
thing I look at often is the rate of
change so if you look at the iPhone 3 to
the 3GS to the for and you look at the
quality of the photos and the quality of
the networking um stack and the ability
to connect, you can see the jumps. So
you're like, okay, if it goes one or two
more jumps, it's going to be incredible.
Same with LLMs. I joined Anthropic. We
had just come out with Cloud 3 and Cloud
3 was our first model that really
started to get more usage. It was still,
you know, limited in a lot of ways, but
then you see the next we did cloud 3.5
and that was a big leap. So you can
imagine that you're going to continue to
get these large jumps. And so as a
product builder, you have to start
thinking, I want to build a product
that's useful today, but is also ready
to catch the wave of what the next big
leap is.
You've closed uh the Instagram
acquisition. Why did you do it and what
are you going to do with it? Yeah. So
Instagram is great, right? I mean,
they're um they're this super talented
group of of engineers. They're building
this amazing product. Um they just
crossed 100 million registered users and
they're killing it. They started off
building on top of our platform. You
know, you can take pictures with
Instagram and you can share them to
Facebook. Um, and it's it's really first
class, right? So, sharing a picture from
Instagram, it basically appears exactly
the same as if you shared a photo on
Facebook. So, it's great. They did a
really good job with that. Our mission
around Instagram is we think Instagram
is amazing and we want to help it grow
to hundreds of millions of users. We
want to help them out um with with
whatever we can. Um, but we we have no
agenda in terms of making them go onto
our infrastructure or something. A lot
of times companies um force companies
that they're integrating to do stuff
like that. I think it's primarily a
waste of time. We're not going to do any
of that. We're going to just try to do
the things that that we would have done
if they were an open graph partner, but
now we can prioritize them more highly.
I mean, they can do a lot of them
directly because they have access to our
code directly.
I like to say that at Instagram, you
know, before the acquisition, we didn't
yet have a company. Um and what I mean
by that was we were 13 people had some
ideas around revenue, but we hadn't
built any of them out yet. still very
much that like early startup. Joining
Facebook was really interesting to me
because they were at the time thousands
of people. They had just crossed a
billion users, so much bigger than than
us in terms of company size. But they
were really focused on preserving as
much of the startup culture as they
could. So for example, uh every 3 or 4
months they would do a whole company
hackathon where everybody would get to
focus on what they were interested in
for a couple days instead of the the
ordinary road map. They really prized
experimentation. They really tried to,
you know, famously had the move fast and
break things kind of slogan. So I think
it was good that we went to a company
that was bigger but not super big
company or slow. And it taught us that
you can grow your team and grow your
ambition but still focus on the things
that keep you moving fast. I think the
value of the team is something that will
stay with me forever because you know
you can have the right strategy and you
can have a good product ultimate the
details that go into those products the
the pace and speed that you're able to
execute on and like how much fun it is
which is also really important
ultimately comes down to having the
right team around you and that's a
mixture of people that are talented but
don't have a lot of ego which is a
interesting and difficult combination to
find sometimes people that are willing
to be generalist lists rather than just
be caught in their sort of individual
silo. And so, you know, at Instagram, we
had people who would start off, you
know, writing the back end for a
feature, but would also then build the
iOS or the Android part. And it's
important, I think, for you to have that
fluidity, especially on engineering or
designers that would code or product
managers that would design, and it's
just not getting everybody boxed in. So,
that aspect is really important. And
then also a team that really cares about
the product they're building, which
again is easily more easily said than
done. It's I've al I've seen companies
where everybody is working and they
could be working hard but they don't
have a passion or really an attachment
to the thing that they're working on.
You're never going to get great products
that way. It just never happens because
the great product breakthroughs come
from people being close to the details,
understanding what could be better,
coming up with the next idea themselves,
not waiting for a, you know, strategy
meeting. So that value kind of
throughout the right kind of people and
the right sort of setup of team is
something that I think about all the
time.
In 2021, I founded Artifact of the same
co-founders, Kevin. Our goal, our
observation was there's been a rise and
at the time it wasn't, you know, LLMs
yet, but there was a lot of rise in
machine learning and the beginning of
some of these neural networks. For all
of that interest and rise, there was
still not a lot of products being built
that felt very personal. Because if you
think about it, the promise of some of
this machine learning was great with a
lot of signals, we'll be able to
incorporate what's personal to you and
also what's aggregated out, you know,
among a broader group and be able to
tailor the experience. But you looked
around and there actually wasn't that
many personal experiences. So our bet
with the company was by combining
cutting edge machine learning and good
product design, we'd be able to build
products that felt very personal to you.
And we started with news uh and articles
in general because that was something
that we felt most people are readers
even if they're not like book readers.
They like reading articles online. And
there's an existing kind of ecosystem of
blogs and newsletters and news sites
that was out there that we if we could
just connect people to those sites be
able to deliver a good product. And the
idea behind the company was this is the
first product, but we'll kind of take
the same personalization technology and
be able to map it to other products that
are also at this intersection of
personalization and content. So we
thought about shopping recommendations,
we thought about local recommendations,
all these ideas around how to
personalize information using machine
learning.
We launched um the product after about 2
years in private beta which I think was
too long because it took us too long to
get out to the market to start learning
and it also meant that by the time we
launched the team was already quite
exhausted for having worked really
really hard on this product for 2 years
non-stop and then we let the product run
for about a year and after a year what
we noticed was the energy was not there
in the system. like we would work really
hard to like improve a feature or add
social features and comments and
re-shares or posts and user generated
content like we we were trying big ideas
like it wasn't like the product was
standing still and it was very hard to
shift the energy in the system and I
think that was because there was not a
fundamental fit around what we were
doing and what people were wanting and I
think there was probably two aspects of
that the first one was even if our
algorithms I think were very good the
mobile web kind of websites that we were
sending people to for this news. They
were often like full of ads or not
formatted very well or full of like
pop-up videos. It was just not a very
good experience once you actually
clicked through. And that was like I
think a hard experience to deliver. And
I think the second part was our product
got really good if you put enough data
in there and you read enough articles.
We'd get very personal to you at the
level of all right, Mike is interested
in Formula 1, but not just Formula 1. is
interested specifically in this driver
and also he likes Brazilian modernist
architecture but also when that's paired
with you know Scandinavian design like
that level of like really specific
knowledge but to get that you had to
read a lot of articles and so most
people would come in they would read a
couple of articles they would say this
isn't very different than Apple News and
then they would bounce off so I think we
bet too hard on personalization without
remembering that you also have to be
good at the very beginning before you've
really gotten a lot of personal content
I think one big lesson is that users are
not going to adopt a feature or a
product just because of the the
technology underneath or just because it
has intelligence. It actually has to
still solve the problem. It goes all the
way back to what I had learned at
Stanford. So as we build products at
Enthropic, of course, the models are
very intelligent and they can do a lot.
But you have to do more than just say
this model is so smart. You have to go
beyond that and say and here's what it
can do for you and here's how it can
connect to you and here's how it can be
useful to you even if you're just
getting started with it. Right? It goes
back to that feeling an artifact of yeah
the product is good if you put a lot of
work into it. Like we need to design
things with claude that are useful for
somebody that's just discovering LLM
kind of for the first time. So a lot of
the work that we're doing right now is
how do we lower the barrier for people
who aren't yet familiar with all the
ways that AI can help you in your daily
life to just give them some really
concrete things that they could do where
it's useful to them today rather than in
theory. So that's a big lesson lesson
learned. I think another one that's
important as well is how do you get user
intent and the personalization more
quickly? And so for us, it's, you know,
when when you sign up for Claude, we ask
you some questions. And it's nice
because, you know, you can actually chat
start chatting with Claude and get a
feeling of what it's like to talk to
Claude. Um, and hopefully, you know, the
questions we ask in that onboarding
process in your first day let us be able
to be more tailored and personal to you
quickly. And that was kind of came out
directly from the Artifact
experience. That's a great question
around like when is it time to call it?
When does the chapter close? The way
that we did this with Artifact, um, and
I think this helped, was we sat down, me
and Kevin, we made a list of like what
are the ideas that we still have in this
space that we will feel really silly not
having tried before shutting it down.
And we wrote them down and then we
prioritized like three big ones that we
said, we want to try this and after we
try this, we'll take a step back and
say, did it change? Did it change the
the trajectory of the company? Um, and
we did that and then we kind of wrapped
up 2023 and enter 2024 and we said we
tried them. It's still not, you know,
it's still not changing the the
trajectory. Then, you know, it's time to
to move on. But it is quite tricky. I
think it's I've seen entrepreneurs get
stuck at companies for years that they
feel, you know, they owe it to
themselves or their investors to keep
going, but it's not likely to to shift
the directions. So I think being
concrete either with a date or with a
set of projects helps you um know when
to move on. I think one big piece of
advice is I think we're often as
entrepreneurs uh we we have a lot of
weight on our shoulders and you know
between Instagram and Artifact I did
some angel investment and it's never
positive news when an entrepreneur tells
you that a company doesn't work but I've
seen it before you know and so it's not
a surprise that some companies don't
work out. that's baked into the model.
And so I guess I the advice I'll give is
really check in with your investors and
don't I've seen entrepreneurs get stuck
in this idea like I have to keep going
because my investor expects me to. And I
think what they'll find is sometimes
investors are like you're trying you've
tried it all in this space. I think it's
time to to call it and that's okay. And
you know it's not it's never a
celebration but it doesn't have to be
you know a tragedy either.
[Music]
I think what was interesting with the
anthropic role is that it was both
joining an existing company the company
was about 3 years old at the time had
already launched models had cloud.ai and
AI but there was still a lot of zero to
one to be done so I don't think we had
our mobile apps yet um we hadn't built
things like claude code which is our
agentic coding tool so there was a lot
of empty space still in the product so
it was kind of a combination of 0ero to
one and established uh we have a claude
character um effort and team and that
team is really focused on what are
claude's philosophies what's cla's vibes
how should claude respond and that's
been uh an effort even from early days
but It's something we've focused even
more on recently in the rest of the AI
landscape. You can often have these
evaluations or evals right where you say
all right how is you know the model
doing at math or competition coding or
agent coding it's a challenge to say
what kind of vibes does the model have
we have some internal ways of doing that
often you can try to use claude to
listen to claude and then say you know
what kind of vibe does it have but it
also comes from just using claude a lot
internally so every day there are
hundreds of conversations that you know
people atanthropic are having with
claude with the intention of
understanding how is Claude's
personality evolving uh when we're doing
training how could it be different going
forward even things like should claude
be verbose like should it say a lot or
should it be concise and the answer
varies on the depending on the situation
I think one of the hardest ones is um we
are building a fundamentally a dynamic
model and a dynamic system and so as an
example you know we have in cloud.io
Okay, we have a a feature called
artifacts where uh you can sort of work
on a document or even a website along
with claude. You know, the model learns
how to make artifacts, but the taste
that it has in artifacts and how it
changes and what language it uses and
exactly what it does evolves from model
to model. And sometimes you don't know
how it's evolved until very late in the
model training process. So, one of the
biggest challenges with building
products alongside doing model
development is they're both moving
targets. Our product is evolving, the
models are evolving. Often the models
are evolving up to like a week before
launch and we're trying to build
products alongside. It's a very
interesting dynamic system. It's what
makes it exciting because the model can
be creative and it can surprise you in a
lot of ways. Uh but it's also um a lot
more challenging than try classic
product development.
I think it's really important to as a
product development team to be really
upfront about the capabilities and the
limitations and the risks. So you'll see
when you sign up for cloud and you go
through the the first conversation, we
really emphasize here's what models are
good at and here's where they can still
make mistakes. Um and here's the
limitations. And I think it's important
to lead at the beginning because I want
people to have the right mental model
when using these models. They're not
perfect. They don't know everything. um
but they can be very helpful in for a
given task. Similarly, I think goes back
to the kind of that quad character
piece. It's important for the model to
also be aware of its limitations. And so
often you'll find if you ask cla about
medical questions, it might say, "All
right, I can tell you more about this,
but first I'm not a doctor." And if
you're worried about this, then you
might want to consult a professional.
And it's not just a thing we put in for
liability. It's a thing we put in
because we think it's really important
to have Claude recognize its own
limitations as much as
possible. Yeah. So it's an interesting
question for us which is how do we
gather user feedback on claude in a way
that is like most helpful and the way
we've currently found although I think
there are probably other ways that we
can continue to evolve it is for every
answer in in claude we have you know
thumbs up thumbs down how did we do for
both thumbs up and thumbs down you can
write a little paragraph about why it
was good or was it bad and it's so
interesting because um and that extra
bit of signal around why is the most
important part and so we have a product
manager and she's She spends a lot of
her time aggregating and evaluating and
looking at how the model is doing out in
the wild. And then you start seeing
themes. So an individual answer maybe
doesn't give you the clue about how you
need to improve the model. But then in
aggregate you say, okay, Claude is being
too too verbose here in this particular
case. We're going to change it for the
next model. Or Claude is changing its
mind too quickly. So when the user
disagrees with Claude, maybe the user is
actually looking for a debate. Sometimes
Claude is like, "It's fine. Like you're
right. I'm sorry I was wrong, but the
user was actually looking for more of a
back and forth. So that kind of
conversational feedback is incredibly
valuable. And we basically for every new
model training will first look at all
the feedback in aggregate for the
previous one and say what do we want to
keep the same and what do we want to
change or what do we want to double down
on and what do we want to make
different. So that feedback process is
very very important and it's actually
the main feedback we get. So we don't
train on any user data um including
conversations for anybody but we do use
the the thumbs up and thumbs down as a
really helpful signal to figure out what
we need to improve. I think there's two
areas of consolidation that I expect to
see. One is on the model development
side of things as these models they're
already very expensive to to build and
train at scale. as they reach even
higher levels of intelligence they're
going to require that same kind of jump
in compute and resources and I think
we'll probably come down to three four
five companies doing that not as many
you're already seeing some kind of
consolidation and and in that side of
things I think anthropic is well
positioned there we've got really great
partnerships with Amazon with Google
that I think will unlock a lot of
compute for us and the other side is um
consolidation in more of the apps side
of things because I spoke at the Y
Combinator batch of startups recently
and everybody's working on something
that is AI or directly uh adjacent to AI
and that's great there's a lot of
products still to be built in this space
but not all of them are going to work so
in the same way as you saw that with
mobile and social media where it's
useful to have that explosion cuz no one
company is going to map the whole space
out then you start naturally seeing you
know what's getting traction what's
going to get consolidated what are good
idea what were good design ideas but
wrong sort of business ideas that then
will evolve into better business ideas.
That evolution I think is very healthy.
Uh I saw that process with mobile, I saw
it with social media. I think now is the
time to start seeing it. Well, maybe you
know in a 6 month time you'll start
seeing more of that within the app space
as
well. I think there's when I think about
where we are and where we need to get
to, there's a couple of avenues I think
are really important. The first one is
understanding people for more than just
a single conversation or even a couple
of conversations. So we're not static,
right? We are dynamic. We have
relationships. We have moods. We have
challenges. We have wins. And I think
for models to be feel really like they
can work alongside us to really be part
of our lives. They're going to need to
develop a sort of empathy beyond a
single conversation and really have that
sort of longer horizon interaction with
somebody. I think that's really
important. I think that comes from
contextual understanding and memory. For
example, the second part is the models
need to learn when they can be proactive
and when they should sit back. As
people, we often know if somebody's
head's down working, we're trying to
we're not going to go interrupt them or
if they come to you for help, we can
answer a question and maybe get back to
work ourselves. So, how do we have that
collaboration with models in a way that
feels really natural? As an example, we
have Claude as a participant in our
Slack channels, anthropic, which is
great. it can chime in and and be part
of the conversation, but we're finding
it still either will not participate
enough or say too much. So, how do we
get it to feel like a more natural
participant in these conversations is
important. And then the third one is
around agency and independence. So, how
do we get the models to be able to take
direction from people but then go off
and either do work or do research or be
waiting for additional input and do that
over a much longer time horizon in the
background. I think that's very
exciting. There's a lot of things that
will be enabled by that capability, but
it's going beyond the sort of chat box
with a single interaction to more of a
longunning agent in the background. One
of the big changes that's going to
happen is the models will start being
able to give you insights about your own
self, which I think is very powerful,
right? Um I I have worked with a coach
for many years. I think it's one of the
most important ways in which I improve
as a leader. I want that for everybody,
right? Everybody has can benefit from
reflection and learning and iterating on
the way that they you know approach the
world. Right now you can go to Claude
and tell it about how things are going
and it will probably be able to give you
some coaching but it's very point in
time. When I think about the potential
it's to be much more of an ongoing sort
of uh improver or you know
conversational um you know coach. I use
this right now with Claude a lot.
Anything that I write, I will put, you
know, if I'm writing a strategy
document, I'll put it into cloud and
say, "What am I missing? What did I
forget? Like, what poke some holes in my
argument?" And it's great to have that
partner. Um, I think that'll be one big
evolutionary step. The other one that's,
this is more speculative, but if uh
models go from being single
conversations, you know, single chats to
being more of, you know, long horizon
almost personalities, I'm curious what
kind of relationship we'll form with the
models. is like will it feel more like a
friend uh in some ways or a co-orker in
some other ways? I think that remains to
be
seen. I think in your early 20s you have
a unique place in the world because
you've you're pretty in touch with the
trends that like teenagers have which is
important especially if you're building
in consumer but you're now able to like
take those insights and make them into
something like a project or maybe even a
company. So, it's a very special time in
your life where you're like at the
intersection of being a teenager, being
really tuned into that, but being able
to do those things. I'd say the two
things I would I would I would add is
one, not worrying so much that every
step needs to make logical sense.
There's definitely things that side
projects I did or explorations I did
where at the time I was like, am I
wasting my time here? But actually
later, I find that it was connected to
the next thing I did. So just trust that
if you're driving towards a direction,
it might take some very strange routes
to get there, but as long as you're
learning, I think that that's fine. And
then the second one is advice that I got
when I was 21 and I still think about to
this day is the companies change, the
projects change, you know, the economy
changes, but the relationships you build
in your career will be the relationships
that you have over and over again. And
so I was working at a startup as an
intern and it was full of people who
were in their late 30s who had worked
together probably three or four times
since they were 20 and it really stayed
with me. So like remembering that those
relationships build on each other and
recur which means that it's you know
it's worth investing in the in that
time. I think for me I was talking to to
Daniela who's one of the co-founders of
Anthropic. I I told her and I meant it I
hope Anthropic is the last job that I
have. I think I see the opportunity here
to be paired with research and build
interesting products for many many years
because I think every year will be
different. When I was 18, I had this
like promise to myself that I wanted
every year to feel different. And this
year has felt very different than any
other year that I've had being an
anthropic. And I think that the year
ahead is going to be quite different as
well. And so that's how I really think
about the next 5 years is just making
sure I'm set up for consistently
learning, evolving, working with
interesting people on interesting
products. And then taking the space at
least once a year to step back and say,
am I still learning? Am I still, you
know, eventually at Instagram, you know,
8 years in, there was a time where I
said, okay, I think I've I've gotten
what I need to get out of this
experience, and now it's time to try
something else. To me, entrepreneurship
is about finding ways in which the world
could be different and better and in
feeling empowered to go make that
change. It's something that really drove
me from a pretty early age. And as I've
seen that manifest both in the ways you
can change your city, the way you can
change, you know, the way people relate,
of course, with Instagram having global
impact, large or small, it's really
about identifying like what could be
different like as getting curious about
the world and then also getting curious
about how you or you and a small team
can see if there's a a change to be made
there. Um, and I'm very excited about
the way AI will empower people to ask
that question and also answer it.