[Music]
You can wear this one tonight. First
into the tank tonight, a savvy young
businesswoman who's not letting age
stand in her way. My name is Briella.
I'm just like any other 20-year-old
girl. I love hanging out with my
friends, going to the beach, and most of
all, I love shopping. What do you think?
I like them. I have always wanted to run
my own business, even from a very early
age. I came up with this business idea
from personal experience. So, it's
helped me, my friends, and hopefully
lots of other women in Australia. This
20-year-old is ready to take on the
world.
[Applause]
[Music]
Hello, my name is Bela and I am the
founder and director of Your Closet. I
am here today seeking an $80,000
investment for a 20% stake in my
business. Please let me introduce my
gorgeous models who will be modeling
some of my gorgeous dresses.
Your Closet is an online service that
allows women to rent high-end designer
fashion from Australia's leading
designers, including Camila Mark,
Nicholas, and Josh Goo for a fraction of
the purchase
price. Let me take you back to the
beginning. 2 years ago, I was invited to
four formals in 4 weeks. First world
problems, I know. And I'm sure you are
all very aware formal dresses are
extremely expensive. And the craziest
thing is we often only wear them once.
It was driving my mom crazy and my dad
broke and he didn't even know the full
story. I launched the business in August
2014. And since launching, I quickly
realized, hey, this business has some
legs. And it's not just applicable to
young girls renting for formal. It's
applicable to all women who want to look
fabulous when it matters most. This
includes going to the races, New Year's
Eve, red carpet galas, cocktail events,
birthdays, work functions, and
everything in
between. My vision for your closet is to
revolutionize the way women look at
special occasion wear and to normalize
the option of renting. I've got the
business to where it is today by myself,
but I need one of you to help me
supercharge your closet. Sharks, are you
ready to dress for success? Ah, well
done. Great job. Great presentation. A
Bella, was it? Yes. Great. So, a woman
can rent a dress for a fraction of a
cost, a fraction of $1,000. Tell us
about that. We rent our dresses out
based on a percentage of the retail
price. So, it's roughly about 18 to 20%
of the retail price of the dress. So if
a dress is $1,000, you rent it out for
about 180 to 200. So just quickly how it
works is you jump onto the your closet
website. You view our big range of
dresses and from the latest designers.
You pick one that you love. You then
choose a delivery date. The dress
arrives to you in a pristine box looking
amazing. You then wear it to your event
and then on the fourth day you simply
slip it into a prepaid pre-addressed
satchel and drop it off to Australia
Post. Sounds pretty good. We take care
of the dry cleaning. That's fantastic,
Bella.
Very clever, creative idea. Thank you.
How long do I have to wait? I've I've
suddenly been invited to an event. It
was very short notice and I need the
dress quickly. What's my minimum wait
time? If you're in Sydney, 3 hours, get
it straight away. And then other capital
cities, one day, so we can send express
to ride the next morning for you. What's
your size range? At the moment, it's 6
to 12. Now, the average women is is a
bit bigger than that. the sort of 12 to
14. Are you cutting a lot of your market
at the moment? Yeah. And I'm looking to
expand this over the next 12 months.
Good. Sorry, I'm Steve. Where are you
from, Briella? I'm from Manley in the
Northern Beaches. Oh, nice. Sydney.
Okay, great. Hey. Um, uh, so I imagine
some of these functions you go to like
races and formals for example, there may
be some especially the races, there may
be some damage to the to the dresses.
How's that handled? How does bonds or
insuranceances work? What happens there?
Roughly one in 200 dresses, so half a
percent of dresses come back damaged.
Women appreciate that these are gorgeous
gowns and they treat they treat them
well. So what happens to the one and 200
that are damaged?
In that case, the customer is asked to
pay a small fee and then takes on full
ownership of that dress. So that asked
to pay the other 90 80 sorry 80 odd
percent. Is that right? Yes. And then we
just send them that dress to enjoy. Oh
hand. So, you said a small fee. So, if
it's if you're only paying 20% of the
dress and it's $1,000 dress, small fee
is $800.
[Music]
I guess that's one way of looking at it.
You damage it, you own it. Is that it?
Basically, yeah, that's essentially in.
Do you own the dresses? Yes. How did you
get the stock? I actually took out a
personal loan to fund the business. How
much of $82,000? $82,000. How old are
you? I'm 20. You're doing a great job.
Well done. Thank you. What's What's your
value in dresses you have in the
business, please? Around $200,000. Where
are you warehousing these? Uh, this has
run out of my house at the moment. You
must have an extraordinary large
wardrobe. I've converted nearly every
room in my house to somehow store some.
Your parents must be very accommodating.
Oh, they're incredibly supportive. So,
let's talk about the revenue so far. So
just say the last three or four months,
month by month, what's your revenue
been? 35, 35, and 36,000.
Yes.
[Music]
And what's your costs against that? A
cost, our profit, it runs at around 55%
of revenue. Did you take a wage? Not at
the moment. No wage. Okay. So the
revenue that is coming in is reinvested
back into the business.
I have two daughters going to formals.
Tell you I have felt your dad's pain
this year. For me, um I I don't think I
add a lot of value as a partner to you
and that's what you need. Someone who
understands the fashion industry um and
will partner with you to help scale this
up quickly and own this space in in the
Australian market. And uh I I think what
you've done to date is sensational. Uh
but I'm out. Thank you for your
feedback.
Reala. Wow. 20 years old. I'm
embarrassed. I can't recall I was doing
it 20. It wasn't this. Um, that's 35,000
bucks a month is incredible. Um, I've
had a lot of similar dress marketplaces,
shoe marketplaces, god knows what
fashion market places presented to me,
and that they they have a lot of trouble
answering the questions that you've
actually proved probably aren't issues,
at least in your model anyway.
Um
um I'm just going to take a break on
that and have a think
actually. See what else is going to
happen. Ladies, you're the experts in
this
[Music]
area. Look, normally if it's something
like $80,000, it's hardly worth
splitting it with um someone, you know,
40 40 is not worth it. In this case,
however, um I'm strong in digital
marketing, but I'm not strong in
logistics. I will actually go if if
Steve will have me, I will actually do a
deal with Steve with you on it if he'll
if he'll take it. Uh the deal will be
$80,000 for 30% split.
Are you going into that ste?
I'm just trying to work out if I want to
get into the fashion.
[Music]
Bria Brown is seeking $80,000 for a 20%
stake in her formal dress hire business,
Your Closet. Glenn is out. Janine has
made an offer, but it's on the condition
that Steve joins her. Are you going into
that, Steve? I'm just trying to work out
if I want to get into the fashion game.
All right. Well, hold that thought.
Naomi, are you ready to go?
[Music]
If I was to make an offer, it would be
dependent on really um making sure that
we do have sign off on the logistics
because at the moment it's literally a
homebased business and your family and
you will implode if that doesn't get
sorted really quickly. You've asked for
$80,000. I'd be looking
[Music]
for 40% of your business.
Wow.
Okay. So, $80,000 for
40%. Janine, a provisional $80,000 for
30%, assuming Steve may go with her. Are
you an 80 or Look, I think you are
amazing and you're incredible. You what
you've done. You've got a great front
end. The the the idea is great. The
website's great, but you're a bit like
Amazon, a tiny Amazon. you've got a huge
logistics back end and that's going to
need a lot of management time and it
will also really damage your margins as
you grow. For those reasons, I'm out.
But I really wish you well. Thank you.
Bit like Andy, I think that you're the
you're the gem in this business. One of
the big issues I've got is fashion
doesn't do it for me. If I were you, I
would try to get those two to go
together on
35%. That's the deal you want out of
this entire tank. Uh I'm out. If you
want, I can help you negotiate with
those two.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
So, Janine, would you go in with me, but
I I want 40%. Yeah, I I would. Um, yep,
certainly love to. You want two sharks
at 20% each? Can I please have a minute
to discuss with my dad? Of course. Thank
you.
How are you? Good. Good. So, it all went
all right. Great. Good. Yes. And the
offers I've got so far is Janine and Ni,
the two women, right, have offered 40%
20% each for $80,000. Right.
What an amazing young lady. I mean, far
out. I wonder if my children surely she
can date one of them. If you felt
confident that they can both add
significant value to that business over
the course of the next of the future.
You go 15% each for 30% for that same
money. I can see the house now, can't
you? Bedrooms full of clothes. Oh yeah.
[Music]
You spoke to your dad. Yes. And what did
he say? What do you think? I'm proposing
30% so 1515 for the $80,000.
I'm confident in the business growth, in
the idea, in my passion, and I think the
skill sets that I may bring. So that's
your counter offer? Yes, that's my
counter offer. 30% 80,000 for 30%. Yes.
The the reality is also we've got to go
backwards, go forward because right now
you're you're in your home. So we've got
to get there's got to be a warehouse.
there got to be more staff. So there's a
there's quite a big execution risk as in
loss making. The other thing is that we
actually know we're going to have to put
more money into the business, whatever
that looks like in terms of loans or
what have you, because you're going to
need dry cleaning on site at the
warehousing so that you don't have that
as a cost. And that logistics is
actually critical to your growth. And
unless you get that right and you know
what your life is like right now, don't
you? Yes. I know. and that is not
sustainable. So the investment that's
going to need to be made to set that up,
there's going to be more capital
required. And you've got, you know, two
business women who have been there, done
that, and there's a hell of a lot of
experience that we're bringing to the
table, not just
[Music]
cash. What I'd like to suggest as well
is, you know, sweat for equity. As you
said, you're not taking a wage, but
let's actually calculate it as we go and
then you can get equity for your sweat
as we go. So, you understand they're
saying because you're working in the
business, they'll give you the
opportunity to get some equity, some
shares back based on your service as the
CEO driving the business and that's what
I did with my business.
Take it Pella.
Reala, basically you're making the
decision about how valuable will be the
rest of my equity 2 years from now if I
go with these people or whether I do my
own thing. Make your call.
[Music]
Let's do it.
Good decision. Oh, well done so much. Oh
my gosh.
Thank you so much. This is the best day
of my life. It's great. Congratulations.
Let's grow this business. I'm your girl,
right? And you're my girl. I And I have
some wonderful sons.
Thank you so much for your time.
Thank you.
So excited. So excited to be 20 and to
have Janine and Naomi on board now. That
is that's huge. Can you even get your
head around that? I can. I feel like
this is a dream right now. I like, oh my
gosh, life goals. We get to really grow
a young entrepreneur.
Next into the tank is a savvy
17-year-old who's not letting school get
in the way of his sweet entrepreneurial
dreams. My ultimate goal for my business
is to be a household name throughout the
world. Age is no barrier.
Cool pants.
[Music]
Hi Sharks. My name is Morgan Hipworth.
I'm 17 years old and I'm the owner and
founder of Bistro Morgan, an artisan
donut store based in Melbourne.
Oh no.
Today I'm here for $200,000 in exchange
for 20% equity in my business. Bro
Morgan was born when I was 13 years old
and I started supplying a cafe with
local goods. From there, things just
kind of blew up. I was featured in
numerous media outlets and a whole
whirlwind of opportunities came at me. I
ended up supplying around 20 cafes
around Melbourne until I was absolutely
desperate on a permanent store. And my
parents being, you know, parents, they
were like, "No, you're not allowed a
permanent store till you're out of
school." So, we came to a compromise
that how about we do a pop-up store? And
before they knew, I was on the phone to
real estate agents and had already
sorted out a location for my store. And
the 8 days went so well, we ended up
selling over 10,000 donuts in those 8
days. Goodness. So, from there, store
came up for permanent lease. I
eventually convinced my parents after
many arguments at the dinner
table and the store's been open around
15 months now. We continue to supply
around 10 to 20 cafes and dessert bars
around Melbourne. So yeah, it's, you
know, keeps me busy as well as being in
year 12 in high school. So I'm in my
final year of school. So I think now is
a good time to maybe try some of the
dough.
Well done. Thank you. Excellent job.
Amazing. First up the good. Yeah.
So we got our cookie monster which is
filled with cake batter. This is our
class clown which is filled with
chocolate hazelnut and then Kit Kat and
marshmallow. A Bruno Mars which is Mars
bar and salted caramel. Triple tease
which is chalk hazelnut tim
tam. Date night which is white chocolate
popcorn caramel and chalk hazelnut. And
then our gay time crunch which is based
off the ice cream the golden gay time
and made into a donut. My favorite. I'll
have that one in the middle there. This
one here. Thank you very clown. Class
clown. That kind of I'll try the middle
one. Yeah. Thank you. See? And that's
got cake batter.
Well, you're going to knock yourself
out. Knock yourself out. Right. You sell
it with a syringe, too. Exactly. Right.
Tastes really good.
And who comes up with recipes?
So, you were asking for 200,000 for 20%
valuing your business at $1 million.
That's right. That's not a bad ask for a
17y old. When you do that $10,000 worth
of sales, how 10,000 donuts? 10,000
donuts. Yeah. And the donuts are 550
each for retail.
[Music]
55,000 on your opening weekend in a
opening 8 days. Yeah. It must have shut
mom and dad down. Yeah, it did.
I work about 60 hours a week on the
business and then I'm also in school.
Take me through your day. A normal day.
Okay. So normal day would be I get up
around 4:00 4:30 um head down to the
shop get some of the orders and the
wholesale orders out and then from there
I'll head off to school and I get in get
all my homework done in recess so I try
and work through all my recesses all my
lunch breaks. You're working harder than
most people I know. Amazing. When do you
have fun? This is fun. Oh good idea.
This is absolutely love. Great answer.
So can we do the your current financial
performance first? So our total revenue
for last calendar year was
$500,000 with net profit $130.
Wow. This year yeah forecast house is
850,000 and then 3 to 350 profit.
Oh wow.
Did you clarify for us what you're going
to spend the 200,000 on? Yeah. I'd love
to have Bro Morgan flagship stores. Our
product is one of those that people will
travel for.
Listen, uh, Morgan, I'm already a
shareholder in a pretty substantial
national donut business, and I'm I'm not
sure I'm the right partner for you to
scale this next stage. I think you are a
force of nature. You're amazing. Thank
you. But I'm out. No worries.
and Morgan. Um, you know, for a
middle-aged guy who's trying to keep his
weight down, I'm really concerned about
this product. Dangerous, eh? That's a
good answer. What I notice about my
investments lately in the food space is
they are in health and wellness
products. Yeah. So, for me, I'm out.
Yeah. No worries.
Morgan, I think you're at such a delight
and such an energy and um I'm sure your
parents are incredibly proud of you and
they should be. Uh it's not an obvious
fit for me in terms of the value that I
can add for this deal. I'm out. No
worries.
[Music]
Morgan, if there was one person in
Australia Yeah. whose business you
love that you'd love to spend an hour
with. Who would that be?
Um, Janine Alice. There we go. Oh, don't
worry.
Hey, mate. You can have that.
So, I'll make you a deal.
I will offer you
200,000 for 42%. A bottom feeder. Come
on. Easy. The reason being is this is
going to take me a lot more time. So,
I'm actually valuing in my sweat.
He's a minor. You can't deal
inappropriately with miners. What are
you doing? Come on now. Hey,
[Music]
are you in or out, Steve? So, um, the
deal I was looking at was uh
$200,000
for 30%.
Yeah.
So, just to summarize, Janine's offered
you 200,000 for 42%. Steve has offered
you 200,000 for 30%.
[Music]
Is 12% of the business worth the
expertise? 42. 42 is horrible. you you
cannot do for I ban you. I I forbid you
from doing 42. Is
12% worth the 20 years experience that I
can bring to you in this business.
I can't I couldn't bear to give away 42%
of my own sort of You're not giving it
away. No, no, I know no I don't mean I'm
buying it and also I'm giving you my
time. I know. I know. She's ruthless. I
think that's a no. She's ruthless. Take
a counter on Can you do any better? I'm
at 30%, mate. I'm at 30%. May I go back
and have a chat with my mom and my dad?
Absolutely. All right, no worries. I'll
be back. Have a chat. Thanks.
I'm not too
Janine. He's not going to give you 42%.
Well, he can come back for the counter.
You're ruthless. I think you need to
send it to dad. Yeah.
Hi. Hey, it's me. Oh, good day, mate.
We've got two offers. We've got one from
Janine Alice
um for the 200,000, but it's 442%.
I think you know how I feel about that.
Yeah. And then we've got one from Steve
for 30%. I think that they're getting um
something pretty easy, but you've got to
stick with 20%. Uh you don't move to
that. Here, here we go.
Oh, there's mom. Ah, mom's cranking. I
can see it. Welcome. Hi. You are I'm
Ally. I'm's mom. Hi, how are you? Thank
you. A proud mom indeed. Yes. Yeah. He
keeps us busy. It keeps you busy and
challenged. And challenged. Yeah. We
just call my dad as well. Oh, good. So,
you consulted the board. I get that. We
did. So, just to remind you, Janine's
offered you 200,000 for 42% of your
business. Yeah. And Steve has offered
you 200,000 for 30% of your business.
So, what are you going to do? So, we've
had a bit of a chat. My dad's pretty
firm, so he thinks that I'm a worthwhile
investment as such.
So would any of you be willing to do
anything for 20?
20% said
no. I will do
33%. I know this. I have lived every up,
every down, every
tier. So I think you're getting me cheap
for 33.
Steve, are you going to revise your
offer? Um, I'm not ch I'm not changing
my offer. Okay. So, what are you going
to do,
Morgan? You're allowed to count it.
Yeah. Janine, would you do 25%. Please
just go into the 20s.
Please,
Janine. That it's Don't get on your
knees, whatever you do.
[Music]
I want to do the deal with you, but for
for me, I'm I'm not prepared to move at
all.
If you walk away from here, I will still
spend time with you. I don't want you to
feel that it's bad. I actually know that
what I've offered is actually a good
deal, but I don't want you feeling that.
So, you've got me either way, but you
can have me as an equity holder. Yeah.
Or you can have me as a mentor. Yeah.
[Music]
Okay. Well, um, unfortunately, we don't
feel comfortable going above the 20%
mark at this point in time.
I I can't go below. That's okay. But I
will still spend time with you. Yeah. We
would love to take you up on having a
relationship. Mate, you've got me. And
who knows, I might be an equity partner.
Yeah. Somewhere down the track. But I
will definitely definitely definitely be
catching up. Thank you. Well done.
Congratulations. No worries. And you
know, well done. Great to meet you.
Thank you so much. So Morgan, well done.
Go out of here proud of what you've
done. Thank you so much, guys.
Take care. Thanks, Morgan.
[Music]
He would have been better off having you
as a partner and he would grow faster.
So, thank you, Andrew. I find that I
think he will find he will do okay. I'll
help him. Next. You've been going for 18
months and you got $4 million in sales.
The biggest deal in Australian Shark
Tank history. That's a first. Is on the
line. You've got an absolute pair
between your legs and it has the sharks
out for blood. Clearly, you don't
believe in it. Please.
I'm speaking. Are you in or out? I'm
speaking.
Next in the tank is an experienced
entrepreneur from Sydney who's hoping to
wow the sharks with his eco-friendly and
innovative product. I'm feeling
exceptionally nervous. This is our
livelihood, this business. We've lived
it and breathed it for the last 3 years.
For the amount of money I'm asking for,
I hope the sharks don't get scared off.
[Music]
Hi, my name is Kane. I'm the CEO of
Icapsulate. 13 years ago, I made a clear
and conscious decision to turn my life
around and build a strong and successful
company.
I'm here today to ask you for $2.5
million
for 15% of my company. So that was 2.5.
It is. Wow.
For 15%.
I'll go hard or go home. All right. Get
into it. Okay.
A capsulate um is a coffee company
specializing in capsules, pods, and
roasted beans. We're the largest in the
Southern Hemisphere.
We produce currently 35 million capsules
and pods
peranom. Uh we have contracts with
Australia and New Zealand's largest
coffee companies. Uh I'm expanding the
formats of I capsulate next year which
will increase that another 20 million
pieces and I'm still to execute two
contracts by the end of this year which
will also add another 20 million pieces
to the business.
The thing with I capsulate is in June
we'll launch a world first biodegradable
hermetically sealed capsule. The
difference between this and other
capsules is ours is biodegradable so we
can drop it straight in the garden. The
other thing with our capsules we we
produce the best. We're 35% higher
coffee solids than any other
manufacturer in Australia. We have the
lowest oxygen residual, meaning the
freshest coffee capsule as well. So what
I would like to do is let you taste the
difference between a crap and a good cup
of coffee. I capate being a good one.
Okay, Kane. And that was
$2.5 million for 15% of your value at
$16.6 million. Yes.
How long ago did you start this
business? Uh, one and a half years ago.
Wow. Well, what a great result that is.
Wow.
This is the first lot. What's this one?
This is the one that you don't want to
drink. Just have a smell first, just so
you know. Um, as a as a point of
difference, smells revoling. Okay, so
this is the bad one. This is evil
coffee. Evil coffee. Yeah, it's bitter.
Um, you'll notice the capsules slightly
different. And I'll bring some capsules
around for you to have a look. Thank
you. Thank you. So, first thing you'll
notice is the crema difference and the
color and I should hope the flavor. Oh,
thank you. Oh, yeah. You can see it.
Yeah, it's massive. What was your past
life? Cuz you only been going 18 months.
Yeah. So, always coffee. My mom was a
chef. So instead of working in the
kitchen with her, um I said I I'll stay
out and do the bar and coffee. Through
school and everything, I continued doing
coffee and I set up a coffee roasting
company. Did that for a couple of years
and I was offered um the technical
position for Daoberts. So I ran all
their technical division for them and
then Gloria Jeans poached me from there
and I ran Gloria Jeans Worldwide for
their coffee and technical. Wow. So I
launched Cafe Italy for Gloria Jeans
into Woolworth. Um and seeing the
success of that I decided to start my
own company.
What are you most proud of? This is um
my partners and my life. Like we we've
invested everything into it. We've lived
and breathed the factory. We installed
the machinery ourself. There's $16
million worth of machinery currently on
the
floor. Coffee is our life.
So your business is not just putting
your own coffee in capsules. It's
putting other people's coffee in
capsules as well. So are you like the
tetra pack of capsules? Yes. So our
customers we can say all of Australia's
leading manufacturers or coffee
companies. All the big coffee brands
that we would know. Y So what are your
sales? So $ 37.5 million at the moment
pieces peranom. Talk your revenues
please. So um last year was 4 million.
$4 million. That is very impressive.
That's very nice. Okay. You've been
going for 18 months and you got $4
million in sales. Well done.
Clearly, you've got everything you need
to run a good business. What extra do
you need from a shark type investor? I
was offered $25 million for the business
probably 6 months ago and I said no
because I I I believe there's a lot more
in it. Marketed correctly, taken through
the right fields and like to to apply
put a different application to it to fit
coffee into it there. I think that's
exactly what a shark could offer.
Kane, you are um very brave. Um also
you've got courage and courage to
actually be allin. So I admire your
passion, your courage, and your bravery.
Thank you. Unfortunately, I own a coffee
business and we sell coffee. I have a
conflict of interest. I'm out. Okay.
Thank you.
Well, I like the space. I think you're
amazing. I'll make you an offer.
I don't like the valuation. I think
there's a risk involved. So, I'm going
to offer you $2.5 million for 25% of
your company. Okay?
And I'm going to work on making the
other 75% very valuable. Okay?
So, Kane, off to the uh up front with
you. Um, I cannot see even where Andrew
is sitting and and my offer seriously is
2.5 million for 40% based on the work
and the numbers you've told me about.
Okay. I will give you the mentoring and
the coaching support you need to go
exponential with this business.
Thank you. I'm buying your growth rate.
You've started from nothing and in 18
months you got to a phenomenal space.
But I will counter that little
conversation there by saying I am the
scaleup guy. I I am so experienced in
taking companies from small to large. So
it is a dream Australianbased mentor
which is what you need. I'd be there for
you.
So So if you want to take a business
that sells pigs ears and have it sell
more pigs ears, mate, Glenn's your
bloke, right? What?
Um I'm I'm exceptionally curious and
these are these inferior coffee pods you
were selling against. What is it their
cost of manufacturing? The cost of
manufacturing is slightly higher, not a
licensed system and not protected by
patents. So the inferior one which does
things in an inferior way. Yeah. Is more
expensive. Yeah. And that doesn't make
any sense, right? I'll explain. We have
the ability to roast the coffee in
house. So one, you save the GST because
they can buy the green coffee office.
There's no GST on the product and sold.
But it's also the road cost of getting
the coffee there, getting it back to DC
where we can keep it all in house. I I
don't believe you because someone has
the inferior product pods thing and does
exactly everything the way you do it
now. Okay. But anyway,
please I'm speaking. Are you in or out?
I'm speaking. Are you in or out? For
Christ sakes, it's my money. We're here
to talk to the
BL. We're talking about Glenn and
somewhere else. Do you do you need to go
somewhere? Right. You you've actually
identified this as a $2 million
investment. Right. So, and two and a
half. I've made a two and a half.
These do require appropriate
questioning. So if you're trying to rush
the process, why are you trying to rush
the process? And we're talking about
$16.6 million valuation. For God's sake,
it's money, people, and this is
business. So I'm on the I'm on the
fence. I'm going to continue to think,
but it's 2 and a half million bucks. I'm
going to take as much bloody time as I
want. Excuse me.
Okay, Naomi, let's go.
I was going to come in with a different
offer than you've already got from Glenn
and from Andrew because I do know that
you do need the marketing and I value my
marketing skills. So, the offer that I'm
going to put you is $2.5
million for 33 and a3% of your business.
Steve,
um I'm having trouble making the
numbers. Okay. I am. I think you you you
we've all said it. You've done
fantastically, right? I've got so much
admiration. You've got a just an
absolute pair between your legs to go
out there and put 16 something million
bucks worth of gear in a confirm in a
factory to to start roasting to attack
the market and to take the market share
you have is is is really fantastic.
So, I'm trying to understand how we can
take this from the the size it is now. I
have a real real trouble with that.
Okay. So, on that, you've got three
offers there. I actually think they're
terrible offers and you should ditch
them all, but there there's three offers
on the table. I wish you all the best,
mate, but I'm out. Thank you. See, all
of that and he's out.
Is there someone you want to talk to?
Uh, Beyonce. Yeah. Thank you, guys. Go
have a chat.
[Music]
A little bit nervous as
I can see. Uh, so yeah, it's difficult.
Like it's
it's they're all they all have really
really good attributes and like I'm sort
of stuck between um them. Can we get the
percentage lower?
Um okay. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Go
smash it.
[Music]
Hello. Hi. So, this is Allesia. Um, my
better half and and the boss of the
boss. Allesia. Beautiful name. Thank
you. Well, you must be very proud of
him, huh? Building a business like that
so quickly. Well, being a better half, I
know I could do better. You mean you
mean you you mean you work just as hard
as he did? Probably harder. Trying to do
my best. Yeah. Fantastic. Kane, you've
had three offers and that's the biggest
amount of money ever been offered in
Shark Tank. 2 and 1/2 million bucks.
That's a first. It's a first. So, where
do you land?
Um Naomi came with with basically the
ability to market with us and also being
local. Glenn with the ability to upscale
um and yourself Andrew you have the
ability for the US and it was really
difficult um where we've come to one um
I I had to still see
was we're sitting with Andrew
um I spoke to Allesia and it was to see
if you could do 20% for the 2.5
So, they're out and I'm in and you want
me to come back at 20%. Is that the Is
that the bottom line? Yes.
[Music]
It's $2.5 million. Yes, it is.
I'm buying a big growth
story. How about 22 and A2?
Let's go. Let's take it to the world.
Well done. Thank you.
Well done. Thank you. Lovely to meet
you. Thank you guys. What an awesome
deal. I know. Great. Well, I'm going to
have the best coffee in town. You are.
You know, at the end of the day, what's
what's important is what the business is
worth in 2 or 3 years. Oh my god, that's
the biggest deal in Shark Tank history.
I know. It's It's crazy. And I think by
the time it died digest and we're in the
car and we're heading home, I think it's
just going to all sort of hit you at
once. I think she's going to have to
drive. How you going to celebrate after
making history? No. Maybe an espresso
martini. A few of them. Yeah, very much
so. Congratulations, guys. Thank you
very much. See you later. See you.
That's awesome. That is the record deal
in Shark Tank history. And it's a risk,
but you know, I just love his competence
and I love his growth rate. And that's
the blue sky I'm buying and I think he
can do it.
[Music]