First into the tank is a solution for an
inconvenient problem in the great
outdoors.
[Music]
Good morning, Sharks. I'm Bob Le and I'm
Keith Lindsay and we are Airboss
Outdoors and we're from Jacksonville,
Texas and we're here to ask you for
$65,000 for a 10% equity in our
necessities product business. At our
boss outdoors, we design and develop
innovative solutions to some of those
age-old problems that outdoorsmen have
experienced for years. In the outdoors,
you go out and you relax and you have a
good time. But there's always there's a
number one problem relieving yourself in
the woods.
[Laughter]
We've developed the number one necessity
for doing number two outdoors.
Let me introduce you to the crap strap.
That's good.
allows everybody a comfortable doing the
deuce outdoors.
Wait a minute now. Doing the deuce out.
You can see how it works. You just
simply attach it around your waist.
Attach it to a strong structure like a
tree or even a fence post. Uh you could
use the bumper on a vehicle even.
You simply lean back and let it fly.
What the hell? And relieve yourself.
Oh, Bob, I was worried we're going to
see everything there. I tried to get it
on TV, but I couldn't get there.
It It will take and hold 400 lb. It's
got two pockets, each one on each side.
toilet paper, corn cobs, leaves, or any
other thing you want to put in it. Now,
how many of you
onehanded can take a piece of toilet
paper and make it into a nice wipable
piece of equipment while you're hanging
on to the tree? You're still hanging on
to the tree. Let's say you get through
that. Well, you got to finish up the job
onehanded. M well let me just tell you
onehanded and you don't do enough and
you leave a residual it's going to itch
when it
dries back now by God the reason you're
laughing is cuz you've been there. No,
it's so true, right? So true. Right.
True.
Now, Sharks, we've come a long way from
Jacksonville, Texas. And we honestly, we
came here today to make a deal with the
Marco, Texas. Get up here, Mark. Go
demonstrate. Mark, no one drops a deuce
better than me. You know, my man, Bob.
Yes, sir. Why do you say it holds corn
on the cob? Cuz anything you want to put
in it to do the wiping job, people use
the corn cups. What? Oh my god. Where
are you from?
All right, Mark. Hey, wait a minute.
Move it down on his waist a little bit
and pull your feet. Pull your feet
forward. Come on. All the way in, Mark.
All the way in. Oh, yeah.
Go. No, Mark. Mark, like Lori would tell
you, knees up. Squatty potty level. I I
need the knees like way up there, baby.
Squatty potty like a dog. Like all knees
way up there. Yeah. Yeah.
[Music]
[Laughter]
This is great. Mark, do you feel like
you're seated? Like comfort. It's
comfortable. It actually works. Yeah,
it's comfortable. That's cool. So, I
have to find out about you. I'm 81 years
old. I'm a young relationship, dude. I
got to watch one. I can bend my knees,
but then I can't get up. And was this
your first invention? No, ma'am. Our
company started with motion decoys.
What's a motion decoy? When you put
decoys out, I go duck hunting. What do
they do? They just They just sit there.
Right. Right. Well, I put a motor in
them so they'd move and the ducks would
say, "Hey, dude. There's someone down
there. Let's go.
Anyway, uh I sold the company and it
whatever and then about three four four
years back got associated with Keith
whom I have known for 30 years and we
developed an outdoor business. Okay,
let's talk about sales. Has anybody
bought the crab strap? Yes. The
crabstrap went on the market in October
of last year. Yeah. Okay. With zero
advertising dollars spent. Y last year
we sold approximately 4,000 units
between October
how many dollars? Every unit went
through our e-commerce website. How much
it charge for it? $49.95 each. What does
it cost you to make it? $50. Wow. 200
grand worth of craft straps in four
months. What does it cost you to make?
Cost $17. And and it was no advertising
whatsoever. No advertising. How did
people know? Was it your existing
customer? Oh, no. Don't know. How did
they know? I'll tell you exactly. July
the 1st, he put it online just just
for one social media post by me. That
was on the first. That's a Friday,
Tuesday. It had been seen by a,200
people. And we had a list of wild and
bully. So, can I ask you what what do
you need the money for? I want to be
clear about our intentions for your
$65,000. Okay? You know, the people that
have been really successful at
marketing, e-commerce, social media,
advertising, we have tried some of that
and we waste money. Okay. We try on
that. We we waste money on that. So, we
get it. So right now what you're saying
is that you want to take the money and I
guess the partnership to do the sales
and market. Exactly what we want. A
partnership. Go ahead. I want to part I
want to have some fun.
[Music]
You know, I think it's so inspiring to
see you here creating products and
building a business. Bless you. And I
think it's a great product because sales
don't lie.
and you've got sales. We did. But I will
not be going on the crap trap journey
with you. It's not for me, but I wish
you all the best. I'm out. But there's
four other sharks and one from Texas.
Well, thank you, Keith and Bob.
Fantastic presentation and right to the
point. I was a camp counselor as a
teenager and I've had my rear end bitten
by mosquitoes while doing number two.
And that's why I have a new motto for my
life. Every night I have to sleep
somewhere where there's a mint on my
pillow. That's how I work. I I think
this is a fantastic product. You think
about products on Shark Tank for 15
years. No, there's never been a crap
strap. Never. Ever. And it works. But
guys, I'm not your Shark. I'm out.
We appreciate you, Mr. Kevin. Keith and
Bob, I think that um I'm actually
interested. I'm one of I think I'm the
only outdoors person here, but I'll be
very honest. Uh there's another shark
here. She would be interested because
she happens to have been in this space
in different categories. Squatty Potty.
Uh I think he has some other products in
this area. I'm asking if I can get
another shark in on here if she's
interested. I I I will go in on it with
you. I'll clear the I'll clear the deck
because I wanted to make sure you guys
got an offer because you'd be fun to
work with. But Damon's the outdoor shark
and he understands better than I do. So,
I'll go out and if their deal is nasty,
then I'll come back in.
So, what are you guys gonna do? What do
you have? Wait, they're getting ready.
You got to stop selling.
Okay. So, Damon and I discussed this. We
realize you need a lot of help with a
lot of things. Yes, we do. Thank you.
Damon and I are going to go in on it,
but we want to be more equal partners to
you. You came in asking for 65,000 for
10%. We're going to ask for
65,000 for 35%.
[Music]
Ichi wawa kamba. It's not bad.
There you go. There you go. So, we will
collectively own one/3 and I'm assuming
45% and be done with this.
Give us a little bit of room. Yeah,
let's 33 and a3. Damon loves that
number.
Bob, we're there. We're done. We're
done. Congratulations, guys.
Well done. Well done. Now you two can
say you help people do the deuce
outdoor. Do the deuce outdoor. Thank
you, man. You did great. You did great.
Thank you. I love you, too, man. All
right. Thank you, brother.
Now, you didn't take a crap while we
were here talking, did you? Damn it.
How did you
know? Bob, you're a star, buddy. You're
a star. Thank you. We love you. It's
going to be so much fun. Oh my god. Oh
my god. Good job, Bob. You go, boy.
We'll all make some money. It's fun.
They enjoyed it. I loved it.