a lot of people think that if you come
up with a really good idea that's all
you need but you need to understand isra
competition who has done this before
have they been successful if not why not
why would you be more successful than
other people you really need to deeply
understand why you will be better than
them and how you will be better than
them and you don't understand why you're
building when you're building it you
can't be successful hi everyone I'm
sheny co-founder in C at merch we help
companies add Integrations through
products really easily across categories
including Hrs ATS accounting serum
ticketing file storage and marketing
automation we've raised $75 million from
investors including Excel Nea and
addition and we're currently operating
in New York City San Francisco and
[Music]
Berlin oh my gosh trying to get your
first customers is so painful we spent a
long time building in stealth before we
started fundraising we were starting to
build a product and then once we
fundraised we continued building the
product and we actually didn't launch
for a year or so and once you come out
of steth you just expect all the
customers to come and they don't so we
were basically outbound begging people
to take a chance on us and to try our
product out and those early customer
sales processes taught me a lot about
what questions people would ask and I
think one thing that Gil and I did
really well was we really packed our
calendars with as many sales calls as
possible so we were pretty much like
from 10:00 a.m. to 9:00 p.m. both of us
just on calls it was a really tough
period in our life um we were just in
phone booths all day on calls and back
to back to back but it's it was a really
great muscle for just hearing the same
call over and over again AB testing
different pitches and seeing how people
reacted also just seeing the wide
variety of questions that people might
ask so by the time we hired our first
salesperson we were able to teach him
the answers to the questions that we
knew were always going to get asked if
we hadn't done that I think it would
have been really hard for us to ramp our
first salesperson we wouldn't know what
questions would come we wouldn't know
how to answer them and so by the time he
came we were able to say hey this is the
way that customers really like this is
what really resonates with them this is
what you shouldn't say so I think it was
really helpful for me and Gil to just
get those first reps in because it made
it so that the first salesperson that
came in and head of sales he was really
prepped and he was he was set up for
success to be honest we found product
Market fit pretty early on I think the
process of finding product Market fit
actually mostly happened before we even
started the companies user interviews
getting validation from people and how
much they would spend money all the
research had really happened before we
even started building I just didn't want
us to start building the product and
figuring it out later I wanted us to do
the research up front and we probably
spent six to nine months of just doing
user research before we quit our jobs a
lot of people think that if you come up
with a really good idea that's all you
need but you need to understand isra
competition who has done this before
have they been successful if not why not
why would you be more successful than
other people also the chances of you
thinking of an idea that no one else has
thought of before is extremely unlikely
probably someone else has tried this
before and they probably haven't
unsuccess successful if you haven't
heard of them or they're maybe in the
early parts of the journey so you really
need to deeply understand why you will
be better than them and how you will be
better than them so we started every
week and we would spend a day together
just reading up on the industry trying
to better understand it trying to better
understand why companies out there that
were weren't solving this problem and if
they were trying to why it wasn't quite
the right solution so I think the
research is so so so important because
if you're not opinionated about it and
you don't understand why you're building
when you're building it you can't be
successful
I think a consistent characteristic of
billion dollar companies is successfully
operating at scale with each team
operating on its own so what that means
is that each manager is successful at
operating their team and the manager
about that as well there's no individual
that needs to contribute a ton in order
to make the company successful the teams
are just operating at skill on their own
and that's really hard to achieve
especially from an earlier stage where
each individual is the one that's
contributing a lot to the company so I
think that transformation from
individuals contributing a lot to the
company to each team operating
autonomously and operating on their own
cross functionally that's the goal but
it's hard to
do it's not always natural for friends
to turn into co-founders and you really
have to have a foundation of trust you
also have to have complimentary Skillet
my co-founder is a genius he is the best
software engineer I know even to this
day Gil and I knew each other from
freshman year of college we met in
orientation and then we were in all the
same computer science class that's at
Columbia and so we knew each other
pretty well socially but we were also
fortunate enough to be on engineering
student council together in college and
that actually became a pretty helpful
proxy for what it would be like to work
together we were class president and
vice president our senior year and after
school we kept in contact and Gil and I
naturally just living our parallel lives
ended up getting skill sets that really
worked well together I'm kind of like a
master of none and I just I know a lot
of things I can code I can sell do
Financial forecasting but Gil is like
the best software engineer ever and he's
a great people leader and I felt like
the combination of the two would
actually be a really great pair the
advantages are it's just really fun
everyone that we've hired is so great we
have such a good time at work and a part
of that is because Gil and I are good
friends like we just really wanted to
make sure like the environment around us
replicated how much fun we had together
and it seems like so far we've been able
to scale that which is great
disadvantages are that your friendship
does change forever it's great because
it's more textured and it's deeper but
you probably don't want to hang out on
the weekends all the time together
because you're always together the
weekday you just end up like having a
friendship that's mostly just like okay
it's much more like you want to just
hang out you want to have a good time
but then now it's almost like you have
like a kid together and you always are
caring about this kid and you want to
talk about this kid together and that's
the company and a disadvantage of that
is just like your friendship completely
changes one thing that has helped a lot
with the really hard parts of being a
Founder is just making friends who are
peers I have a really great group of
female founder friends in New York City
that I made after I started merge and we
just talk about everything like
everything bad especially and it's
really hard to break that barrier with a
lot of Founders because people just
don't want to share that kind of
information it's very very sensitive
like you don't want to share your
numbers you don't want to share like
things that are going badly you don't
want to share about people who hate you
you don't want to share about customers
that hate you but like having people
that you can talk about that with really
makes it easier because everyone's going
through the same thing and everyone
hates their lives and I think just once
you realize that every founder journey
is really painful and that no one has it
easy it just makes it a lot it makes it
a lot better I think one thing that I've
learned is as I'm living through life
I'm not really grateful for the time
that I'm currently in but then as time
passes and I'm in the following year I
look back and I'm like wow that was such
a great time period and that actually
has consistently happened every year now
and so now I've realized like I'm
currently living in a time that I will
like look very fondly on in the future
and at some point like this journey with
merge will end and I'll be really really
sad about it so I think right now I'm
just really trying to like appreciate
every single day as much as possible
[Music]