We certainly, you know, had a decent
early success working with different
types of investors. A lot of them were
promising and also big deal at the
time. And after that, um, then came the
crypto winter.
We were watching Bitcoin falling below
$6,000 overnight and all of those
alternative coins were down by much
more. There were just a loss of VC
interest. uh there were loss of
institutional interest and it's about
minimizing like uh me and like my
co-founder's cost of living at the time.
Obviously there were a lot of you know
stress there's a lot of uh concerns
about what if you know the money runs
out tomorrow. So for us you know we had
to earn every single user we gained over
time. We had to earn every single dollar
that came in. We had to really really
learn how to be extremely efficient and
scrappy with the incubation capital that
we were given.
I think we had a lot of privilege by
initially going through the 2019 period.
We had the experience and understanding
that capital might be very very hard to
come by for an extended duration of time
and that's been basically the mindset
that we have. Ever since then, that made
us uh to be conservative during
very optimistic times and at the same
time being extremely
um optimistic during very fearful times.
The way we did it was focusing on the
long term. Plan for the future, ignore
the present conditions. So, if I have a
time machine and go back and and tell
myself at that time, it would be cherish
that moment because you're not going to
have a lot of those. And it's probably
the most powerful feeling in the
world. Hi, I'm Eric Chen, co-founder and
CEO of Injective Labs. We built
Injective, which is a blockchain built
for finance meant to democratize
financial access for all. Injective is a
multi-billion dollar network that's
currently delivering more than $50
billion of exchange volume with more
than 1.4 million addresses and users as
well as 1 billion
transactions. I studied uh computer
science and uh finance in college. I was
in a bit of a soul searching process
where I didn't really know what I was
truly good at. I couldn't really find
something that you know really piqu my
interest. Everyone doing finance wanted
to go into like the banking, hedge
funds, private equity, whatever. And
everyone like doing computer science
wanted to go into like Google. For me,
it was just uh very very torn. I think
one of the most interesting part of my
college life was certainly learning more
about crypto and understanding that
there's a lot of very interesting like
research uh subjects. But the first
thing I did of course was trying to mine
with the free electricity from the dorm
room. What truly made me excite excited
at the time was when I was doing
research on you know a particular issue
that was like plaguing the industry
which was uh front running exchange
collision sandwich attacks and stuff
like that which basically the simplest
way to understand it is that it makes
general users or traders lose part of
their money because some guy can find
like a better price elsewhere and then
arbitrage their orders on chain. For us,
it was basically a very simple
understanding is that it's a it's a
problem. We can come up with probably
like a pretty elegant solution to solve
it using some cryptographic trick. I
think the most interesting part about
Injective is that it's very much of a
blockchain built for finance. Let's say
we were talking about a smart contract
platform which is like Ethereum, Salana,
etc. The way these blockchains operate
is that it tries to be web through
computer that no matter what you toss at
it, it will figure out like a way to
make it work. The way Injective works is
that instead of always having to figure
out ways to optimize for application
trends or use cases, Injective decides
to be anchored for financial
applications. Hi, I'm Albert. Hi, I'm
Eric. We are Injective Protocol. The
best and most secure experience for the
centralized exchange. During the early
days, in the way the first 100 user that
was acquired was actually very simple. I
basically went into uh every single
group chat that had anything to do with
uh crypto to reach out to a lot of the
participants or the vocal members and
trying to tell them about hey like use
uh this interactive exchange try it and
let us know what you think you know whe
what whether it makes sense whether it's
a horrible idea and then we should stop
doing it. I just kept doing it the first
50 the first 100 the first god knows how
many hundreds or thousands and I think
the most interesting part is that
there's a lot of very vocal and negative
people in a lot of these like public
group chats or you know public forums.
Hey, like why do you have this? It
doesn't make sense. Why do you have this
feature? Like no, no one needs it. It's
always very very stressful for you to
talk to them or for you to even reach
out to them. But if you fight through
that like initial embarrassment
interfacing or like dealing with their
negativity, they end up being a lot more
valuable of an ally than you can
possibly imagine. A lot of these like
highly critical people are equally
critical to everyone and therefore it
means that they first of all they care
and second of all they give you
extremely valuable feedback and third of
all they're a lot nicer than what they
perceive to be. facing that negativity
with a very positive light and more
importantly listening and give everyone
no matter how negative they are or how
positive they are time of the day to
listen to their feedback and implement
upon it and it's about presenting to
them with a positive can do attitude
addressing every single concern or
problem that they might have listening
to every single one of their feedback
the product around people that voice
their concerns and opinions and really
iterate that way because you don't know
the right answer especially as a builder
to what's going to happen in the future
with a 100 or a thousand% precision and
accuracy. What you really need is have
user informed the direction that you're
building and listening to them because a
happy user will become the most valuable
ally for no matter what industry you're
in, no matter what product that you're
building. We certainly, you know, had a
decent early success working with
different types of investors. A lot of
them were promising and also big deal at
the time. And after that, um, then came
the crypto winter. We were watching
Bitcoin falling below $6,000 overnight.
And all of those alternative coins were
down by much more. There were just a
loss of VC interest. There were loss of
institutional interest. We had to
really, really learn how to be extremely
efficient and scrappy with the
incubation capital that we were given.
being crammed in a 70 or 80 square ft uh
apartment within New York with three
other roommates moving around in a world
trying to source talents at a
cost-effective way and trying to work
with as many globalized you know
developers and users and trying to
figure out ways to you know make
everything work. I think we had a lot of
privilege by initially going through the
period where we had the experience and
understanding that capital might be very
very hard to come by for an extended
duration of time that basically made us
to be conservative during optimistic
times and at the same time being
extremely optimistic during very fearful
times. It allows us to basically no
matter what condition it is always
ensure that you know we have a certain
amount of runway and we always can
survive for more than 5 years. The way
we did it was focusing on the long term
plan for the future ignore the present
conditions. Being around enough cycles
helps a lot because during extremely
bullish times uh during extremely
optimistic times we slowly become more
and more jaded more and more fearful. we
have like a innate sense of uh it's
almost like a primal instinct that
something is about to go wrong and I
think this helped a lot because it's
basically like an instinct that was like
developed over time after being in so
many cycles even before an injective on
another hand it's just like aial
question like have you earned it? uh a
lot of times you know like the success
is asymmetrical to the output and to the
fundamentals and oftent times we at all
times question ourselves whether we have
like earned the success that we have we
are often very very critical so we
always doubt that we did earn it and I
think that's still a very strong
relative benchmark to see how long-term
you
are I think the most exciting thing
about uh injective especially at the
current stage is about decentralizing
the access to finance to everyone.
Finance is truly a game for the rich and
it really shouldn't be. Whether you have
just $1 or like $5, you get to have
access to the same type of opportunity
to those with uh, you know, $5 million
or $10 million. And this is completely
not the current financial world.
Basically, if you want opportunity,
especially high growth, it's just layers
and layers of like investment advisors,
brokers, and stuff like that to purchase
one share of Apple, you have to have,
you know, hundreds and hundreds of
dollars. There's not even a
fractionalized concept within the stock
market. For us right now, the most
exciting thing is about being able to
bring in real world assets, being able
to tokenize so many exciting
opportunities happening in the
cross-section of traditional financial
world and also the crypto world. This
has just been always a dream of us, even
during the early days of Injective,
which is being able to access a lot of
these traditional products like Tesla or
GameStop, creating it in a platform that
also has access to different types of
crypto primitives while at the same time
being able to access it from all over
the world, from Argentina to Europe to
Asia and everywhere in the same easy to
access, easy to use platform. Basically
making uh financial products and assets
more accessible than ever.
I don't think there's going to be a lot
of uh material change uh for people in
the world. Their day doesn't just
suddenly become completely different at
full 180. But I think it's really about
the subtlety of things. Maybe you just
have more savings in your bank. Maybe
you can connect with your friends 20,000
miles across the world a lot easier.
Everyone is just a little bit better off
because of the opportunities that was
now accessible to you. I remember I uh
came up with Injective at the stolen
co-working space from my friend. It
wasn't something too flashy. It was just
hey this could be a solution to
something at that time. It was a very
very rare feeling to have the space
especially at a time was just
ostentatious way too much grandiose like
visions and stuff like that. So oftent
times it felt like it was losing touch
with reality. So that was a very rare
feeling for me even though these days I
get more and more of these feelings. uh
uh at this point in time. It was very
very rare at the time. So if I have a
time machine and go back and and tell
myself at that time, it would be cherish
that moment because you're not going to
have a lot of those. And it's probably
the most powerful feeling in the world.