this is funny shut it off hey stop
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
guys today my mom I love saying stuff
that like Mom and Dad do that's funny
because then they watch the video and
get all excited we talked about them
yeah but today my mom came up to Matt
and goes you wanna know what your
necklace reminds me of honey and it's
like a horse well we're expecting like
we're all expecting like keep in mind
I've also I don't know when I that video
that we were in that hotel because our
house started flooding and I hit Nick in
the face with the pillow and he said
okay and Nick snatched my snatched my
chain because I hit him in the face of
the pillow and we got into a big fight
boring heard it the day that that
happened I switched from that chain
because it broke to this horse one so
I've seen my my mom multiple times with
this I wouldn't say multiple I'd say the
last two trips okay she goes up to Matt
and goes you wanna know what it reminds
me up and it's a horse so we're all
expecting something like a beautiful
story like a spirit free in the wind
like jumping in correct we were
attracting something wholesome and sweet
and she said PF Chang's the restaurant
it shows PF Chang's in Boston and we're
like What like where's the food place
and she's like P.F Chang's because the
horse out front and I Googled it and I'm
gonna put a photo on the screen right
now but this is what the horse looks
like outside of P.F Chang's in Boston is
it it's just like a massive horse
sculpture
it's funny because it has nothing to do
with PFA it looks like every other horse
on Earth ever but to Mom it just really
sat with us friends it's so funny
because it's that horse has nothing to
do with the PF Changs being in the
background that's just what it does
that's just no it's just there it's not
PF
Chang's and figure yes I don't know if
that's like P.F Changs search up right
now search up right now is is the horse
normal at PF Changs because I think it's
a boss as opposed to why like do you
think like that Matt's just saying every
PF Chang's doesn't have a beautiful no
I'm saying if that's not North Shore
malls there's a horse outside the PF
Chang oh so it might be a PF Chang's
like this is that PF Chang's thing
because in my head that building can get
knocked down and you can put a Burger
King with a PF Changs that means
I don't I don't what's up with this fire
there's got to be something happening
right dead over there right around that
corner there's something bad going on oh
no there's a there's a horse outside of
many PF Changs oh I stand corrected so
shout out mom she figured it out yep
yours kind of looks like a UFO
bro oh our horse statues have become a
PF Chang staple standing guard as the
token of strength this is good you can
tell people you have your horse because
of PF chat I actually love that it's my
token of strength I actually really like
that that's really cool see mom's
amazing beautiful what an amazing story
that's awesome I was playing I have I
actually never been a new piano I was
planning on getting a horse tattoo when
I like retire this chain because you
know how people say like oh haircut
you get I didn't even notice the
glass you just got you know how people
say haircuts like Matt do you see the
yeah you know how people say I'm
happy you just did sorry I'm happy you
just did that because you haven't poured
something like pulled something out of
the back in a while
so I really appreciate it
I have my sweet tea
oh
is it where the did you get that so
mind your business it's not even in like
the house or anything
it's brand new custom-made did you
actually just buy it
don't worry about it
there's a trigger free not such like a
you know when people like he's like yeah
like is it sugar-free
what it's my first sugar-free red ball
ever and I can tell
anyway
that reminded me of a story you know how
people say yeah
I had something to say like five minutes
that I can tell my story oh good go go
ahead you were stuttering for 10 minutes
okay it doesn't matter I'm interrupting
you and I I'll own it um
they get what I was gonna say anyway
finish it then no it's fine go okay
something real sad see we can get some
edits out of it too maybe sneeze
afterward too okay go ahead I'm really
hoping I sneeze tonight
me too I just want to look super strong
when I sneeze oh I wore myself
[Laughter]
sorry excuse me that was nice we'll move
on yeah um I hate you both yeah please
don't edit that I'm super like shy about
your big arms my muscles but that
reminded me of the story The Mattress
said oh the person who had a sugar-free
Red Bull one time me and one of our
friends were going to get ice cream and
we're like oh Matt what do you want and
it was like from this vegan ice cream
place that why are you saying one of our
friends this story's been on the
internet I think it's I'm just saying
one of our friends it was Maddie and it
was it was vlogged fully I'm pretty sure
was it yeah
yeah I think this is already in the
internet oh but never mind my stories
are all but yeah because you got that
goofy haircut the same day remember
you got the Google that Salon won't
leave me the alone actually email
email we're open for another cut if you
want one I'm like off you my
out they have DM me every day I
showed the lady oh my God can you talk
about this the story there
the lady cutting your hair
okay I don't remember it at all he said
that she was like this Brazilian lady oh
no it was it was woman the woman who cut
my hair there like
I try to be like I'm all for women I
love them
this woman
had
breast implants for sure not that this
is like a bad thing it's just critical
to the stories that's why I'm bringing
it up but usually I wouldn't talk about
a woman's breasts but it has to go with
the story so I have to bring it up but
because she had breast implants her
boobs were obviously huge so she was
cutting my hair she was cutting my hair
and as she was cutting my hair she was
getting so close to me while cutting my
hair that like her boobs were like
resting on my neck and back and
shoulders and head and like she just
kept going around me cutting parts of my
hair and I'm just like I'm happy I was
like gay because otherwise like like I
was just scared because I'm like if I
was anyone else I'd feel very violated
like I was very comfortable but her
boobs were everywhere around me like my
back my shoulder if you're if you're too
straight man you're getting the wrong
impression no absolutely like I'm just
like like it was I just tried to forget
it and that's why it took me so long to
remember that because I was so like just
in shock because it's not something I
ever want but there was boobs all over
me oh that sorry killed me and I got a
bad haircut out of it so that's awesome
that's so funny that that story
actually took me out when he first
talked because I was happy that killed
me well no I was saying I was happy that
it was me and not someone else because
yeah someone that would like take
advantage of that yes exactly like a
rude weirdo
um well it was a woman's Salon Nick was
just getting his hair cut there oh
really yeah yeah so she wasn't used to
it did she know she was like comfortable
with me I'd say okay but not that's not
what I should do that just saying but I
did leave with a bad haircut so I don't
suggest that experience for anyone yeah
maybe you shouldn't have a good enough
View
I'm gonna hurt for you is great you
off my sweet tea dog I have to pee so
the faster you drink didn't even think
it was mine they're like taking the last
sip like stingy One Step well it's
brutal when it's the last one I went
there and bought it you know how much
Christmas beverages like this is gonna
be an ongoing argument what if you took
medicine that kept you alive and it was
the last one and I took it
what is that it's not medicine that
keeps you alive that's a dollar
sweet tea from McDonald's
it's just saying like
the last of something you can't give
someone their back but if you took a
metal set but it wasn't hate it you just
took another set okay
where the did you get your balance
break dude what's Triscuits and cheese
okay where the did you get this
little medicine reference is weird
she's don't smell good but cheese
doesn't usually smell good
I was like okay we're gonna play a fun
little game I have a challenge for Nick
and Matt
nah
he's checking this Oh I thought he said
nah to my challenge I have it you know
Ice Cube yeah of course is it is it late
probably it could be expired but anyway
it's late now we're good oh okay I just
didn't like that are you paranoid no not
anymore I just read the day I
thought you were scared okay you guys
are you up for the challenge
yes go okay I'm just gonna say a word
and you have to say the first thing that
comes to your mind easy okay ready
grenade explode
launch yeah Grenade Launcher only
closure
sandwich
pie
bread you're not saying the first thing
yeah first thing okay your answer should
be the second he's done with the word
ready brick wall bruh I almost said
brick again oh my God I'm just so
excited I was a brick Rock
something smells bad
what'd you say you oh that's crazy
bait or blank Bait and Tackle
right that's way too long no it's not
yeah it is like my creative brain
doesn't work like that I'm thinking of
like the whole sentence blank Bait and
Tackle Brian's
Big Oak Tree fat green
tea
leaves cup
what
stupid huh homework
I keep wanting just remix
I don't know that's
library book quiet
silent but then I was like okay that's
all I got Matt you look up some jalapeno
peppers
nacho cheese tall boy rap
necklace
you just said box of paint
PF Chang's horse
I don't want to get out I think it's
fine you think I trust it I hate I don't
like trusting it because it happens
where dude stop getting random snacks
give me some though can I have some
absolutely ask politely may I have some
of your apple chips
appreciate the love
it's my little kitchen back here you're
so weird welcome to Nick's kitchen do I
have to order something no baby I
haven't had those since like I feel like
babies like those I'm a baby like little
babies are like nothing apple chips yeah
Fuji
Fu G it's f-u-g-i Fiji
it's Fuji it's Fiji is it g or J it's j
it's Fiji or Fuji Jay it's it's Fiji
it's Fiji it's a you it's
not Fiji it's Fuji
where's my phone are you for real yeah
oh my God he thinks it's Fuji F it's a
Fiji Apple a Fuji apple
you sound actually like they're making
funny I'm
it's Fuji wrong it's a Fuji apple Let's
Ask Google translate wait Fuji now he's
got me saying it wrong Fiji it's Fuji
listen
Fuji apple you it's Fuji it's not
Fuji apple Fuji
and then if I go Fiji
f-i-j-i uh easy apple which is like the
water Fiji
people whoa
hold on it's in Croatian hold on
it's Fiji
it's a you it's
I didn't know that you dummy now
what was your question no it sounds I
feel stupid I thought it was Fiji
Apple my whole life
did you you saw the sweetie too right I
worked at a grocery store too fiji's the
water
no I'm probably just confusing I don't
eat fruit so I don't know I saw a tech
talk I have some
what do you want Fuji apple crisps
thank you I saw it talking this guy put
like a chain around an ATM and then tied
it to the front of his truck and then
drove away
I'm gonna try to like pull the ATM away
with them and it caught me thinking
how much money is in an ATM for you to
really want to like steal not that much
it's not like minimum or Max like 10K in
an ATM
I'm thinking last something like six
thousand what is the average ATM money
in so they're gonna think you're gonna
steal it nothing Nick what do they what
are they gonna do about it how much
money should I put your house kill you
start you bring you to the area
project if Mac gets trench dark I'll let
you know
wow
most machines contain less than ten
thousand you you so you said
this is less than ten thousand no not
ten thousand I should maximum 10K I
literally said exactly what Google just
did okay whatever me but like
10K to rob an ATM it's like I mean I
guess it's a it's a pickup
hm's in a really dark skill any amount
of money you Rob
is a good amount of money because you
get it for free you didn't have to work
but like what you shouldn't do it I
agree it got me one would be crazy if
you steal it and then you're bail to be
bailed that was like 4K you know one of
them are still in the price no you're
not they take the money back you know
like you know like money heists you're
actually dumb as for that that's
like money Heist and like that like
banks with like the big safes and all
that there's no way like every
single bit what was that maneuver there
like the crank of the Vault okay just
wanted to make sure it for me it's like
I really thought about this like you
know how like in oh in um The Dark Night
like the opening scene where they're
like getting all the money and the
duffel bags and all that stuff
yes you know what I mean there's no way
every single Bank in the world has like
those like giant racks it's just money
all over it I mean there's definitely
you know banks have very minimal money
nowadays because of the lack of cash in
the world most people are using their
cards
the other day and they didn't accept
cash oh yeah like you but like if I had
a thousand dollars in my hand or like 2
000 in the bank I would Flex the
Thousand because it's just like there
yeah like you're holding it like oh a
thousand dollars then two thousands like
oh cool
when money's in your hand it feels like
you have way more you know what I mean
so just everything it's about
perspective that's how the life it is
about perspective but like I don't know
I feel like 10K is not worth I feel bad
though because I never have cash anymore
and this guy asked me for money the
other day it's homeless duties like can
I have a dollar I was like I got you on
the way out like I don't have cash on me
right now and I went in and like I was
like oh I still I'm not gonna have cash
why would you lie well because I thought
I for some reason I thought that I was
gonna get like change
we were gonna get cash back but we
couldn't get cash back because you can't
get cash back like Apple pay what
what you know
you're not gonna believe me what that
Domino's 18 wheeler just drove by
and I heard it and looked up
and I saw the big pizza on the side and
I'm scared why I thought it was like
something coming out you're insane like
I saw the big pizza but because of this
like brick column we're next to I didn't
see that it was a truck and I thought
that there was a big pizza one it scared
me I was actually just what's your
favorite pizza place
please
infiltrator
where are they
what's your favorite pizza place my
favorite pizza place oh they're getting
out of the car
I'm gonna drive away is it a cop you
think no
oh you're scraping off the lot
dude
what is he doing
Darren
he's like that's like really scary yeah
the one downside of filming car videos
is we always witness really sucks
late at night yeah but it's fine all
right guys sorry it's raining right now
so that's what you hear we have to drive
away from that parking lot because that
man was a little scary but we usually
film for about 30 minutes and you get 20
minutes of content and I think we're at
about that so we're just gonna wrap it
up and film an outro in this park and
it's just hard to rain it's hard to rain
it's hard to film when it's raining
because then we have to go to like
specific area
so yeah
so
we don't want to have to drive like far
away I I think we filmed a great video
I'm very happy with what we just talked
about and I enjoyed it yeah can I have a
Fuji apple crisp you're a
I said it right yeah but you're just a
you
Nick you a little Hut to Molly aren't
can I have one you can off
I really wanted that
and all the things