hello everyone and welcome back to that
holiday game show on the stery Olo
triplet YouTube channel you know what
time it is you know who I am Barry MC
holiday spirit and today we're here with
some contestants willing to sacrifice
their life for holiday spirit I'm super
excited for you to meet these folks
we're going to bring on up the first
contestant but before we get started let
me tell you the first
[Applause]
game today's first game that we're going
to be playing is that's a good PR
or
coal welcome in our first contestant
they've been waiting outside all morning
like we got a new iPhone or something in
here Chris
dero hello how are you how are you
welcome to that's a nice's
present or
[Applause]
Cole are you willing and ready to play
I'm willing and ready Barry did you sign
your consent forms on the way
nope all right we've got green with gold
Ribbon or silver on Silver the choice is
yours one you will dread the other you
will enjoy basically how that's a nice
present or coal works is one of these
presents is equivalent to getting coal
on Christmas morning and the other is
like the best day out of the year so
each of our contestants will have the
choice between two gifts in front of
them one good one bad the choice is
yours I'm nervous Barry you should be
all right um I want to go green cuz I
have green on but I also have gray
shorts on so this is like kind of a a
rough go I don't know what to tell you
the choice is yours I'm me go with this
one all right let's see what it
says you got a nice
present nice I was reading it I was
reading the whole thing you got three
tops of your choice you can one to three
you get one really Grand item three not
too shabby the choice is yours now let's
see what he could have
got I could have got calberry let's see
it chani yogurt you dodged a bullet
there I let's bring up our next wow I'm
so so fairy I got the good item yes
let's [ __ ] go now I get to go pick up
a nice fancy thing yes on the on the
dime you and man yes nice yes all right
you get out of here let's go with Chris
to get his three new
tops hey guys for my um for my reward
Nick and or Nick and Chris Chris who the
[ __ ] am I talking about kid we've been
doing this for 2 and a half years shut
up Matt anyway Nick and Matt just took
me shopping and I got yes girl I got my
stuff this is ridiculous and I
appreciate the gifts guys I got like a
hat a jacket and a nice sweater all all
right welcome back folks we are done
look at those three amazing tops
Christopher got from playing this
amazing game next up we have a
contestant who's been waiting outside
since last week don't know how he's
still here bring him on up Matthew
stolo sty recording all right Matt you
know how the game works we just played
with Christopher are you prepared yeah
did you sign your consent form on the
way in when oh nobody's timeing those
whatever let's bring forward your
presents it's time for another Roundup
that's a good present or
cold all right you have a stand and
watch of course you can the choice is
yours make a good one you could be
getting coal oh goodness this isn't
stage either first try when you're
standing up here you get a little
nervous you're shaking
yeah something's drawn me this yellow
one let's do it that's definitely gold
but let's see what's underneath it's
telling me it's not good
oh wow okay red it is eat 10 french
fries in ketchup you got cold that's not
happening yes it is it definitely is
what happening that's what happen all
right guys let's see what you could have
got
,000 cash what an major upet an upset
from this kid not [ __ ] eating them
you absolutely are let's cut to him
eating it that's not happening 10
one yummy I feel bad I do feel bad I
don't know if I like the T no it's fine
it's fine
two around let him just do it again if I
hated ketchup I could not do this I
agree like I could never do it he's
doing it very Calon collected right
now
good boy Matt all 10 fries gone how was
it all right moving on yo what the [ __ ]
is up you just saw that other idiot eat
10 [ __ ] french fries and cry about it
but now we're back to our last and final
contestant come on up
sweetheart I've been offended you my
whole life I can't we find show yo this
is actually making me sick what's your
favorite Barry M holiday spirit moment I
know everything about you I loved 10
years ago when you and your wife cut
down your Christmas tree it was like the
highlight of my life you know how to
play right of course that's a nice
present I've seen every single episode
since season you
got all right we got two gifts here one
is good and one is bad are you ready so
based on the statistics of the holiday
game show that I've watched in the past
the last one is almost always bad so I'm
going to pick the right
one drink coconut water no you got the
bad one cool I [ __ ] hate this show
all right you want to know what you
could have
got yeah free dinner on Matt and Chris
aux for the car ride hoodie and a shirt
and 100 v-bucks no yeah you would have
got spoiled it was good and but he
gotal
no I'm actually
devastated what someone drinks this as
their favorite snack just think of that
yeah it makes me even sicker drink it I
need something to like like I need like
a shooter like you know you like take a
shot and like bite a lime or something
yeah whatever drink it can you shut
up look at him go see like the the gold
thing
that was good how much did you get down
oh okay a little bit I really just did a
great job of cranking my body into
thinking it was pineapple juice it was
the last thing in my mouth can we put it
in a
cup can I put it in a cup
sure okay you don't have to do that that
was terrible shocked no let's move
on this is all right you're making me
sick I'm scaring you yeah all right
sorry I just heard an amazing joke from
Shannon over there in my earpiece don't
tell my
wife this kid
is classic like TV guy anyways our
contestants are back Matt and what the
[ __ ] that idiot's name um what's the
gay one's
name now it's time for part
two what do you guys know what game
we're playing no you should it's always
part two
anyways we got the holiday spelling
be
yeah each of your contestants is going
to come up here one at a time and
receive five holiday words that they
have to spell but some of our
contestants are notorious for not being
able to spell anything basically each
contestant is going to come up here try
and spell five words and whoever gets
the least out of all five words spelled
correctly gets a pie to the
face do you know what you're up here for
I'm here for five holiday spelling be
words yes you are let's get started your
first word is
Krampus nobody wants to be Krampus this
Halloween I mean what crem c r a m wrong
got cold I'm pissed Barry I'm pissed
security get Shannon out of here safely
quick your second word is
slay are you serious and it is not this
type of slay you're thinking slay
s SL L yes sound it
out e yes I yes g h yes that is slay you
slayed I did it your next word is
another tricky one we have vacation what
does this have to do with holiday
holiday vacation b
a c
a t i o n correct two for three let's go
Barry breathing f r e e z i n g
correct decorations d e
c
o
r ray d e c o r i wrong it's a why
would why would it have an I I literally
knew we didn't have an eye in it's all
right three out of five words correct
let's see if Nicholas I suck at spelling
let's see if Nicholas or Matthew can
beat that Score first word is holiday h
o i l wrong gar land g a r land l a n d
correct
correct don't know c h i m n yes e yes e
no your next word is Jolly j o l l y cor
correct your next
word is Miracle it would be a holiday
miracle if you m i
r
yep I no no no I got one yeah he's down
mad what is winter St size I don't know
I don't write the w i n t e r s o l s t
i c e
wow wow correct police na f e l i z n a
d i d no n a v i d a d oh I rushed I
just let everybody know I actually know
how to spell I just SP things wrong for
entertainment all right your next word
is wreath w e a t
h yeah crap
icicles IC e nope what I can't believe I
got icicles wrong am I like not using my
head Tabernacle t a b Matt what are you
doing like tab t Okay e r mhm m a c l e
yep correct Tabernacle wa is it right oh
I'm not getting pied this you get pied
all right you've lost the spelling me
how do you feel [ __ ] awesome looks
like you're getting ready for a haircut
that's all we're here for though are we
no what's your punishment
I'm getting pied pie to the face
everybody say it with me pie to the
face that's right say it one more time
pie to the
[Music]
face goodie for Berry huh yeah a little
snack see you later Shannon mat I'm
sorry I'm going to try and be as gentle
as I possibly can
I love
you a I'm sorry if it's not this I mean
habanero peppers you
know yeah it's in my nose that's good
pie to the
face like how does this even happen oh
and you missed Barry what a good Dodge
Barry Barry knew it was coming I had
contestants try that before and you know
what happened to them 12 years in prison
all right guys now for the final part of
today's holiday game show it has been a
blast we're getting to the point that I
love so much when this real fun I love
so much when this show comes back around
it is time for whatson Santa
sack since Matt lost the most amount of
competitions today tomorrow we're going
to be back live for the next part where
Matt is going to use his budget to fill
a Santa sack with 10 items after Matt
Phil Santa sack Nick and Chris will take
their best guesses at the amount of
budget that went into it per item and
whoever's closer to the total will win
all the prizes from Santa sack so stay
tuned Matt basically went shopping at
Target today and he bought 10 gifts
inside of a gift bag and he's going to
pull them out one by one and then me and
Nick are going to take turns guessing
the price of it and then we're going to
add up all of our price at the end end
and whoever gets the closest to the
price of all the items wins the entire
bags and the holiday game
show oh my God a
ripstick a ripstick a red structure
something oh Squirtle stuffed animal
right down your
guesses oh my God that's lit is it a
robe a wearable Ninja Turtles blanket oh
I need a win I need a win I need a win I
need a win I need a win I need a win I
need a win are you nervous Nick all
right o water bottle fortnite water
bottle it's like slurp juice a pumpkin
mocha candle M oh that's big it's not
yane candle it seems to be like Target
brand yes
next what's this silly scense mini art
case oh I have no idea how much this
going to be polar bears that's so
[ __ ] cute Lego polar bears oh I want
this so bad that's so [ __ ] cute dude
Slinky the dog oh that's so fire I want
this my really bad that's actually so
sick
okay dis one and two ultimate hits Nick
you're going to love that last last one
this one's a bit of a blast from our
past H like PR no that's why I saw it
and I was like got to get it cuz that we
used to play with these as
kids Lincoln Logs Lincoln Logs oh my God
once to go first Chris I said $60 I said
$89 that one's going to go to Chris it
is $54.99 let's pumpkin candle what did
you say Chris I said $24 I said n bucks
I no candles are always so [ __ ]
expensive it's how much is it$
13.99 I said 24 what am I thinking
LGS I said eight bucks eight bucks is
Crazy Chris I said $16 $24.99 what link
also purposely low balled I said eight
bucks Nick are you serious are they
giving [ __ ] away at the Target $8 you're
insane I said 20 1999 good job within a
cent get [ __ ] polar bear Lego said I
said 16 bucks I said 16 bucks as well
$12.99 damn Crayola silly sense okay
purposely low balled again what did you
say $17 I said 11 bucks 179 oh my God
I'm so good I am unbelievably good
Squirtle I said $24 I said
$29.99 that's insane how much it is I
said 16 bucks I said 18 bucks 2049
wa
2049 fortnite water bottle 12 bucks I
also said $12 $1 199.99 wo I thought
that I was lowballing it yeah that's
expensive hly
wow your Disney hits vinyl I said $25 I
said 23 $24.99 good J that's everything
y'all now it's time to add up see who's
closest to Santa's budget I guess
$24.99
$14.99 I guess
um it's going to go to Chris here
$240 wow I was within $8
Nick you cannot beat that I was within 8
[ __ ] dollar wow I'm actually not that
upset I was within $8 I was $35 off
let's [ __ ] go I'm so excited that I
just won that you have no clue well
thank you guys for watching the
Christmas game show with the cellow
triplets we hope you enjoyed the
Christmas content so far and cheers to
more cheers to more look at that the
holly jolly
Christmas it's the best time of the year
jingle bell jingle bell Jingle Bell Rock
jingle
bell jingle
bell me yeah you miss me and all the
things that we did we said we going to
travel from the island to Madrid we had
a lot of plans but they
alled because but it's okay cuz I'm
moving different don't be saying when I
post with other [ __ ] for my brothers