I hate this kid's like [ __ ]
not literally it's ridiculous
what's up with this toward you idiot
like I did that dude he's not even gonna
be in the [ __ ] video in a second
[Music]
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah
yeah
I got you the sticker cause you the goat
hey
you put that sticker on I actually you
actually got me this so I can't do that
yeah I got it for you yeah plastic he's
been acting brand new ripped me out the
plastic I've been acting brand new bro I
want to eat wings write me out the
plastic I've been acting brand new I
want to eat Wingstop Whitlock I'm a
lotto's biggest fan I genuinely like I I
don't I'm not her biggest fan in the
sense of like music like I couldn't tell
you every single song but I just like I
think a lot is a real ass [ __ ] I said
what do y'all want to see in upcoming
car videos is this story not because I
need ideas but genuinely because I want
to please the people watching the videos
right
someone goes
rare feet picks
at any feet pick you get in these pretty
rings
they're already in rare territory
without any of them are no need in the
specification level of like that that's
crazy no but like literally I don't
think I'll I'm never comfortable with my
foot just like everyone's just out there
no remember that I came
um to the car the other night fully
Barefoot okay remember we went to
McDonald's and then I put my foot on the
oh
a month and a half ago so yeah like the
other night okay well now we have to
check because two weeks the other night
fine it was like at least a photo dump
from before our last trip to Boston
that's not true Nick
it was July 14th
weeks ago all right you win whatever
whatever what about this what about it
he's just wrong I don't know oh Rarity
picks down
down what am I a [ __ ] puppy
what that photo of you from last Vlog oh
yeah it's so funny I saw somebody
compare you to the dream man no
literally insert the photographs
[Music]
dude that's like not the first time I've
been a [ __ ] meme
oh yeah when you were when you wore the
hellfire club shirt it's 7-Eleven
someone else said dude someone else goes
do you guys miss your teenage years that
was like four days ago relax I actually
do people thought we were gonna age
vampires in the sun he does tell us
about it I just miss it you know being a
little goofball okay stop talking I
genuinely think like that there were
people talking about like I was turning
20 like Angry like we had everything
it's Our Fate
[ __ ] hella close like legit why does
he have a juice box
yes guys I feel bad they made fun of his
Juice Box no I'm just confused but I'm
shocked I just feel like all people I
didn't make fun of it I said why does he
got one because he's just like a kid at
heart probably I love juice boxes I'll
probably no that's like you said that
before what video did you say the Capri
Sun thing in
last week now was maybe unreleased pod I
think it's unreleased pods never mind
never mind never mind never mind never
mind scrap that scrap that scrap that
scrap that oh God you're funny nick what
are things that make you angry oh just
make that blood boil things that look at
how cute that dog is
oh he is really cute no he's got [ __ ]
hanging from his lip no he doesn't oh he
does he looks like a little potato
though I don't like the word potato I
remember when potato was like not not in
the tents you just used it that was okay
I'm just talking like in like 2016 when
people were just like me and potatoes
like crazy like everything had to do
with potatoes and they're like oh I'm
like you're a potato like I I really
like I hated with potatoes potato okay I
hated the potato hype seriously that's
it I hated working at a grocery store do
you know what I mean then potatoes had
such a severe all the different potatoes
I got so used to it like I could tell a
russet from a regular I just made
everything roasted potatoes every
potatoes
mostly apples too and if they were all
red they're all going the same way
that's crazy I was so good at my [ __ ]
job yeah except you were [ __ ] skin
and
I
genuinely was probably the best employee
at the grocery store they had ever seen
in their life and I think that's why
Jesus Christ blessed me with the
position of becoming a YouTuber and
being able to do this for the rest of my
life because I took my Star Market job
as serious as the [ __ ] FBI I went in
that hoe trying to figure it out and I
was just getting people their groceries
I don't think anyone was ever I think
Pod episode about that would be really
good
oh my God Nick you're like actually the
funniest person I know I'm fully aware
thank you
Nick if you were a flower what would you
be
I feel like whoa why'd you say whoa
I don't want to say it say it it's
embarrassing why I was thinking of
dandelions and I'm like what are like
cute cute but rude name at the same time
like Dandy's so fun and then lion is so
aggressive
definitely I would have kept that in
mind well it's just like the perfect
amount of fun because it's like Dandy
lion like it's so like
probably kids drowning in the pool
when I think of dandelions I just think
of like kid what was that half ass God
it was like right there the sneeze it
was that Fireboy and Water girl when
they hit the water or like the lava
whatever on there no I think that's just
them jumping is it yeah yeah you just
sound like Fireboy and Water girl insert
the sound are you actually good
no someone else can do it I'm not
feeling up for it yeah
um oh my God Nick you make me laugh
that was a good one I hate the Power
Rangers
like what the [ __ ]
you don't know [ __ ] about being uh
um a kick-ass teenager fighting the evil
from other planets okay nickname for
Power Rangers
what by name yeah why I've been testing
you Zach Kim Aisha and um Jason it took
you a while didn't it no it didn't yeah
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles are better
than the Power Rangers
also wrong what's up with you guys in
wrong opinions today like what's up
I love Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
Matt yeah last night did you ask I
actually know we didn't ask him did you
ask him what
no I was just wondering why you were
just saying [ __ ] that no one cared about
yeah you're a funny dude I was just
getting confused
doggies people's walking so many doggies
today
oh now let's get a little pepper what
classified as like a doggy like there's
dog there's puppy and like is it like I
just call All Dogs oh the little puppy
oh dog I could go oh I could call a dog
on its death bed literally getting
injected to be put down a puppy like I
always do that yeah the puppy could be
blind hairless and crooked and I'd be
calling it a puppy yeah I call all dogs
I call dogs puppies and then once
they're dogs
what dude I want my rap name right yeah
puppies are like puppies is a word if
you say it too much it just sounds weird
puppies puppies
I just say oh puppy to any dog like it'd
be literally withering away and I'd be
like oh poppy sometimes I noticed about
Nick
we we met someone the other day the
other day for first time at a party and
like when meeting people or like
reintroducing it I know I know what he's
I know what he's gonna say Nick always
goes like this like you like you and me
walk up to the person and go oh what's
up you're like I'll go oh what's up nice
to meet you in the Nicholas hi nice to
meet you
salutes and then shakes
was it for fun is it aside
it's honestly to break the awkwardness
because when people meet us I'm usually
like for some reason it's not like the
person's picking I'm just usually the
last person to say hi I don't know how
because you're like the least
approachable I feel like okay that's
awesome that's a nice fun fact about me
um
you really just said oh you're a [ __ ]
beast no one is no one can go near no I
just feel like if I was at an event
where all three of us were that'd just
be the last one that you'd approach you
would be the most intimidating to me yes
because you just look like you're gonna
like rip myself like a ravaging mutant
scene yes you look you look angry that
was so funny no it's more of like you
just have the most like like you like
I'll stand there and I'll be like this I
got the most grit and you're just like
this you'll be sitting there like
[Music]
imagine you meet someone and they go to
you and they go hey what's up yeah no
it's not like a salute it's like it's
two fingers it's two figures
outro Trend yeah like the people like
yeah play their outro and then leave the
room and then go like that and then like
walk out the door nick does that before
it's simply to break the awkwardness of
like they looked at Matt said hi looked
at you said hi I'm just like uh like
it's like a it's like in addition to
like but I do Converse use a lot of
people because like when I go like this
I think they think I'm like they see my
arm go up so they think I'm gonna go for
a hug but then I that's like this first
and then I go to shake their hand and
then they start to go for the hug so I
have to like pull my arms I hate the
in-between like oh it's so weird I'm
mostly a handshake guy
I'm a hugger for sure unless it's a
straight man because I'm just like I
don't know where your level of is like
no that's how I feel about like meeting
guys that have girlfriends like I'll hug
the guy and then I'll shake his
girlfriend's hand yeah I always do that
you know what I mean that's such a [ __ ]
thing though like if you're if you're a
man and you have a girlfriend
no I know you don't care what I'm saying
like if you're a guy who has a
girlfriend and you're scared of like the
girl like hugging a guy that she meets
like yeah
you're an insecure loser I agree with
themselves I agree
um but but it's never like I feel like
like that like the hugging thing when
it's like never mind I'm not gonna get
into it go ahead get into it you want me
to get into it yeah go ahead okay when
when you normally when you're normally I
know no because I'm down it's just like
if you I don't know just say it with
pumpkin fun if you were to hug a girl
how are you hugging a girl right
over the over her should like is she
much taller than you no yeah what was
that you can't do like because you're
most suffocating most of the time the
girls hands go over and then the guy's
hands go under yes I know that but like
when it's like friend level
say hypothetically you're anyone new
that I'm eating if you're a guy and I if
I'm meeting another guy I'm like oh hey
give me a scenario who Nick is you're
true best friend okay and I'm
introducing you to my other guy best
friend okay so you're my bro and you're
my bro but like hey
and then one armed hug with hands in
between yes yeah I hate when Stripes
that's my least favorite why why I just
don't like it so broey like like I'm
never doing that ever okay I'm usually
like hey
who's here okay okay I wouldn't let go
that slow you're just far from me it's
like I go like this
yeah like yeah I guess yes
so that's Bros right
if I'm hugging a girl yeah I always try
to go above their shoulders I don't like
both my arms
I feel like I feel like arms is a girl
that's like that wants like is flirty
yes get away but like also it totally
depends with the girls throat where most
of the time I'm just gonna shake
most of the time I just want to shake
your hand get away get away get away I
need my space I don't know hugging is
weird as [ __ ] because at some point you
do like figure eight
like what not figuring not figure eight
but like yeah like an X just hugging you
right there I think hugging people you
don't like is like really scary yeah I
don't like touching people and I don't
like someone and I'm hugging them I
always feel like my feet are like
further away
like it sounded like a top hug you know
what I mean like a lean yeah yeah I'm
not trying to be like yeah you know oh
my God hugging is so strange it is
that's why I'm saying I'm mostly a
handshake guy unless I would never I
don't like the idea of like hugging
people that are on like stranger level
for me I hate it that's why I'm saying
like you guys said you're Huggers like
I'm I'm a hugger I'm a hugger future
with the person in my life if I know who
they are like if I'm like friends with
you I'm gonna give you a hug like every
like when you're when you arrive when
you leave I'll give you a hug you know
what I mean but if like I just met you
I'm not gonna like give you a full
Embrace unless it's like
unless it's like you're friends with one
of my friends you know what I mean or
you like know each other online yeah or
like I always do like the half hugs too
sometimes and like we're meeting for the
first time I just be like oh yeah what's
up oh I did the wrong one no it's just
like yeah
it's really weird
it was like you were taking a photo
together yeah no it's like a all right
that was terrible oh little kid
oh wow where's where's her parent oh
there he is okay oh a little it was like
weird no I was just confused I was like
why is there a little kid driving around
alone
that was so weird little kid
no just ready you wanna see you want to
see me make my thumb disappear I've done
this before
I've done that I did that once once in a
video yeah
once I did that once I did that was a
tweeting for his life guys I have a PSA
to all the people out there if you see a
blue UPS truck or USPS shut the [ __ ]
enough about this a year ago almost no
it wasn't that was like two months
please send me a photo of it please go
ahead Nick tell them no yes me and Nick
had a bet because he [ __ ] thinks that
a blue USPS truck exists and it doesn't
they don't [ __ ] first of all
let's show them what the right we have
fans from all around the world so if
you're unfamiliar with USPS it's the
United States Postal Service and I swear
to God I saw a blue USPS truck Chris
claims that every single one is they're
all white this is what they look like
from Matt's phone right there put it on
the screen I've seen a mix and when I've
seen it no you haven't this is the last
you oh yeah you saw that Nick what were
you [ __ ] like
were you [ __ ] churning butter when
you saw it drive by and don't drop off
your [ __ ] package I was actually
riding my cherry at home okay
weird dude run back dream I had one yes
oh my God I don't even get into it that
was the most violent dream I've ever had
I remember when I was like when I was
like six years old
I had a dream and I was 11 years old
why'd you just buying a drink I'm not 11
years old about what are you doing my
next
in my dream I know that's like just wild
it was my grandma and grandpa but not my
grandma and grandpa and people I call
them Mima and pop pop and I mean I've
never seen the people in my dream ever
before and Nick had a dream you know I
saw a thing that all the people your
your mind can't like make faces so
everybody in your dreams even if they're
don't believe it you've seen them you've
seen them in real life disagree
completely disagree I don't there's no
way your brain doesn't have the ability
to just create a new person in your
brain but you know how many people you
see a day that you don't even realize
you saw
I know it is bad is true like what if
like Papa could have been your doordash
driver no I wasn't doordash and [ __ ]
back I'm just saying up like I am now
okay buddy you guys got the dash pass
and he thinks he's off you know me what
would your guy's favorite tree be tree I
want to go in the one that you can drive
through the forest I actually want to go
to the Redwood Forest yeah
Chris I want to go to like I want to go
to all the nature places like Yosemite I
want to go to I [ __ ] did a project on
the Redwood Forest tell us all about it
oh my God I want to go to Yellowstone
really bad mine was about the Grand
Canyon where's Yellowstone I went
Yellowstone National Park
I'm gonna go to Iowa
calling
let's do answers
thank you for calling Yellowstone
National Park
you have reached us outside our normal
office hours
if you have an emergency requiring
police fire or medical help and are
inside Yellowstone National Park hang up
dude hang up no no outside Joseph
Park I need emergency police assistance
within the park please call 307
what that freaked me out I thought you
were calling like a stranger I want a
churro what four states are part of the
Grand Canyon the four corners of the
Grand Canyon are New Mexico Utah
Arizona and Colorado
hey she's getting it
screenshot that
you're nuts it just it was funny it was
funny that is just crazy that like
that's I just don't believe in States
like when I see [ __ ] like that my
imagination of living in each state just
completely floods with falseness wow
that was a crazy sound I want to go back
to Route 66
did we've been on it yes will Mater the
photo of me in the green green face that
was that yes oh we have to go back where
cars I love cars and I have the gray
Crocs on the Green Stripe shorts and the
green yeah
back to Route 66 I want to go dude we
gotta go back there
dude look it oh
okay Lou posted oh my titties popping
dude
photos from back then Christ oh my God
that would have bullied us
like what possession look at me what
possessed me to put a Venus I look at
least three years younger than you both
yeah
you really were get at the Vineyard
Vines Chris has got the [ __ ] crooked
feet
yeah you're holding this camera what
actually
wow that's crazy
damn did it
font for the Hoover Dam I'm so
underwhelmed that just looks like that
that looks like a bored Taurus person
okay this is the Hoover
I need something with like it says like
Hoover damage extreme I agree yeah it's
like that is a boring yeah this Fountain
this one's not going on
he would always just eat things that
were like blue raspberry flavored uh
whether it was ice cream a popsicles the
kid's mouth was always blue for so long
it always looked like someone was
pushing Matt's head forward when he took
photos what it looked like someone's
like this smile and like shut up if you
have to swap your head out with one
fruit what would it be oh the camera's
about to die holy [ __ ]
did you say you said I know what you're
saying how you how you miss me
[Music]