get in
dude I think someone's smoke
alarm I think someone's smoke alarm is
going off you have hair okay I'm helping
you out hey guys welcome back to another
Friday video with the stern old this is
Nick Matt and Chris and today we are
going to be answering like you think Ugg
has real alpaca fur inside did they ever
say that they had real alpaca fur I
posted a thing that said car video topic
ideas what do you guys want us to do and
then someone was like oh what would you
do if a genie gave you three wishes and
I said that's not an idea but I love
that question so then I posted a
separate Instagram story and said ask us
questions similar to what would you do
if a genie gave you three wishes which
isn't really a video topic but that's
kind of what we're going with and we're
just going to answer whatever questions
you guys put there it's more of just
like some random q& A's yeah some random
question and response crazy that bears
just sleep for like one/ third of the
year no they don't actually you're lazy
get up they don't actually
do that that's what I'd say I I'd poke
the bear I'd go into the cave and say
hey you're missing World out here it's
been a while since you've seen the Sweet
Sun correct and it's like I just feel
like I'd miss out on so much if I were
to hibernate for like a third of a
season yeah Bears definitely don't have
fomo yeah just get up hello so let's
start with the question that deemed this
video idea what would you do if a genie
gave you three
wishes
something about like the air that
popcorn occupies I feel like I'm like
not being able to breathe I agree like
sometimes there's popcorn in the air I'm
just like literally I feel like I'm
stunned my skin dries out I go no I was
in a hot tub and I get so hot in a hot
tub but I don't want to be the first
person to be like hey maybe we should
get out of here and I was so hot in a
hot tub the other day but there was like
five other people in it then I started
to like rub my hands along the side and
gather cold water on my hands and then
go like this like cool myself down like
I started cooling myself down with like
older water that got cold all right one
of the qu next questions what would you
do if you met a
leprechaun I know what I do I wouldn't
say hello I have a list of things
there's so many things where's the Pot
of Gold what's Over the Rainbow can I
have your autograph let's take a picture
holy [ __ ] what's the weather there you
know what I mean I have like five
questions or requests immediately the
first thing that I would
say pot of gold no ask if he [ __ ] at St
Patrick's Day or if it's like kind of
like a hey we don't talk about that type
of situation I feel like I feel like
leprechauns would all be like like if if
I brought up St Patrick's Day in front
of aund leprechauns I don't know if
they' all be like oh like this guy's
sick or if they' be like can you [ __ ]
chill like they hate talking about his
Hy be what they do it's one of the I
feel like I would instantly look up cuz
I if I see leprechaun I'd already think
that I'm at the end of the rainbow oh
wow you very Lal i' be looking for the
arch yeah why asked the rainbow it's
like you're pretty much there uh-huh I
mean the leprechaun's there so it's like
how big way smaller Nick like Smurf yes
no like when you just asked me what I
would do if I found a leprechaun I was
going to say take them and put them in
my
pocket like a little guinea pig so wait
with his pot of Co what his pot I feel
like they're big pot of gold just be
like by meter money if he's that
small you know what I mean like if a
leprechaun's actually decides like a
Smurf would would it be fair to say that
his pot of gold is just like my bag of
quarters for the meter or my piggy bank
right well I feel like they'd be gold
not silver what else could you do with
the pot they're not cooking it they
could cook in that thing what could I
make what could you make in a for meal a
meal for you in a leprechaun wait so how
big do you really think it is like this
big or likef yeah Smurf or like a foot
and a half say foot and a half a foot
and a half uh-uh well if they're that
small they're just a gnome at that point
remember that movie The Little
Leprechaun basketball player yeah
hey keep the popcorn in your mouth buddy
I get it we're excited around here yeah
it's all right I know it's hard to
breathe and stuff too whatever you're
saying next question if you could have
picture each each other's names at Birth
what would they have been each other's
names I feel like we were too young our
names really mad I was [ __ ] to an
umbilical cord so yes I feel like I was
too young I wasn't even eating for
myself yeah that's too young for
anything literally I was crying and they
were like thank God this Baby's alive
he's crying that's all they could think
right that is that is the definition of
too young I haven't even had a thought
yet my eyes are covered in goof
it's go like this so wipe my eyes
they're still debating 50/50 whether or
not I'm an alien or not and they're like
damn there's two more of these other
[ __ ] too yeah too
young I didn't even know my name when I
till I was like six I feel like yeah
when I was a kid I wanted my name to be
Antonio moving on to the next question
wait wait what what's the question we
just skipped over if we named each other
what do you think if we named each other
what do you think we would name each
other or have named each other IM said
they would be too young to name each
other right away yeah yeah granted well
let's think the circum if we named each
other what do you think we would do like
in current day yeah me and Matt think a
good nickname for you would be scratch I
agree cuz you're always itchy but yet
again to counteract that maybe we just
nickname you lotion so that we don't
forget so that way you don't itch as
much right okay or moist I proba name
Matt
crusty hi crusty Nick would be the um
the
jester no I'd love for my job to just be
to juggle for the king I was going to
say you're you I thought you were going
to say that you would you would love if
your title started with the play the
jester the jester or like if you were
like no no I agree I was thinking of
something else okay next question the
headless horsemen like you just like
that be my favorite thing if you could
if you would create a potion to bring
you back to your childhood what
ingredients would it include you feel
like a Skylander
giant yeah probably or not no not like a
sky like I think it would have to be put
on like the Skylander definitely
SpaghettiOs like a heap of that like a
big a big Heap and scoop of SpaghettiOs
be a laptop that doesn't work yeah okay
okay I'm thinking like a space heater
okay weird like a space heater it's
giving like we lived in a cave no no no
just like a space heater maybe ancient
Egyptian hieroglyphics
no no no no probably not yeah no
probably I'm thinking like those little
kid scissors like the oh safety kids
kids friendly scissors fun scissors yeah
if you could go back in time and change
one thing what would it be probably my
to get all the king horses and All the
King's Men to get back Humpty Dumpty
back together again think about it if I
go back it's crazy they got all the
king's horses and All the King's Men for
for an egg that was sitting on a Ledge
Humpty Dumpty think about your decisions
right go back to Prime fortnite is that
what the question holy [ __ ] is that the
question moving on holy [ __ ] we're done
what would you do if you could transform
into any animal going be an arachnet so
I could scare Chris in his sleep like a
little spider I'd kill you no you
wouldn't [ __ ] you'd run away no I
wouldn't I'd call Matt and say hey kill
this thing exactly what said um I'd
probably be a little mouse and crawl up
Nick's leg I was thinking a mouse and
then I eat your cheese [ __ ] that would
probably cross the line if I ate your
cheese yeah get out of my get out of my
house you cheese eater okay dude I think
I just want to be our M our mice really
eating cheese like this I don't think so
where the [ __ ] are they getting
cheese what every single time we're
using a cheese for a mouse or not we but
the we as in the people yeah we are
killing the mouse or trapping the mouse
mouse trapping where do they get cheese
otherwise is it like a cheesy thing like
do they get cheese all the time they
might but how is that the food I I don't
know I don't know who declared cheese my
food I feel like they're more of like a
crumb like anything those [ __ ]
e anything they're rodents I feel like I
transform into I keep seeing something
like go by like I keep seeing something
in my peripheral and looking up and
there's nothing the engine heated
up was that real I thought there was a
video no that was no that was me I could
be easily use remember red from us when
she's
like don't do talking like that I could
do that wait I would love us three in
that movie like imagine three duplicates
aome six I'd kill you so quick the red
one the red one the other the I think
it'd be F I think it'd be fun to be like
who can outwit the other like if they
like a clone of you I want to get to
town I want to battle
him you know what I meant you know what
I me like I just want to see like if we
could wrestle or box without we should
just organize it with our other three to
do a tag team wrestle like get a whole
ring and then like and then like me
versus me and tag next next Imagine Nick
you're like climbing up the top ropes I
tag you in and jump on the alterate te
version of me from that
movie he'd be
scary he'd be a scary scary person like
I'm already a little scary but I'm nice
you know I got like the sweetness to me
I don't I don't think he would at all I
think he'd be like kind of like like me
on a bad day plus like a dark energy M
okay God you know what I mean though
terrifying right next Nick with like a
really straight face just would freak me
out just yell at people like that do you
remember when the dad in the movie was
doing that next they just be doing stuff
and he'd be
like just yell at them okay that
literally sounded like the um the
Scooby-Doo cartoon Frankenstein guy when
he like falls down the slide you know
what I'm talking about when the DAP
catch this the Frankenstein next I think
we need to bring back there is a person
there I'm not going crazy Scar the [ __ ]
out of what would you draw if anything
you drew came to
life a key that unlocks every door okay
a US Government valued government money
printer o o yeah ooh a US grade money
printer yes isn't that crazy like what
is money paper if it's not
money how how do they print that what
quality paper is that I think it's um is
it like I think it's actually
cloth you're full of it no I'm not full
of it paper money is like cloth almost
you're full of it yes I'm being honest
it's like a face cloth almost would you
ever name one of your future kids after
your siblings or parent no no give us a
minute please we're 20 if what you're
one of Santa's elves for a day what
would you make um I would probably make
the classic diary that opens up to a
song and you have to like use your voice
code to open it hey diary it's me oh my
God
shut oh my God that's
terrible if you three never have to
worry about again what would they be
nothing I want to constantly be worried
cuz that's the only way that you make
progress yep you have to be
uncomfortable to be comfortable up top
give me five brother man what's the
first thing you would do if they
announced a Purge in the USA wrong those
who wronged me no no I'm just kidding I
wouldn't seek revenge I do something
super simple but like slightly illegal
run a red light like take a tip jar from
a restaurant that's just mean Nick come
on well no notz I don't want them to
have their tips but like the excitement
of like the tip bottle jar whatever is
right on the counter I just want to grab
it and leave yeah I'd probably something
bare minimum like that nothing too crazy
I'd probably boor up my house so no one
can come in that's see you're taking a
defensive approach everyone's always
like this and then I run outside and
punch the first person I see is hard as
I can what would you do if you could
only have oh my God that just made me
think like if there was a purge one
thing that I feel like a fun activity
that would be really comical is like
sitting on the roof with like a ton of
tangerines and as people like walk by
just throw like a like a Halo or like a
cutie like one of like something that
size where it's not going to hurt you
know what I mean it would hurt no
no it would if someone hummed a CU
[ __ ]
roof it would hurt it would hurt no you
are [ __ ] I think that' be so funny I
I would want to be able to
teleport here and I am now I'm gone I
would also wish to be a that's like so
clutch just to be able to like oh I want
to go to a
meeting there dab into the teleportation
is that how you guys I feel like I do it
like this twist I feel like you wouldn't
have to do anything I feel like you just
like think hard enough
I feel like you have to do it through a
doorway hello
[ __ ] here like you just come out
of nowhere okay that's how I think it
would be hello [ __ ] I'm here
yeah that's exactly what I think it
would be I think of it as more of like a
like you go to a door and you just pray
to end up on the other side that's how I
introduce myself all the time no you
don't my name is Christopher one of
three triplet you don't say that one of
three triplets not one of three trip ret
that makes no sense they get the gist I
mean yeah they get the idea but your
your grammar is
wrong you doing let's move on I don't
know the gist just seems like a dance
move I like oh they got the gist I
expect to see someone like hey like
getting it okay dude what would you do
if you woke up as a girl and buy a pair
of boots and a Minik skirt and FL my
[ __ ] around really i' walk like SE my
head up and with my little mini skirt on
what would you do if you woke up and
anyone else body doesn't have to be like
a girl like what if you what would you
do if you woke up in a body that wasn't
your own well if I woke up in yours it'd
be like wo why am I so annoying all of a
sudden like why do I feel like I need to
prance around like a little monkey dude
stop saying monkeys don't prance they
climb horses prants okay I'd be like why
do I have to why do I feel like I should
just jog around like a tiny pony do you
want to ask me a question or what jog
around like a tiny Pony weird I feel
like he has that you I'd probably
stretch first
okay you know I'm saying if I woke up as
anyone else but one of you guys I feel
like I'd be just
me say that again so that we can I'm
saying like if I woke up if I woke up as
one of you guys I feel like I wouldn't
know right away until I like look in the
mirror i' know immediately no just cuz
of how similar we are you're an idiot I
know if I woke up as you Matt I'd be
like whoa why do I have like Matt's
tattoos what the [ __ ] and then and you
wouldn't think I wouldn't think I'm in
your body okay like and then I'd look in
the mirror and be like wait it's really
me then I go like that like that and I'd
look and I'd be like oh my God Nick do
you have answer to this question that
makes sense I'm just a little confused I
don't think I'd feel this way at all I
kind of agree I think I'd be shocked
yeah I agree I
would I didn't even mean to hit you I
just like instinctively was like that
was me being like stop making this noise
like I tried to put my hand up or
something all right so what would you do
with if you were me a propeller hat I
like that nickname come on PA put it on
oh that was Noble very curious look as
no Noble it's like very h define Noble
you define it no I didn't use it nothing
defines me I Define myself I make my own
destiny what would you do if you realize
your whole YouTube Carew was a dream and
you woke up um better go back to bed oh
that's a good answer go back to sleep
mhm um I would probably well you could
say we're living the
dream good joke good joke good joke good
joke it depends if if I woke up and our
YouTube Carew was just a dream I'd wake
up as like past Nick a sophomore in high
school no
senior oh no cuz that's when it started
we would be like sophomores like Juniors
yeah oh my God yeah what would you do
well I would just take all that
knowledge and be like that's what I
could be I just need to work hard and I
would use it as motivation every single
day I wouldn't inside and out you every
single time I wake up from a dream I
immediately my first thought is like
that's never possible for me no what
what would you do if your Shadow came to
life like okay Peter Pan literally [ __ ]
skip around try and find it pin it to my
[Laughter]
feet I think the funniest thing about
Peter Pan is his Shadows missing and
he's trying to pin that [ __ ] CH
he's trying to pin it down what would
you do if a genie didn't give you three
wishes I'd probably shake it out of him
where are the wishes give me my wishes
if you kill the
groove yeah yeah what would you do if
you got the urge to break dance and you
just couldn't sit still break probably
break dance and it just wouldn't go away
I probably have to break dance what
would you do if you were granted the
power to heal others but only by using
your feet heal others with my feet and
they just have to get over it that it's
with my feet how would I do it like if
you want to get healed yeah that's right
like direct contact or is it a ray no I
feel like it's like a rub like you just
had to like rub your foot on them oh I
was taking full medic IAL procedures but
feet SCA like this you're insane that's
the craziest thought that's literally
what I was thinking the power to heal
people I don't consider that a power I
consider that I what don't deny the
don't say that I think doctors and
nurses stop itching your face it's
making me feel itchy all right let's
each before we finish this video like
each have maybe like five things we just
love about Matt um I love your your
determination to get things done when
you want to your blue eyes
absolutely your silky soft beautiful
skin your nice hair your nice flopy
fluffy hair when you walk around that
cute little sheer night
gown get
it all right let's fil an outro all
right all right guys that was this
week's Friday video stay tuned cuz we're
going to be posting again on Wednesday
and Friday on the stern little triplets
YouTube channel if you like this video
go like this video and then while you're
down there you're going to be so close
to the Subscribe button so go subscribe
and then make sure you check out our
merch website at
www.st.com because when we hit 6 mil
we're going to be doing a merch drop on
there so get ready for that all right
guys we'll see you next Wednesday Friday
peace out we love you all you mean to
your friends I mean tell them you love
them