can see it and it looks fine I can see
clearly now the rain is gone all I think
of is claran can we see my balls or no
can we see out my pants I
wish this video is going out the day
after my Matt and Chris's birthday so
happy 21st
birthday and we're filming it right now
and our birthday is in a half hour we're
filming in the mid our birthday is going
to you want to know what in the middle
it's kind of all hitting me at once
right now say it actually nck you always
look good new glasses guys I'll never
complain about not is what I was going
to say just it's so important it's so
important I just want to see if I look
good first cuz we I want to make sure
that they can see I want to make sure
they see me listening to you okay great
go ahead Matt
um I hate saying it was all hitting you
all at once filming car videos less
frequently now feels more like we were
doing it when we first started our first
oh
genus it's tickling your
te what how old were we when we filmed
the first car video were we 17 yeah 18
19 20
21 or are last car video is 20year olds
y we just saw some lady hitting the
Crooked Ducky on the way here crooked
ducky the Crooked doggey no she was
going H way yes sorry I just like I
complain all the time about how like I
can't have [ __ ] I know you are but what
am
I crooked ducky I prefer crooked ducky
over cred ducky ducky like it sounds
kind of like more like a move like a
crooked ducky I could see someone
hitting the Crooked ducky for sure like
no definitely okay I have all right
first car video we're filming back from
a while we filming in a long time and
I'm so excited to lean back more you can
see SOC Del deep delve deep Into the
Depths it's time explode I can't believe
babies don't know anything until they're
taught like I like a baby say the abc's
[ __ ] it's like the easiest thing
it's like all humans it's like AB why
did I do it in Spanish first ABC the I
what am I doing I'm like mixing between
Spanish and English right now as if I'm
like triling um du lingo I mean what's
two what's two dualingo no it's it's um
duing triing is two do bilingual
bilingual du lingo is that the app
that's the [ __ ] app um no ABC it's
like you can't even say the ABCs cuz no
one taught you yet you're a [ __ ] baby
babies learn everything from the adults
around them and that's crazy yeah it is
crazy am I crazy for thinking that the
other day I think I saw a baby and I
wrote that down in my phone I was like
this little baby his opinions are
exactly what his mother and that's why
know I've said I know I've said this in
a car video before I know I've said this
in a car video before because I want
about it babies a lot of babies first
words are baby or baby because people go
out and be like hi baby hi baby and so
many people will get them excited and
like calling them baby and stuff baby
they're like baby like I'm baby like
that's how they feel you know what I
mean Nick I saw this video and it was
like this lady doing like an assisted
gazelle birth or something or like this
like sorry what like this like
some sort of like I've seen the assisted
cow I've never seen some sort of like
land Nick just hit me with that some
sort he goes over two gloves and just
pulls gloves that go up to here no she
was like that's the cows she was like
ankling it the cows yeah but I thought
it would Orting all wait it's like on
the ground all sloppy purple and wet and
she like what are we talking about happy
21st birthday sloppy wet animal I want
to talk about the kitty in the airport
can we do that the what the kitty the
kitty yeah the kitty that was sitting
next to me oh my God the gamer Kitty no
not the kitty the gamer Kitty what were
we calling her the kitty that sat next
to Matt um the girl in all pink [ __ ]
what did I call her it was really good
it was creative and quick funny was it
danger Kitty or like princess kitty no
definely I didn't definitely didn't say
that wa um we were psycho psycho Kitt
psycho Kitty I was like I I texted you
guys I was like yeah I'm standing over
here trying to avoid psycho Kitty we
were sitting out at the airport Matt
Chris than me and Matt and Chris got up
and text the group chat and he goes I
got up cuz I'm trying to avoid psycho
Kitty cuz this girl was sitting next to
Matt and she had like all pink on head
to toe like like a like a hallucinogenic
pattern like I was looking at her and
I'm like I'm getting dizzy when
hieroglyphics bounce around your clothes
like I don't even know what's going on
I'm like if she did a 360 I would have
been [ __ ] in her psycho Kitty trance
immediately pause and then this is she's
sitting there with her headphones on and
she's on the phone she had Kitty
headphones on which is the most
important thing that's why she was the
psycho Kitty yes that's why I called her
psycho kid and I have my headphones on
in the airport cuz to be honest with you
I don't want to talk to anyone in the
airport so I have so I have my
headphones on I'm facing this way like
this like she's Chris and I'm facing
this way and I just hear like really
loud dog I'm so thirsty Taps Chris and
she's like oh I know this like
embarrassing I just put lotion on my
hands are like slippery can you open she
held up her hands like this like showed
him his lotion she was like yeah I just
like put lotion on and does like a
double like hands spread like if you
could give a caveman one thing from
Modern time to like absolutely blow his
socks off what would it be cuz I already
know mine would be I was think I can't
say my first
either vibrator doildo no we're in the
same ballpark same here what
would I think would blow a caveman's
socks off like literally not even blow
them off deteriorate them right there
what
wait what caveman doesn't wear socks
that's my point that's my whole point we
should bring him fuzzy socks regular
cavan there's no grooming back then and
they were like just so covered in hair
like a caveman probably had like really
hairy
feet I've never cut my feed hair in my
life I have no I don't I have I would
never do that I don't do that I don't
have like was what I was saying like I
would bring to a caveman if I wanted to
shock a caveman like IM can I [ __ ]
say it go say it you're edging me no not
every time I get there I'm being edged
me go I would bring a caveman a lighter
cuz they're always like o fire like
they're looking for fire and [ __ ] it's
like bro it's in this palm of my hand
this Bo you need a fire I got you
immediate spark what are you doing
nothing staring behind me like a sick
anal animalistic creature weirdo the
other day we went to The Quiet Place
movie The Quiet Place day one do you
remember the old lady that had the
audacity to stomp out of the movie do
you remember that oh my God it's the
movie's a quiet place I should have got
up and tackled her I just think about it
like in the movies if you did that if
you did that in the movie you'd be dead
by a creature an animalistic alien
creature now what if you're ass it's the
no hold on let's who wears high heels to
that movie no it was like boots she
clicking mov clacky clicke clacky down
the stairs of the movie theer It's we're
watching the movie I'm going to Sucker
Punch you a [ __ ] goddamn large bucket
of popcorn you [ __ ] sick animal you
sick big [ __ ] the whole point is to be
quiet and this lady sitting
inconveniently in the back row gets up
like and then goes like
this like this and walks in the bathroom
we had to be silent and she's literally
like
this like Stomps down get to bathroom
and then comes back and is even louder I
should have literally went like I should
have made the noise and just tack
imagine if she was stomping out of the
theater and everyone was looking at her
and I went
like like the I I I don't know how to
make it's like then it's like a and I
ran at her and tackled her over you
should have
nicked I should have just shot like a
bow and arrow at I don't know blow my
mind is how do you not have the fear how
do you not how do you not feel everyone
looking at you're in a quiet place and
you stomped out you she literally she
was not in a quiet place [ __ ] was in a
loud
obnox was in a [ __ ] crazy Loud Play I
just Queen loud obnoxious place I just
think the only excuse is if she forgot
her hearing aids at home and she
couldn't hear herself sh my little devil
let Matt speak I I just like I can't
even bring myself to like laugh at a
joke I think is funny out loud in the
movie theater I don't do anything out
loud nothing right nothing would cause
me I think there could have been a
[ __ ] level 17 earthquake fallout
shelter gets to the basement of the AMC
and I wouldn't have moved as quickly or
as loudly as that
Tonka that lady was of a woman guys a
least favorite breed of dog least
favorite least favorite breed of dog
Chihuahua like clears like oh my god
well I just think any dog that's like
small and annoy and Loud obnoxious step
on you like an ant right now you're
stupid I wish a dog dogs could speak
English that I could just go up to like
a chihuahua and be like I don't know
what are you worried about stop worrying
no like I was
baring talking I was going to say
something a Chihuahua I was going to say
something more poetic like a bark and a
bite type situation like your Bark's
bigger than your bite okay but I was
thinking no it wouldn't even really
settle in
anyway do you remember Pedro's dog
Charlie that bit you at the house party
I almost kicked that we' talked about
this before like ridiculous eating
cheese yeah we talked about it before he
his mom was like oh go ahead you can pet
Charlie and I pet Charlie and he turns
on and bites my finger like off my body
I know infamously I know infamously that
one of Matt's least favorite things is a
girl who's has a birthday week I can't
do it it's well like I just think I just
think like my birthdays actually was 2
minutes ago happy or right
right now right now happy midnight my
birthday is right now happy birthday 21
happy birthday Queen so it's like my
birthday is right now and like I'll
celebrate my birthday tomorrow when I
wake up I don't need like the whole
buildup you know I need the week I need
the whole week you need the whole week
my birthday week I need my big
shoes what I don't know no it's just
crazy when like I can't with the [ __ ]
that shows up the school with like the
Sash on oh like I remember it's like I
get it it's your special
whatever I can't like when they show up
and like they're like in on my birthday
oh c it's a you're my birthday party how
many times have you heard that one
before I think that us three ex always
exchanging a birthday birthday party
together just having it together it made
it like made them it's all like a
special my day it's like oh it's
cool we're lit today if it was your
birthday too come I think I would say I
think a lot of them are going to disag
because yes and that's okay you can
disagree with us peacefully peacefully
everybody their take on birthdays is
horrible
oh stop his face you look like Creeper
Creeper it's just so annoying that I
vocalize an opinion and people disagree
with me like shut up you're wrong you
disagree with me what no that's the
thing like I don't really care like
people will disagree with an opinion I
have and act as if you're mining through
[ __ ] gold to disagree with me I've
been stating opinions at 5:30 on a
[ __ ] Friday for 2 and a half years
congratulations you disagree with one of
the nonsensical things I've said you're
one of many you [ __ ]
idiot made the world
perish because I know
everything like holy [ __ ] you and a
bunch of other people go outside with a
sign with all your opinions on it and I
bet you a [ __ ] will walk by
disagree with you it's the world we live
in we're all going to die disagree with
me until I am buried underground you
[ __ ] the other day during our photo
shoot for the let's trip [ __ ] where we
did the polar Ray and stuff the other
day a month ago stop stop saying the
other day the other day a month the
other day a month ago the other day like
I can't even remember how long ago the
other when I say the other
day the other day is the last like 90
days for me literally when Chris says
the other day hear I no it doesn't shock
the other
day mat look it doesn't shock shut up
shut don't ball
me when Chris says the other day I'm
going to put a visual on the screen
right after I explain it because I need
them to also see okay this is what I see
in my head I hear literally it can he
can say the other day and actually
talking I know it's going to be on the
screen no he can say the other day and
actually be talking about like two days
ago
but no matter what second he says the
other day close your eyes I I see I see
a book like a vintagey book with like
brown papers shuffling quickly through
the pages and like a map with like red
lines popping out and then like it
brings us over like a traversal drone
shot of like C and woods and then into
like a little
village and then like an x on the ground
and you meet like the main characters
like that's what I see indefinitely side
by side when Chris says the other day I
see a passage into an otherworldly Vis
immediately Vis the other day can be 10
days ago and the second the second we're
double digits stop saying the other day
I agree got it but go ahead the other
day mon ago when we were doing our let's
trip shoot we went into a gas station
and I think it's unbelievably funny how
amused Nick was by the minimal art Det I
walked into the gas station I felt like
I was at Disney world like it literally
it had like a painted M&M and then like
madebe like a mountain ni was like this
is so cool yeah cuz when I usually go
into a gas station there's a crack
addict and a [ __ ] one cooler of half
empty soda I go and they had good snack
choice in some beautiful arts of course
I'm tell me your average gas station
experience you took a photo of it it was
on a story it was a big deal it was sick
I agree was beaming across it was like
comically funny how like blown away he
was by it it was a sick gas station it
was fun yeah I was in Florida I feel
like a kid the other day I was in my
room crossing my eyes how many days ago
this is actually like 3 days ago cool
crossing your eyes so you're just in
your room like this yes like I was I
have a chronic fear of ending up cross I
was doing this thing like this I was
doing the little kid thing like this and
listen I have this take little kid thing
yeah you know the little kid thing where
like f your finger and you're like this
and you like you get crosed I was doing
it the other night was doing it the
other night and I was thinking I think
it's crazy how when I was younger with
ease I could cross the uncross like I
could just be like this in my room like
when I was younger but the older I get
the more risk and reward I think there
is to crossing my eyes like I think I'm
going to do it one day and they're never
going to return because I'm old now
and it feels it feels a little like it
feels like it's like Rusty it's e good
to be friends with this kid had he had
like an aunt or a mom who was crossy and
like when crossy I'm the worst ever when
when they when you cross your eyes and
people are like oh don't do that or
they'll end up like that they stay like
that if that's not true I feel if it's
not true that your eyes can end up like
that if you cross them too much I feel
so bad for that lady cuz I remember so
many kids in school used to like cross
their eyes and then people be like oh
don't do it or like you'll end end up
cross out like permanently that's what
happened to so and so's mom and then she
would be like yeah like that's what
happened to me so if it's not true she's
putting on this major front of like
pretending that like she did it by
accident no but it does feel like it
could get stuck easier nowadays if I got
pulled over I'd fail a a sobriety test
sober probably cuz like most people
would they like say that ABC's backwards
jump from what's what is the ABCs from
from from from T to Z Right Now TV WXYZ
that was easy that was good okay in
order you no [ __ ] you just said it in
order no the crazy [ __ ] is when they're
like oh say the abz is from Z to a z y v
v w x yeah I'm done I'm TI idiot idiot
brain dead both of you in the trunk in
The Slammer bringing you to jail love
the straight line test give me the
straight line test any day I'd fail that
I think Nick you would fail you're the
first [ __ ] to fail the straight
line test I could do the straight line
test on W with a [ __ ] red afro and a
red clown nose no you couldn't ni
promise I promise you you couldn't do it
do it right now no you could not Nick
you I'm not getting out put me on a
tight RPP across the grand can you can't
walk into the kitchen without bumping
into at least two walls CU there's
nothing on the line [ __ ] put
something on the line put me above a bed
of nails or a bed of spikes I'll do it
with e what if I put a marshmallow at
the end and waved it around maybe you do
it good too a marshmallow or he's a
chocolate I was like Nick come get it ha
I hate [ __ ] that love a
marshmallow I like you're telling me you
can't think of a single other Suite than
a oh my God remember are you ridiculous
I remember when the teachers used to
give out marshmallows awards are we
bunny rabbits are we fat little
rabbits I get something right teacher be
like here's a [ __ ] marshmallow bu
like stop I'm the bunny's like Marsh I'm
checking myself for little pa and he's
like delusional you're who's the number
one consumer of a marshmallow Not bunny
rabbit the teacher would give me bunny
like they give me
um the teacher will gave me like a
marshmallow reward and I literally have
to look at my body and be like who am I
he thinks I want this
marshmallow Nick unless you're bringing
me a campfire wood gasoline sticks
Hershey's graham crackers and the
[ __ ] 20 minute break I'm good I'm
good on the marshmallow treat reward
unless we're taking time bring some hot
dogs too for sure let's set the whole
campfire scene dismiss me from school
remember when there was like fluffy
sugary
pasty I want this paste coating the roof
of my mouth do you remember the teacher
that he gave he it was like the social
experiment where it's like he put all
the marshmallows there and then if you
wait did an hour you get a second
marshmallow it's like I could wait the
hour cuz I don't want the Marshall I'll
wait the hour take the second
marshmallow and shove them up your ass
literally disgusting what get out of
here and the kids would take both and
they go look and marshmallow like do you
have parents that love you do they keep
treats at all at home or no that's
actually a good test of like if someone
has cool parents or not if like you go
to give them a marshmallow and they're
like feing for it it's like maybe don't
make him your friend when we were at the
airport my allergies were kind of bad
and I was like sniffly and Sneezy and I
was um I was going through I was going
through the metal detector and I had my
arms up like this and I thought to
myself imagine a boogie filled sneeze at
TSA before getting metal detected like
you just put all of your stuff down you
don't have a tissue you don't have
anything to like cover yourself you're
wearing like a shirt and shorts why
talking and you sneeze and you have like
boogies on your face but you're like
three in line from getting metal oh my
God what do you do like a boogie covered
face while you wait to get metal
detected I just request to go to like
the private room or something the guy oh
my god the guy fondled my nuts at
PSA it happened did you enjoy it Nick or
no no it wasn't like I didn't either it
was like just a shuffle like it was like
Shuffle I was like bro what he like
tapped the back of my balls by accident
I think like he was like feeling up my
leg and he's like all right you're good
and like as he pulled his arms between
my legs something even crazy like a back
ball slap like something even crazier
though I like wo
hello like jump started me like I I was
just shff I was shuffling through my
stuff like I was put my stuff in my
backpack at record speed like I just got
a little like but can I like I was going
through TSA I'm tired I hate going
through TSA it's my least favorite thing
boom ball slap jumper jump start like a
jumper back on the game no no just a
quick PSA that's what it is right yeah
PSA PSA public if you ever meet me at
the airport I'm sorry from you you met
me at my most miserable State cuz that's
my least favorite place on Earth the TSA
guy and like the having like the
security of like needing to like I went
through the TSA metal detector and there
was a big red square on my dick and
balls and they had to they had to check
of course to see if I have a gun but
like even with the level of
fondling I was like if I did have
something in my balls or buy my balls
that I shouldn't I don't think you would
have like I think you got a like I was
like by the way the amount I got touched
I was like if I was hiding a little
secret between my
like you know I was like I don't think
you would have got it sir totally get it
you know totally get it and that's just
the thought especially in the
trunk I was like I don't know if you did
enough for
the my favorite thing in recent time has
been people like adults figuring out
like brain rot stuff and like that my
God have you seen the video of the guy
and he like the mom is is chill but like
the dad's got to read the
script the mom is like this is so skibby
Duke Dennis R like then they're at like
vacation and then they have like their
dad and like it's so but I just love
that it's gotten to a point of like I
thought we were all in on the joke of
like oh brain like this how you talk to
kids like not thinking that even like
the kids were even joking no like the
kids are serious oh they're dead Ser
they're ski
like oh skib Phantom tax I'm like what
yeah like y'all are for real with this
to some degree yeah well you have to
think about it like this is like I want
to shoot myself in the head saying this
you have to think about it it's like
it's this generation's like like I can't
even be on camera when I say this like
like the like the white Vans thing like
the Daniel white van that's those
Generations like that you know what I
mean the other day me man and Chris went
out and we were filming a YouTube video
on the way home I fell asleep in the car
and Matt and Chris when I woke up told
me I was just the most peaceful sleeper
on no well we were talking about how
like when something with a lot of energy
and
and so it's very the key of physics is
an object in motion stage and motion and
an energy full of kinetic
speed well basically what we saying you
are the opposite of kinetic speed Noti
slow [ __ ] noticed a very peaceful
change in Nick when he's asleep and it
was just it was just very easy to be
around around him and it was very
interesting and I was like wow no Nick
fell asleep and me and Nick me and Matt
were actually like looking at him asleep
didn't notice yeah these people are like
going crazy actually the other day we
were um what were we talking about hold
on we got interrupted cuz we thought we
were getting followed Nick fell asleep
the other day in the car and me and Matt
were just laughing and talking about it
because Nick carries himself with such
emotion and such conversation and such
like high energy when he sleeps it's
actually the most peaceful thing you'll
ever see in your life because it I just
need to know that I'm a beautiful
graceful he never gets to like full
level zero I'm resting like peace unless
unless he's sound asleep what is buy two
get one free it's like oh buy the whole
store you can leave with the [ __ ]
side of the curb too I hate when they're
just throwing in all the [ __ ] deals
oh if you buy a [ __ ] you buy this
then this this this this this this and
this you can get that for free it's like
oh awesome now that I have a brand new
fridge thanks for the ice cube
tray like it's like you're so unhelpful
if you buy a brand new screw driver set
you'll get some free screws we'll throw
some screws in there oh whoopy [ __ ]
[ __ ] I'm buying the screw driver cuz I
have [ __ ] to screw already correct it's
always like oh we'll get you we'll give
you this for free if you get that I want
to see I buy ketchup give me mustard I
want to see that type of [ __ ] yes what I
want to see I buy hot dogs give me the
Buns like that's a
better I want to see not buy 36 hot dogs
get 12 more get seven packs of hot dogs
you can get some bacon too yeah oh yeah
give me a breakfast meat on top of this
I just think it's what one of the best
ones is buy three tires get one free cuz
it's that's cool that's legitness yeah
set change are you sweating like a big
monster planes going by in the sky is
the most put a beat on it
unbelievable thing we don't ever think
or talk about as humans imagine way back
when there when there was dinosaurs when
there was dinosaurs imagine like we are
in the modern time of which I could be
outside in a park in the middle of the
woods and an aircraft vessel carrying
human beings from one part of this Earth
to the other can float above me and it's
so normal for us to see planes flying by
think of that think of how crazy it is
that I could be in the woods [ __ ]
bird watching and cloud seeeing like
this and a plane could go by and I would
not think for a [ __ ] second what is
that also let me just say that such and
people are like oh AI is scary all this
new technology is crazy we already live
amongst the planes let me say this I
think it's a good thing to not crazy
that Nick is the most
stereotypical motion person of movement
or character or pose like and what the
[ __ ] and does that even [ __ ] mean are
confused this is what I mean dude I feel
like how how to cartoon sleep Matt how
to cartoon
sleep like this that's a Nick sleep pose
how do cartoons relax like this or like
this like Nick is a cartoon of a human
being like you could Google like 50
human poses to draw and it's probably my
default yeah every every time don't cry
about it was horse a big horse in your
throat there's a horse
hereo I just turned 21
today we should go to the liquor store
and get alcohol and drink until our
livers explode I want to wake up in a
[ __ ] Park tonight give it to me
somebody somebody go from this part of
the video right now what did you say
somebody go from this part of the video
right now in the start and screens
screenshot the difference of sweat
I feel like a big Angry beastly monster
what degree is it in here look at I'm
like sticking it's so hot we should
together like we didn't we were babies
cuz we're 211 I need to screenshot I
think if someone took if someone took if
someone took a full set of unsticky
sticky notes right now and just hit me
with them they're sticking to me like I
am I am covered in Mage guys thank you
so much we're going to enjoy birthday I
don't know like what we're going to post
where we're going to do anything I feel
like we need to do like a grand or more
fun thank you in another time I just
can't focus to do it right now yeah for
real like we've been like that means
we've been doing this [ __ ] for like four
years it disgusts me that this I think
if I was at like a water park right now
I had no hesitation go on every ride
imagine the big bucket right now oh that
feels nice I think was at a water park
right now they'd be like oh you had an
out cuz you look so expect the whole
[ __ ] day here already you're done
your fingers are pruning from from doing
nothing but thank you guys so much for
watching this video keep subscribing
we're on the road to 7 million we're on
the road to 10 but Seven's a mile yes
yes we're almost at 7
million happy Friday thank you guys so
much for watching this video love you so
much so thankful there's so many words I
could say there's so many things I could
do car videos feel and I think are way
better now that now that we post once a
weeky our more to build and and and and
just release after and I know a lot of
you we're just edging and edging and
edging waiting to film another car video
I know we told you guys we were going to
be Twitch streaming more with like the
lack of videos but we haven't been in La
we're celebrating our birthday and stuff
so like we will twitch stream more when
we're around a twitch setup I don't want
you guys think we're lying we don't have
a computer anymore this schedule is so
helpful for just like our ability to
make better videos and just be happier
with our Liv cuz we have more stories
like psycho Kitty so yeah it's been so
amazing yeah and we thanks to you guys
that's it thanks thank you so Nick dude
I have like a really really weird like
bizarre like subconscious like fear of
the taste of truffle fries like it PTSD
almost
what no I do but I like I smelled them
tonight and I was like like I was like
me why it freaked me out bad gay
truckers I'm kiding oh
did it break
[Music]