head to your drop off at Los Angeles
International Airport
LAX on our way to Chicago for summer
smash pulling an all nighter haven't
slept in like 30 hours or something but
we're locked
in you hear that what Chicago if you're
boarding go to gate 58 or am I tripping
balls well we're going to Chicago we'll
see you there Sam's about to perform you
guys know Sam he's been in some photo D
some Vlogs he's a good friend of mine
and he is opening today at Summers smash
which is like a very awesome thing and
I'm excited for him shout out to dollar
sign
am
what I appreciate y'all for having me
y'all make some [ __ ] noise for S baby
[Applause]
[Music]
yes sir yes sir yall Make some noise
[Applause]
[Music]
how are
you bro get the [ __ ] up open your
eyes you baby onong kid do you start
walking and I wasn't trusted all right
guys I'm about to zoom in a Matt's
nipple bro get the [ __ ] out of here like
dead serious bro kid put a shirt on I
told you to stop wait a second all right
wait for big baby to get dressed big
baby you want to see big baby's nipples
is crazy I just got these two vintage
hats o three I'm the triplet you know
this one why not Patriots team there we
go and then I got a little I got a
flannel and I got a Chicago Supreme crew
neck because I just thought it was cool
and I want a memory for being in Chicago
yeah and then I got these camo pants
which they're going to hate cuz they
hate seeing you in them still yeah bro I
literally it's just like I'm wearing
pants like they needed to
chill
Chicago
Chicago hey Chicago just posted in his
close friends on Instagram and we can't
stop laughing so look at this video who
the [ __ ] gives a [ __ ] goddamn to-go
drink in a [ __ ]
bag kid was so mad look at his tacos
like covered in soda ew that [ __ ] is so
disgusting Celtics time we're locked in
who I'm with it's Nick on the phone Matt
hitting the dance o o get it I haven't
done [ __ ] Nick get the [ __ ] up and go
outside and do something me yeah I did a
bunch of [ __ ] but I like couldn't I
didn't like Vlog anything like I went oh
did you see me go out on stage and all
that
stuff yeah was it fun it was so cool we
miss you brother how about them Celtics
the Celtics won tonight Nick are you
hype I don't care at all we're so hyped
right now it was fabulous that's so good
you love the word fabulous you little
gay icon what stop saying that how often
fabulous it's just a good word you're a
queen oh my God how is Barry
doing who Barry I hate that idiot what
he's annoying it's like not even mine
he's like perking on my bed like get out
I love Barry I put Barry in Nick's room
I'm doing nothing I told you aund
times you're so
funny n you make me
laugh
okay and put your turn around and pull
your pants down real slow
no I was going to say something but I
keep forgetting tomorrow wait are you
frozen you're just not
moving Nick how do you feel about this
beautiful artwork on this wall you mean
that
not look at it oh my God it's actually
like black crayon bro all right here we
are lyrical lemonade headquarters Matt's
about to put up a three oh three yeah
hold
up it's crazy bro if you look at all the
old videos and my bedroom back home they
shows how how dialed in I was to just
the um the lyrical lemonade lore the
history everything it stands for it's a
very fun
moment crazy like we're triplets and
[ __ ] but I'm way better at basketball
than you are your jump shot is broken
it's actually kind of
insane kid thinks he Dude Perfect bro
[Music]
this the most ridiculous thing
yeah let's go
here okay crazy trick shot first try you
got
it hey
hey brother what's up is Sam with you
yeah oh I heard more footsteps I was
like who else is coming Hi
Sam I feel like I don't know who you are
like get away from me I've been alone
for like 5 days in a
row oh my God new merch samples I know
photo shoot and take some pictures yummy
apple no it's just like woof can I have
turn you into a dog literally can I have
a little pce yeah
it's good I'm just getting a lot of the
minty toothpaste I just used that's for
me what Mom at least it's not orange
juice I hate vlogging this
stairway go You Deja Vu that electric
katchup what did you just say did you
get deja vu of that electric katchup had
I thought it was like a different
language you was speaking I was so
confused well you are pretty [ __ ]
stupid low key was speaking French
what all he said was Deja Vu that's a
French
word if I said Deja Vu Kung Fu I didn't
say a single word in English I just
spoke Chinese and French to
you like if I had Deja Vu about Kung Fu
not one word did I just say he was
English I'm bilingual you're
[Music]
oh yeah okay a come on girl yes yes what
are you doing give us a pose
yeah no no like something like that like
an edit like if you were to move like
for that like just move like like Chad
he's gonna punch the camera can you not
like you look nervous to be here you're
like you're walking you're the brand new
bombshell in the Villa give us the
walk pose cute yeah okay good
Chris go go go go go okay ready yeah
you're going to walk at me three two
boom yes yes yeah okay again again again
again again but now I'm going to stay
here 3 2 1 oh I don't have a zipper I
was going to go like this and go Chris
no come here go again only like like
keep it straight but only my feet okay
good nice I hit the wall okay now you're
going to come you're going to come here
and as I walk toward the camera you're
come in there now we're as I walk toward
the camera you're going to back up
you're going to come okay as I walk to
the camera you're going to back up okay
three
two oh Jesus again now go to the front
and then drop come back up it would be
really
cool is that good yeah do it again do it
again I know what you're doing you're
planning you schemer no I'm not no it's
like man when he drops get his back I
get it still go Nick do it
again that
was we got to do the pr for the for the
for the show what we got to be like I'm
looking for a girl in The Villa your
turn I'm not doing that yeah come on we
got back that all opt out that's what
they need like that's why I feel bad
they need to stop they need to stop with
the pr on love Island every single year
a year ago there's a podcast clip of me
making fun of the pr they make those
poor Islanders say the goofiest [ __ ]
ever what did he say last they walk in
they're like o it's like just like cave
it's like I'm a microbiologist I'm a
microbiologist outside the Villa but
inside the Villa I'm not looking for
anything micro give us your Best slogan
no I don't have a slogan outside of the
Villa I'm a YouTuber with many
subscribers inside the Villa I'm looking
for a guy to subscribe to me oh that was
good that was good right it's like goofy
[ __ ] it's like chill chill with this
cornball [ __ ] let them fall in love I
couldn't imagine my love life being
documented and like actively happening
I'm would not say this is my best friend
and this is not a drill so true yeah
right you
ate gay love Island season one call me
I'll do all the stupid PR [ __ ] no you
can't I'll do all of it I'll do all gay
island is like whoa gay island it's like
I I wish I could be there gay island why
put them all in one it seems anti-
Progressive you know but all on an
island let us roam free in the world
that's what I was thinking gay pride
happy June June's over
no I know it's devastating can you not
pull me on you guys are pulling me like
ET you got two fingers you're going to
rip me
open okay what's next a ball dropping
mat has entered the Villa ball dropping
yeah um a brand new bombshell has
entered the Villa from Chicago give us
what you're looking for I'm looking for
a girl in The Villa
I'm not what are you looking for we're
some Bros looking for some hoes no this
is terrible this is terrible you're
looking for a girl in The
Villa no exercise just extra fries E
look at for a girl in The Villa to buy
some let's trip merch hey what were you
saying uh we have a merch drop tomorrow
4th of July celebrate the fireworks not
only in your wallet I mean not only not
not only in the sky fireworks they going
to go off in your wallet is that Nick's
it's ours it's mine what's yours is mine
what's mine it belongs to
me you belong to
me all right if you guys didn't realized
that Vlog was kind of ass the beginning
of it cuz Matt and Chris were away and
they're terrible at vlogging and I'm the
career the care
benefactress basically I carry us
throughout our vlogging career enough
enough touching me I'll do it myself
thank
you we spent five days the part for the
first time ever so we're going to best
five days ever get
away so basically [ __ ] dummy [ __ ]
what was that so basically now that
we're back we're going to interrogate
each other and figure out what we did
while we were apart for 5 days did you
have a blast mhm who is your favorite
performer I always like to see Skies but
Sam was an underrated pick this time he
he had the under don't sound too excited
now you're going to rile up the fans
what was your favorite part of
Chicago um pot belly it's our bastard
holy [ __ ] pot belly just tell you guys
live
to like three times oh I'm so jealous
hot belly
sandwiches good job you're good at this
thanks me and CH AR is good
interrogation Duty get up get
that that that top 10 L of M clip new
clip who's song was that under your bed
[Laughter]
what
what enough of this time's up boys how
many uers did you buy too many too many
hundreds of dollars in Uber actually all
good songs my friend all good songs my
friend I need to learn how to drive all
right that's it put him in The Slammer
put the [ __ ] Red Bull down and answer
me do you have any intention of making
music no are you going to nope did you
have a blasted Summers smash absolutely
did you enjoy going on stage with sky or
Sam Moore both of them equally good
question answer thank you well Sam was
like I had more of an activity like shut
up no explaining okay did you have a
blast with Cole Bennett your idol icon
legend that was great I saw him and you
went to the lyrical eleminated
headquarters how was that it was very
cool very fun did you beat Matt in
basketball or did he beat you I did beat
him 5 to four what was it like little
Christopher stolo being in the lyrical
em headquarters did you feel it in your
bones and your jibblies I did I
definitely felt it in my bones I cannot
account for my jibles but I did feel it
what did your jibles feel when you were
in Chicago it was just fun it was
exciting um I think my favorite no we
don't care and enough okay no you can go
I think my favorite part was going down
like the hallway with all the
memorabilia from all the videos it was
really cool well I'm glad you had a
blast you're good to go get the [ __ ]
[ __ ] out of my [ __ ] camera shot all
right a couple more things before we get
going and this video is over just like
Matt said we have a Fourth of July merch
drop first link in the description and
the link across the screen tomorrow at
noon Pacific Standard Time merch will be
available there's limited qualities
let's just show them the merch I'll put
it on the screen it's over there limited
quantity so it may sell out quick so act
fast you are loved and amazing thank you
so much for the support and you do not
need to buy merch and order to be a fan
of us you just need to hit subscribe and
like today's video and you are just as
important as the those that are shopping
for Merch let's trip red and gray star
hoodie so cute so fun and if you're not
a hoodie person it comes available in a
black T-shirt super summary design let's
trip big back print blue hoodie
established in 2003 the year me Matt and
Chris are born super cute super fun
Super Summer we have this let's trip
pink graffiti design this is probably
one of my favorite designs from the
entire drop and lucky for you if you're
not a pink hoodie person this is
available on multiple garments such as I
don't have anymore I told you we didn't
[ __ ] have at all I so I guess I'm
showing you a quarter go check the
website for the rest but the merch is
available right now all right guys on a
more serious note I know we've had this
discussion so many times Wednesday
videos are this going to be a Wednesday
video no Wednesday video this Wednesday
video no no Wednesday video oh and we've
said it like a million times but I think
we've decided that today's Wednesday
video is going to be one of our last
Wednesday videos for a while simply
because we want a lot a lot of time
focusing on more things and put out
quality content over
quantities of content and I feel like
right now we're just spitting YouTube
videos at you guys but we want to focus
more on filming better videos and just
having more fun and being more positive
people I love it yeah and also I mean
you guys have been seeing we've been
going live on Twitch every once and a
while so if you want to we're probably
going to start frequently Twitch
streaming more with the lack of actual
YouTube content going out so go make
sure you're followed to our twitch
stream so that you can tune in whenever
you want um we also have a plan to start
posting our twitch streams onto Stern's
live that YouTube channel um so that if
you don't miss if you miss the stream
and you're not actually like one of the
live viewers while it's happening you
can just re-watch it at a later time so
basically all we're saying is the lack
of Wednesday videos on this YouTube
channel does not mean you're going to
get any less content from us it's just
going to be replaced in different ways
like twitch streams twitch streams
turned into YouTube videos more
Instagram posts more Tik toks and us
just being more active across all other
platform forms is literally all it is
yeah I agree and we're not remotely
close to quitting so yeah a lot of
people think you're quitting thank you
and that's the T sis God I want to play
the [ __ ] quadell om my let's do it
[Music]
thanks for watching merch Dr tomorrow
peace and love see you next week
subscribe like do all your things
[Music]