hey y'all what's up it's I love
y'all even though y got no snacks in
this house oh [ __ ] they're coming I said
hey guys we're spending the night in the
North Pole we're going to do North Pole
activities that you would do in the
North Pole and survive the cold and
we're with our friends
friends you got lar and Nia dor
yeah wait why do these feel so weird I
feel like I'm squeezing it and it's like
it feels like it's like is that like a
dryer ball no it's a
snowball oh you can popcorn read the gra
oh love I need to PR public speaking
boring I was always a kid that didn't
get popcorn too bro cuz they knew I was
St ow [ __ ] that's the second time got
hit in the eyeball okay [ __ ] you
[ __ ] okay ready yeah ready every
who in hooville liked Christmas a lot
but the Grinch Who Lived just nor north
of hubo did
not French hated Christmas the whole
Christmas season now please don't ask
why no one quite knows the
reason okay
ready I'm thick cuz I beat eat it's hot
as [ __ ] the GR in Christmas the whole
Christmas season now please don't know
why no one oh we already did this me
that was my
private it could be his head wasn't
screwed on just right it could be
perhaps that his shoes were too tight
tomorrow is Christmas it's practically
here oh so it's Christmas Eve and he
growled with his grin fing nervously for
tomorrow he knew all the who girls and
who boys would take would wake bright
and early they'd rush for their toys and
then oh the noise oh the noise noise
noise that's one thing he hated the
noise noise noise noise I don't like
that part why does it say so many
times that [ __ ] B away
boring guys when I was at Target and I
was buying that book my cashier was like
she was like she told you not to tell
anyone and now you're she with the lady
she goes I have to tell you something
you can't tell anybody and I was her to
tell me like a secret she was like when
I was a kid I remember the Grinch coming
into theaters like the first original
Grinch I like her and her friends were
super
excited said all right oldie scan my
book I didn't say that I did not say I
did not say that words come on you old
[ __ ] I think she probably thought that
I was younger than I was and thought
that I like never heard of the Grinch
I'm like I'm I'm very familiar dude
that's so insane wait I don't get
it old enough to see play like wait what
mie the original Grinch movie She alive
since then wait she see be like dead
correct said all right scan the book
wait when did this come out when did
this movie come out here absolutely yeah
yeah do men just like fight when they're
mad no no oh we got these you guys can
try too oh hot chocolate
Oreos hot chocolate we actually knew
that and that's why we got them you guys
are so sweet oh my
God wait okay Nick listen you keep
feeding me this [ __ ] I'm going to blow
this [ __ ] up let's do
it that's kind of crazy let's do it
czy I hate sitting crisscross applesauce
I feel
ridiculous leg put my leg under your
legs you're good oh so uncomfortable
someone did me dirty recently and I've
never felt I was F with rage you know
you know Tik to you feel in your toes
what they do what they do what they do
oh did you go like this B this out bleep
this out but you can even just leave
what I
say
and you know what when I saw that I
was and I woke up with just rage and
I've never felt so
alive I believe czy I believe in karma
though Karma work is too slow I quick
yeah what should we do that
we
no I say when she comes back we all boo
her just boo her
and boo her oh we're King let her sit
down
[Applause]
yeah y talking sh get her what the [ __ ]
no wait that was to get my ass no oh go
Jester entertain us wait you're actually
him like you're more him than I thought
oh [ __ ] you made lose it you distracted
me you got
so wait should we do like like you can't
leave the tent or you have to do
something like the first to get out of
the tent okay Mr be
yes give 10
$10,000 wait are you guys still hungry
should we make Moores please mean you
have like a fire no over
there that's what you guys brought up
actually that's crazy actually works
watch it catch
fire what a sad looking that's such a
sad looking location
area what is Godzilla where am I get
down yes it's up to me and you for the
$10,000
next time you come in here you're going
to bring me my money wait what's so I
need to put it on something so it
doesn't burn the tent down put it on
$10,000 oh bring it to me okay I'm
putting it on that oh my God I hope our
house doesn't don't put it on this put
it on this I am flame there's no flame
it's just hot this thing's actually
going to get hot SM I hope that that tin
doesn't like catch on fire on heat off
[ __ ] why what's the word here oh
oh oh oh wait you don't have to touch it
you no no you're good you're good you're
good that's
yes once I start smoking we're in
business guys my biggest pet peeve I
think is smoke detector noises oh know
me too like shut up it's so you got to
change the battery oh my God it's like
the worst thing ever
guys oh we're in
business let me see you take a bite of
that oh wa take a bite the
camera oh that's a
good got take another bite for the cam
for the camera do it for the vibe I'm
going to do it take a
bite I cured
myself well that was delicious what Fu
up he's ready to move on okay hello can
this thing activate dance boy wait
work
wow I made a we got you we'll wait for
you guys okay it's okay the gloves from
I made I dro the gloves W it smells like
come on guys Nick get your get your but
I
my done holy a Perfection you're done
you're absolutely done and none of yall
looks like
mine how crazy is that dude
my let's move on I don't want to
participate I really don't go wipe [ __ ]
this thing unplug this from the
wall that's why I got
on wait
the sleeping bag oh my [ __ ] God you
burn the sleep I almost started out fire
like what are you I'm just pissed it
never look at what this kid did I have
Tock
that look at that wait if our smoke
detector goes off and
like this is like mentally unstable Nick
this is why our house caught on fire the
first time oh my God I really almost
just caught the house on fire yeah I
don't know why did that thank God I had
the oven mitts so you were the one that
was like getting angry you would punch
toes in the wall you don't you don't
have to e you
sure string out I didn't have much rage
as a kid my rage is
new tons of I made it I put the work
okay take a my rage is like very always
be the one to strike first no no I
awkward Chris used to hit us
everyone's like looking at each other
talking I was the one who stri first no
said no Chris used to have the most said
so quiet strike first like in the gut or
in the face
no he's a pincher he's like a little he
pinches pinching is I hate
pinching here's the thing right ever
would pinch me I'm stabbing you here no
it's ridiculous the pinching is I think
that a pinch actually shows that the
person likes you more than if they hit
you I disagree I'd rather be
hit
[Music]
just it was
this it's my dad's fault sorry oh my
God y'all I love her I literally love
women so much you guys know that can't
believe there're just I can't believe I
did that I'm a little shocked I'm so
happy I had the oven Miss ready yeah I'm
lasagna I know all say random [ __ ] so I
want it to fit in [ __ ] y I don't get it
what should we do next Nick let's make
toys for the kids oh F yeah ready 10
minutes timer we're doing in 10 are we
making it for the
person what your fav color all in favor
10 minute challenge wait 10 minute
challenge whoever I won't I won't is it
just whoever's the best or whoever is
the best and then the whole top off
who's going to wait you can't start yet
you can't start yet you can't start yet
you can't start that's crazy who's going
to vote who's going to vote who's going
to vote what's going to happen here you
guys vote okay ready okay and we're just
we're not making it for someone else
we're making it just like for ourselves
for ourselves what your vote you know
how to do or you can do whatever you can
do one okay okay ready all right wait 10
minutes is that enough your favorite
color yeah you're just going to move
fast okay wait can I have a brush favor
color is red 1 2 Go 10 minutes opening
this [ __ ] thing up
what the hell I can't I haven't done
thing either guys I actually suck at
painting like I have no artistic ability
that's being sucking at things is a
mindset what is your favorite gift
you've ever
gotten probably my JBL speaker I got
from my brother cuz I still use it to
this day that's a good gift you always
use
it I always use it guys know that audio
where it's
like there like something creepy going
on what are you
eating do you know what you're talking
no it's like this creepy ass audio and
like it's basically people like showing
like parallels in their world whatever
like just weird scenarios and wow and
just like like hypothetical things
whatever [ __ ] happening basically this
girl took a photo of herself and she was
like little I saw this and she was like
oh like me and my like imaginary friends
I used to have it was like like like
some [ __ ] crazy names like very like
like particular yeah like very
particular names and then it turns out
she took An ancestry thing when she she
turned like older and it was the name of
her [ __ ] great
grandparents I know what you're talking
about I know what you're talking about
like the one that's like um um I've been
here or something something like I know
you yes it was so scary like the girl
was like just like oh yeah me having two
imaginary friends when I was younger
than them being my grandparents 20 years
later [ __ ] oh this is horrifying
see never show me that again
wait cuz y'all got me working oh my God
the kids need kicks guys we better hurry
up I can't this is like so stupid what
like just hearing all the brushes
like brushes
down brushes down put it down yeah in no
world oh
brushes wait you're the you did the best
I
think wait brush us down if he can keep
going then I brush us down
no Max penguin's
scary okay she's scary people with blue
[Laughter]
eyes okay wait let me see your ice
skates the ice skates are uh well
they're there they're
there they're definitely they're cute
they're cute yeah I like them I actually
do like it you just painted
red well what
else big red
truck wait lar that's crazy wait the
boat this is my
boat little boat we should put an ant on
it and actually set it to sail [ __ ] yeah
all right I think we're done with the
crafts with
everything with everything correct okay
ready oh my God the we're doing the
death nut challenge do we 100% have them
like actually we do I'm not eating a
death nut just one little peanut no what
do a peanut got on you it's called the
death nut it's just a little peanut the
Peanut's going to take me out you had
them like out of the package like
straight not only is it spicy but it
probably expired it's not expired a
death stale death nut are you down wait
are we actually doing this I'm not
eating a I'm down for a l I'll you said
you were
down to because I'm down for like just
one we could do level one no cuz there's
levels there's levels you're already C
okay so that's crazy Carolina Reaper
no and count me out that's all I need
throw the whole package you can't even
sell those at the
store wait don't eat it did he eat it he
licked it and that's enough and
that's
so
much don't eat if you eat this I'm not
eating it I can feel it though you want
to see you want to feel it why is it
just feeling the nut okay I'm not
calling it The Nut goodbye everyone
thank you guys for watching how was our
Christmas Adventure your channels are
going to be in our bio and all their
good stuff so yes all your good stuff
okay