wow W I have like the [ __ ] shout out
Stuart he ate Stuart devour these are so
yummy hey guys sorry for the brief
intermission from our current car video
but we are coming in with a major
announcement we are now YouTube's vinyl
figures look at that what a dream you
can get Nicholas Matthew and Christopher
literally right now from the YouTube's
website at you.com or the link currently
on the screen a couple things to know
about our YouTube the figures are
limited edition and never being sold
again once they sell out yes the sale of
our you is also available for only the
next 14 days from the moment this car
video comes out so you have
approximately 2 weeks right now to shop
our you's on the you's website and then
you're never going to be able to shop
them again so if you want me Matt and
Chris in little figure form now is the
time to shop get them while you can the
link is on the screen right now and it
is the first link in our description
down below but go check out our YouTu
these are so super cute it's a dream
come true I've always wanted something
like this of myself I know I've always
wanted a little figurine it truly is
amazing they're so adorable I'm going to
get mine of Nick and Chris's too and
leave them in my nightstand yay and
enjoy today's car video thank you we
love you wear a hat You're So Vain you
probably think this song is about you
you're so we'll deal with
it is anyone else getting a cold tangle
down their spine I just feel such cold
breezes flying my way I told Nick that
might be the ogus rubbing up against him
okay you didn't say that do you feel the
ogus rubbing on you map stop talking
where would the oenus rub up on that's
what I want to know can you guys stop
saying this I hate I hate that joke the
oenus yeah I hate that joke we're going
to move forward for sure welcome back to
another Friday video all of the sternol
triplet fans today we're here in this
vehicle and we're going to be talking
about some
things some topics some topicy topics
but just two orange drinks but of a
different
kind to that one healthy one
unhealthy yes so many things alike yet
not alike one glass one plastic oh my
gosh and look at how far that shows the
development of
everything that's just
amazing I think if you listen closely to
that clip you can hear me almost throw
up
if anybody drinks orange juice with pulp
it's like you're begging for a bad start
to your day correct pleas can I get an
orang can I get an orange juice can I
get some can I can I get some pulp in
there I feel like I'm swallowing a
little bit of Flem when I drank my
breakfast literally why would you ever
get pulp correct where was I recently
where they gave me pulped orange juice
the zoo nope yes I didn't have it at the
zoo IDI there's just nothing worse than
what it says there no pulp but there's a
little there's a lot of things worse
than that what I don't know okay a flat
tire do you guys know how sometimes we
like walk past each other and like
karate chop each other or like we like
joking I do that all the time well today
dad was walking into the kitchen and I
thought for sure it was
Chris and he was like refilling his cup
of ginger Rail and he was like walking
with his cup and he like jingled his ice
like this like you went like wasn't
really paying attention so it's like I I
am a slow human being like I am not very
agile and mobile or flexible but I have
the mindset of a [ __ ] Cobra like my
my my I get stimulated and then it's
like my reaction is just like I want to
like just break something in half like
I'll hear like a noise behind me and
I'll think I'm like a [ __ ] elephant
and I can turn around and just [ __ ]
Pummel it over elephant can't turn fast
but yes shut the [ __ ] up but I'm walking
and I hear like the little glass jingle
and Cobra Nicks turns on and it's like
oh I need to [ __ ] attack so I hear
the jingle of the ice and I I swear to
God I just started laughing instantly
cuz my body didn't physically do
anything but mentally I just wanted to
kick the glass into the ceiling have ice
[ __ ] fly everywhere like my brain
just attacks my physical body and it's
like attack attack attack like you knew
you were dialed in like if it was you
and not Dad I think it being dad was the
only thing that set my brain back to
like relax but if it was you and not dad
that ice would have hit the [ __ ]
ceiling let's move on all right we're
going to move on today I asked you guys
to just name three random things and
then I don't know picking our favorite
ranking them one two three destroying
one of their feelings until they did you
say ranking them one two three or
ranking them one to three it's up to
your imagination could work wow I'm
feeling like I'm having an allergic
reaction already orange juice GES
pineapples and
sunflowers let's all do the vocal
exercise I'm not doing this I'm not
doing
this I'm not doing
that you can't do anything fun Matt I
can I do okay do the craziest thing you
could think of like just like a physical
Outburst like your dog you got the
Zoomies what's going to be your first
move oh he's driving Matt Matt oops
like what are you
doing like you just like
[ __ ] that was that was the craziest
thing I could think I loved it now you
have to go recheck the camera I wouldn't
be surprised if the camera's [ __ ]
broken after that that was insane all
right moving forward into the topic cuz
Matt didn't hear it I'm going to say it
one more time what would you like shut
the [ __ ]
up it's not going to I have something
good I have something good whatook
cookies I have something you're
interrupting me to say you have
something good if there's not a baked
treat under your ass I don't want to
hear it if I'm not getting a rice krispy
a [ __ ] two for one on [ __ ] cake
pops shut the [ __ ] up it's not worth
cutting off my sentence it's good it's
good then you're baking me a treat when
we get home my hair looks fun thank you
bayy Smurf in the car with us today bayy
Smurf Google bayy isn't it bie bayy I
don't think it's viny
whatever vayy Smurf is crazy wa
next thing you know they're going to
bring out girthy
Smurf shut the [ __ ] up that's terrible
it's a kid show it's a kid show it's a
kids show what would be like the
craziest Smurf dude everyone think of
one what is actually the craziest Smurf
what are they named off of adjectives
what's the yeah clumsy Smurf like he's
[ __ ] idiot no what would be like the
craziest Smurf actual craziest Smurf
road rage Smurf he's like [ __ ] you and
he's like always in his little onion get
out onion yeah his little mushroom
mushroom no not even the same family
girl we're not even in the same produce
section oh it is mushroom correct his
little mushroom car like I think like
just like Papa Smurf like Papa Smurf's
making his new spell in the woods he's
like [ __ ] you papa what about a drag
queen Smurf tall Smurf tall Smurf just a
big guy and he's like bigger like
slightly larger this is the dude that
was doing donuts that one time oh no
oh
wait no Nick leave the light on that car
just started yeah leave the oh it's this
dude walking over Mama made Pizzeria
that tell where's he at no there they
they did that thing where you start your
car with the app and you walk over maybe
he was in his boyfriend's car what who
whoa whoa oh no yeah he's hammered
they're drunk he better not get in this
vehicle all righty wait so can I say
what I was going to say earlier Nick but
basically guys there's a little bit of a
Time jump right now because
some Hooligans well apparently we got a
local group of gay truckers that like to
make out parking lots late at night so
that's what's going on where we live in
Boston I guess just gay truckers at the
middle of the night leave a bar go on a
truck make out all right I'd love to
know where they're coming from
why that they stay there and have fun
okay all right um what was I going to
say not cuz you want to join the group
or anything right no okay we were
talking about Comfort zones and I wanted
know like what is the most comfortable
comfort you could have and then what's
the most uncomfortable you'd be most
comfortable I could be is in a bed with
10 girls and a pillow and a big blanket
we go cut for one pillow with 11 heads
and one yeah we're all going to cuddle
for warmth Nick that was crazy probably
on like a giant bean bag chair I love s
you guys are going physical Comfort oh
you're talking about I yeah I was
talking the comfort zone like what's the
dead center of your comfort zone I don't
know you need to answer the question
first we need example upside down roller
coaster is outside of my comfort zone
slightly all right so if this is your
comfort zone what's right in the middle
my comfort zone is being with a group of
friends that conveniently walk at a nice
Pace I hate slow Walkers and sometimes
we got a group in the a person in the
group that's just running beining
yeah give some hair to the other side of
that here I'd love to have been at the
movie theater that Abraham Lincoln was
at just because like I would have been
like hey get out of here like
something's behind you no one saw the
guy creeping up behind him I think
what's going on in your peripheral if
someone snuck up behind me I feel like
I'd know that they were Cobra Nick would
know yeah I'd be like my lip would CER
and I'd say yeah I turn around with a
[ __ ] Sucker Punch faster than youe
Bolt running in a [ __ ] Marathon
faster than a cheetah my fists would
[ __ ] Pummel through their mouth
faster than a cobra dude be like a Gummy
Bear my face would punch and their their
face would be in their face would be in
my fist but my fist would be through
their head like in the Power Rangers
like my fist would be here and the
[ __ ] back of their head would be
here talking so you just stuck up behind
me all I need to do is
this deep deep inhale deep inhale and I
sense all of my surroundings and I turn
and
I I was just
if I snuck up my neck and I just I'm go
like load up like how funny that would
be for me I do anything to have just a
crazy martial arts trick under my belt I
want to spin and [ __ ] oh my god oh I
need to know I'm going to sign up for a
ninja throwing class a ninja star
throwing class what Nick I need to walk
into a bar and then there would be a
person all the way on the other side
that I'm like trying to get their
attention and instead of saying hey
what's up I'm just going to go boom with
a ninja star and it's going to go right
by their nose negative like feelings
towards this person or you trying to
like RIS him up with the star neither or
okay I'd
say like hello and i'' be like whoa who
threw that ninja star and I'd be over
there my Fedora and my trench C turn and
I'd say you're looking for me I think
dog lotion and
shoes dog one dog is one I'd hate to see
a dog covered in lotion wearing shoes
imagine that that was the first thing I
thought of was like a big long dog
covered in Lo
with on that' be awful what are you
doing silly goose that's what I'd say
come on man get those shoes who had that
story was it was one of you where the
girl in Target dropped a a Juggle lotion
oh my God was that oh my my God some
some girl walked up to one of them and
there was like a very small like kind of
like those little like um what are he
doing okay there was like a little very
small little like container and it was
like a try me on it yeah and it was like
a very small version so it was the try
me hundred of the other ones obviously
in the shelves ready for purchase if you
like the larg SI so we've got a little
girl Scavenging through the try me
lotions correct instead of grabbing the
one that said try me on the top she
grabbed the one right under it she
thought it was like
above the she thought the TR me sign was
above instead of below oh dude these
morons oh my God these guys are
fighting the gay truckers man they're
they get wild at no he's actually
throwing Hammer fist at his boy they're
no way they're mad he so she grabbed she
grabbed one of the big ass ones like
huge instead of the actual triam one and
keep in mind it's like a little [ __ ]
girl like she's probably like 3 years
old so she can't even like hold it up
right can't hold that juggle lotion on
your own somehow she gets the lid off
puts the lid back on the shelf and she's
holding it and she goes to like take a
big scoop of it and it's like it's not
like a Clear lotion like it is fully
white like it looks like sunscreen
almost right she Dr drops it on the
floor awful and this girl is probably
like 2T tall cuz she's like 3 years
old lit it hits the floor and the the
puddle that came up of lotion was taller
than her tsunami of lotion what lotion
literally she got to feel like a Smurf
in those circumstances literally hit her
like in her hair hit her face all over
her I'm sorry she'll never be dry I'm
not she'll never be dry never dry try
again I think two of them just kissed
actually what yeah two of the truckers
kissed I need to get over there I think
so I just want to know what's going on
do you guys remember like as a kid I
feel like I had a deep obsession with
cucumbers yeah you did like I used to
just cut them off there some salad
dressing on them you would I used the
salt cucumbers and just eat them cuz I
like salt so I'd be like go I need a
salty snack let me just get these
water-based vegetables and [ __ ] Gob
down yeah we soak them with salt you'd
put way too much salt oh cuzz you
wouldn't even now explain to me why I'd
be a freak if I just ate a cucumber
without cutting it that's really strange
why though we do it with bananas and we
do it with carrots give me just a
[ __ ] cucumber I want to eat it throw
some salt some dressing A lot of people
we eat pickles like that it's a [ __ ]
no we don't they're pickled do you know
what a pickle is a cucumber pickled
cucumber correct bring back to the roots
I want to gobble down a cucumber by
itself I think it's the skin that's like
not the best you could eat the skin you
could but it's just a tip you don't want
to eat like the little like part of I'll
cut the tip off and then I'll I'll
gobble up the rest okay you want
what freaks me the [ __ ] out copious
amounts of just creamy peanut butter I
actually I'm not afraid of peanut butter
I don't want to be those weirdos that
say they have a phobia of everything oh
I have a phobia of this I have a phobia
of that people pull phobias out of their
[ __ ] [ __ ] but if I saw a TV like
if I walked into a room and I saw a TV
and a table drenched in just creamy
peanut butter I'd lose my mind it'd be a
sensory overload imagine there's a solid
granite table lathered in peanut butter
and you just press your hand in E Nick
disgusting dude yeah it's a horrible my
God I think no oh Skippy peanut butter
balls with the peanuts inside oh the dry
Sahara Desert shoes [ __ ] those things
literally I used to be feing for water
what were you saying I was going to say
when people recreate the the peanut
butter baby videos dude you're a [ __ ]
weird would you ever do that no I'm not
I'm not a baby it's called a peanut
butter baby cuz there's a [ __ ] baby
making a mess out of peanut butter keep
it to the babies you don't need adults
cosplaying peanut butter baby covering
themselves in peanut butter and I almost
said Nut
Butter you don't need adults getting in
diapers covering themselves in peanut
butter if you don't know who the pean
peanut butter baby is it was this was it
a Vine I think it was a Vine it was a
video vine of this little baby and he
was sitting on a counter and he goes and
he turns around he's [ __ ] covered in
peanut butter and he goes so covered go
and it's it's it's like that's the
peanut butter baby self-explanatory I
see that I see that thing I say two
things come to my mind you want know
Peanut but baby peanut butter and baby
for sure that's it that's
him never need to be replicated by ad
Again by an adult yeah we should try to
duplicate it and do like the um we
should go as famous as the peanut butter
baby but we should be like the Mayo
triplets oh my God there's so many
things I'd hate if my body was lathered
in and mayo and peanut butter are both
one of them I've never been snowboarding
but what blows my mind about snowboards
is your both your feet are
[Laughter]
trapped both your feet are trapped to
that snowboard if you tip over you're
dying no you can uncp
it you can uncp a I can't touch my toes
you should in order snowboard you should
be able to touch your toes what the guy
upside he's buried alive he's and then
the other dude shovels him out oh
biggest fear biggest fear biggest fear
biggest fear biggest fear an avalanche
what are you doing in an avalanche Nick
I'm laying down and saying God please be
good to me send me out I got a stuffed
animal the other day I said to you guys
guys take a look guess what his name
is are we in an iPhone did someone put a
Minecraft block
down
[ __ ] I went up to you guys with a
stuffed animal the other day and I said
hey guess his name you guys said I don't
know I said his name's Jerry and you
guys yelled at me for naming all my
stuffed mat has
Matt across his
lifetime go ahead Matt across his
lifetime has named 10im up words of
eight stuffed animals Jerry he's like
this is Jerry this is Jerry like named
all girl vers monster I'd do anything
for it to be fall and me to be watching
girl versus monster eating pumpkin
cookies with my toes in a blanket right
now I kind of agree the visual I just
got was crazy my toes in a blanket yeah
just like curling them up just gripping
a blanket toies gross I love just having
nothing that's better actually there's
not many feelings in this world that are
better than having warm toes do you want
to know what I want to do what do you
know how people that have pools put
Kitty pool in the pool and they float on
that pool and girl I never want to do
that I want to do that so bad that's a
bizarre thing and I want to no like with
the blanket and like a pillow oh no yeah
I'm I want to spend an overnight on a
boat if I ever was awoken by copious
amounts of water Nick stop saying
copious copious copious copious if I got
woken up and someone was drenching me in
water putting like in the LX when they
throw that [ __ ] in the ocean the
little bears and [ __ ] if I ever woke up
in the the bears oh my God I Su the next
living I know the next prank we're
dumping water on Nick when he's asleep
what would you be mad if we did that if
we dump water on you in your sleep to
wake you up for a prank wouldn't talk to
you for a week the spork to me is an
invention I don't think a single soul
needed the [ __ ] I never forked
something with a spork never I never
it's cuz it's like it was always it was
always a spoon to me well who I need to
I need a face I need a face to face
session with the guy
who don't disrespect my Spork you
[ __ ] L you use that more than you
ever have any other utensil and you spit
on your forehead I'd say that's a damn
false lie no he wouldn't he say I got
the proof every day you went in the
Middle School you touched a spork you
then every day I went home I used a
spoon or a fork what's your [ __ ]
issue how about you invent the how about
the [ __ ] who created the little
plastic thing with all the knives and
and the napkin and the salt and pepper
oh
I know what you're talking about that's
up to you the little packet to take out
meal and it's got the little goodie bag
a [ __ ] Fork a knife a spoon um salt
it's like dude I got soup and I got
everything you know what say like I love
those for joining us this Friday video
we will see you next Friday I'm going to
go join the gay truckers I need to know
what's up all right have fun happy
Friday we'll see you next week make sure
you're shopping from
www.ssoc.com if you want some
merchandise for these amazing videos you
watch
[Music]
yo