Hi Sharks. My name is Kelly
and I'm Christina. We're from San
Francisco, California. And today we're
seeking $200,000 in exchange for 10%
equity of our company, Yard Sale.
Sharks, if you've ever skied, you
probably agree with us. Ski poles kind
of suck.
They're clunky and easy to drop.
Plus, they're made of cheap materials.
They come in limited colors, and I think
we can all agree, they're pretty ugly.
We're lifelong skiers and know firsthand
that people are constantly looking to
upgrade their ski gear. But when it
comes to innovation, ski poles have been
well long forgotten.
That's why we started Yardell.
Yardell ski poles blend clever design
and great style for the everyday skier.
The best part about yard sale poles,
they're magnetic. We've hidden magnets
in the handles in the baskets that they
stick together, making walking to and
from the car or getting on and off the
lift an even easier experience. Skiers
love how yard sale poles are fully
modular, so you can mix and match
between the five eye-catching colors on
our website to create your own custom
pair. With Yardell, we're not only
making ski days easier and more fun, but
we're creating a lifestyle brand for the
millions of recreational skiers out
there.
So, Sharks, who's ready to ditch your
old poles in the snow and ride the
chairlifts with yard sale?
Oh, I love it.
I just got to ask name.
Yes.
Why the name yard sale?
Okay. Haven't you ever had a yard sale
on the mountain?
So yeah, Kendra, are you like what? Are
you a black diamond skier? You don't
know what a yard sale is? It's when you
lose everything. Your skis come off,
your poles come off. It's like they call
it like, you know, like a yard sale,
like a garage sale.
So like, does everybody that skis know
that because
it's kind of it's kind of an insider
term. Kendra clearly is a skier in the
room
and clearly I've had a lot of yard
sales.
And it actually goes a bit back to the
origin stories of how we actually came
up with the idea. Christina had a
infamous epic yard sale or wipe out and
that's where she came up with the idea.
I had a bad yard sale. It got me
thinking about my greatest frustration
with the product,
which for me is when you're carrying
them, they're always crossing over.
They're falling down. And so I thought,
why has nobody put magnets on ski poles?
And are you the only one doing this?
Yes, we are.
I started tinkering with my old poles
and I basically taped some magnets to
the handles of these. I walked around
the corner to Kelly's house cuz he lives
very close by to me and I asked him what
he thought. No one has ever in decades
rethought the humble ski pole. Yet every
skier needs them to ski.
What are your backgrounds?
I've always been passionate about design
and so I was very fortunate to follow uh
that pursuit to MIT where I studied
mechanical engineering and product
design. Um afterwards I worked at Apple
as a product designer across various
teams and as an avid skier I was ready
to jump into a consumer product.
So are you guys full-time in this?
We are.
We are. Yeah. So my background is more
on the marketing side of things. After
college, I worked for a um hardware tech
startup in marketing and then I
transitioned to the venture capital side
where I was the head of content and PR
for a VC firm in San Francisco.
One of the most important things to note
as well is that over 60% of our
customers online customize their polls
which means that we have a huge
adoption.
You're not doing any retail, right?
So we are in a few specialty stores.
So what's your price compared to a
regular pole off?
Absolutely. So we just launched 6 months
ago um and we uh make the product for
about $30. We landed it for 42 and we
sell it for 139. It's 75% margin.
What are like the average poles?
Great question. We're in the upper
middle range in the market. So on the
lower end you have about $50, $60 poles
which are just cheap aluminum ones, but
on the upper end you have really
advanced poles, but we sit really in the
middle and there's other poles that are,
you know, in our range, but no one that
offers features like we do.
What have you sold so far?
Yeah, great question. Yep. In the first
month, uh, right before the holidays
this past year, we did $100,000 in sales
in our first month. So, we are fiscal
year to date uh $220,000 in sales.
220.
Yes. And we are forecasting to end the
year, which for us ends in September at
$300,000. Next year, we're forecasting
$2.1 million.
Where and how did you sell them?
Yeah. So, we we launched DOC only. Um
we'll be expanding into retail next
winter.
With with who?
Well, what was really exciting is in our
first 30 days, we had REI reach out to
us backount dathlon in Europe. When I
get new poles, I'm in the boots in the
store and we're sizing and the, you
know, we're trying to figure out exact,
you know, the pose, right? So, what
happens to you?
Those are a little
Do you need multiple different sizes of
this inventory?
They they come in five sizes. Um, but
that's that's an inventory nightmare.
Well, we got an answer for you, Mr.
Wonderful.
What you can actually see in our kids
poles, which are on the far left here,
is that they're adjustable. And we'll
have adjustable poles for adults next
year as well. Wait, you mean so they'll
continue to slide?
Yeah. So, actually, as kids grow,
they'll grow with the thing. I have kids
from ages 10 to 22, by the way. I don't
see that out there.
Let me just tell you how I feel. So, um,
first of all, I don't really love the
name. I think it has a bit of a negative
connotation and an incorrect connotation
for a premium quality brand new item
that's innovative. Yard sale just feels
like it's a disaster and it's when the
worst thing happens. And then I'm not a
skier and have to feel passionate about
the product. Love the people, but don't
feel it here. Um, so I'm sorry. I'm out.
Thank you so much.
I love the name. So when I saw a fubu,
they were like, "What is a foo?
Is it Italian? Is it Japanese? Is it
number three on the poo poo platter?
What is it?" And that exactly became a
conversation that stood out from
everybody. So, you know how many times
people come up here, their name is too
close to something else, and then they
spend a lot of money and they lose it.
They
I will say it is one of the biggest
reasons skiers have paid attention to
our brand.
I agree. I'm part of the the snowboarder
community, and we hate you guys.
So, I I don't know. I just don't like
skiing. Um, this is just not for me. Um,
so I wish you all the best. Great
innovation. I'm out.
Thank you.
Thank you, Damon.
I've never skied once in my entire life
and I have no intention of starting. So,
for those reasons, I'm out.
I love this. I love the name. This is
really great. It's catchy, but you know,
you're early. This is 6 months in.
You're putting really a $2 million
valuation on a business with what you're
asking.
And we realized there's a high risk
behind that. And so, actually, one of
the things that we did was uh we we, you
know, are obviously asking for $200,000
for 10%. Um, but we do have a lot of
profit margin in our product. And so
therefore, we do actually have a bit of
a secondary offer in our back pocket,
which Mr. Wondery,
Mr. Wonderful, we'd love to talk to you
about. So, if you're willing, we'd love
to make you an offer of $200,000 for 5%
with a $3 royalty until you recoup your
initial investment of $200,000.
That's the first time a company has ever
offered to Kevin a royalty.
A royalty. You know, we afraid of a
royalty. That's a first.
I would prefer to model it this way. Um,
uhoh. I'll do the 200,000 for 20% and
I'll take my chances on distributions. I
want a distribution when you distribute
to yourselves, but I want I want to wet
my beak on this one. I want 20%.
Yeah. Well, yes, absolutely. We'd love
to talk about what Kevin would have to
do uh to roll up his sleeves and really
help us. So,
well, I don't want a job. Okay.
You know, you just said you need
somebody who's going to roll your
sleeves up. Honey, I've done it. I get
retail. I get omni channel. I think you
have a great direct to consumer, but
wholesale is where you can really build
this business. That's how I started
Kendra Scott. I like I'm going to do 20%
as well. Plus, I want the $3 back until
I recoup my 200K. Okay.
Thank you.
All right. The difference here is I
really do think I can help you with this
wholesale strategy.
I'll drop my ash to 15%.
But I'll take the $3 royalty till I get
back 400,000. So, it's just a 2x.
Would you be interested in doing
$200,000 for 8%. We'll drop that equity
down, but we'll increase your royalty to
$5 a unit until you recoup $300,000.
I'll do it at 10%. I want the royalty,
but I want a 2x on it, right?
That's just going to put us in a really
tight position in the future. Actually,
we think at five at $5 a unit, we can
actually get you your 300K back if you
take we'll take that offer within under
two years.
Getting my money back is not not why I
do deals. I want to get a multiple on
it. Kendra, would you be interested in
that sort of a royalty offer, which is
$200,000 for 8% uh with a $5 unit
royalty until you recoup $300,000 back?
You know what? I actually really like
that. I like that. I do like it. Can we
do 10% and you have yourself a deal?
If you'll drop to 250 on the royalty
payback, you got yourself a deal. It's
300.
Oh my god. $50,000 cash. Come on. Will
you up the upfront cash to $250,000 at
10% with a $5 royalty until you recoup
$300,000 back?
Done. Done.
Let's go. I'm going to come over here.
I'm skiing over.
Thank you so much. Thank you, Kendra.
Thank you so much. So much fun. I'm
going to have these everywhere I go.
I'm so excited. Thank you all. You skis
deserve each other.
That was insane. Well, Kevin has an
amazing team, but Kendra was really
Kendra's a she's also a billionaire.
She is a billionaire and she seemed
really excited and really genuinely just
like willing to roll up her sleeves and
help us with all the things that we need
help with.