So were were there days when I regretted
taking the step to create our own
company? Yes, there were mainly nights
like dark nights when the demons come
out and things are really tough. No
funding, capital markets have dried up
and a short runway. I went out and I
started asking all my mentors and all of
the uh people for advice and they said,
"Lay off everybody you can except just
the core people. protect the IP, live to
fight another day. George and I looked
at each other and
said, "That doesn't really align with
the core values that we said we were all
about. And if we don't use our core
values to make the hardest decision of
our life, then they're not really our
values." So, we said, "All right, we're
not going to do that." Instead, we got
the entire team together, about 25
people at the time. Uh we told them
exactly the what was going on. We asked
everybody to take deep cuts to have a
belief in the company and us to feel
figure out how we're going to weather
this storm and we ended up keeping
everybody. I don't think I slept during
that period. I mean, yeah, I closed my
eyes at night, but you know, it was just
terrible. It wasn't just me anymore. It
was 25 people and their families who had
a belief in what we were doing. And
during that time, that's when we did
find our product market fit. It was
during that time we got the first call
from A&D networks and they said, "Can
you help us?" And we said,
[Music]
"Yeah." My name is Pete Thompson. I'm
co-founder and CEO of Lucid Link. Lucid
Link transforms cloud storage into an
unlimited high-performance drive that
can be accessed from anywhere and
collaborated on with your team without
having to synchronize, download or ship
files around. Lucid Link has over a
100,000 active users now and we've grown
the business over the last few years
from effectively zero to over 40 million
in ARR. Our next stage is we're focusing
on that 50 to 100 million ARR milestone.
Embracing
ambiguity. That was one of the things I
think I learned early on in my life. I
was in a program to become a doctor. I
was in a premed program. I thought
that's what my path was. And it was just
by chance that I had this opportunity to
go to Japan. And as it turned out, it it
changed the trajectory of my life. after
I had spent a year of uh university
studying in Japan and just realized that
I wanted to do something in my career
that involved Japanese that I had
learned. So I joined data core as uh
employee number 20. My role in dataore
was to help them establish their
business in Asia Pacific. But in doing
so, I spent a lot of time traveling to
these areas and speaking to people and I
had to speak to them as the
representative of data core as a storage
expert. But there was a problem. I
wasn't a storage expert at the time. I
needed to be able to gain their trust. I
couldn't lie to them. I couldn't pretend
that I knew things I didn't. So, there
were a lot of very uncomfortable moments
where I was kind of right on that edge.
I knew I was slightly out of my element,
but I was honest about it at but at the
same time they realized, okay, he's
still, you know, we can we can trust
what he's saying. And gradually over
time and through a lot of uncomfortable
moments, I just that's how you learn.
You know, you push yourself out of your
comfort zone and you gradually one day
you wake up and you realize, you know
what, I kind of am an expert.
At some point while I was working at
dataore I realized that my job was
becoming easy for me. It became a little
bit repetitive. I wasn't growing and I
didn't have that feeling of challenge
anymore. So all of this told me it's
just time to move on. But I wasn't sure
how to move on. But uh it was at this
time that a friend of mine had gone
through the same program uh the Sloan
Fellowship program at Stanford. Well,
Mike and I were fishing buddies. So,
while you're sitting out on the ocean, I
learned more about the time he spent at
Stanford. And he finally said, you know,
this was you should just go there, do
this program, find a figure out
something to do and start a company. And
I said, "Huh, yeah, maybe I should. Let
me try that." And so I I was accepted
into the program and I went into it with
that. I said, "Okay, I I'm I've got one
year here. I want to address some things
that I want about myself, challenge
myself in in some uncomfortable
situations and either come up with an
idea or meet some people who have an
idea that I can join and start a company
from scratch." How old was I when I made
that decision? Uh I was 48. I was the
oldest person in the program.
How did it feel to go back to graduate
school after such a long time in the
workforce? It felt really uncomfortable,
but also it was amazing. I was worried
that the time was going to go too fast.
I was worried that after a year maybe I
didn't know what that next thing was
going to be. I felt I have to make the
best use of this
time. I think it was October or November
when I was in in the program. I didn't
know what I was going to do, although I
was certain that it would have nothing
to do with storage. That was the last
thing I thought I was going to do. All
of a sudden, my co-founder George called
me up. We didn't work very closely at
Dataore, but I knew him well because he
was the first engineer that they hired.
He was known to be a brilliant engineer.
He called me up and he said, "Hey, Pete,
I don't know if you realize this, but I
left shortly after you did because I had
this idea in my head. I needed to get it
out of my brain and into code and see if
it had merit. Are you interested in
seeing what I built?" And I thought,
"Yeah, of course I am." He showed me a
demo that blew my mind after all those
years in storage. I said, "Wait a
minute. Is this just a demo or is this
actually happening live because this
shouldn't be possible? He said, "Look,
I'm I've got this idea. I'm looking for
some partners to help find investors to
grow the business, to do all of this,
and I'm at Stanford learning how to
start a business, get investors, know
how to build a business, and I'm looking
for an idea. This could be a perfect
combination. Tell you what, let's use
the rest of the time I have here at
Stanford and the resources, some of the
classes that are available to me to
really pressure test this idea. Let's
try to prove to ourselves that there's
nothing here. Let's try to disprove this
theory that there's a company in this
technology. The problem that we were
trying to solve was you've got large
sets of data and a whole bunch of people
that need to access it. Some of these
files within this data set are super big
and that makes it even more difficult.
Today you have two choices. You can move
the compute and the applications to
where the data is stored or you can move
the data and the files to where the
compute is running but they have to be
together. And most of the technology was
all based on either moving the data
faster or creating replicas of those
files so that they were next to the
applications. What we were doing was
something completely different. We said
keep the data stored where it is, keep
the compute running to where it is. We
will present it as if it is local and
our technology will solve the problems
around performance and collaboration. If
you can break that fundamental
difference or fundamental dependency on
an application requiring a file to be
right next to it, now you can make those
decisions separately. You can choose
where to store stuff based on place to
store it and you can choose where to run
your applications based on a separate
set of criteria. That unlocks all of the
productivity that we've been doing. But
first, we had to get funding. We knew
this was going to be a difficult and
highly technical product to build. So we
needed funding and we needed time. After
I graduated from Stanford, we began
pitching to VCs
and they all told us no. They all told
us it'll never work. It's a bad idea.
People won't pay for it. Even if you do
get build it, they won't care. There
were so many reasons not to invest in
it. And that was hard. Let me tell you,
venture capitalists are very smart. They
see a lot of great ideas. They have a
lot of success uh investing in
worldclass companies. So when they tell
you that your idea sucks, it's hard to
say you're wrong. But you have to you
have to believe you have to say that
there's something that they don't see.
There's something I know that they don't
know. They're a generalist. They see a
lot of things. I'm a specialist. I know
storage. I know this problem firsthand.
So, what was the problem? Maybe I'm not
uh pitching it correctly. Maybe I have
to change my story, you know. So, we
kept iterating on trying to figure this
out. Finally, after 33 rejections or 33
nos, we finally found an investor who
said, "I think there is something here."
And he was willing to invest in us. That
was Steve Anderson at Baseline Ventures.
He was well known for picking winners.
So the fact that he saw something here
really motivated us as well. So we got
funded and now we had to build the
product and it took 2 years to build
this
[Music]
product. From 2017 to 19 we were
building the product. From 2019 we
really had the product out and we were
trying to find the initial product
market fit. So we were getting close to
that in 2020. We had to go out and get
more funding. We weren't funding because
we had the metrics. We were funding
because we were running out of money.
Not a great position to be in. So we
knew that this was still going to be a
case where we are going to have to sell
vision. We were ready to to do that. We
got um a whole list of uh VC meetings
set up and on a Monday morning we were
driving up Sand Hill Road in early 2020
and suddenly we got a phone call and
they said, "Oh, hey, by the way, we're
going to have to cancel this meeting
today. Uh we're not allowed to take any
more in-person meetings. We're going to
put a pause on all new investments until
we kind of see how this CO thing is
going to shake out. It'll probably be
maybe two weeks or a month and then
we'll be back back to business as
normal. Well, we've got a couple hours
before our meeting in the afternoon.
Let's go to a coffee shop and work on
our pitch deck. So, we go to the coffee
shop and walk in and we get another call
the next meeting. Basically, the entire
week of VC meetings got wiped out in one
day. No funding. Capital markets have
dried up and a short runway. That was
kind of a moment we went,
"Uhoh, what have we done?" I went out
and I started asking all my mentors and
all of the uh people for advice and they
said, "Lay off everybody you can except
just a core people. Protect the IP. Live
to fight another day." George and I
looked at each other and said,
"Hm, that doesn't really align with the
core values that we said we were all
about. And if we don't use our core
values to make the hardest decision of
our life, then they're not really our
values. So we said, "All right, we're
not going to do that." Instead, we got
the entire team together, about 25
people at the time. We were very
transparent, which is one of our values.
Uh we told them exactly the what was
going on. We asked everybody to take
deep cuts to have a belief in the
company and us to feel figure out how
we're going to weather this storm and we
ended up keeping everybody. I don't
think I slept during that period. I
mean, yeah, I closed my eyes at night,
but you know, it was just terrible sleep
and there was a lot of pressure and it
wasn't just me anymore. It was 25 people
and their families who had a belief in
what we were doing. And during that
time, that's when we did find our
product market fit. It was during that
time we got the first call from A&D
Networks and they said, "So, we don't
know anything about your company, but
somebody over at Adobe said we should
call you. Um, we just sent home 80
engineers with a a laptop, a hard drive,
and a VPN connection, and that's
probably going to let us get through
about the next 2 weeks of production,
and then we're just not sure what we're
going to do. Can you help us? And we
said, "Yeah, yeah, that's exactly. We
can absolutely help you." So we set them
up on a P and they the P ended up
running from directly into production
and we closed them at nearly 100k ARR
contract. Now remember we our total ARR
at that time with 50 customers was
around 100K. So this was huge and it was
during that time that we got the next
call from Viacom CBS and then the third
call from Vice News. And all of them had
the same story, the same problem, the
same outcome. And at that point, we
said, "All right, we are no longer a
general file access platform. We are now
a creative content collaboration tool."
And that's when we went from 100K in ARR
to a million that first year and then
went from 1 to 5, 5 to 15, 15, 30, and
we're still going.
to people who haven't found their
product market fit or are trying to wait
for their opportunity to come. I guess
I'd say
believe. If you have done the work and
you know your product and you know the
market, you know there's something
there, you have to believe in it and you
just have to have the resilience and the
grit to to keep bringing it every day.
That's the hard thing about being an
entrepreneur. You've got to dig deep
when no one else believes and you have
to believe. Not only do you have to
believe, but you have to make sure that
your team believes. That would be my
advice. You just you can't give
up. I was worried that after a year
maybe I didn't know what that next thing
was going to be. I felt I have to make
the best use of this time. So, did you
make the best use of that time? I think
I made the best use of the time there. I
mean, the fact that I was able to start
Lucid Link and it's become such a an
important part of my life and an
important part of almost 200 people who
work for the company. It was absolutely
worth it. I think u I I can't imagine a
better outcome for me personally. How do
I think about uh the ability to nurture
instinct to challenge yourself or just
to put yourself in challenging
situations? I think this is something
you can nurture. People talk about
growth all the time. They say, "Oh, this
is amazing. We get this chance to grow."
Growth is hard. Growth is painful.
Growth kind of sucks sometimes. The
result of growth is awesome. The process
of growth kind of sucks. It's hard. How
you can do that? It's through habits.
It's through not taking those shortcuts.
It's through recognizing when you have a
a decision in front of you and doing
something that is right, not necessarily
easy. The more you do those, and those
can be small things. They can be small
things like waking up and being like,
"Yeah, I don't know. I don't have to go
to the gym." Or go to the gym and say,
you know, I'll just do one one set
instead of three. every time and no
matter how small or big those decisions
are that you take not the easy path but
the right path you're going to gradually
build that habit within yourself. You'll
build that muscle uh to be open to
challenging yourself. How you do one
thing is how you do everything.
[Music]