for people just starting their career I
have a bit of a different advice I think
a lot of people say go start your own
company learn by doing I highly don't
recommend that route I would recommend
most people they actually go see what
good looks like and that doesn't
necessarily part where I talk about
Prestige is that like just because
something prestigious doesn't mean the
right place that you're going to learn
the most from the thing that might have
made that procedure might no longer
still be relevant because of people who
were there that got it that state might
not be as involved it might be a much
larger company might be a lot more
process it's very much about I would say
go look for the smartest people you can
surround yourself with and try to work
there and just do like little flavor one
year at a multiple companies like you
really want to understand something from
first principles which really requires
spending multiple years trying to work
through some hard problem you definitely
want to try to look for places have
already had some level of success and
you're going to continue to build on
level of success the reason I call that
out is because there's some pretty
interesting companies with smart people
that seem smart from the outside as a
22y old or when you're young it's hard
to evaluate like what is smart or not
smart because everyone smarter than you
hi I'm Kake I'm the CEO at sift at sift
we're building the data tools to go
build modern machines and a lot of it is
inspired by workflows and processes and
how we built machines back at SpaceX
where I spent the prior 4 and a half
years before working on the dragon
flight software program and dragon was a
capsule that carried astronauts and
cargo to the space station so we have uh
seven publicly announced customers we
raised about 25 million most recently
the series a was led by GV Plus Google
Ventures previous rced was led by two
firms in LA CA Ventures focuses on a lot
of Enterprise SAS Riot Venture is one of
the best like Hardware investing firms
I was born and raised in a little suburb
outside of LA right next to JPL so I was
about 10 15 minutes outside of JPL so I
actually grew up going to Industry days
where you can just walk in there's a lot
of photos of me actually with like
playing with the Mars rover and the
Legos and stuff that they had at JPL I
would always grew up with Legos but then
like my first real like machines were
LEGO Mindstorms you can build all robots
and you can make very simple programs
with these Legos I started that around 9
so I was like fourth grade always had
fun with that with my friends and I also
this thing called first Lego league so
first robotics they have these
competitions it's most known for the
high schoolers that are building like
these robots they'll have like they'll
be like three on three and they'll have
some sort of like theme saying like Hey
we're building a moon base so you have
to build a robot that can go drive
around on a slick floor the floor will
be all whiteboard material and the
wheels you have to use are basically
like a whiteboard material so it's like
super slippery and we all have some sort
of competition we to like move these
massive balls into a net whatever it is
but they also have younger levels it's
Lego based so that was kind of my
background I was like around engineering
but it wasn't like a hardcore
engineering like stem background it's
like I had the exposure but I had a lot
of freedom to do other things there's a
little bit more Nuance I knew that the
whole like PayPal Mafia so basically
during undergrad that's when Peter teal
came out with 0 to1 so that book 0 to1 I
liked it a lot kind of more contrarian
very much promoting first principles
thinking of that I was looking at more
of like the PayPal Mafia companies but
PayPal was also like much later stage I
I didn't think it was the PayPal in the
early days but a lot of these other
companies like paler SpaceX Tesla were
really interesting so that's what I was
looking at as opposed to like the
prestigious companies I actually would
as part of advice I would highly
recommend people not optimizing for
Prestige do you know the atmology of the
word Prestige the atmology of the word
Prestige is actually it goes back to
like the French word for illusion and
then it goes back to the Latin word for
playing tricks Conjuring tricks the
whole concept like Prestige and a
prestigious Place actually a bit of an
illusion you just want to go to places
that are like have results like can like
see people say it's great but you can
actually see with your own eyes on the
ground truth with space xile was clearly
visible
are you a tech startup founder building
something cool if so listen up EO has
teamed up with tech domain to give
Founders like you a rare opportunity to
pitch live directly to topy seas in
Silicon Valley and get featured on this
channel viewed by more than 350k
subscribers worldwide the only condition
your startup must use a do te domain or
plan to upon getting selected to pinch
and erase Less Than 3 million doll in
funding after all if you're building in
Tech do te is the most relevant domain
extension to get it tells the world your
website is all about technology and hey
it's cooler.com some of the coolest Tech
startups are already using te domains
and we've been highlighting their
stories in eo's original interview
series Beyond Tech now it's your turn
head over to www. pitch. or check the
video description to apply
now I joined space act there is a lot of
stuff to learn one of the Dragon
missions as is coming back to Earth the
Dragon capsule has four parachutes one
of the four parachutes it didn't open
until a pretty low altitude of course
there's redundancy built in it was
always going to be safe even though that
parachute didn't open it wasn't an
expected Behavior and the way that this
works is these Dragon missions work on a
scheduling is as soon as you bring these
four astronauts back you want to launch
another four immediately to get back on
a space station our scheduled next
launch was actually just one week behind
but then NASA said hey this parachute
didn't open how do we know this is not
going to be a more problematic issue on
the next mission and then they grounded
the next flight until this result for us
to actually figure out what was
happening we need to see all the data
that was collected from the vehicle but
it's stored on this like black box on
the vehicle just like I was an airplane
has like this black box that stores all
the data and the thing is that this
capsule it lands in the Gulf of Mexico
you don't have internet connection in
the Gulf of Mexico to go debug this so
at that time starlink was like a very
experimental program so we like shot
over and email the Starling team and
we're like hey is there any way we can
get internet over the Gulf of Mexico
they activated some cells over the Gulf
of Mexico upload this data from the
Dragon capsule while it was sailing this
is before like Starling was a thing so
like getting High through put internet
in middle of the ocean is not heard of
we're able to send all the data back to
the headquarters we able to run it
through the whole testing Suite do all
the analysis basically say that the next
mission is good to go it's very
interesting you have very smart people
that are basically able to coordinate
satellites to beam internet when it was
a very experimental program to go
accelerate your physical spacecraft
company at the time so I think that was
just like a very cool experience I think
the biggest things I learned was just
seeing what good looks like which I know
is like very broad because I I actually
noce you were asking the question
earlier about what advice would you give
and I think one of the things is just
learning from the smartest folks and at
SpaceX I just saw a lot of people that
were operating a very high level and
sure you can criticize that like maybe
certain things like management might not
be what everyone else likes but at the
end of the day you see it with your eyes
it's like the largest rocket ever
launched and brought back in landing
until you you can like push the boundary
and like show people things that have
never been possible and you're like
super proud of the work you do you work
really really hard but then you can look
back and you're super proud of what you
do I think the key learning was just how
to operate at that very high level the
things that stood out of operating that
high level La is just urgency so it's
just like high urgency High iteration
rate you learn the most if you just have
that urgency to move faster it was
mostly I just wanted to see what good
look like so I was interview on
companies I thought were really high
performing at that time this is what
2017 is when I decided to join SpaceX I
was just pretty much looking for
learning from very very high performing
companies because I knew eventually I'd
either be running a company or starting
company or be in a high leadership
position let me go see how it was done
by the best so I was interviewing
companies I thought were very very high
performing at that time stripe was one
of the hot companies at that time was
like really interesting at the time I
just wanted to learn from people who
were doing well what stood about SpaceX
like the interview process was just very
different than every other company
nobody was pitching me on benefits no
one was pitching me on like work life
balance they were pitching me on Mission
and the work that you're doing here
there's a lot more Spartan but it's also
something you can look back on and be
very excited about and you can like
point to something great that you
accomplished with another team that was
grinding very hard that was the main
reason why I chose it so while I was
there I learned a lot about how to build
machines that are safer more reliable
fall tolerant I wanted to bring a lot of
those ideas and practices The Wider
industry of people building machines
that's why we actually started sift to
productize some of this knowledge into
tools for the rest of the hardware
industry I see Sith growing in like the
vision that I would have for it or my
goal I want a percentage of the physical
world to be operating on Sith I want at
least a percent of the trains the planes
the automobiles the drones the aircraft
things that are out there I want those
operating on sift whether they're being
designed whether they're being
manufactured if they're out in the field
they're generating data they need to be
maintained there should be at least
percentage of the physical world running
on
CFT process for acquiring cft's first
customer was actually kind of Novel we
actually just rented space parallel
systems's office they're the autonomous
rail company they were our first
customer they have a pretty cool office
and we literally just asked them if we
can rent one of the rooms as we build
out the product and that was just
motivated by at SpaceX Elon always
wanted the engineer on the factory floor
so we said we should just be embedded
with our customers let's go rent a room
and then as we built the product we had
new features we just go grab someone
else in the office and say what do you
think of this what do you want what do
you not like our early road map was
completely driven by them the evolution
of our sales motion to the next first
few customers it was a lot of it was
like using things in network we were
lucky that there's vibrant SpaceX Alum
Community we also were able to reach out
through existing investors our investors
that were generally interested in Sith
uh for introductions and also just even
just reaching out on LinkedIn talking
about this stuff that we so what we
wanted to do showing the product but
then also we had a competitor started
around the same time as us we actually
had a few of those bake offs in the
early days the other companies knew that
there's final customers do with their
multiple companies in the space invited
us to a bake off because it definitely
added a lot of urgency on our team and
we won all the bake offs that we've done
to date that was actually a bit of a
novel experience I would say compared to
most companies I think some of the
biggest lessons I've learned is that
like it really all just comes down to
people you have one life to live like
spend it with the people you want to be
around there's a lot of urgency I have
very very limited time if I'm going to
go spend my time with someone I want to
be the best person I can spend that time
with and that goes into everything
whether that's work whether that's
personal so choosing the best partner or
that everything that you do is just
inform other people that are into that
the end of the day like CFT you can talk
about all this Tech you can talk talk
about this architecture you can talk
about all this cool stuff that we do
even our backgrounds or whatever but it
really just comes down to people without
the people we have at sift we wouldn't
have the company to sift make sure you
bring together the best team create
opportunities for everyone to grow keep
everyone happy to be there that's the
main lesson I
learned and that's actually a big thing
I would call out because a lot of the
audience here probably it looks cool to
get some person that's like oh the CEO
or that person who it's like a really
high profile sounds really you just get
them as advisors but if they're not
invested in your success significantly
they're not going to be actually helping
you they're not going to be doing
interviews they're not going to help you
on the trenches and you need to get
people who are going to do that and in
that process they're going to challenge
you and get the smartest folks around so
the best way to evaluate what is a good
team or smart team honestly is just a
kiss a lot of frogs maintaining that
Talent bar and looking for people who
want to do something challenging that
they can be proud of they're going to
work hard and they can think around like
the same level or smarter than you even
better for people just starting the
career I have a bit of a different
advice I think a lot of people say go
start your own company learn by doing I
highly don't recommend that route I
would recommend most people they
actually go see what good looks like and
that doesn't necessarily part where I
talk about Prestige is that like just
because something's procedes doesn't
mean that it's like the right place that
you're going to learn the most from the
thing that might have made that
procedure might no longer still be
relevant because the people who were
there that got it to that state might
not be as involved it might be a much
larger company might be a lot more
process it's very much about I would say
go look for the smartest people you can
surround yourself with and try to work
there and don't just do like little
flavor one year at multiple companies
like you really want understand
something from first principles which
really requires spending multiple years
TR to work through some hard problems
you definitely want to try to look for
places have already had some level of
success and you're going to continue to
build on a level of success the reason I
call that out is because there's some
pretty interesting companies but smart
people that seem smart from the outside
and as a 22y old or when you're young
it's hard to evaluate like what is smart
or not smart because everyone's smarter
than you you want to be careful to not
go somewhere spend a decade and if that
company shuts down you don't know what
that company did that was successful or
not successful that's why it's good to
go to place has like some level of
success that has momentum and it's
continuing to grow so like SpaceX was
really awesome in that regard they were
actually around the time I landed was
the first time the Falcon heavy was
launched they already had rocket Falcon
9 rockets that were launching they
already had the Dragon 1 program but
there's still a lot more they were
planning on doing they weren't just like
sitting and resting that's what I would
optimize for the reason I call out the
prestige is like I would completely
remove the prestige like if you really
want to do that go do that the reason I
call that out is because a lot of times
people will go into that career purely
for the sake of that saying like it
looks cool you can go tell your aunts
about it but are you going to learn as
much are you doing like hard skills are
you actually working on the problem are
you completely abstracted away are you
just multiplying the Grump work that's
being done so like are you actually
going to ownership of things or are you
just like being the grunt work
multiplier for someone else that's more
senior so the reason I recommend people
to join a company doing something hard
and like seeing what great looks like
it's very difficult to strive for
greatness if you've never seen what
greatness looks like cool you can go
watch as many podcasts as you want you
can go see what some blog posts but it's
kind of like Instagram right you only
see the best of someone's life you only
see like a very curated version that's
in like a blog post but what were the
decisions that got the company to that
place what were the nine failures they
had for that one success that's what you
learn by actually solving hard problems
and you don't get that by spending one
two years at like six companies and then
saying I'm going to do an MBA and then
go start company for example and you
just really have to work deeply on a
hard problem with smart folk and a hard
Problem by the way can be different
problems like you don't necessarily have
to go build Rockets even just like
growing like a software startup there's
a lot of challenges in building that
company honestly like I don't think it's
a complete reflection on the other
person not being smart I think just
what's the right role for the person
like for somebody join your company it's
like it's a pretty big risk it might be
very different than somewhere else that
they've been very successful at someone
who might have been very very successful
like a sales force they might struggle
in a much earlier stage role like I
wouldn't hold it against them it's just
a process like don't feel as bad about
it everyone does it everyone struggles
everyone finds it hard but as you're
talking about iteration rate you want to
kiss more frogs you'll see what's good
what's not a lot faster than sitting
there trying to grind through a bad
decision the best things I learned while
working at SpaceX very very strong focus
on first principles thinking you can
just keep asking why a lot of times
people push something off and they say
oh well we're waiting for this person
before we have that meeting is something
scheduled for 2 weeks from now it's like
why does that person even have to be in
the meeting what can we go around and
still move let's say something's not
working instead of just saying like oh
that's not working because it's just
broken or it's like a thing that you
can't do like people say you can't land
Rockets like why why can't you land
rocket we fly and land planes all the
time people like oh because of this or
this technical reason and it's like well
not actually blocked by physics it's
just that nobody's ever done it before
basically you keep asking why till the
point physics is the reason you can't do
it I think that's what I would consider
first principles but it applies
everywhere it's like I think a lot of
times we have a tendency to just say oh
the hardware team says we can't do this
it's like well who on the hardware team
and you go talk to that person you
realize they actually can do it but it's
just like some other thing that they
also need and if you as long as you get
that then you can actually get this
thing a lot faster there's actually this
plays into a lot of like Risk as well
Warner Von Bron who used to run NASA
back in the during the Apollo era he
noticed that let's say some engineer
identified a risk and then they told
manager about it the manager would
downplay that risk it would go from
saying oh this is fatal when you stop
the mission to the manager saying hey
this is a really high risk that person's
manager says oh we need to go look into
this by the time it reaches Warner Von
Brun he would actually just basically
someone would says oh everything's good
to go he actually implemented this thing
called like weekly notes so what he
would do is he had every individual
engineering squad or team write notes
and his team would compile them into a
book and he would actually review all
them so he basically sees ground truth
and he can actually make decisions from
first principles about what's holding of
the program and basically that's how we
put a person on the moon those Rockets
probably have the compute power of like
a ti84 calculator you can do some pretty
cool things when you actually dig into
[Applause]
yapor
engines we can see those chck
[Music]
let