Right. That doesn't sound like an AI
recommendation, but because they told us
they all the pitches talked something
about AI. To be honest, like many of
these these are more of like a buzz
word. They are using it more like a buzz
word. Hi, I'm John Willie. Uh I'm a
three-time founder. I graduated from MIT
and from Stanford. I I won the best
thesis award at Stanford. Had multiple
exits so far. also started Inception
Studio which is now the top accelerator
program for early stage AI founders here
in Silicon Valley. You know I've I've
been an engineer since I was 5 years old
when I start started programming. I won
the USA computer olympiad as one of the
top 15 programmers in the US. As an
investor I'm looking for venture scale
opportunities where I can put in a
million dollars and then I have an
opportunity for at least 100x return you
know coming back to me within you know 5
to 7 to 10 years. Pitch.te Tech is where
bold startups on tech domains get
game-changing insights from top VCs.te
domain instantly signals you're all
about cutting edge tech and innovation.
Building a tech startup build it on
tech.
So we are raising around our preed round
of 1.5 million. The goal of today is to
meet investors and potentially close our
round. Let's go. My name is Laurana. Uh
I'm a co-founder and the CEO of Rexalto.
We have developed and introduced an AI
dynamic pricing engine. We previously
co-ounded one of the largest European
car sharing companies. Company generated
75 million uh annual revenue and what's
more important it was cash flow
positive. What's happening now in the
car rental industry? Increasing prices
of uh vehicles, uncertain residual
values, and growing percentage of
electric vehicles are forcing car rental
and mobility companies to put more focus
on not just reselling cars as they used
to do before, but actually making sure
that they do money on their
cooperations. On top of that, for
mobility companies especially, they
strive to increase their utilization to
improve uh fleet distribution and all of
that can be done with the correct
pricing. Taking all of that into
account, we have engineered an AI
dynamic pricing engine that basically
sets the right price at any given time.
First class of economics, bringing
supply and demand into equilibrium. So
the way it works is we look into the
company's historical data, market
historical data, competitors prices, and
many other factors that help us forecast
demand. Things like weather forecast,
flight information, booking information.
We not only set the price for the for
our customers but we also push it back
either into their fleet management
system or to the OTAAS the aggregators
where they get rents from. We currently
focus on the North American, Europe and
the Middle East. The segments that we
look at and work with are either small
companies or large enterprise companies.
What differentiates us is that we uh
work not only with car rental industry
but with mobility industry and of the
technology because for mobility
companies we use up to 500 data points
for car rental companies it's about 20
30 maybe 40. We offer three pricing as a
service for our traction. We currently
have uh 20 customers paying customers
plus piloting customers. We have
integrated six uh reseller solution. We
uh generated about 200,000 uh annual
revenue. Uh this year we are raising a
round of 1.5 million. We closed 950.
We're now closing the remaining 550.
Thank you very much. You mentioned kind
of in the presentation. Okay. Like you
have uh some of your customers are using
this for kind of rental car rental car
rates. Are there other kind of things in
the automotive space that you're using
for that dynamic pricing today or is it
a lot of companies in mobility are using
that. Look at Uber, Lift, other mobility
companies. It depends because you have a
lot of smaller players players for
micromobility for instance and they use
third party solution. They don't have
their proprietary software and this is
for us they are resellers because we
integrate into their platform and they
sell us to their uh to their customers.
you know, for any tech enabled platform.
I mean, I imagine like they're already
doing something like this or they're
doing some version of this where they
have they're going to have some pricing
engine. They're going to be able to like
determine prices like this is kind of a
common thing. I mean, you mentioned Uber
and Lift, they obviously do all of that,
but then now I mean everything from
concert tickets to, you know, things
anything e-commerce kind of often doing
this type of this type of dynamic
pricing, this might be like core to
their business, very important. So, like
they may want to like develop that
themselves. they have all the data about
it like what type of customer would use
like a service like yours uh versus like
hey we're going to de we either develop
this in our own inhouse or like use some
other very good good question first I'll
answer who are the companies that
develop their own like I talked to head
of revenue management of get get around
they spent a lot of money and many years
developing the dynamic pricing and it
didn't work it's not that simple right
because you need to know how to do it
not to reduce your re revenue even by 1%
right because if you do that you're
fired. So they said we cannot just use
your service software because we need to
make sure our work so we'll keep on
advancing our technology and use it at
the end of the day. Who answering your
question who are our customers? We have
either very small companies that have 50
hundred of cars. They don't have their
proprietary basically their fleet
managers right they're operating their
fleet and they want to do it in the most
effective way. they have a third-party
software solution and they compete with
a budget enterprise etc. So they need to
make sure that they somehow stand out.
So these are our customers and they use
our standard dashboard self-service
dashboard. Then we work with large
companies and these companies are not as
big as enterprise herds but they have
hundreds of thousands of cars still
huge. They basically manage their
franchises. So they need to make sure
that their pricing is consistent
throughout their uh network that they
offer the same quality of service and
that they actually their franchises do
well because they get a percentage of
the what franchises earn. So that's our
second type of customers big groups and
enterprise companies that manage
franchises. What what makes your dynamic
pricing engine better than the
competition? First, as I said, like it's
it's the number of uh data points that
our engine can absorb and make this
decision and judgment. You saw that we
have an AI in the beginning of of this.
Every company
now flexing internet. Yeah. But I'll
tell you where the AI comes. Uh so it's
it's it's it's a bunch of ML models that
work together, right? So that's not
there's this is this is not AI but where
the AI comes is that we every time our
model works in a certain location for a
certain customer it learns from its past
uh performance and next time makes
better predictions make better
assumptions and improves the quality. I
mean, and and on that topic, I noticed
your pricing model is that you're
charging like per car, you know? I mean,
and if if you actually are really
confident about, hey, we're gonna have
this R this is the ROI that we're going
to get. Like, why are you not like
saying, hey, well, you get you're going
to have 90% of the up and we'll just
take 10% of the of the one customer with
who did that. And that was the I was
like telling my team like, let's move
into that like we will make sure our
customers do better and we'll do better.
It didn't work. uh we we still have one
customer on that contract and I'm just
waiting for the contract to renew to get
get away from the the reason why you
always have to you need to have a
baseline. So what are you comparing to?
So usually you would oranges to oranges
December to December, January to
January. But then when things like
Easter or Ramadan happens, they move
from one month to another. Then they
like yeah but the increase was not
because of your pricing model but
because it was uh Easter was in this
month and last year it was in a
different month. So much time is spent
on actually this argument because they
don't want to pay you more, they want to
pay you less. And we said like at this
point we cannot do this. It's it's it's
crazy. So we said we want to be uh clear
and straightforward. We'll do uh
standard pricing per car per month and
that's that's good enough. Yeah. I mean
but that that also I mean you point to
like kind of fundamental problem which
is like that is like measuring like the
the improvement in lift that you're
going to have like from this because
Yeah. I mean, how do you compare apple
to apples like when you're kind of
revenue over time? still compare. We
still they have dashboards. They see how
their pricing increase over a longer
period of time. Like okay, maybe one
month to another might be tricky. But
then if you look on a year scale, you
still see the increase. Do your
customers do AB testing. They can run
two side by side. We usually start with
AB testing especially with big uh
customers but we don't do it within one
city because you can't you cannot do it
in with one location. The customer will
choose what is cheaper. So you have to
do it different locations. So we would
choose few selected location usually the
way our pilot works two three locations
one would be maybe the top location
another one would be midsize location
and third would be like the small
location and then we will see the
results in those those and what has been
the result worst result that we had was
plus 5% of revenue increase. Our best
was it was six times but that was a very
particular case a luxury uh car rental
company that was staying within within
its boundaries. We analyze also the
supply and we said it's Dubai end of
December there are two Lamborghinis
available and there is a demand for 100
you can put whatever price you want you
will still sell it right that doesn't
sound like an AI recommendation no that
I mean like that because they was cap
they called us because they called me
they were like a brilliant your system
is crazy that tells me to put I don't
remember the price something is wrong
with that I was like hold on let me uh
look into this so I looked into this and
then we said like that's what you should
put customers don't like dynamic pricing
because it's like wait a second. Oh, you
got you got a different price than I got
when I like when I went you know went to
for this or like it's you know there's a
lot of backlash around pricing and like
these these sorts of things which
ultimately ends up kind of a brand risk
there which is like why sometimes like
even though they can you know they could
potentially uh you know try to do this
like kind of they're they're careful
about time to do this. So what what are
your thoughts on that side? First of
all, uh revenue is not the only KPI why
our customers use us. In many cases is
they want to avoid human mistake. Many
most of them they do uh they look at
competitors prices and they do their
manual and I mean the level of
complexity you have different codes zip
codes like cars are divided into codes.
You have different lengths of rental one
day, two days, three days etc etc. You
have different locations. So actually
the number of price points you have to
change every day sometimes even every
hour it's tremendous. So if you do it
all manually you do mistakes and this
this is what our top managers of the
companies tell us. We know that this is
not
ideal or we often have to actually cut
cut cut the road. So like okay we'll
like not put too much effort here
because just too much. So we'll make an
assumption. So without basing their
assumptions on data. So automatization
of the process and pushing it back into
the system is number one KPI for many of
our large companies. Secondly, we don't
change the price depending on the
customer. So this is up to the company
whether they want to charge C different
customers have their loyalty programs
for mobility companies. We do we don't
look at a particular customer because we
don't have the data but we cluster them.
So we understand that this customer
falls into this cluster at this and so
there's a different coefficient but
that's what all mobility companies are
famous for because they uh they give the
car to to different audiences. This is
very interesting because I mean I went
to your website actually to very nice
looking website uh to be honest looking
at your website I had no clue what you
guys did. Uh, so like this is uh like uh
hearing the pitch is like actually like
now I have a much better idea of like uh
what what you're doing because like I
think it just at least in terms of like
the copy that was on the website they
didn't it didn't come across like on on
there. You you cover the team extremely
early. Um which to be honest like before
I know what problem you're solving it's
hard to be able to judge wait is this
the right team that sort of thing right?
Um, so like you know sometimes better
like say that later like after oh and by
the way this is why the this is here's
the evidence is why we're the right team
to do this right and so like what is
your connection to this problem this
space and like how about the rest of the
team like how like why are you uniquely
suited to be like you're the ones in the
world to solve this problem. So that
yeah the actually the reason why I
showed it in the beginning is that in
our past company when we exited and
decided to do something else together we
started thinking okay let's share our
knowledge with other companies we
definitely decided not to build another
car a car car sharing company anywhere
in the world it's very operationally
intense business and then we thought
maybe we do consultancy maybe we do that
that that we said listen let's do what
we did best and we really were best on
the market in terms of pricing correctly
distributing the fleet pricing
uh being considered to be the low coster
and yet making more revenue than our
customers competitors. So that's what we
did and we said let's try to replicate
it uh for other companies. So we started
initially with car car sharing and
mobility companies but then we said
listen there's a much bigger market here
car rental which has it's a dinosaur
industry. So we started looking into
that talking to potential customers and
that's how it all started. Thank you.
Thank you very much. I grew up in a very
international environment. I'm half
Russian, half Indian. So I was always
exposed to different cultures. I
graduated from two US universities, both
in Russia. Then I traveled abroad. So I
started my previous uh together with my
co-founders. We started the previous
company back in 2014 and we were running
the business for 8 years. I left the
country in 2022 for for the war reasons
and it was one of the most difficult
moments of my life was very stressful
was very uncertain and we came here to
US together with my family with my
husband after maybe half a year I said I
want to build something new together
something new here we wanted to use our
knowledge that we gained in our previous
company and the experience that we had
and the understanding of the market and
share it with other companies not only
cautious sharing companies but mobility
companies and also car rental companies.
The thing I like about Rick Alto is is
that uh she is a successful founder that
she built a very successful business
before and based on that experience has
come up to solve this problem in a
compelling manner. What would been great
for me that I would like is uh uh fairly
early on that once she explains that
this is her product is to have a slide
that first says I have six customers
right now because in the beginning I'm
wondering is this an idea? Does she have
customers? Does it work? All these
things. But if I know she's got like six
customers that like it then I know this
is great. And then the next is uh in the
same slide is to show in one year I'll
have 20 customers and these are the
customers that I'm working on. And then
maybe 5 years from now this is what I
want 1,000 customers. All the pitches
talked something about AI. To be honest
like many of these are these are more of
like a buzz word. They using it more
like a buzz word. I know we need to talk
about AI so let's like try to craft an
AI story like on onto our business.
didn't really talk about why is a why
using AI, why is this important, why we
have a tech domain. I think the domain
that you choose it should reflect what
you're doing, right? I like the idea of
highlighting that it's a tech company,
it's a tech product. And I think it also
we stand out uh to our competitors
because it we highlight uh highlight
this point.
[Music]