idiot not wearing those but you look so
cute I'm good
okay and all the things that we did we
said we going to travel from the island
to Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
alled why oh because
of
um imag oh all right guys think about it
ready I'm going to put us all into a
scenario what's up guys happy Friday we
don't have a car video topic today but I
have something to say ah call me a
rappers think about when P said get me
got me
good like what you just said got in like
three different tenses and you're
rapping and it's amazing I don't know
what else he is such a dog he's so horny
all his lines why are you saying this
cuz it's about women yeah I understand
but you don't have to vocalize so
strongly about it what do you keep
looking over there Matt keep looking
there you did it first every single time
he's got out of the car he's looked that
way what is it just life just Santa just
life imagine if it was oh my God him and
his sack and all the reindeers it's why
Santa sack so big cuz he only comes once
a
year that's insane that's gross I don't
like dirty jokes about Santa he didn't
do anything but nice things to us and
we're making fun of him you know what I
mean like it's like when the poor cute
like little girl like is like like and
they bully her it's like why you
bullying picking on someone that's like
already like pick on own not pick your
own why are you picking on someone who
already got the [ __ ] out of the stick
pick on somebody with like full joy and
happiness is you know it's also like
it's also the term getting picked on is
so funny stop picking on me if you're
going to be a bully and you and you must
bully someone for your own selflove
bully someone that is like amazing and
like super like self across the board
terrible advice from Nick St obviously
obviously I'm not obviously obviously
bullying isn't that to do it's not right
if you're going to bully someone bully
someone who has it all is all why bully
the girl with nothing everything you
said everything you've said and your
mouth open since after the whole Santa
joke has been terribly wrong and Terri
obviously not right because bullying is
wrong and I'm just already trying to
wrong I'm trying to write someone's
wrong already don't bully anybody but if
you're going to bully someone bully
someone who's got it all stop no but
someone who pretends to got it all is
actually the most emotional person
sometimes you look too like chill like o
like you need like look at the contrast
between you look stupid yeah see you
look to stupid there it is and Chris
thinks that [ __ ] being disgusting is
humor so that's where I'm not being
disgusting what did I do I haven't seen
these in years get off my get off my
face to no they don't oh my God I didn't
know we had those still shut Matt you're
just you Nick stop [ __ ] reaching for
my eyes before I knock yours in the
[ __ ] back of your head you're not
going to do [ __ ] you dumb pun Matt
thinks he's like chill like Matt thinks
he's like why you hate on that cuz he's
like this the whole time
here guys we don't have a topic today
it's Friday but I have a question at
Matt Chris both of you I need you to
shut your eyes shut your eyes think of
this what you're in the dead center of a
cornfield cornfield you're just waking
up and gaining Consciousness your eyes
are opening slightly and you're like
looking around like you're waving your
arms through the air where am I and you
see nothing was I supposed to open my
eyes when you said that I did too so I
don't okay you open your eyes into the
cornfield you you just see corn like
behind you before the corn field
everywhere and and you're in a big corn
maze okay you don't know your way out
and right as your eyes are opening for
the first time you see I thought my eyes
were already no no right as your eyes
are like like what they focus like
they're open but they're like dilating
to like your surrounding yeah they're
blurry vision blurry these [ __ ]
flirting I been I think my kidneys hurt
and then once your vision that shut the
[ __ ] up no it is in quiz time
[ __ ] no trivia a crackhead ass
talking like shut up [ __ ] I didn't
download the app anyways you're sitting
here it was two chains I don't care I
told you shut up twice I care Nick what
where are we going with this I'm trying
to get there this [ __ ] won't let
me stop speaking it's two chains you're
sinking my [ __ ] [ __ ] let me get
to the point you wake up you gain
Consciousness your eyes finally gain
blur like no blur and right as your
vision is good crystal clear a thing
sauces through the
air you hear a a low hum
vibration and then you see like like
shoots of light and then into the sky it
goes and you you then for the next year
of your life have these crazy empathic
thoughts of
aliens how did you get out of the cormet
like what would you do do I remember
anything else but like just think of it
all is that all crazy Nick that was good
that you have a past of your childhood
how old am I you're
yearning
but you're yearning for your childhood
and you're trying to gain back the right
yarning you're yearning for your
childhood you're trying to gain back the
consciousness of who you are what are
you saying yearning yearning it's a word
doesn't sound like a word Google it
[ __ ] I'm not going to be the
encyclopedia I'm already trying to ask a
question that I want answers to I
haven't heard of an En encyclopedia
since I was like dictionary tomato
tomato both of them it's so wrong it's
so wrong uh Google it yourself but what
I'm saying is what would you
[Applause]
guys like that's so disgusting that's
exactly what I'm talking about and
that's exactly why I like actually I
actually like can't do [ __ ] when Chris
does that and when he burps and when he
farts and when he's just gross what are
you doing Nick I don't [ __ ] know okay
we'll simplify it then do I remember my
childhood you remember like everything
okay okay so I'll just be like what the
[ __ ] happened to me and then I'll try to
figure out and if not I'm going to go
about my life the
same you're telling me if you got
abducted by aliens left in a [ __ ]
goddamn cornfield you'd live your life
naturally the same no I would you
wouldn't live I would go home and I
would look in the I want to hear what
man has to say the story the story you
said had nothing big goof oh my god do
you ever shut up and stop I'm done yeah
where's the off
switch okay Matt
go
go Matt that's how you wish ignore him
ignore him that they act Matt it's just
me wish how they act just you and me at
all you wish they laughed hard at that
one no I don't it's like years old
traction control disabled oh oh oh oh
enable it enable it if you were an
animal you be a bunny rabbit no he
wouldn't what I don't even know what I
was
saying what would you do after the alien
light show oh no that whole story that
you said had nothing to do with anyone
getting abducted by aliens yes it did
nothing well no it no no okay it's more
of your return to nothing about
that I was trying to help you guys I was
trying to go for the storytelling
approach and I wanted you to know that
you got abducted by aliens by the story
I told I didn't so we're abducted or
we're not
abducted it's like the ENT shut [ __ ]
mouth it's the entry back from abduction
correct there it is I know you said you
start walking around in a corn field no
no you're waking up see you weren't
listening right I walking around you did
I didn't no no I
didn't my words again you did did you
started it with imagine you're walking
through a cornfeld waking up no you said
walking through a cornfield then why are
your eyes closed waking up in a
cornfield you're gaining Consciousness
your eyes are finally crystal clear for
the first time I remember quoting myself
and saying that you see like the low
remember that was the
probably I would get up I would go home
I would get naked and check my whole
body for Marks to see if the aliens did
tests on me I love that okay first thing
I no wait I feel like you'd be I didn't
add this in the story I will say but I
feel like you'd be dropped off naked
after alien abduction no would it dress
you but you wouldn't be in human clothes
you'd be in some crazy alien attire
ready for like alien dinner Nick what
are you say I'm serious like if you
think if you get abducted by aliens
you're going to you're going to pop back
into cornfield with like a flanel on no
you're going to get dropped off an alien
dinner attire obviously corre that's
what you'd wish I said that sounds
stupid you're an idiot being realistic
what would the Al I want M to speak
[ __ ] shut up every time his mouth is
open you've interrupted him basically
what the first thing I'm doing is
probably dude you can't catch a goddamn
braak [ __ ] touch me don't [ __ ]
touch me why is he so
mad you want to SW seats what
what no I'm going to die can you stop
burping you remind me why CH reminds me
of and you'll agree I retired that seat
from here on out for the rest of our
YouTube career I will hereby hereby what
do you want a [ __ ] crown and a big
staff shut your mouth I hate it up here
I hate it up here never ever in my life
sit there ever agains can I tell you
both of you let me [ __ ] settle this
no more you are going to get you're
going to get your opinion to speak in a
moment I want to hear what you had to
say about the alien dinner attire you
remind me of a
godamn little Bab shut up shut up you
remind me of a sticky [ __ ] Green
Block like when you go into the daycare
preschool and there's just a wooden
block with oo and undesirable goo just
on it what that's what you remind me of
a a dirty Kid Block so behave if I was
in this close to you all the time right
now I feel really up in your grill up
here I don't like it feel burping and
sneezing the reason we this argument is
cuz you went a on me
in your face I agree Nick I look like an
idiot spitting on camera in your face
right now and I don't care cuz it's
gross it's funny so it's it is funny
Once [ __ ] it's been the 34th
time the humor's dead um I don't care
what I wake up in just ignore him flush
him out flush him out he's not in your
thoughts um I don't care what I wake up
oh should we all make a big deal with a
big Burpy go gas cloud take a THS you
gassy [ __ ] oh burp burp burp not funny
not F yeah it's very funny it's real
funny man you want to throw a hisy face
I'm never going to do anything again
burn I'm King I'm King clean I'm King
healthy he's not King Health burped for
comedic reason and maybe that wasn't
comedic reason I burped down like I
actually I'm not saying that was not
saying that was I been burped for a
comedic reason in maybe n 10 years and I
haven't
burped probably within the last eight
[ __ ] months and you're just a Pepsi
drinking [ __ ] loser all you do is
drink soda and bubbly drinks in burp
24/7 okay can you weigh your opinion on
alien denner tire and no one speaks of
burping again burp is a bad word you'll
get stabbed in the gut if you say it
again think of that okay um I don't care
what I'm dropped off from the alien
abduction in my biggest concern is going
to is sorry it was the way you said
biggest it's more funny it's sound like
a little
airup you're not being nice keep going
that you threw a K in the middle of big
sorry that was really go I'm interested
in what you're saying I'm sorry my
biggest
[Music]
concern my biggest concern I my biggest
concern is going to be how the [ __ ] I
get out of the cornfield I'm probably
going to have to walk 2 to 3 Days To
like a street and then 2 to 3 days
what are you FedEx no you're the [ __ ]
you're the only one you're the only one
that put thought into the fact that I
said you'd be gone for a lot like you'd
be in the middle of a cornfield M thank
you for acknowledging that i' have to
find a street naked 2 3 days later I
have to find a street I'm not going to
have phre I'm not going to have my phone
and I'm not going to have money so I'm
going to need to find a gas station mhm
and like a pay phone maybe call someone
get picked up go home and then the
second I get home my first thought is is
going to be the shower let me check my
butt right God and then after that I
guess your second
thought I think it's included in the
shower what you're thinking okay second
y are icky after I shower I guess it's
just straight to the drawing
board like what the [ __ ] happened to me
where's my family how do I do oh I'm not
going back home to you guys oh no you
could be but like there's so many
possibilities I AR you guys get as
adventurous as I am with the thought you
could be anywhere You' be in
Arkansas you could out of all places I'm
in Arkansas could be you never know I
don't know like we're just playing off a
Vibe here right like us and you me and
you guys what could be happening dinner
party cut the dinner party [ __ ] please
that's what I'm saying I'm literally
going to go home however I have to
boring yeah tell us about that really
boring how are you getting home how's
how you have to I don't think Chris is
putting as much thought as we are get
into it a little bit show some effort
into something other bur okay the first
thing that I would do burping an alien's
face you're so [ __ ] funny I'm lit
going to get up I'm going to wake up and
I'm going to say where the [ __ ] am I and
I'm going to find a different get up
wake up a that a d corio song get up
wake up no get my bread up that's a song
it is yes I would look in all the
directions find whichever one is the
best to go I wouldn't even change path I
would say North and then just go north I
would keep walking keep walking keep
walking keep walking keep walking I'm
bored and then until I find I'm bored by
this you're walking North for days I'm
bored oh well I tried to summon up and
you're like Nick's over here no get us
to merge Us in the
thoughts go
ahead get us into it but I'm bored I'm
just I'm not saying that you have to
change are you bored or tough which one
bored here's we go here's my biggest
problem with this whole conversation
wait before we start this can I say one
thing sure like one thought yeah can we
believe that like there was a some point
on this earth when like brothers and
sisters were like were like [ __ ] and
marrying and [ __ ] okay don't say that is
that not
mindblowing that was a time in our life
I mean in the world not our life F we
literally have to rule it illegal like
get out of town girl oh my God exp the
world here's my biggest thing with
Chris's whole little oh you feel tough
you feel relaxed if you're sitting there
like this and making a couple jokes here
and there you're tough and relaxed but
it's normal to go like
this this go like that and you're like
yay
yay you think that's that's what is that
I feel like I just attacked by a what's
that that was the funniest you've been
in your whole life congratulations the
funniest yep I feel like that's the most
[ __ ] stupid I've looked in my entire
life and you do that every Friday
congratulations we're going to add an
element to the story here are you guys
ready no what three things you get
when you get returned to the cornfield
field what three things would you hope
to have with you a gun get two more what
about a snack lasagna okay um lasagna
who the [ __ ] is he what about a snack
lasagna what about these
things I think lasagna being a snack in
Nick's eyes is so no no I said like a
snack comma lasagna yeah therefore a
snack no no no the snack was a general
topic I wasn't getting into the snack
topic I was throwing up other offers
all right I would [ __ ] run in One
Direction hey baby you light up my world
like no they're not your neighbor you're
in the middle of a corner I'm not going
to go knock on a random House's door
because then I'm like I don't know if
they're also near the alien compound
they could be abductee yeah like I just
got dropped off I don't know where I am
so then I would find a hotel mhm I would
really hope I'm not naked guys oh my God
I would find a hotel shut up just throw
my whole vibe cool I would I would go
into a hotel find like a brochure or a
map of where I am because they always
have those little pamplets at the thing
panflet pamplet panflet who's this guy
name pant flat that's you by the way
okay and somebody says anything wrong
pant
flat you're the world's toughest tough
guy man I know and then I Chris lives
his life like he has one of those I
Carly remotes where he can just like
play a soundtrack that's how you live
your life like oh I'm done with alien
[ __ ] okay we need to get into to the
dinner attire though no we don't okay
what is this
a we're good dude you're crazy dud you
get scared guys like what if it's a
stalker would you rather throw a cinder
block up in the air and then have it
land on your foot or throw a brick at
your best friend as fast as you can I
feel like oh I'd just take the center
block you know have had a brick thrown
at me no it wasn't full brick kicked at
you no it was smashed near him yes that
was it it was smashed in close proximity
and then the brick shards cut cut my
eyeball I can't believe cars have like
serial numbers and why is cereal like a
thing like isn't that like a breakfast
meal why do we make that a whole thing
it's spelled different cereal is spelled
an S yeah I don't like it though it's
like so similar like what the [ __ ] wait
they're spelled differently blue like b
e w no like wait what is the topic blow
your house down like a big old
wolf the Pig goes no wait wait what are
you imagine building your house out of
straw knowing that there's an enemy wolf
that's going to blow your house down I
don't think he knew that I think they
knew he was coming no well it's like
girl where' the third Pig get the brick
let's all correct why did you just say
oh I'm going to go ahead and build it
out of brick I don't get why they
couldn't be roommates if we were the
three little pigs I would have built
mine out of brick that's good Matt would
have been straw cuz he would have been
tough go I don't need a big old house I
can just
do I hate that stores have baskets and
carts
I don't you feel tough when you just
grab the
cart garam out Matt reminds me just a
little worm okay wiggling around causing
problems in the dirt I've never met a
worm causing problems in the dirt guys
what would you do if someone came out of
the sewer all covered in like sewer
juice and it was like like there was
like a big sewer monster just attacking
the city is he tough or is he like he's
really tough oh no Tougher Than Me uhhuh
Oh God I don't know if I don't know what
i' do well like what's the i' I'd say
[ __ ] take a
bath bathe that
off imagine smelling like
sewage God forbid holy [ __ ] it's all for
real jumper cable tell you just how I
feel so wake up all right guys that has
been this week's Friday everyone name
everyone say a word they W everyone say
a word they
love um T hippopotamus follow us on
Instagram at st. triplets stuff you can
find all of our personal Instagrams on
that page and we'll see you guys next
don't follow Nick don't do it like I'm
trying to make something I'm trying to
make something so simple happen I'm
trying to end this video so simple
follow us on Instagram don't follow Nick
I'm going to [ __ ] I'm big tough
guy you miss me yeah you miss me and all
the things that we did we said we going
to travel from the island to Madrid we
had a lot of plans but the
all because of some but it's okay cuz
I'm moving different don't be saying
nothing when I P with other [ __ ] for
my brothers