some cuties for the
Cutie all right guys devastating news
they don't have my asparagus but they do
have Chris zucchini so even though I'm
the head chef tonight I will have a
partner in
crime you can lemon lime juice I've
never seen that that's oh it's just lime
I've never seen
Li but I could chug one of those with
like no sour face you know it's flexing
his no sour face it's lame to say Matt
let's not open
it let's get lemon juice I want to show
my lemon juice Talent getting the lemon
juice I actually can do it no
soure oh
God sugar be I want a pineapple but I
don't want to deal with cutting it yeah
get the pineapple we don't let obstacles
in life challenge us things earn going
to blow out that was insane your what my
kneecaps going to blow out speak up my
kneecaps going to blow
out is that asai Nick guys look at how
healthy the STA triplets are being look
it we're on like a they're prepackaged
but we did find some
asparagus we're trying to be you always
drop the a you just say asparagus I I
dropped a lot
okay I don't I don't know I don't like
speaking so the the shorter I can make
my SE going to be like even by one
letter yeah what color of the Johnny pop
can you reach um probably the purple I
can get wood probably I get you I love
it's called a Johnny yeah what a perfect
name
see this I just got to I feel like I got
to try this awful no wait minions you
see what it says it says freezing to
pleasing where where
what e wait can we get the can we get
the minions no Minions look at them wait
do they have Gumball eyes CH blue why is
why is pleasing the furthest down you
can get freezing to pleasing God that
sucks that's crazy why do I feel like
it's so dark in here I agree maybe cuz I
think I feel like I feel like I'm
falling asleep right
now wake up my fingers smell good why no
one's snipping your fingers I was good
to Hest
no no they don't they smell like an
orange ow your finger yeah peel an
orange an orange people going to be like
oh my God so
ften
[Music]
okay all right salmon hold on can we
reintroduce this style of video what's
up we're about to cook um last time I
cooked burgers this time Matt's cooking
salmon yep basically here are the three
fillets fillet that's what it's called
buddy it's a salmon fillet buddy get uh
who's going to get the scissors I'm not
touching this meat once will you get
this for God knows what reason we have
like this shot thing what is this um I
got that I got a um
Pepsi um package and it was you're
supped put buffalo sauce in this and
make like a buffalo thing like a buffalo
Pepsi can you show them the Pepsi logo
so they know we're not [ __ ] secret
alcoholics it says Pepsi on it and I got
it gifted from Pepsi themselves Thank
You Pepsi Thank You Pepsi how many of
these should I do to show my no sour
face yeah just rip one you're not
supposed to take a shot out of that
that's like a to serve yeah thank you
that's why I have a glass as well oh my
God I'm going to be sick chug chug chug
let's get it no alcohol I like don't
know if this is good no sour face no
sour face no sour face you can't do
it trying to flex the no sour face is
crazy nice it's good I like it wait let
me try I want to do that wait Nick let
me do it do you think I'll make a
sourish expires for next year it smells
like sweaty socks dude it's the fish
it's the fish it's is that no it's for
sure that it's expired lemon it's lemon
smells like lemon
holding your nose is crazy holding your
nose is cheating no sour face holding
your nose is cheating that's a big sour
face chis get a smaller Bowl I don't
know why oh my god dude what do you want
the world's smallest Bowl guys I don't
really know what I'm doing oh my God
okay um you're a terrible head shot are
these good they don't look good right
that's why SC did you check the date
there wasn't a date on them then okay
[ __ ] it let's eat let's try
it can you give this a goo
okay let me go it say generously
generously seasoned coloring dark spots
or filmy white residue then it's a sign
that the salmon has spoiled it's so it's
spil you bought bad salmon Matt I didn't
think that it was bad it was on the
thing that that said fresh cut today how
could it have gone bad is this bad Nick
go to images go to images and see it
like what bad salmon looks like fresh
yeah but this was pre package stuff like
this can't be bad it was in the package
I think we're also just really paranoid
but it smells good like if you sniff it
it smells like goodness it doesn't smell
like if if it was bad Badness I say
Badness if it was bad like we would tell
by scent like we'd be appalled right now
Matt how do you buy bad CH I it smells
good though like not it's bad I would
lick this confident like and be like M
yum like it doesn't smell terrible Chris
this salon's gone bad can you get me the
package so I can Google exactly what it
is so I can see what it looks like yeah
good idea yeah you got a weird you got
hot smoked Alaskan salmon Chris I walked
over there it said no that's what it's
supposed to look like you got like a
different kind of oh [ __ ] yeah then
we're dialed in let's go yeah you got
like red salmon
whatever you want to know what that
means we're going to try something new
it smells great it's it to spoon
it it like spoon it and drop it in yeah
I got that like Chris you got to do like
a
don't worry about me dude guys I'm
scared that the salmon looks bad but now
that you start shy up I feel bad it's
it'll be fine we'll be able to tell by
like when it's cooked I feel like yeah
it could tastes really bad
BR Chris you don't we should do a
cooking show with like a professional
chef and we just help them the whole
time they'd probably want to kill you
I'm like very worried I'm not worried at
all I'm just un like I unfortunately am
starving so if this is like terrible I'm
going to still need dinner
you know what I mean I'm
scared who was
that our oven just saying us a little
song My Brothers my cooking Pals we have
done it we have seasoned the salmon we
have Googled the knowledge we have
overcome obstacles forgetting that I
have to like be entertaining and stuff
because it's like I'm so lost in like am
I okay okay okay I figure this out I
don't know that's the same s the same
asparagus like topping no what's going
on Matt yeah no this is moving you
should have done the oiling before give
me a paper towel on that I'm just going
to take over and be head yeah no
[ __ ] Matt's just nervous that we're
not going to enjoy I know you guys
aren't going to enjoy my food it's okay
Matt shut the [ __ ] up you [ __ ] baby I
know you're not going to like my food
oh yeah guess get that [ __ ] all oiled
[Laughter]
up all right
let's kid comes just kid just comes back
with a Crispy Cream
donut You're such like a Nick if you
were food I think you'd be a donut I'm
[ __ ]
starving that was the funniest thing
you've ever done in our entire YouTube
career I'm so wow this is a lot of
asparagus
asparagus I just said that you're saying
asparagus am I losing my mind like
you're saying I thought you were going
to yell at him for repeating you not I
might not be The Brightest Bulb in in
the in the ceiling you know not the
phrase so therefore but um the salmon
comes cooked in this package so it has
just sat in the oven for 12 minutes and
it was already ready to eat that doesn't
sit well with me though yeah that
doesn't sit that really freaks me out
freaks me out well that means it was
already seasoned as well yeah what's
happening I don't know what I did I
don't know what's going on but this
total and warm it on warm it for 15
minutes in a
275 temperature oven now you got that
thing for 15 minutes at 400° take it out
of the oven now take it out of the oven
hope salmon is already cooked this
doesn't look good at all this looks
frightening Nick I'm really Ser well
guys this was here's the thing this was
supposed to eat it right out of the
package like it's like sushi or
something actually I think no way dude
what the [ __ ] dude I hate when I feel
like completely dumbfounded by something
that someone probably finds so simple at
all I know but Guys Smoke Zone is
already cooked so it needs no further
cooking yeah we understand that guys in
my defense smoked salmon it's already
smoked guys in my smell hello hello in
my
defense um this was the only salmon in
the store at the at the time
um that's all I really have to say I
just can't believe not one of us used
our
brain I was just honestly focused on the
other groceries cuz I thought head chef
Matt had his recipe in me too I thought
Matt for sure knew what he was doing
wait that wasn't a bad bite really yeah
I'm sure it's not bad this [ __ ]
is drowning in oil by the way this
asparagus I've learned let me get some
of that yeah this shit's fine I've
learned the type of salmon that I like
and this is not it I will eat it but
this will be this is a learning
experience for me I can't believe just
not want to stop you and I can now say
that that's just good though this was
our first failure wait that tastes good
Matt I know I'm eating it it's not a
failure it tastes good it actually
tastes great so so Chris you should get
one and eat it off the oven guys we're
good we're going to eat really lemony
yeah you guys put too much lemon yeah
you bought the rock salmon I just like I
know what I like and this is not it it's
good but I know the mistake I made for
the future and we will who are you
trying to prove it to bro like we get it
like you're really trying to sell
yourself on this salmon catastrophe here
you're
good stop worrying about it eat some
[ __ ] asparagus it's actually good cuz
I stepped up and cooked
them all right guys Matt went to cook us
dinner today the camera's already under
you talk you're like all right guys the
you're screaming into the microph shut
that off right no we have to Vlog come
over here and direct yourself to the
lens [ __ ]
weirdo who does that who's a
professional YouTuber for their only job
and stands behind the camera to do an
outro or
transition are you [ __ ] dumb are you
a [ __ ] dumb what's up all right guys
Matt tried to make salmon and he failed
astronomically
Ma just cooked fully cooked salmon we
bought like pre-prepared salmon and then
cooked it wrong and it didn't taste good
and I was scared for my health the
salmon the salmon initially on opening
already looked really like who goes to
the grocery store and and and Matt
didn't check the date on the Sal I did
it's prepackaged and pre-cooked some
sick [ __ ] go into the grocery store
grab that and eat it off the shelf I'm
going to Google search e eating smoked
salmon and I want to see an idiot just
eat raw salmon what is going on she's
cute she looks so sweet yeah she looks
nice she looks so cute actually this one
oh my heart she's I'm just Nick gets
really emotionally attached
to [ __ ] can't guys she Nick she
probably lives a good life no cuz it's
like [ __ ] I'm just really stupid at
least she's smart enough to eat and
enjoy her lunch we're doing it we're
cooking already cooked this girl looks
so sweet
guys I look really stupid no you don't
Matt I tried to cook smoked salmon it
doesn't matter dude what's going on we
Mis Matt misread a label I misread every
label and aisle in the store [ __ ] I
have something we can do for the Vlog
the cream the creamer what the creamer
the the Dr Pepper float did we get the
oros did we did we I didn't you [ __ ]
[ __ ] IDI OT Matt did nothing like why
do we do anything Matt sees Oreos and
they have like churro filling and like
he gasps and it's
like like in the store and I'm like get
them and he goes no like they're
unhealthy I'm like Matt we eat unhealthy
stuff all the time like get them we can
post like content with them just get
them we we TR try for a Tik Tok or Vlog
no one grabbed them so and he gasped
like a [ __ ] he too busy and already
cooked salmon it's okay Matt tonight I'm
a failure
no but tomorrow I'm a winner I'll be a
different man I may have lost in the
dinner
department but what I did win is
knowledge was knowledge
yes another day another mistake which
means another mistake to learn from and
that's and that right there is the
biggest blessing I feel like stupid with
this thing on I know I feel so stupid
we prepared for a fancy salmon dinner
it's I feel really dumb it's okay God
this is like what's the this is like
horrible I feel I'm embarrassed are we
going to put this out there I'm super
embarrassed the we tried to what's the
Kardashian that like cut the Cucumber
like the long way that's how I feel it's
okay I feel like a [ __ ] it's okay I'm
I'm embarrassed that I didn't stop you
so I can only imagine how you feel
buying it and preparing it and putting
it in the oven I knew something was
wrong the whole
time okay that's the thing I knew here's
here's your problem mat tell me you
would have done fabulous if you didn't
buy the wrong salmon that was already
smoking but that's the thing I'm not
joking that was the only salmon in the
in yeah like we went to the salmon
Seafood section and it said salmon it
was right there it was too late at night
and there was none like that were
freshly cut so it was just those on the
shelf and I should have known by the
fact that there was none freshly cut
that I was doing something wrong but I
didn't know and I was hungry yeah then
you had he had a recipe for like a non
prepackaged salmon I had a recipe for
salmon you cook yeah and it was already
cooked this is embarrassing this is a
loss this is a lot for me to handle it
yeah I don't know how often our viewers
go to top golf but they have this thing
called Dirty Dr Pepper and as you know
we're we're big soda drinkers over here
and I think I found their secret recipe
so what we're going to try to do is
recreate the HP golf Dr Pepper all right
so it's basically Dr Pepper and then
coconut put some cubes in there we have
ice cubes we don't have ice cubes that's
so embarrassing that we're filling a
glass with soda with no ice we don't
have ice I know it's just embarrassing
well our fridge is
broken I just squirted the coconut cream
everywhere
oh this is is good
oh I could probably not kidding on a on
a really sad day drink this straight up
you want to know what I think we should
do you would I that's disgusting I
haven't been enjoying Dr Pepper as much
recently that's a lot of creamer yeah
you don't start storying oh I love that
it's bubbly hold on is it bubbling
bubbling I really think this is the
secret recipe too can you get out of
here with that spoon in there you just
told me to stir it with like a
straw it's like milk that looks gross
you can add a little more of this
yeah a little more of that all right
stop judging me both of you shut the
[ __ ] up wait you want what else came
with your
thing look it oh yeah hold on throw this
spoon away throw
it you missed the sink go put it in the
sink now and wipe the
counter wipe the counter clean counter
it's clean I'm promised there's you're
an idiot move M I'm promise nice to meet
you promise you are dumb you're also
using that
wrong you're blowing all over a drink
I'm supposed to what sitp from like no
no that's what I was thinking I'm try to
kill the foam this is take a SI get the
[ __ ] you give me a second I'm explaining
something I'm not kidding guys like dead
serious this is exactly how the one at
Top Golf looks I really think that this
is the secret re we got a winner I feel
like planked in right
now okay let's try it sit down can I get
a photo you to
yeah say salmon on three
salmon did he must like it yeah he's got
it that's that [ __ ] if that was ice cold
I'm I'm I'm a [ __ ] I'm a fiend for
that [ __ ]
okay yeah you taste that coconut
cream can't that's a good recipe right
there that's that's a good one
it tastes like just like
samoas that's what it is don't say it
like that s'mores SAS the Girl Scout
cookie brain dead [ __ ] I'm not talking
about s'mores I'm talking about the
coconut cookie what is that Samoa the
girl s yeah saying it like that's lame
though what you call them
samoas oh sorry coconut Delights that's
what they are I don't even know what
they are that's good this is
not only a lesson for us but a lesson
for you don't cook smoke Sal no no when
you get a recipe
looki bu the right sometimes everything
in your life might look like it's going
the right way right until the very end
you can't let that breakdown at the end
ruin the rest of your life you got to
turn from there yeah like what if we
just get dinner tonight and be hungry no
we're going to persevere and do
everything might even if you're on the
most perfect path path ever there's a
giant boulder in the way that's still
the perfect path you just have to push
it out of the way that's a beautiful
statement thank you yeah the other the
alternate path could have a bigger bould
I could have taken this L of this salmon
and I could have been like wow I'm so
embarrassed Nick don't even put that on
the internet but you're sh you're
sharing it with that I am cuz not only
do you just the internet's not perfect
either why top of nobody shares their
mistakes I don't know it's okay Matt I
don't know tonight was a loss for me and
St we're all right rock on see it's okay
see you next time see you next time bye
cheer the [ __ ] up I'm fine bye I'm
fine like I'm with that crazy Muppet you
remember me that orange dude like
[Music]