say cheese
sounds like he's singing at a cathedral
today all right
wait wait wait wait wait I need to hear
more about this cookie they were talking
about yesterday yeah Laura got me this
the other day
bro 10 out of 10 cookie
oh get that bite yes looks like I've got
that little ring like that
cinnamon sugar flavor I love oh
really chewy still it does look so soft
actually it is wrong it's kind of like a
h
we need to get rid of that mirror I just
saw myself in it it was like so scared
like that was so crazy I just like to
Vlog you and I'm like right there that
was crazy I just like pop party
we're going from L.A to Palm Springs so
let's take you with us Atlanta pumps
there's no PS
um what was it gonna say oh yeah and
yeah let us get furniture for our house
because look at look at how cute it is
over here
it's like very minimal it's
um our house is screaming furnish me
Furniture say it again me and Nick are
at the dentist Matt's right next door
getting his teeth fixed and stuff and
then we're leaving to Forever Springs
Beach getaway I just want to punch
myself
rings and there's like not one beach
Chris
get off his case okay we're gonna
[ __ ] YouTube vloggers but I have to
get off his case so give me a minute
this is Carl's Jr and at the beginning
of it
go with him
I started trying to Vlog Chris and he
told me to get off his case that's why I
saw him vlogging he was all up in my
meat and [ __ ] about it I opened the
store immediate blue light you wouldn't
believe it blue light watch is it a UFO
or something
[Music]
couldn't wore me on the step down
what the [ __ ] Terminator Judgment Day
this is what day Nick lives in every day
he just judges people that's crazy
thank you
[Applause]
poker
poker table poker table
you got a three let's see it what the
[ __ ] I think they don't got sand already
on the shuffleboard we need that oh wow
this is the first shelf of what I've
seen with the scooper though
wow you're pathetic
yes
damn y'all suck it's very like slanting
yeah okay I'll do a first try first try
and you owe me a million dollars a
million shut up [ __ ] he said later
there's some smooth
like no one's talking to you yet hold on
go Matt's phone and Japanese go
yeah okay first try told you what were
you saying that now that it's your time
to speak he said either later today
we have to let some real creepy old dude
here to fix the grill because he needed
like an extra part and it's leaking and
he said that he hopes it's no bother
I was like
um he said it was a creepy old dude why
not creepy you just said it's like an
old guy white long hair he's gonna come
and fix the girl up tomorrow morning or
later today I have no idea oh God okay
let's play basketball someone reported
me pop a shot
arcade I'm getting ready for a tour
oh wow you're terrible
[Music]
I mean we don't
you're dead
hello your dog [ __ ]
you're just [ __ ] rematch
what are you doing kid just impressing
the world
okay ready ready
oh my God I gotta hit that shot oh my
balls crazy each other that's crazy
okay good job Chris yeah you see me
perfectly set up for later honey tell
them for those of you that don't know I
bought a wizard mask and it's some
creepy older with white long hair so I
just set up that good joke and I'm Gonna
Stand by the grill later and pretend I'm
fixing it with my ass crack out and do
the whole way ew dude
ew don't put your ass crack up oh my God
and welcome sweetest fish Minnie
welcome to Matthew's
I'm trying to think about I'm trying to
think of a creative name hold on give me
a second Matthew's mocktails
what I'm gonna make I'm gonna make
everyone some drinks I'm not drinking it
where's the cuppies no I don't want
those cups I want see-through cups so
you can see the creation Strawberry
Shortcake bars Strawberry Shortcake
because things are actually unbelievable
eat
eat eat
what do you say okay oh I gotta eat I
love doing that okay what did I do in
Denny's once I was like I don't know
oh you're taking a bite
Maddie
I don't know no one's gonna drink this
disgust
I'm really afraid Matt
First Steps first
don't waste it I'm not wasting your
attention anymore
[Music]
just use two let's make it easier no
don't trust the process and that's the
problem it has a problem with most
things in life everyone wants things
that are rushed and overdone get out of
the way
foreign
just get a cup of ice fill a cup of ice
Matt you don't need to open it that way
[Music]
and that's why I'm here the shock Factor
the shock Factor
Perfecto
Rebecca was insane can you see where I'm
going with this oh
no I'm kind of interested now I didn't
see all this hold on
wait Max
wow hold on hold on
oh okay tough guy
terrible
oh I gotta get cinematographer come on
come on
yes
yes yes Matt this is insane right
oh oh I love the new color that we're
getting with this
yes Matt hold on hold on you're kind of
going crazy right now I'm not gonna lie
we got the drag or no not that one
ah the garnishes
yes Matt the blue lagoons oh
oh yeah good wait Matt you should log me
in Chris try it if you want to try your
creation before anyone else tries it
um you should try it first as the
Creator Chris don't take a sip yet come
on Matt these have to have to Maddie and
Laura because the presentation's the
best so I got it okay
um
oh it's actually delish Perfecto nice
wait let me try one I'm gonna go give my
presents oh they fell anyway whatever
the blue lagoons enjoy it
Chris what are your actual thoughts it's
actually not that bad but I'd rather
just like have both drinks separate you
know what I mean let's go that way oh my
God a lizard it's gay it's gay as [ __ ]
gay lizard okay have we played Bocce
before on a vlog I don't know have we um
if we have you I know what's up if we
haven't basically you throw this little
white ball and then the two players
which is gonna be me and Matt have to
try and throw these other balls and see
you can get the big old balls the big
balls just you can get huge balls all
right the Big Balls the gigantic balls
to see who can get closer the massive
balls just even get closer to the white
one so the little ball so I'm blue and
red I'm gonna be green and yellow
I'm blue and red normally
I'm blue in your head it must look so
good in the sun right now you do
see the white ball everyone
nice pathetic throw from Matt but or do
you want to go you start fighting the
ball you know that was weird why'd we
play in the direction of the [ __ ] so
I'm gonna go this way it's an added
obstacle see ya
good Nick
clothes first
oh
it definitely does but
wow Matt
would have been good but it wasn't Nick
going with the Slow Roll technique here
off the wall
I think next in the lead oh
oh Matt Knox Nick right next to it bocce
Slow Roll technique again coming from
Nick
I'm trying to get Matt's way at this
point oh okay good technique whoa Matt
comes in with some heat oh my God and it
worked out oh he's requesting me to move
see what he does here ladies and
gentlemen Slow Roll technique once again
oh oh oh and he can't just creep oh and
he creeps into the lead
it's all comes down to this
oh my God
get [ __ ] Max
good game you lost yeah shut up loser I
win with a big ball take this neck oh
gigantic balls look at that lying Roar
no way there's like a lion slide like I
feel like I'm 12 but in the best way
ever
not him holding his nose what are we for
yes how does it feel
S I know I made fun of you
that's really an uncomforting feeling
three sad lonely disgusting Swedish Fish
sit at the bottom of this cup
what a shame but the drinks were good so
hit this golf ball like really hard or
something
come on
who want me to document you do things
wrong
God it's crazy how far they travel Who
golf balls oh my God I have an idea I'm
gonna start carrying bouncy balls
everywhere I go and just hitting them as
hard as I can and just seeing where they
end up
you're insane
imagine when in the hole would you be oh
my God Nick did you see how close I just
got
if I had to put there it's like a what
that was very mediocre no it wasn't Nick
look how close it was you idiot
let's get it in
thank you all right I really want to do
some fun stuff
you can only do some one step take this
oh he got a corn toss oh brother this
kid he's a joke
[ __ ]
awful pathetic
that actually went in right
after that second one go in oh that's
how you feel you think you're the man or
something [ __ ] sit down be humble
everyone Matt thinks he the man
uh y'all hammocking
Chris spin them spin them spin them
Chris I will [ __ ] kill you
what s-p-o-p do you need to spell go
down the slide I dare you go down the
slide in those jean shorts Nick come on
I would give you so much money if you
end up not going on the slide in jean
shorts look at those shorts put them on
no
I already dried off 10 bucks if you go
in there right now 10 bucks I need a lot
more than that come on for the Vlog okay
for the Vine
no you do for the vine you jump in I
ain't gonna do it do it for the vibe I
ain't gonna do it do it for the Vine I'm
not gonna do it do it for the vine your
whole fit and I'll give you 500 actually
um no okay then Max 100
Max 100 light
50. how much are you Chris stop lowering
it 50 bucks no okay 100 bucks it's 500
on the record if I jumped in the whole
fit
if you guys both go in I'll give you 200
each 200 is a lot of money like that's a
lot of money I don't know if I'm willing
to give that
you just placed that bet no 100 each if
you jump in can I take one article of
clothing off maybe
if I can take off one article of
clothing I'll go in for 100 bucks
oh
someone's unlacing their pants
Matt 100 bucks on the line if you jump
in like that
150.
three million dollars
I'm kidding
[Laughter]
Matt take this okay
oh my God
you turn the slide on how prank over
there
Nick
what am I doing
what what what thing
I don't know what the [ __ ] you're
talking about idiot
this
[ __ ] he's stupid
wait lay back down let's rub each
other's feet what
I don't know how to say it in another
language
okay this is really cute Vibes no yeah I
think so like give me the camera I'll
show them you no yes no we're laying
together no rub my feet for the Vlog
oh
how many people Wish You Were Me Right
Now
I bet you all of them
but you're none of them everyone
[Laughter]
swimming swimming swimming
yummy yummy Swedish yummy yummy Swedish
say super duper yummy sweetie super
yummy yummy sweet yes fish I wonder how
many sweetest fish you could eat in like
one go me yeah how many you think you
got I could eat a lot but I'd [ __ ] bad
what about um stop looking over my
shoulder I'm not I didn't look on your
shoulder one time I thought I saw like
the wind blow something behind you
that's why I was confused baby if you
like it how many Swedish fish do you
think you could fit like in your mouth
at one go and like eat them all
eat them all different like chew like do
you know when you have like a big glob
of gum yeah
at least 25 25 and eat them you're
insane like Extra Gum Oh I thought you
were saying like extra pieces of the
brand no probably like
a double trouble I was gonna say Trident
is that one
oh look at like this silhouette of my
foot behind you looks so gross
this is eight sweetest fish in my mouth
already and I can talk no way do more do
more but I could fit a lot do more no do
more no do like eight
oh my God
Nick
exactly
it's actually a stranger I think it's
the guy that means the grill
should I talk to him well I'll get your
ankle
he is scary
let me warn them
Nick
what the [ __ ] is that go say hi to him
what
I don't mean to be rude but he's really
scared
oh my God I guess insanely white hair
like long white hair
he looks like he watches hey what looks
like he works for the Hunger Games it's
President Snow
what was I saying obviously this fish
could you paint your mouth no oh my God
Nick look at that guy
stop
oh my God look at that
how do you get in here
I don't like how easily he did sneak up
on him yeah we almost foreshadowed it
okay I know
what do you think he's doing
something to grow
Let It Go say hi no go hey it's the
grill man
I'd go say hi if you went with me
he like actually looks like a cartoon he
looks like a cartoon let's get next
offer him a sweetest fish
he's a mine
okay I gotta chill baby
oh God
stop it
okay you're done you're done he can't
even see
he'd usually think so
you never know I'm gonna say hi
hold it at your waist no
come with me
did you leave
Nick I just want to see how long he's
gonna be here it's a [ __ ] random ass
dude
I honestly don't care
looks like Santa maybe he'll bring us
gifts
[Music]
[ __ ] [ __ ] it's a mask it's a
Wizarding because where did you guys get
this did I do good yeah you did great I
thought I had no idea you should have
ran at me or something I thought you
knew I was I had no idea that that was
you mad oh my God
you actually had no idea no clue I just
couldn't believe how long that guy's
hair was
that was good I told Maddie too I like
warned her like oh someone's here I'm so
surprised you did like clanging
everything yes that was great I had no
idea I honestly had no idea when did you
guys plan that I saw us in the store I
was like [ __ ] I'm gonna get it we
bought it at TV
earlier was really special like earlier
when we first got here like it's on
camera Nick the guy was showing us
around yes yeah and Laura he actually
told Laura something was gonna happen
with the girl yeah some guy has to
actually come and fix the girl tomorrow
morning I thought for sure you knew when
I was over there that you you knew it
was Matt no clue the black hoodie I
changed into jeans literally no clue I
was like this hair is is crazy I did
just think it was some crazy old man
there it is I'm so I need to see that
one I need to see like you guys
recording me do crazy I almost know how
I looked doing that well I didn't see
the face once I just saw all this hair
yeah I was crazy
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
that we did