-Who doesn't love
Anne Hathaway?
Thank you for coming.
-That's very nice.
But you know when you have
a moment, you're just like,
"Oh, I'm gonna remember
that forever."
Thank you so much for that.
-There you go. It just happened.
Come on. The Roots.
-Thank you. Hi, everybody.
-Thank you for playing
"Reverse Charades" with me.
You're a great partner.
-Thank you.
-I mean, are you are you
competitive when you play games?
Do you play games at home?
-Oh, I don't mean to be.
-I know. Me neither.
-I don't mean to me.
But then you saw her over there,
I was like, "No, it's just
a nice, friendly game."
And then the last, I'm like,
"But the points are on.
Like, it's on."
-Let's go. I want to win this.
-Something takes over.
I'm less competitive now.
-Why?
-Kids.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-I think maybe being competitive
is genetic,
because my kids are, like --
They're competitive, too.
And it turns out
motherhood has softened me,
and I like to watch them win.
-Yeah.
-Aww.
-My kids are
very competitive, too.
Well, my one daughter is.
Yeah. Yeah.
The other one doesn't
really care.
She's like, "That's fun.
It's all good."
But the other one
really wants to win.
And I don't throw the games.
You know, I go --
I really -- And I play for --
I play for money, too.
Are you -- Is there a party game
that you're especially good at?
-Es-- No.
I mean, you know,
I was playing a game --
We play a lot of Pokémon
and we play a lot of Trouble
and Sorry!
But there is a game --
I was working last week
and I was on set, and we were
just passing the time.
And have you seen
that movie trivia game
where it's cards and they --
and it just asks you questions?
-Oh, yeah, I've seen --
Like, they have a bunch of
quizzes, like sports and movies.
-And I was just having one
of those, like,
runs where I couldn't miss.
Like, I just knew and I was,
like, surprising myself.
-Well, you know your stuff.
You know movies.
-I didn't -- I mean,
apparently, I do.
And then I got to
this one question,
and they were like, "Oh, okay.
So, uh, junior executive
assistant, 'Devil Wears Prada.'"
I'm just like, "Emily Blunt."
And they were like, "No."
And it wasn't her. It was me.
So...
I was gonna say, "Wait..."
-But I was genuinely confused.
I'm like, "Wait, but it is her."
It is.
-"That was me, but I'm the..."
That's wild.
See, when it comes to you --
-Yeah, so...
-Do you ever -- Do you
kind of do a project
and then you kind of block it
out of your mind or no?
You just --
It just so happens you...
-I don't know.
I'm not huge on looking back.
It is kind of funny
when -- Like, because,
you know, I was in this movie
when I was 17 years old
called "The Princess Diaries."
-Yeah.
[ Cheers and applause ]
-Have you seen it?
-I watch you all the time.
To this day, I watch you
all the time.
-Really?
-My family loves you.
-It must be your girls.
-We love you.
Yeah, they love you so much.
-I love that it's become kind of
one of those family touchstones.
So, anyway, people quote it
to me all the time,
and I don't know what
they're talking about.
I haven't seen it in a minute.
-But "Devil Wears Prada" --
I recently saw a photo
of you and Anna Wintour.
You made your kind of Broadway
debut together in
"Gutenberg! The Musical!"
You guys stood up.
-There she is.
-Did the crowd go nuts?
-So, they --
So, by the way, I have to say,
that's Josh Gad and that's
Andrew Rannells.
They're both dear friends.
And they're so -- They were
so brilliant in the show.
It was really next level.
And at the end of the show, they
invite two people up onstage.
And, so,
they said my name first,
and the audience had
a very nice reaction.
And then they said Anna's name,
and it was like rock star.
-Really?
-Yeah, rock star.
-Because you don't
really see Anna do many things
that are outside of her --
-Wear a trucker hat.
-Yes, exactly.
You'd never see Anna Wintour,
from Vogue, wear a trucker hat.
That's correct, yeah.
But everyone just went nuts.
She's also a New York icon.
-Oh, yeah.
-So I think
if she shows up at a pizzeria --
-Yeah, she's a New York icon.
She's a worldwide icon.
-She's a worldwide --
She's everything.
Is she fun
to share the stage with?
-Yeah. Yeah, really, really fun.
And just -- She's been
incredibly sweet to me,
and I'm very -- I'm just very
grateful for our relationship.
-She's so cool.
-So cool.
-Do you get nervous around --
I get a little nervous --
-I absolutely do.
-You do?
Now, I have less to lose,
because I'm never going to be
on the cover of Vogue,
so I have nothing
to worry about.
But she likes me, and we've been
friends for a long time,
so I kind of -- I'm comfy around
her, so I can --
-I don't mean to --
I try to keep it comfy.
I try to keep it cozy.
But inside, my heart is --
I just respect her so much.
-Yeah.
-But I feel very comfortable
around you.
-Yeah, good. You should be.
You should be.
I'm your bud. No, please.
I totally -- I got the respect
and also the dig
at the same time.
So it was perfect.
-That's how well I know you.
That's how cozy I am.
-Yeah, exactly.
You know, I saw you,
by the way --
I was going to say
on Broadway, but it wasn't.
It was Shakespeare in the Park.
-You were there?
-Yeah, I came to see you.
Absolutely.
I'm a big fan. Yeah.
You did that.
-I feel really bad about
the dig now.
-You better keep digging me.
Are you kidding me?
I have -- Please, if you don't
laugh yourself, then come on.
I saw you,
and it was at the...
-"Twelfth Night"
at the Delacorte Theater.
-...Delacorte Theater.
-Yeah.
-You were amazing.
Do you get nervous?
Does anything go wrong?
Nothing went wrong
when I saw you.
-Nothing went wrong?
Thank goodness.
-No, you were perfect.
-Well, because --
So, the Delacorte Theater
is an outdoor theater in
Central Park.
And, so --
-And you're doing Shakespeare.
-Doing Shakespeare.
And it rained
almost every night.
And, so,
but it's kind of amazing,
because every night,
the last line of the show,
which we actually sang, was for
the rain, it raineth every day.
And so the audience,
at that moment,
always burst out laughing.
And the whole show was
so joyful.
I had such a wonderful time.
But one night, something --
I don't know if it went wrong,
but something happened.
And, so, there's this scene.
My character, Viola --
she comes onto the stage.
And I knew
that the line was funny,
but I couldn't figure out
how to make it funny.
So every night, I was
just trying something,
just anything I could think of.
And I was,
you know, go out there,
audience wouldn't laugh,
and I was like, "Tomorrow."
And then, one night, I went out
there and I said the line,
and just the house went down.
-You killed it.
-Killed.
And I was like, "Oh, I found it.
This is such a good feeling."
And I just like --
And so then, of course,
I leaned into it,
because you do.
And so I lean into it
and I'm just --
The audience
is losing their minds.
I look under the wings,
the cast is losing their minds.
I'm high-fiving myself
in my head.
I'm just like, "I've arrived.
This is happening."
And I get offstage
and I'm just like, "Well..."
And they go,
"Did you see the raccoons?"
And I'm like, "The...what?"
And then they just go,
"Behind you.
As soon as you came onstage,
a family of raccoons came out.
They were so cute.
Couldn't focus on the scene
because the raccoons
were so cute."
So I was like, "Well, actually,
high five to the raccoons."
-See?
You got to work with everybody.
-Absolutely.
-You got to work --
You play well with others.
Let's talk about
"The Idea of You."
Oh, my gosh, buddy.
The trailer alone has
gotten over 125 million views.
-Yeah.
-It crushed, broke the record.
Most-watched trailer of
any streaming movie in history.
Can we set up what
the movie's about?
-Oh, sure, sure.
The story is
about Solène Marchand,
who is a woman
who lives in Silver Lake.
She's a gallery owner.
She's a mom and she's got
this really wonderful life.
And she unexpectedly meets
the lead singer
of the biggest boy band
in the world,
a 24-year-old young man
named Hayes Campbell.
-Yeah.
-And he thinks
she's kind of great.
And so the story is about
how they fall in love.
-Yeah. Because you're just a mom
and you're chaperoning
this thing
and you go to this thing
and then you see this boy band.
-I love hearing you describe
my movie.
"Just a mom in this thing."
-Yeah, you're a mom
in this thing.
That's how I described it.
Mom is chaperoning,
like, a Coachella type of thing,
like a giant outdoor festival
thing, and the biggest boy band
in the world,
and then the lead singer --
-Oh, yes, so, my daughter
is off watching St. Vincent.
Because she doesn't like
the boy band anymore.
She liked them in seventh grade.
But, anyway,
I have a backstage pass,
so I'm a -- all-access thing.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Somebody tells me
where the trailers are.
I go and I walk
into the wrong trailer.
-Yeah. And the rest is --
High jinks ensues.
But remind me of the actor who
plays the lead singer.
-Nick Galitzine.
-Oh, man,
you guys have great chemistry.
Did you know when he
was auditioning?
You go, "Oh, this the guy."
-Oh, yeah.
Yeah, no, as soon as he --
I actually burst out laughing
when he walked in, because --
Has anybody here read the book?
-No, we don't read.
-Well, you should.
It's fabulous.
-This is "The Tonight Show."
Yeah, you want to go over
to Stephen --
You want to go to
Stephen Colbert
if you want to get
people that read books.
We don't read.
Lame!
-Well, you have an awesome book
in store for you.
It's written by --
-Lame-O!
We do Audible here.
We do that. Does that count?
-I think it's time for you to --
to get me back.
-Yeah, I know.
-Okay, so --
-It's based on this book.
-What's a book?
-Yeah.
No, too late. No, too late.
But this is based
on the big best-selling book.
-Well, the book does have
a fan following somewhere.
And -- Anyway, and I think
the book is incredible.
And Hayes Campbell is so
beautifully written in the book,
and so we knew that we just
really needed to find
someone really special.
And he walked in, yeah,
and I just thought,
"Oh, that's Hayes Campbell."
And that was
almost two years ago.
And now Nick and I
have become really good friends,
and, yeah, it's opened up
in this beautiful way.
-It's really great.
I want to show everyone a clip.
Here's Anne Hathaway
in "The Idea of You."
Take a look.
-Hi again.
-Are you a part
of that ASMR community
that gets off on listening
to people pee?
-No, I wasn't --
-Because I don't think you can
just go around assuming --
-It's actually my trailer.
-What?
-It's not literally mine.
You know, I don't own it.
-This is your trailer?
-Yeah, I'm in the band.
We're performing on
the main stage.
You know, I'm Hayes Campbell.
-August Moon?
-Yeah.
-Well, I absolutely know
who you are.
Um, anyway...I'll...
-Yeah. Come on.
You know how to do it.
Anne Hathaway, everybody.
"The Idea of You"
begins streaming
on Prime Video this Thursday.
We'll be right back
with Melanie Lynskey.
Stick around, everybody.