hold let me get naked real quick wait
what miss me and all the things that we
did we said we going to travel from the
island to Madrid we had a lot of plans
but they all
dis who's
screaming um I saw some like legit
[ __ ] Zombie Walk that way it's that
guy right with the two bags he looks
like a zombie he was like throwing [ __ ]
in front of the bank earlier you sh man
shut your
door show me what you got is that what
he's
saying it sounds like he's saying show
me what you shut up and I can maybe hear
I know that's what I want
to well at least he's heading home it
sounds like someone's leaving an army
outside like St right right we should
all hide under a traffic G and like use
our TIY toes to like travel somewhere a
[ __ ] Toy Story yeah like real sneaky
kid the traffic goes out to be gigant
you know I saw some guy do that to steal
his neighbor's mail with a ring
camera has to be a little kid or a dwarf
all right guys welcome back too triplets
car videos today is Friday and today we
are going to be filming a Anonymous
confessions I think part 4 but I'm not
too shabby just kidding saw this on tour
and I was like hm I should probably
bring this into a car video complex
posted Bigfoot sighting in Colorado
question mark with eyes with eyes
there's no question mark I made it up
and then is it for real 44 second long
video just squatt it
down I can't I can't see [ __ ]
Matt
we got him hold on we got him hold on we
caught him hold
on and there it is not blurred not shaky
nice camo for bigfoot there he is we
caught him no no no we caught him he
looks just like the movies like that's
what big puts big put big fo that's what
Bigfoot's supposed to look like I don't
think we got still we got another see if
that was me I'm getting a Tran Dart
immediately with a [ __ ] blow tube and
I'm going to go and then [ __ ] in
Bigfoot's neck and he's like obviously
not face he's Bigfoot he needs way more
energy he needs way more Tran you
getting the TR I'd have my Bigfoot kit
ready to rock and then I'd
go bing bing bing bang boom bang boom
Bigfoot and then obviously where do you
have to hit him at you don't have a TR
where do you have to hit Bigfoot the
feet the without I get him right with a
like in zootopia when the big [ __ ] lamb
comes in with a blueberry gun do me a
favor
yeah and then I get go like
this why just clear that clear that my
throat's for normal right now go I have
nothing in my throat I'm just probably
some
honey from being fine to that is crazy
bang bang bang in his foot ding ding
ding I'm want to get one right this P me
playing an arcade game it's like pinball
and then you'd go down and then I'd go
and I don't I don't like want to kidnap
them I don't want anything to do it DNA
swab put it in a tube put it in my
Bigfoot kit that and then I what are you
going to cross check the DNA and then I
would cast a form of his foot whichever
one's bigger it's a Tran Dart it's not a
[ __ ] bullet dude he's going to be
he's going to wake up in like 45 minutes
it's a 25 a 20 24hour trank
oh sorry sorry sorry I forgot I forgot
it was right there oh no sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry a 24-hour trank Dart
and then I'm going to take a cast of his
foot they're already [ __ ] I'm going
to take a cast of his foot and I'm going
to put it in my truck and then I'm going
to drive away the one oh selfie with him
obviously and open up his eyes then make
him smile and go cheese selfie and go
smile all right we're going to be
jumping right into the anonymous
confession
that my I had a crush on my step cousin
stop what what's was the [ __ ] incest
I talked about this last week what
happened I had a crush on my step cousin
what so I went to their house like
normally and it was cold and I said that
so that when we went upstairs to grab a
hoodie from his closet he gave it to me
and that's when it started this is all
fake all fake I can't I literally can't
hear about incest right now
like I cannot do it I can't do it I
actually refuse to hear about this [ __ ]
right I like this big OB session next
I'm not listening to a girl willingly
flirt with her cousin let me say the
rest of it's not take it out just
pretend it's like not cousins that's
what she's doing Nick I'm sick to my
stomach I had this really big obsession
with him and the worst part about about
this thing was I live on the other side
of the world that is not the worst part
at all definitely that's
honestly scenario at the end I realized
that I didn't I didn't ever really like
him I just made myself I just made
myself for some reason because he gave
me his hoodie oh my God this girl either
that's actually like this girl either
like really [ __ ] stupid or like whoa
Matt a little bit I'm being honest she's
really stupid or 9 years
old hey get a [ __ ] muin X before
speaking to me gross [ __ ] you look like
the muin X green annoying dude that's
okay that [ __ ] is in your throat right
now so I wouldn't be saying too much
don't tell me who's in my throat and who
isn't what he missed the lot what is
going on it in Focus I wouldn't come
back in here if it wasn't Nick we've
been doing this oh you are just
King when I was five some girl pinned me
down in a tent at skl and the tent in
the t skl hold on let's decipher that
and the tent is the tent that everyone
went to fart in and she started [ __ ]
scratching at my face like a
furry what she got stuck in the fart you
got stuck in you got pinned down in the
fart tent I can hear them make fun of
her you stink when I was in kindergarten
I went to school where we changed
classes to do different activities like
music and art Etc the one time we had to
switch classes I was with the mean
teacher and I really had to go to the
bathroom so I asked the teacher if I
could go and she told me no because we
had recess and I should have gone then
so I sat in my chair for a while and had
to go really really bad that I ended up
peeing in my chair safe to say I told my
mom wait how'd she get out of it she
pissed her draws in front of the whole
class class and then just went to the
bathroom wait waited cuz recess was
going to happen Okay safe to say I told
my mom and never had to go to that class
again absolutely girl says they have to
use the bathroom and it gets denied the
privilege of we've said this in a video
and it went viral years ago well it's
true it's like yeah if you ask the
teacher hey can I use the bathroom and
they say no get up and go to the
bathroom and then say I was going to
[ __ ] myself or I was going to piss
myself and then and if the teacher has
something to say say go to the principal
and literally say Miss [ __ ] goofball
wouldn't let me use the restro and then
guess what she's literally going to get
fired or piss and [ __ ] yourself on the
ground literally if you piss yourself in
a classroom and then say hey Miss dummy
[ __ ] didn't let me use the bathroom she
should be arrested I mean she should be
no if you piss or Shake Yourself that's
kind of a boss move cuz it forces your
teacher in a way more uncomfortable
position correct one time I threatened
my chemistry teacher I if I was back in
I school I just whip my [ __ ] out and
piss on the floor don't use the word
[ __ ] I hate that with my [ __ ] out and
piss on
the I feel like I'm drifting apart from
my best friend and I feel like a bad
friend cuz my mom hates her and takes a
toll on the friendship and I feel
horrible about the whole situation did
you say horrible horrible like the
gummies he tried to
throw it depends whether or it depends
what the reasoning is on your mom hating
her if your mom hates your friend most
likely she's a [ __ ] unless your mom's
[ __ ] next I like my friend's dad but my
friend found out and we're not friends
anymore you like him like like has a
crush on her friend's dad I think so
that's so weird dude next one how the
[ __ ] can people do that [ __ ] oh my God
what would you do if the shorty had the
apple bottom jeans and the boots with
the fur okayy had them Apple Bottom
Jeans whenever you're ready I'm 99% sure
I always forget how many trees are
really in this world until I'm outside L
night not really confession but story
time I guess story time I guess there
was a group I hate saying I guess like
you know it's a story time yeah delete I
guess from your
keyboards please there was a group of us
delete them there was a group of us that
were friends I'm going to put their
names as initials only me a E H and M so
first M gave her H her Snapchat and
number and they flirted and talked I
don't know this then and then only okay
[ __ ] I can't read hor Cod a a said to M
A said to M that M likes folded tables
and then B said not at my dinner party
what I made that up that's good I can
tell oh my God here we go when I was 6
years old my parents got this brand new
TV for their bedroom and my me and my
sisters weren't allowed to use it so 3
years later or something like that when
my parents weren't home one day I went
into their room and I started walking on
the bed disclaimer I'm really really
really clumsy I knocked over their lamp
and it broke the TV I ran out of the
room when my parents came home and asked
me who did it I said it was my sister
I love that since they already knew she
goes into their room to watch the TV I
love it they believed me and grounded
her for 2 months damn what does your
sister like can't defend herself none of
my parents know to this day that it was
me what why didn't your sister say [ __ ]
I would have tattled so hard I would
have tattled crazy oh my God I would
have said no whatever my sister's being
an idiot mom and dad I didn't do that
[ __ ] she literally broke the [ __ ]
thing sister's being an idiot mom and
dad I would have literally never let
that [ __ ] slide your sister's a real one
actually yeah no like you owe her your
life absolutely your life is crazy shut
up Matt I was little maybe in the second
or third grade we had two playgrounds
one for the kindergarten one for the
kindergarteners and one for the first
Raiders they had had just gone to recess
and was playing on the monkey bars
before lunch my teacher told us my
teacher told us we had to test it so we
went to jump from the second bar and
everything kids literally circled around
me and my teacher came to the school
with my little cousin my test that day
also in kindergarten I had one of the
kids push me so dramatically I fell and
gave me goldfish and make the kids push
me say what's going on I have no idea I
have no clue I feel like I just heard
like read like a [ __ ] do you know the
Books of the magic treeh house like I
feel like that was a Magic Treehouse
event like that was like insane no idea
what's the night of the playground fall
I went down the ladder and then fell
down got gfish with third cousin
McDonald's day off no
test I really love the reflective tape
ripped in front of all my friends in my
crush it was so embarrassing like don't
confess something like that that's
boring I want to hear like some crazy
[ __ ] you remind me of toad like Blue
Toad from Mario you remind me of an
idiot and I'm what are you being so
hurtful for not Matt is so hurtful guys
we're just saying things that remind
each other of each other no you remind
me of Blue Toad when he's like like now
toad doesn't say anything and then is
there a cartoon character that burps and
smells bad when I was a baby I used to
eat why are you saying everything weird
neck baby when I was a baby I was
laughing dummy [ __ ] when I was a baby I
used to
eat when I was a baby when I was a baby
I when I was a baby I had re's and
headbo I'm next reading all these when I
was a baby I used to eat cigarettes that
I found on the beach oh my God what's
wrong with you stop she a baby Chris
okay but still don't eat cigarettes a
baby that baby shouldn't be eating
cigarettes where's your mom
Corral your little kid into the the
beach tent and then I get that Chris but
you're calling the baby stupid for
eating cigarettes like they know better
mat I knew not to eat [ __ ] when I was
[ __ ] 6 months I knew not to Matt was
e what you were cigar someone I
accidentally killed my sister's pet bird
it was let out of the house one day and
I had no idea until my sister came up to
me asking to help me find it we were
searching around the house and I took a
step backwards and heard a
loud I looked down in the bird we were
looking for she was so mad at me I felt
so bad rest in peace bubbles that's not
your fault bubbles bubbles should have
flown away if your sister was a good
caretaker of her bird it would have been
in the cage and she would have been
looking for it her fault no it's
bubble's fault no it's not Matt saying
bubbles should have flown I agree what
is Bubbles doing just getting stomped on
any other bird would have flew you're
bird get some High Ground correct get to
a a bookshelf or something someone said
they used to take their clothes out of
their laundry and before putting them in
the dryer would squeeze the water out
into their mouth that's actually the
most disturbing thing I've ever heard in
my life why I mean it's clean no it's
not it's soap Matt it's chemicals soap
is clean [ __ ] oh yeah go eat a bar of
soap then you hungry [ __ ] what are you
going to eat Dove soap cuz it's soap no
I'm just saying at least it's clean it's
not clean it's chemicals Matt it's
cleaning the clothes it's clean but it's
not helpful it's not clean water you're
not ringing clean water in your mouth
you're ringing soapy dirty [ __ ] in your
mouth understood but it's clean dirty
water into her
mouth it's not dirty water dirty water
into her mouth what you British this
argument you're just dumb you're dumb
she squeezing dirty water into her mouth
Matt go ring some water in your mouth
then when I was 8 years old I was doing
parkour at my grandparents house and I
was jumping from couch to couch but one
of the couches was again the wall so I
accidentally jumped past the top of the
couch hit the wall leaving a knee sized
dented hole in the wall and started to
cry not because it hurt but because I
didn't want to get in trouble that's
awesome that's [ __ ] hilarious yeah
something you wouldn't do if you don't
have any fun when I was seven I walked
home from school and my house was locked
and I couldn't find a spare key so I had
to I decided to go for a nude
swim oh yeah that's a great anyways I
really needed to take a [ __ ] so I didn't
didn't know when anyone in the family
would be home so I took one in my
backyard in this bush but then my dog
started to eat it so I'm naked with an
unwiped ass trying to get my dog to stop
eating [ __ ] the dog eating the [ __ ] is
the least of my War she ended up eating
it and I got a rash because I couldn't I
didn't choose a good Leaf to wipe with
oh my God that's not the only bad
decision you made that day you sick
freak yeah it started with oh locked out
my house a quick naked what are you
doing with a [ __ ] loading you know what
I'm doing if that happens what sitting
on my porch waiting for somebody else
correct I'm breaking in my own home I'll
find a way I'd climb the [ __ ] fire
escape to the roof looks like I got 30
minutes to swim naked like I would
literally run and Sprint and kick a
window in and then just get in the house
and then repair it somehow if I had just
[ __ ] so bad people are weird dude so
weird how's your dog outside too if the
house was locked what does your dog
permanently stay outside bad dog owner
what are you a fiber
fiber not a deep and dark confession but
funny story freshman here in high school
we were split up in the gym guys and
girls for exercises we were about to
finish but then we had some time left
over so we got to chill for a bit me and
my friend sat on the bleachers which
were those ones you could pull off the
wall middle middle ones were closed so
only the top and bottom seats were open
I sat at the top with my friends when it
was time to go change we were all
getting down and I decided to jump oh
they were like dancing bad move my foot
missed the bottom step so I fell forward
Jim went silent and filled with laughter
from all the girls when I tell you I
fell and it looked like a caution taped
body crime scene is exactly how I looked
anyways I had just swollen ankle for the
next few days and now it's this story
that completely makes everyone die of
laughter hope you can picture it yeah
that was dropped like 10 falling falling
in public or falling in front of a big
group of people most embarrassing thing
ever only if you really really care
about it my dad and I moved into an
apartment at the beginning of my sixth
grade year we lived next to it the
manager of the complex wal to wall and
she was a [ __ ] and used to always
complain about the stupidest
[ __ ] where's that dog you
farted my dad work M made stinky my dad
worked a Night Trips at the hospital and
one time I woke up in the middle of the
night after where he went to work what
sprinted up what he say he said sprint
it upstairs no what did you just say her
dad worked night shifts got home from
work and she ran up and down the stairs
that were connected to her wall banging
on the walls just because I was in a
goofy mood she called Neighbor yeah she
called my dad and told him there's a
crazy obnoxious loud sound coming from
the apartment and doesn't know if it
could stop or if she had to call the
police and so he called me and I
answered the phone as if he had woken me
up in the best sleep I ever got and I
told him I had no idea what he was
talking about and went right on with my
night I love I love it I love [ __ ] like
that that's beautiful when I was 12 my
grandma's husband step Grandad I guess
took me and my cousin to the Gazebo by
ourselves we were both 12 years old
what's the Gaze and he told us to drink
mixed berry Smirnoffs we both declined
and he called us [ __ ] and
[ __ ] that's terrible I didn't want my
cousin we have a great grandfather I
didn't want my cousin to have to drink
so I told him that if he got shot
glasses I would he did find some and
then I don't know how many shots he made
me drink I do remember the stuff he told
us though plot twist my grandma was out
there the whole time listening I've
recently started telling my story I
still feel guilty at fault sometimes I
just have to remember I was a child my
grandma is now telling everyone that I
was lying about this happening that's
actually so her grandparents are getting
her that's horrible I was just laughing
at like the shock of the situation
that's it's like the SM like the name of
the Dr that killed me that's so funny
that's insane I was in second grade I
went to a daycare after school I was
sort of friends with the daughter of the
daycare hair lady but she was super
bossy and straight up mean like at 6
years old you were super bossy and
straight up mean like at 6 years old
this [ __ ] was dead calling me fat what
how she was sick that's wait who is this
I feel like that's all you got who is
this Anonymous confession no the [ __ ]
beginning the teacher her daycare
teacher no it's not her daycare teacher
n fat her daycare teacher's kid when I
was in 2 grade I went to daycare after
school I was sort of friends with the
daughter of the daycare lady but she was
super bossy and straight up mean yeah
the little kid oh I don't I think she's
talking about the just go like at 6
years old this [ __ ] was dead calling me
fat yeah the girl 6 years old one day
she having a play date somewhere else so
lucky me got to use her special pink cup
with a built-in straw she never let
anyone use this cup I was always so
bitter about it so little me was from
the cup and pret sticks I realized the
pretzels are the same size as the straw
in the cup so I shoved a pretzel in the
straw and it was permanently stuck in
there and I never got to use her pink
cup again I'm 19 and I'm still so proud
of the fact that I stopped her from
being able to use her pink cup awesome I
love that when I was 6 years old I had a
massive fear of toilets I was so scared
of the flush and have to like push the
lever and bolt my ass out of the
bathroom that's embarrassing at daycare
I couldn't do that so normally I would
just hold it until I got home all day I
had to [ __ ] so bad I [ __ ] in the garbage
in the bathroom and then covered it with
toilet paper
I lost my privilege to go to the
bathroom at daycare after that being
scared of the flush of a toilet is
insane when we were in school I I vivly
remember pissing myself during cot time
once when we were in school I used to
remember kids like crazy [ __ ] I remember
used kids doing crazy [ __ ] in the
bathroom like not being able to do like
like [ __ ] on a wall or like throwing
up and [ __ ] at the same time here
the thing I was like how are their kids
doing this the thing about preschool is
every teacher know every kid goes to the
bathroom one at a time and the teacher
knows if it was you that like made it
messy okay I went to Disneyland for my
10th birthday and we were allowed to go
on the one of the last rides and had to
pick between Splash Mountain or some
other ride that I don't remember but me
and my cousin chose to go on Splash
Mountain and I had to pee really really
[ __ ] bad on Splash Mountain like so
bad at the end of the ride when we got
hit with a bunch of water I peed when I
got off the ride and I just acted like I
got really wet from the water my cousin
didn't know that she literally got
covered in my urine that day and I
didn't tell tell her until like 2 months
ago and I'm 14 now that's fine I [ __ ]
used to take baths together and piss all
over each other I'm sure we're babies
like come on Nick we were babies you're
telling me we w't babies I don't we were
babies I'm glad that my memories don't
go that far back yeah I don't remember
[ __ ] from y grou you guys don't remember
group bath group [ __ ] bath time group
bath cut out the f word okay do you guys
remember y'all always say that like the
f word of worst times group [ __ ] bath
time okay do you guys remember come on
do you guys remember when we did take
baths together no we were [ __ ] sick
cut that out you have no memory of that
no I don't I have like just memories of
rat first rat in the while you see it no
I just I saw it's in that little Bush
being a little [ __ ] muskrat what's a
muskrat I don't know I it's being a
little cheese eater I saw your cheese
eater go eat some [ __ ] Mouse TR
cheese [ __ ] yeah go eat some colby
jack I hate you so much I hate foldable
sign I used to carve huge holes into my
wall what by my bed with my bare what
are you escaping prison what this Al by
my wall with my bare hands and when I
rearranged my room my parents thought we
had ter
what the [ __ ] just get like a [ __ ]
scratch board or like a stress ball or
something a scratchboard for a human is
crazy do something the wall what's it
called like the bills bills Mafia thing
when I was younger I used to take giant
slices of butter and just eat it like it
was a
lollipop Nick hates butter fun fact my
friend told me that she lost her hamster
and then she found it a week later I
guess had gotten out of its cage and
crawled up and drowned in her
toilet oh my God imagine how devastating
you'd be if you had to [ __ ] on your
hamster well so you have to [ __ ] so bad
who the [ __ ] what oh oh my God I thought
there was someone there I actually did
usually you just look over my shoulder
that was I thought there was someone
there oh my God I actually thought there
was someone behind us I'm not lying
Jason dulo everyone sing a Jason dulo
song with me um
you spin my
head follow us on Instagram at stolo you
can find all of our individual socials
from there I'm follow
Nick yeah you miss me and all the things
that we did we said we going to travel
from the island to Madrid we had a lot
of plans but they
all why oh because of someid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
saying nothing when I'm PST up with
other [ __ ] for my brothers