I didn't have a Pepsi one time in Boston
this whole time we've been here and
today I had three do you ever go to like
bed and think of just like what if I
wasn't doing this and I was doing
something else and just like you
fantasize about doing something else are
you like admitting something right now
or no no no no I just do you hear how
crazy that wording was I just sometimes
think like what if I was just a clown
that lived at like the carnival you mean
like fully like that I thought you meant
like maybe like work St or like oh maybe
yeah like I work as a clown instead no I
meant like working on the job that you
currently do every day yeah um I was
talking about being a working clown
instead like well you're already a
working clown I really kind of am I like
that I like that I could say that like
like if we were doing our career right
now old times we'd be old times we just
be clowns and Jesters like that's our
job that was like OG entertainment was a
man who could juggle in a funky scit
like we are lowkey the jugglers and
clowns of the new generation Matt how
does that make you feel that makes that
fills my heart with joy Matt um do you
ever think of that like it's so it it
actually pains me when I hear [ __ ] like
that cuz I'm like am I that like dull of
a human being that I don't ever think
that deep into anything at all no your
brothers
think is very I hate when people call us
like a thre Su of people never I've
heard like that is so s to say to Triple
ever said never happened to me and if I
did hear that in person come on don't
make you seem crazy no you're nuts
you're nuts I don't like know who you're
talking being called the trips is my
least favorite thing yeah being called
the trips makes want to pull out a taser
from my pocket and just shoot the person
with a taser no just tase them to the
ground I love I wish that more people
could just tase one another no you don't
Nick no I really don't wish for that if
we a band what would our band name be oh
good question oh the girl yes remember
that girl from the other video like two
videos ago we were going to answer this
girl's questions then we forgot and did
it at the end what the Tik Tok the girl
asked the questions and we were like oh
we'll just do it next video oh and we
didn't do it next video now we're doing
it today's video was that one of our
questions you having such an open mind
and a good question segue our video [ __ ]
happens when you guys let me speak but
what should our what should our Trio be
name small medium and
large how do you feel about hold on I
have to burp I feel like I'm going to
throw
up we're going to put the whole video on
pause so you can burp for a second if
you had a garden what would be the first
thing you plant you're speaking my
language right now
pumpkins
pumpkins um mine pumpkins I wonder what
Nick says I love edits like that I
wonder what Nick would plan pumpkins
pumpkins pumpkins pumpkins and then I
get like an apple tree and then C donuts
and then CER Donuts he's going to make a
donut no no no like I would love to have
a house where I can plant pumpkins and
then throw a bunch of apples and hay out
there and then also bring like apple
cider donuts and it's like dude it's
like lowy I have I have kind of a funny
question answer what would you here's my
question do you want to hear my answer
that's a funny question go um a
sunflower
that's so your Vibe I love it your
tattoo Oh I thought you were just
like love
hey yeah that's what I thought he just
did I wish we could go back in time to
like Prime fortnite because no no listen
this one actually has a good reasoning
Matt get the taser tase me we should do
a video like trying to do emotes like if
we if we were YouTubers in Prime
fortnite that would actually be
something we could do if there was a
stero University what would the mascot
in colors be and what classes would be
taught there every okay so it's us three
like I have my answers for me but we
have to think as a group and decipher it
together I think the mascot should be
the c a candy corn and he like runs
around and he's just like a big corn and
he's like it's like one it's like one
terrible it's like one piece of candy
corn and he just runs the [ __ ] around no
no I think we do something with three
heads like
Cerberus and then that like that's our
masc got cuz it's we ever tell these
people that we were Cerberus the
three-headed dog in a fourth grade
school play no we didn't do we never
tell you guys I don't think we did oh we
we need to find a CD in that for a
fourth grade play mimat and Nick were
cous for the three-headed guard dog of
the underworld our costume was we each
had dog ears on and we shared a blanket
with like holes in cut out and so it was
like one big suit I remember we had one
scene in the show where we had to like
run across the room and I was in the
front and I ran out and then I tripped
and since we were all in like the same
shirt we just like landed on top of each
other no but we also it was we actually
were pretty skilled and talented in that
because when we had the three heads it
was like we had share sentences so like
it was like I would start a sentence
Nick would let's do it right now improv
improv real quick just to like so they
have an understanding
hi you're in the middle
idiot I'm shy yesterday I went to the
store and I [ __ ] your mother so yeah
it was like that and it was like it was
just super it was it was insane it was
cool though but yeah that would be our
mascot so cus the what would our
colors I they need like a good rust gold
like a rustic vintage gold I can [ __ ]
with that I like wooden nature colors
and I feel like we all do wouldn't we is
that a word I don't know but I like it I
teach people how to edit videos oh
that's a good one good one so much yeah
no problem I I do driving lessons
driving driving where you at um I would
teach people conversation
starters that's great good question
great I disagree awesome cuz you're
psychotic the whole class like would be
always gets mad at me because I have
such unique ways to ENT room am I mad
well no you always like get enter a room
are you throwing smoke balls no I just
think of our he drops a blanket I think
when we had a meeting with our agency
and I was that was that was psychotic no
it wasn't no no NOP nope I'll say it m
meet you guys they're ready to talk
we're ready to talk business we sit down
and Chris goes to everyone in the room
did am I the only one that knows that uh
today's not true they introduced the
topic to me no no you said you said hey
guys they said how's your
day that's not said Chris how's your day
is the gateway to say whatever you want
this said okay yeah how's your day Chris
says uh my day is going pretty good the
only thing is it's 7-Eleven free slurpee
day and I no 7 Bring Your Own Cup Day
and I and I haven't gone yet and he was
and I'm in a meeting like I I was just
letting them know I I I I have better
places to be so take your time for
granted that's I think that that
sentence came out completely incorrectly
it did I don't know it's more of like
like oh how your day I'm good I'm ready
to meet but I rather at BR my own cup to
7 yeah but like you have to keep in mind
it's a little weird no it's not cuz I'm
excited and I was telling them all like
isn't it crazy you could bring um a KFC
bucket you could bring that's the ideal
one that's like the best one you can
bring because it fits in the thing oh in
my opinion you let me know when free
slurpie day is 7-Eleven January
11th wrong January is the first month of
the year June January febr March April
May June July July it's all those JS
[ __ ] July 11 two months yeah we have to
go fre cup day would you put in your
donkey pale work donkeys when they're
traveling have like a little pale of
food that they can start eating whenever
and I just want to know what food that
they would put in their own donkey pil
if they could just be stressed I feel
bad I can't even think of that well
they're eating they're just happy it's
like they can eat whatever oh my God if
I ate a donkey pil okay Matt we all know
yours it' be like rice or chicken
yeah I'm talking to you stupid let him
answer mine would be jumbo shrimp flying
around in that thing I'd be catching I'm
allergic to shrimp it can't be something
with like heavy sauce imagine like um
your no that's what I was thinking like
if you imagine soup in there and it's
just like soups on your face like
burning you and [ __ ] it's like dripping
off your yeah I think of like I think of
like alfredo sauce [ __ ] nasty white I
think see what I think nasty and gross
what I'm thinking is I like to like eat
cereal just straight out of a cup and
that's kind of what that reminds me of
when I like cuz sometimes I do just like
so like Cheerios wow you need drink mine
would be popcorn I'm thinking like I
could stick my tongue and just get one
Chon I'm thinking like tricks Frosted
Flakes multigrain Cheerios something in
that alley I loved your answer than no
problem like those questions were so
good because they allowed you want to
know what's insane stop smacking your
leg you're like you want to know what's
crazy you want to know something crazy
don't hit that while my [ __ ] teeth
are on it okay this is probably the like
most embarrassing do you know I have
half a fake front tooth yeah I went on a
rant about this before right yes you
have I think so still the most shocking
piece of information I've ever got in my
life go ahead and relay it I know you
want to go ahead I went to the dentist
and the lady was like I I feel like I've
told a story before and if I did I
apologize if you guys are like oh ni
shut up you already said that you're
going You're going to hear you're going
to hear me say it again go ahead my I
went to the dentist and the lady was
like how's your attachment
doing I literally
to like an owl turn my head 180° I said
o embodying the owl who who are you
[ __ ] talking
about no one in this room has
attachments on their teeth nobody and
then I she goes yeah yeah you you chi
your tooth like 2/3 of your tooth and
half of your front left tooth is not
real were you stunned Chris you couldn't
believe it I literally like I've never
like I'm loud like this to you guys I'm
not usually like s I'm loud in public
I'm not like insane in front of people
I've never met you said what I think I I
think I did I was like
what I was like half of my tooth is in
real and I was like to me like if you
have a like like I can't take it out I
can't take it out no [ __ ] Nick it's a
rest of your Toth but that's why I was
confused like cuz I just assume that
like if your tooth's fake you got to
like put it in and out I'm like I know
I'm not doing that so I don't think I
have what you think I got okay yeah but
I had it I have half a fake top tooth
what now do you think it's my real tooth
just glued back on or do you think no
are you stupid it wouldn't grow anymore
it's the one on the front too did a
great job do I have the same size teeth
than when I was 10 years old what was
that noise I didn't hear anything I
heard that I didn't hear anything it was
like
guys we're at our gay trucker spot this
is where the gay trucker yes they're not
here tonight um but what was I going to
say what was I talking about I don't
know sorry that threw me off what was I
saying dude oh yeah do you think I have
the same size teeth and like when I was
tag I think when your baby teeth grow
youing I think when your baby when when
your baby teeth fall out and you get the
new ones I think they're the same
forever yeah those on same size though
is what I'm saying or they grow they're
constantly going down it's going down
down down your teeth are constantly
growing your teeth will get bigger when
your 90 years old mhm do you know your
nose is always getting bigger too that's
something that always gets bigger that's
a lie who wants to go to Four Seasons
Orlando
me I want to go [ __ ] that big scary
baby what now that baby has half a fake
front tooth for sure no that baby's
insane God I have so much sweat on me
right now I think I could like don't say
that what wherever you're about to go
with that leave it where it is thank you
so much it's just gross I'm disgusting
right now it is gross isn't it crazy
that Brands can trademark a
color a in different categories correct
but like isn't that nuts like there can
be something that's like specifically
like oh this is blue that's like our
blue hourglass I that's what I want to
do if I was a native language speaker
and I had to learn English I'd just be
so mad if I hour and hour is two
different words and they're spelled
different I think if I was arguing with
someone about time or something or like
if they're late or something I'd want to
say a really funky word like like time
is a mystery or like time is of the
essence something ridiculous whatever
and I'd want to pull like a a normally
large hourglass out from behind me and
shatter it and then just fade away into
a hallway what I don't know I feel like
imagine that like you're talking to
someone you just met at like a about
like time or something and then you're
just like they say something crazy and
then you just say something nuts and
then shatter you want to know what I got
to say an hourglass and F and they never
see you again I love when I meet someone
and I'm talking to them and I know I'll
never see them again that's like one of
my that's my biggest fear that's like
one of my favorite feelings ever
actually I got to give it to you both of
you what you shock me every time isn't
it crazy that like if you had a stranger
to that level like and like there was
someone you didn't know at all complete
stranger and you look at them and you're
like oh I'll never never see them again
if you have free will as a person if you
just punched them in the [ __ ] face
you'd have to see them again like you'd
go probably go to court there be like
that's a crazy like that's crazy no
there's something that could be a
stranger that you walk by I want a
lawsuit with this but if you suck punch
in the face you're going to know you're
going to see him again I'm sure of it
that's crazier it's crazy that we just
have free will I could just grab a
[ __ ] banana in a store and throw it
at someone but I don't get dude really
that's like the most cartoon thing I've
ever seen in my life ever seen did you
display it listen that's slipping on
banana peels I can't believe when people
like witness crime or something they can
like just describe someone perfectly
whenever there's chaos in suing I'm not
taking details of like what the person
looked like I am I'm one of those guys
I'm one of those guys I can tell you
everything people are like bushy
eyebrows a goatee black hair I just
can't believe those [ __ ] can
the we got rended yeah yeah you want to
know what she was wearing no I could
tell you what is it blue jeans black
jacket oh that's Shir that's like simple
said like you say cheetah slides and
fuzzy pants blue jeans black jacket
white shirt I just can't believe that
people like like there's like the sketch
artists that can draw with crazy that's
the
crazy what what I couldn't even describe
Chris it looks just [ __ ] like
me my God I couldn't even get them to
draw a picture of my mother they draw it
and they turn it around the person
instantly has
[Music]
a that's crazy go take a go work at
Pixar we need a new movie dra that's
crazy that's that's
insane why do I have my seat belt on I
don't know but the video oh my God
that's a good idea what we should get
one of those sketch artist people try
and find one I don't really know how to
get and describe our and describe people
we know and good idea we need them we
need them if you know how to If someone
knows how someone who do that we need to
do that I need their phone number but
like that what do you say like oh their
eyes are about like 4 Ines apart no [ __ ]
I think they give you examples oh maybe
right potentially like what eyes are
most similar it's like building a we me
almost you know how what if that was how
they did it like they were like like
they were like you got like mugged and
you're like trying to describe person
they pull out a we they p a wee me
Creator which hair which haircut what's
their favorite
color be so [ __ ] funny that's like a
SK be so that's a [ __ ] funny we need
to do that as a they were wearing they
were wearing red pants
favorite we they're wearing yellow pants
like I'm sorry that's not an option
correct some people are going to watch
this video and they don't know what a
Wii is grow up I remember playing the
Wii actually I saw a video the other day
and it was it was Black Friday when the
Wii came out I saw that was the most
nostalgic thing I've ever were people
each other no the guy was like the guy
Nick the guy was the guy was like the
guy was like oh you should probably get
a nun truck now cuz you're going to need
it for some of the games you and it was
just like crazy it was nuts all right
we're going to go home and shower
together cuz we're all sweaty thank you
guys so much for joining us on this
Friday video double location car video
it's kind of rare um some l subscribe
button hit the notification Bell so you
never miss a video I don't know if you
were in the room but Ro milon subscri
there's a video clip of me where I go
like this with my fingers yeah you're
[ __ ] stupid and then I go oh I love
that
[ __ ] like how crazy is that someone
posted it and goes this is the
definition of ADHD you're weird cuz you
guys are talking and I'm going oh I just
love this [ __ ] you're [ __ ] crazy
you're psychotic and we have a new merch
coming soon hopefully
[Music]