should we go front door yeah let's go
front door front door cuz something was
growling at
[Music]
me
Nick rise and shine rise and
[Music]
shine I can't believe you sleep with a
shirt on blows my
mind I need to sleep with a shirt on I
it's
9:53 in the morning this is like the
earliest you've ever been up in your
life are you [ __ ] dumb no school oh
yeah you're right it's so crazy like how
much like my bedroom door needs like
WD40 it's the loudest thing world like I
was sound asleep before you open the
door wide awake now
yeah well good morning good morning Nick
Nick why are you running I'm going right
here we're headed out we're going to the
Madison Beer show come along okay dude
what was that like that looked like a
house tour you know when they do the
start to like the house tours the our
textual digest
okay oh wow come with us oh
hey fornite fornite fortnite fortnite
[Applause]
you're [ __ ]
[Music]
kidding what's up you guys I'm going to
go upstairs and I'm going to try and
scare the [ __ ] out of either Matt or
Chris whoever is easier to scare and
whoever is more clothed
and enough
Nick ow you think you can just run
upstairs and scare me like that
tiptoeing like a [ __ ]
psychopath knock back up get away you're
lucky I have my [ __ ] belt in my hand
you're done that was perfect timing I
was I was worried I wasn't going to be
able to see either of you it was so
silent my room's right there no one's up
here I almost took my dick out decided
to go in here and pee I literally said
that I was going to I was going to scare
whoever was more clothed and I saw you I
heard you start to turn the corner and I
knew
success okay I put this ring on and then
my finger too hot Chris once again scare
one of you like and you're going to be
like in the shower who are you talking
to no one's listening go ahead mat I've
got nothing left to say yeah all right
guys welcome to essentially our May Vlog
even though we're kind of already far
into May two updates randomly is if you
were wondering if Chris ever found his
belt I saw someone wondering the belt
was found no more discussion and then if
you were worried about Matt's ankle Matt
went to go see a doctor and he's
basically doing like at home Physical
Therapy but he'll be fine um yeah but we
got to Boston the other day we landed
went to sleep woke up got haircuts and
then now we're here and we're it's like
our fourth day here or something fifth
day here yeah and our friends are here
so come along with us we're going to
have an amazing lovely month but
tomorrow's Mother's Day so we got Mary
Lou a card some flowers and then
earrings but she doesn't wear stud
earrings but the risk was taken and we
got her stud earrings we'll see if she
likes them I slept and I woke up and I
felt like I had like a a film come in my
eyes for like 20 minutes there's an
added ruti for parties over six
just
four five incoming so we'll be fine
unless the ghost yeah have [ __ ] that up
you can count on
that oh hey hi buddy Nick is see our
friend look at our friend I'm not do it
do it do
it like
this do you think I could get this
around me no what you know you can get a
dog harness your
bodyes place a clip got all the way to
this I easily could I look it let's see
it brother like if the clip was there
yeah right the clip is not there I know
oh it's on the I can do it on my thigh
good job Chris thank you nice little
thigh action come here
what Presley and this goes okay I don't
know if the public knows about how Matt
stretches Presley Matt is Presley's uh
strer don't say Matt is Presley's
personal stretcher is okay you come on
stretch them out Matt give give the
people a dog if you have a dog at home
follow these Simple Rules which Matt
came up with by the way oh wow that was
a fast one nice no don't he thinks
you're putting that on that away thank
sorry you're distracting from the lesson
sorry
sorry nice oh that looks really
comfortable I want to
try it's a CR oh he's so cute he's so
happy open your letter from this hotel
and read it yeah what does it say I
don't know closed completely sealed out
I know what it
says sealed letter oh I can't read cive
you got to do
it you can read that no try to read it
madis Madison welcome we are delighted
to have you with us this is
scary I trust you whatever read it I
don't God read it I trust can I give it
to me oh my God this is I trust you will
find no no I was getting there welcome
we're delighted to have you with us I
trust you will find everything
in can't even read it what is that ashes
exactly like what say ashes all right
Nate stepping in Nate stepping in what
is this word everything I truthfully
don't even know what that says find
everything in is it the name of the
hotel no but
because that says please bro oh but
please but please do
call they're trying to be too fancy like
bro just write it down like call if it
was like hope your stay is good call you
need anything everything in
Oasis no Omni Oasis that's what I said
it aside but please
in in maybe please do call should you
need maybe hope you find everything in
your room like in like like it doesn't
say your room but that's what makes hope
you find everything in your room but
please call if you need in cheers from
Michael Jorgenson shout out you shout
out Michael Jorgenson what is he going
to call you're in a kilt and do a little
dance for us kill is crazy I'm really
devastated about these strawberries here
I went to eat them last night Madison
claimed she was going to have two of
them and then didn't any of them I had
one I had one there's six here and I ate
one look this is was me that doesn't
count that's there if there's still
chocolate showing bitten It Was Bitten
but like bro I would oh my God it was
like B
like Batman like this is my city the
glass are you sweating I'm really hot I
don't know would you
trust yes I would actually you body slam
the glass I would do it for no money
that's I was going but they didn't let
me it would not bre I cherish his life
there's no way don't try
it no there's no way oh my
God body slam do it a body slam might do
[ __ ] imagine if I'm saying get out of
here well
that would if Madison died on the Vlog
that be so be good
content going to kill you we're going to
the
aquarium I'm like I'm like kind of
sweating right now I'm going to turn
yeah you just literally jumped 8T in the
air what that's a little
starfish cute compared to my finger look
at this look you can't even focus on him
you see him Matt look stand here you can
see it it's on the glass don't throw
anything in there open air exhibit I'd
love that for them look at got he got no
Nest said they're all sleepy right now
I'm going to scream get up penguin get
the one in there where the one in there
oh my God look at him look the flips up
that was so cute thep oh oh my God this
dude's falling asleep right in front of
us this poor soul needs to go to bed
he's exhausted camera's about to die
[ __ ] of course yeah Nick's a bot saky
pengu dude he's fading away like falling
asleep pins is
44 wow
44 private
Skipper Nam our I forget no Rico private
Skipper and there's one more isn't it
just like meal or something like it's
like no it's not we're think
W wski what is it Google what is making
that
noise what is
[Music]
itki search it up Matt search it UPI
analysis what I'm picturing okay what is
it Matt it's
Kowalski had
them all of them ksk analis Kowalski
analis and then there's Dave I don't
know who the [ __ ] Dave is Dave is not
penguin bro this is what I imagine he's
like hey what theu
[Music]
going what that
thing that thing's gigantic e e e look
at your face say I'm like terrified
no that looks like I have an octopus
tattooed on me no wait you actually yes
yeah look at him what's the octopus's
name look how big that starfish
is the octopus can get like like that
Octopus
get crazy I am I could watch her all day
look at that like curl of her oh my God
if this thing touched me I'd be [ __ ]
disgusting I would I would touch I would
touch you would let it like suction on
you and [ __ ] what if they told me right
now that I could reach my hand and she
would like wrap around my hand I would I
would never do that like really freaked
out what like I hate that I'm looking at
it suckers and that's a quote from like
the aquarium Lady it's literally called
a sucker look it it's moving it
individual like one sucker at a time
yeah look how old that dude is bro look
at it you see it oh I didn't see him
Turtle hat Big
Win
w you guys look like scary kind of I'm
walking with
a Chris I'm shocked out of everyone you
didn't get turtle me too that's very you
I know
what was everyone's favorite part um
proba the P clap in the
side clap in the did you see it yeah but
that's a crazy way to word clapping that
Bow Bow Bow
Bow did you guys none of you else have a
favorite part no I was going to say mine
was the um the penguin jumping into the
water I agree when
was oh no and that octopus bro yeah that
octopus was crazy this is my go-to
default nixo is in Boston
t-shirt I was fixing my balls I thought
you you were fixing yourself and I
thought you were going to say outfit not
t-shirt so I like went to show know I
kind of like provoked it all right Guys
Madison leaves tomorrow for the rest of
her tour so go check her out if you
haven't if you haven't seen a Madison
Beer show live you should go do that
but we went to the aquarium today and I
got this penguin stuffed animal I he's
yet to have a name but by the time this
video comes out he'll 100% be named um
I got him because there was this species
of penguin at the aquarium today and
they were gay and I was like I need to
get the gay penguin so that was this
this wasn't a fun fact that the lady at
the aquarium no no no no no she was
pointing at the straight Penguins cuz
they were like on their egg and they
were like she was like look that's a
couple and then that's a couple and then
I was like there's got to be gay
penguins in here too she's like oh for
sure for sure and she was like the ones
over there like they like everyone at
the aquarium when I said it like in
unison agreed that like the Penguins
over there were gay so I like if
everyone's saying it it's got to be
true
Nick good thing they keep the gay
Penguins away from the other Penguins we
don't need them imprinting their stupid
gay agenda on to the other Nick it was
so funny in the car earlier I was
looking at like the top and like this
print right here it was like dark in the
car so it looked Brown I thought it was
a Gucci hat I was
like weci they Gucci hat head look it's
a [ __ ] Turtle me Nate and Madison got
them so RP it most of us who are at the
aquarium today had been to that aquarium
before and they have a 95-year-old
turtle there so it's like crazy to think
like we've seen that Turtle
before no dead serious like I I like I
saw a turtle I'm like I know you see
that that big ass fish she was like oh
yeah he's been here since the 80s H
80s like that fish could have bought a
Coke for five [ __ ] cents literally
that's sick literally ooh shepherd's pie
one of my favorite home-cooked meals in
the this household I already told Nick
and Justin my dream this morning yeah
where's Justin I didn't see him you guys
said you were hanging out with him yeah
he's back in I think he left I don't
know I already told them my dream this
morning and Nick's scared of me again oh
God a little while ago Nick got really
scared of me because I had a dream or
I'd call it more of a nightmare that I
you killed me I was stabbing Chris in my
dream crying and shedding tears and
freaking out cuz I didn't want to kill
him but in my dream I had to like what
did I like that's insane had to do
that's insane and Nick was really scared
of me warranted
behold yesterday's dream so I'm sleeping
I'm having a dream okay yeah this is the
most Vivid dream I've had in years if in
2 months if you asked me about this
dream I could give it to you all
straight out okay I remember it
perfectly Chris me and Nick and 14
others are paragliding over a city that
we we have no idea what it is but we're
with 14 people from there there are tour
guides they're everyone we need they got
they all this we look down snakes
everywhere grab onto a fence that's
really tall like 80 ft in the sky the
snakes disappear in the morning climb
down in the morning all the other people
me and Nick thought they were dead that
those people were our tour guides they
had the passports they had our phones
they had our money they had our food for
the week stranded in a foreign country
have no idea how to get home hungry
we're sleepy we're scared everything we
go into a convenience store I stole food
of phone all the essentials Nick stole a
notepad and a pen don't know why don't
know where some kid notices us okay hi
he goes oh my God this turn Tri he's
recording us through his legs like
trying to get a video I don't know he
was one of he was one of the people on
the paraglide he was the only Survivor
but are the passports he goes the king
and queen have them we we go where are
the queen and the King he goes in the
town hall the town hall is just a
regular are you playing Clash of Clans
now or no I can't I can't even believe
it the king and queen yeah they're dead
asleep like watching TV you know what we
have to do right and he goes yeah we got
to kill
him he goes to where the knives are and
right next to the knives is the bag of
every single person who's power power GL
or power sailings passports he grabs the
bag of passports and gives me the knife
I stab and kill both of the the king and
the queen crying in tears because I
didn't want to but I had to are these
people we know no idea but I I had to
kill him and I had to leave and I was
just emotional I didn't want to but I
had to to leave the country and get the
passports and Nick took the passports
already and I don't know so then Nick
leaves I kill them I go outside I drop
the knife and I go all of that and we
didn't even find the passports and Nick
goes I have
them so I get mad at Nick we start
arguing all the way to the air happen
all the way to the airport we fly home
yeah that was
it that's
ridiculous you don't recognize the king
and queen at all I recognize nobody from
the dream except for Nick I have no idea
it's raining
Chinese food hold on Chinese food it's
raining it's snoring the old man is what
snoring you're sick and
like we have way too much content of you
driving on your
phone you need to not do that yesterday
me and Nathan were in Target and we saw
this thing and I was like this is the
thing we need we could easily filmed
something with this so we bought it
insert clip of me and Nathan buying it
you vlogged in there slightly oh
goodness get this and then get like
gross food and then if it bites you not
only does it bite you but you have to
like eat something nasty that'd be crazy
I forget what I said I was going to do
oh he got his haircut that's what wait
did he I can't even see on the camera
look so handsome they oh it's so short
it's still wet did you take a shower
yeah I had to get all the hair off
imagine we got lost in the wood dude I
should have wore like hiking boots or
something it's like so muddy the one day
I didn't wear my timy e e do you hear
that do you hear the squish squishy
squishy
is Chris was like oh my God there's
definitely a tadpull in there boom we
saw a frog hello I'm going to guys what
if there was an alligator we have to
check if the coast is clear cuz I going
to piss myself okay guys so when we come
back home we do a lot of sitting at
Nathan's house and doing a [ __ ] ton of
nothing so we decided it's time to end
the trapped indoors and explore the
outdoors together yeah so we basically
made it out the group chat for is that a
bird that's a bird on the on the thing
where the the thing the my God yeah it's
a goose he just does do you ever
remember one time when I was peeing in
the backyard and a [ __ ] bug landed on
my dick I don't I how would I remember
cuz I took a video I was recording a
video to the video not of my penis of my
face sh stop saying the word penis so
loud I was recording my
penis no take camera camera no no
mat just thre out the whole Woods I
don't even think I can speak that loud
though I think they heard you over there
you're ruining the vibe come on he he
goes take the camera take the camera
he's like a loading up the screen about
Matt every single day we're in La he's
like oh I just want to be in the
wilderness I want to be outside the
peace and quiet and then we get him to
the peace and quiet and he shouts penis
every time I'm just trying to show you
there's nothing to be scared of don't
you just feel like a free bird right now
FL thr you in the pond right now I'm
just trying I'm just trying to take the
optimistic approach with everything
recently oh that's a yellow belly tip
titty titty bird what yeah you know that
yeah yellow belly titty dude we should
get like a book like one of those books
that's a big titted bimbo that's the
that's the that's a big tted bimb we
should get a we should get of those
books that's like the nature life
magazines and you can read about it and
we can study and Nate oh my God that's
actually a good idea you and me are
going to both get a book and when like I
go to California I'll try like to check
off like the West Coast exclusives and
we have to see all the birds in the book
man you look very nature in the outfit
today do I yeah that's what my that's
what I try to give with all of my
outfits don't fall if Nick just fell
that would have been the funniest angle
ever that grown-ups movie where the when
he tries to go in the swing and he like
fully eats rocks I wonder if there's
like poison ivy out here probably you
know poison ivy is actually part cashew
and not an ivy and did you know that
poison oak is not an oak but also part
of the cashew family Nick the type of
guy to find a Snapple fact and start
reading it as like he like his own
little thing I did that yesterday and
I'm doing it right now bless you don't
sneeze while I'm [ __ ] speaking shut
the [ __ ] up
idiot you're gay if you skip a rock [ __ ]
you oh that was so cute you see that
leaf fall right in front of my face yeah
guys what if I [ __ ] right here Chris
yeah oh oh my God wait guys this is I'm
not even trying to be like nature guy
here like Beaver that is the work of a
beaver look at look at How It Was Bitten
and that is work of a beaver [ __ ] get
your beaver work that's work of a beaver
oh my God wait I actually feel really
cool like knowing that like you know how
like they like they did it to this one
too
isn't that that's sear search up a tree
that fell over cuz of beaver and that's
it that's it search it up dude that's
work of a beaver oh my
[Laughter]
God tell me that doesn't look familiar
that's a huge tree though that Chris
look at that a snack that's exactly
that's exactly look he ate all of them
there I feel like one of those guys
where like they like find like the scat
and they're like oh this is like the SC
oh my God this is 8 hours old where the
trail is hot like that type of vibe the
lily pads are cool all right thank you
kids are raiding his Outdoor Experience
well yeah you got to like is that a
beaver it might be a beaver cuz
damn you're weird beaver I hardly know
her
Beaver that was a RuPaul joke I been I
hate when a school bus goes by it's like
get these gross kids far away from me
I'm ready bow we got the AL Ator it's
going to bite your finger and then not
only not only if I have a no you go you
go if it bites your hand when you push
it down you have to take a shot of lemon
juice oh the reveal is crazy I was going
to do it like the same time okay let's
do
it good game guys good
game I used to actually think that like
my hands were going to like bleed if I
did this have you seen the guy on like I
used to be terrified did you see the guy
who did this and he like replace it with
like needles or like push pins that's
terrible no you this was supposed to be
shot glasses but I like door dashed it
and they must have not had shot glasses
so they just like just don't you don't
put too much it's like a shot like a
little less than e why is it like chunky
is this
enough is that enough okay Chris oh my
god oh
no dude if it hold I'm adding more no no
oh no I'm getting the back
Muller oh
no Nate there's three left it's like
impossible for me to get
it it's one of me what if it just do Let
It Go
Down actually [ __ ]
hurt Yes actually kind of crush I really
wish you didn't say that oh my God my
heart's pounding
actually that's worse of
the Hope knowing how it feels like
actually makes me more
nervous I hope you get it again
this is like how we should start like if
we are debating something this is how we
should
pick oh my
God oh my God three left again it's got
to just come
down please
again it yeah this is rigged drink up oh
yummy I need to see if it gets it oh
okay squeeze it
[ __ ] a
lot this is giving me a heart attack I'm
scared the back MERS never do you
wrong God I hate when you hear it like
really
click
up God M give it to me
D it yeah it hurts doesn't
it oh my God it like the ti it hurt got
to do it it kind of does hurt e goodbye
allig yeah you whoever Just sh you're
not even hitting it I hit three right
there
you need to go poop I know who whoever
keep farting bro all right Chris what
did you decide on the name of the
alligator I don't know his nameer is
Jerry and he's going to Matt loves
nameing things Jerry do you know do you
know this joke Matt has a stuffed animal
named Jerry and I'm like Jerry the fth
ever since we were kids Matt just named
everything [ __ ] Jerry can you put it
down
matt I think we should name him Alonso
alons
Trevor leaving
buddy one day we're going to Vlog and
Trevor's going to be dead Chris I'm just
saying it like I I I'm not even like in
a negative way I'm just like one day
we're going to go to Vlog Trevor and he
won't be with us cuz he's just a puppy
well he's not a puppy he's actually way
he just said that is like insane like
Trevor is so old he's 9 years old now
and I love him so much he's my cuddly
friend Nick can you take a photo of me
in TR yeah I cannot believe the word
that just came out of your mouth Nick it
wasn't like a negative way it was you
literally said you're like one day we're
going to Vlog Trevor and he's going to
be dead yeah it's true like I'm just
it's the harsh truth yeah let me take a
photo of you guys cuz you know he's
going to die one day do you smell that
smell what The Boy trip oh my God I
smell it Matt smells it Nick can you get
me I'm very happy with the lack of
things in the oh fun fact see this on
the fridge yeah this is Chris's first
ever mockups for his brand logos boys
trip boys trip boys trip boys trip boys
trip boy MX get the camera get the
camera get the camera get the camera
that [ __ ] hurts like you're he's like
pushing my [ __ ] shoulder back like
that's not even funny at all stop boy
strip gritty your turn your turn to
gritty your
turn like I I hate having arguments when
the documentation of me being right is
on [ __ ] camera look at how hard he
pushed me I tried so hard every day to
[ __ ] kill being
dramatic look at this Matt watch stop
look at how hard Matt pushes me here and
tell me I'm being
unreasonable look at how hard he pushes
me that one I handled but oh my God my
whole neck looks like it's I look like a
Jack In The Box it looks like my neck's
going to fall off my body again
again again this is
unbelievable unbelievable and he's mad
cuz I did the exact same thing to him
and he's [ __ ] hitting me all pissed
look at
this this is
unbelievable I can't believe it can you
see it from there can you see it
I can't see hear
anything [ __ ]
unbelievable should we find a place to
sit first or no we find a place to sit
first order what's up
dude hi your out how you doing I got
a I thought he was joking no no we're
YouTubers okay let's
go nice to meet you have a good one nice
to meet you what are you guys going to
eat we should we need a mozzarella stick
that's a group consensus I agree okay
are you feeling
Tipsy that's what it it says that on
there like a plain cheer it freaks me
out in restaurants have this many
options like y'all can make all this
back there that's kind of crazy I want
to own an island I don't care if Max
Island I want to go bowling Beach relax
oh what's that new space camp
everywhere you're a clam chowder hater I
hate you I've never had clam chowder in
my life no way never in my life that
looks good I'm a clam hater you don't
like
seafood I like seafood I'm allergic I
Seafood I eat
it I'm allergic to Seafood really no
you're not no I I really am that Seafood
diet like I'm not like allergic to
Lobster it makes me feel
sick that Seafood diet this isn't funny
you Seafood you eat
it
guys it's one of those
moments life thre a curveball at
us they [ __ ] up my burger they put
lettuce and tomato on it I don't know if
you guys can see that can't do tomato
the
[Music]
Tomato he sound like a four-year-old
trying to say tomato the
Tomato it again I love
booies Gay
what
what put it down
like Matt can I move it it I'm trying to
put it back he's like you got way too
much height on that get away from me eat
your [ __ ] meal see you just said that
it's crazy cuz you it's crazy that the
clouds can block the sun uh-huh right
but what I think is crazy is that the
clouds block the Sun but they don't
block it enough to make the world black
you know what I mean like it doesn't
look like nighttime it's like an
opaqueness
oh that dog looks like a cross-eyed
freak how much I love that thing's not
even cute it's like freaking me out like
it's like looking at me when like I
walked by and it's tongue was already
out it's so cute oh my God I can't look
at it I I can't believe the that tongue
is attached to that he's so cute I can't
believe his tongue is on his body oh he
does he went away want to know what like
blows my mind those cigarettes on the
dash of the dogs not the guy sorry I got
to focus real quick don't Focus don't
Focus o
maybe not that guy that has that dog I'm
going that way by the way we're going to
Adventure at the corner if there's a
spot to pull over do it what do you mean
at the corner like right over here I
want to look at that Outdoor Theater
thing well we can do
that nothing like friendly East Coast
service am I right nothing like
it yes s right here no you already
passed the
corner what are you talking what are you
looking for the park on the corner you
passed the corner Corner no longer do I
need to be pulled over what's your goal
at there was there was a public trash
bin at the corner that I was going to
utilize oh I didn't if you told me if
you said pull over at the trash can I
thought the corner was subjective of
like the corner of the road the corner
is usually where two angles meet exactly
what the [ __ ] I meant no I get that but
I didn't think you actually wanted to be
exactly where the corner met say I never
say something I don't 100% mean all
right whatever dude there Tois on the
side of the road oh my God that's the
stola triplets in Turkey format how
crazy oh my god dude they look so cute
they're kind of [ __ ] hideous when
they stand still you could think they're
statues sh sh Matt tell them what was
what we were doing and what's happening
we were watching plan of the Apes we had
that light on cuz we were eating food
and then Nathan saw a black spot on this
curtain so I turned this light on and
the black spot is a giant centipede on
the window look at it Chris oh my
[ __ ] God I haven't seen it yet it's
huge
what is that it's like no can they can't
fly right no I don't want to kill it
look at on the of that you got to do it
bro let me see this thing look at it
Nick can you get like a good photo to
edit into this Vlog oh it's huge bro
wait it's kind of
cute okay hold on hold on hold on hold
on it's not going to go outside it's
trying to be a superhero it's going to
climb up your arm okay no I will but we
need three paper plates to go boom boom
boom so it lands on the plate and I kill
it on the plate and not the
floor don't you dare [ __ ] with me
mate hold on I think it could be dead
already all you ready go ahead I'm
scared Nick wait hold on Nick get on
light duty no cuz if it comes at me
there's light get on light duty I'll get
light duty youlog duty something too
cray cray what do you mean crazy I'm
like don't like violently shake
it it's off we oh
he oh oh my God okay so that didn't work
I can't sleep here tonight after knowing
what I just
witnessed H he's on the other one I
think we should have terminated him
right away we tried to be nice people we
should H the bar trying to kill him
either way no cuz if I hit H the bar
it's going to land like behind no no
just like kind of give it like a boom
like see what he does not bad not that
hard because you don't want to knock him
Off the Wall he's right there he's on
the left where oh yeah left far left far
left in in the loop in the loop what are
you looking at is he in the curtain
right there he's in the curtain on the
left right there right yes okay wait
where on the left
side where wait I can't wait don't oh he
ran down quick I don't even know where
he is now I don't have a visual look at
this monkey praying for us on the screen
oh he's up to
going where he's up the top he's going
up the top okay should I shake it again
on the side he's on the side Matt you
got to just kill him through the curtain
onto the wall I can't kill this dude
through the Cur onto the wall Matt you
can easily kill it we all give you per
cuz Nate if he's going to keep climbing
threw the curtain into the wall yeah hit
him out the wall give me this you have
this it's it's oh my god do we see him
cuz this
ni push him oh my
God kill switch do it
Nick no where is he where he's dead he's
dead he's dead he's dead he's dead he's
dead he's got to be dead he's got to be
dead oh
no tell your [ __ ] friends don't come
back man take the
Vlog tears in my ass oh my god I've
never jumped up higher and faster in my
life shout out grandpa that was his Cane
oh on you who's taking this thing
outside oh put him on the plates yeah
get the plates get the plates and to
those of you animal lover freak that are
mad that we just killed that bug come
help us where were you at there was
nothing we could have done dude that was
insane dude I'm like sweating like I'm
literally sweating bullets right now my
came back that was gross does anyone
else feel reallyy sh Grandpa and me and
Nate were about to come up with them you
want to know my idea let's hear it I'm
going to get a house boat okay and I'm
going to go like a boat house like a
house boat so the house is already
attached to the boat it's like is the
house the boat or is the is it like a
it's a a boat house a boat with that
looks like a house or is it like a house
that's buoyantly on water a house on
water okay a a houseat
I think that's more of a boat boat
there's a boat like a boat that drives
around but has like multiple bedrooms
inside the boat no he means like a house
floating on top of water that has like a
jet ski attached to the house that you
can I'm just going to search up house
boat and see what pops up I I need a
house boat house boat okay yeah wait
hold
on I need to see like this whoa well I'm
was thinking more of like a real boat so
you want like a yacht is what you're
saying on a boat I just I need no no no
no no I need a boat with like bedrooms
and [ __ ] like that's a boat that's just
like a big
boat what oh I said
bore I'm like why is there a [ __ ]
wilder beast in the
boat look like that's what Nate wants
yeah that's what I need right there that
type of vibe all right and then and then
hold on let me see kid get in the shower
I need what's inside this coconut
[Laughter]
I need this to take photos for my brand
cuz we're dropping a coconut flavor and
Nathan wants to open it so we're going
to go open
it all right ready yeah oh good H oh my
God right away hold on wait Nate wait
thumb it right there don't thumb it
don't thumb it don't thumb it not do it
see wait try again one more bang I'll
probably do
nice nice oh my God you kind of slid
Nate
nice
nice what is this called the the the hay
the hen I don't think it's called Hay I
think it's more husk husk that's exactly
the word I was looking for Nick yeah
what did you do that for you keep wiping
your hands on me like I'm like a big
face cloth yeah yesterday we went out
and we were skipping rock
and Nick has his hand all Sandy and like
I was picking up a rock here and there
and skipping it my hands weren't getting
dirty like I was like picking a rock up
like this off the beach so I really only
was like wiping like two fingers off he
[ __ ] digs a rock out of the sand hand
covered in dirt and sand and he skips a
rock he goes where have you been wiping
your hand I go on my pants like just
like that L like this and he goes okay
yeah and like just goes i s ands his
candy hand all over my [ __ ] hand I
want to kill him wa is it a filter kid
you're seven years old what is
it what is it guys our boys trip our
boys weekend has commenced but our boys
trip has just begun yes right same time
next
weekend right Matt it's kind of hard
when you clarify things as like a boy
trip cuz it really is always an
adventure with us for you know it's boy
life it's always it's always a boys trip
what do you think is so funny Matt Chris
grabed these pizzas and then something
fell on the floor and he went to and he
went to that was a cartoon like if you
record in the fridge and there was a
little monster that was pushing [ __ ] out
I would have been surprised something
fell on the floor and he went to reach
TR and grab it and that exact box of
egos fell and almost in his head yeah
like like if that thing egos was like a
[ __ ] metal grade hand bell
yeah [ __ ] boom boom
dude dude come on is this dude for real
Matt take off TR I'll rip your [ __ ]
Supreme flannel right you will buy it
I'll make you buy it no you won't I'll
make you give me your money put my hat
on my head put my popsicle on my hand no
then no no right say bye to your [ __ ]
shirt say bye to your sweatshirt I don't
care about their sweatshirt this is my
least favorite flannel fru Matt put my
hat on my head can we trade oh your
chain that will gone that would hurt yep
put my hat on my head I'll put my hand
on that you put your hand on this and
then we let go what are you doing do you
know the [ __ ] circus dude with the
ladders that like climb up
it Niche reference or what I know what
you're talking about like the whipping
it up the [ __ ] thing anyway what are
you
doing Red Baron pizza sponsor me you
guys want to know how CHR lives I wake
up eat nothing eat a mini pizza go
outside get home eat another mini pizza
that's what I
do and it's not find down with your girl
you could yeah you could Photoshop Matt
it's like a hundred different locations
right now cuz he's just like standing
against a at the beach say Matt say I'm
at the
beach not at the beach all right guys
today right now it's currently the last
day of May May 31st it's the same day
this video is getting uploaded we forgot
to film an outro per usual but we just
want to say thank you so much for
watching this very long video we hope
you enjoyed it videos like that to film
are so much fun for us recapping like
the best moments of our month especially
when we're back home in Boston we were
here for like a couple weeks now this
has been our longest trip been a month
yeah it's been like our longest trip
home in a while feels good so we did a
lot with our friends and everything but
we're gonna go back to LA soon get some
work done but yeah that was our whole
month of May pretty much and we would
love to start filming longer Vlogs like
that if you guys enjoy it so if you did
like definitely let us know cuz today's
the last day of May so we can get
cooking on June true very true and if
you and if you like it make sure you
like the video so that we know you like
it and as always we're about to go back
to LA which means we're going to get
work done so keep your eyes out for
sternol triplet merch at coco.com
true first link in the description we
hope you guys had a beautiful month we
obviously did as you saw it was very fun
and amazing spent with friends and
family and um go tell someone you love
them and have a beautiful day
[Music]