I'm literally out of breath cuz I'm like
that big.
What are you talking about? Like I went
upstairs quick to grab something before
we started filming and I'm out of
breath. That's nice. Why am I winded? I
went up. I can't fool myself. Don't want
nobody else to ever love me. You are my
shining star, my diamond light, my love
fantasy. It's not a minute, hour, day,
or night that I don't love you. You're
at the top of my list and I know he's
dreaming of you. What would you do if
the world was end
up?
Guys, I'm addicted to this new game
called Royal Kingdom. This is not an ad.
It's so addicting. Ridiculously.
Chris is genuinely like how a person
who's making a royal kingdom ad would
sound is Chris's life motto for the past
week. It's concerning and crazy.
Completely agree. Up everybody. Welcome
to another Sterno triplets Friday video.
Um today we don't really have a goal in
what we're talking about. We just know
that we want to talk. And I feel like
this is when the most magic happens in
the Cernolo TripleA universe, right
Nick? I have no idea what that means.
And I don't know if I agree with it
either with my haircut right now. I
currently feel like like the Soundcloud
rapper that just keeps threatening to
drop music. Like that's how I feel. He's
like I can't have long hair. I'm going
to do something crazy. I just like I
have had the same exact haircut for 5
years. Uh-huh. And it makes me sick to
like see a video from like 5 years ago
today and feel like I look the exact
same. Like I feel like my So what do you
want? You have to do something about
this. You have to cut your hair. I feel
like my physical growth like has like
Chris told me he's like next time I get
a haircut it's going to be crazy. Like
I'm cutting all my hair off. And then he
went to get a haircut and then he came
back in 20 minutes. Like 20 minutes
passed. Mhm. No time passed and you
looked exactly the same. I just can't I
can't pull the trigger on it. I need to
do it. It's time to jump on it. You You
can't get what you don't ask for. I just
want to go to the doctor and bent over
and just put like 40 needles in my back
and test me for everything cuz I keep
sne I just keep sneezing. I keep with
your hair. No, it's like my allergies
and like Yeah, my hair made me think of
it cuz my hair like my hair like coming
down the doctor to bend me over. No, my
hair in my face is making it worse and I
I like just feel like I get it. Oh my
god. Sorry you deal with that. Like
every day I'm sneezing. I'm coughing.
I'm wheezing. I have dust in my throat.
I need to like question. Yeah. Is there
anything me or Matt can do about it? No,
I just No, but I I get this talking to
my bro. I feel like I need to my bros.
When will you understand that we are a
sibling related YouTube channel on the
internet? I will say I will. I will say
I don't think you ever will either. I
will say I've been pondering the thought
of a cat for a really long time and I
think the day will come where I do get
one. It's just like allergies, man. Why
why have to be in some sort of fatherly
role soon? Not like a dad to a baby.
That's insane and intense. But I really
feel like you project this this warm
comfort of needing a cat or dog. Like an
animal would feel so safe in your
presence. And I think you need to to
level up your life. I think taking on
that level of responsibility. You also
talk like you're 50. Like it just would
s like if you were the type of guy who
like brought your dog or cat places you
went, it would add up. And right now I
feel like it's like a missing element in
your projected vibe. Um hello. Um I was
wondering if I could order one
attentions please. It doesn't have to be
in a size large. It can be whatever.
Really bad audio. Really corny. But look
at that. Super cute dog. Can you imagine
that? That's an adult human being who's
saying those words. Probably my dad. I
just want to take a spoon to the back of
my [ __ ] eye socket and go like that.
Pop it out. I want to re reverse what I
just watched. Oh my god.
[Music]
Spinning him around like a little
helicopter. Super cute. Back to the
allergy [ __ ] I feel No, I swear I don't
want to seriously I feel like I wake up
every day not reaching my full practical
limit of like a human being because of
my allergies. I feel hindered every day.
Hindered. And I want I want I want
everyone to know that. Wow. I'm happy
that you're expressing that. If that's
something you feel like you need to
express, I'm happy you did it. Loud and
proud. That one podcast episode where
Chris sneezes the whole time. That's
what the vibe he's been on recently.
It's just like I can't I feel like I
like if I'm sneezing before I'm even
like getting out of bed in the morning.
I sneeze before I feel hunger. Why do I
feel like I can't get up and then put a
nice outfit on. Oh, and you don't. So I
I get it. Like I'm just like I'm like
I'm like you witness that behavior every
I've been wanting to wear this nice new
thing I got, not wearing it today cuz
I'm a sneezing mess. And then I end up
wearing like just neutral clothes again,
like jeans and a black shirt. There's
nothing wrong with that. And there's
nothing wrong with it, but it's like
sometimes I just want How is one to
elevate with sneezy attitude? Could I
could I wear a vest practically and be
sneezing to this limit? No. I'd be like,
why does a sneezer have a vest on get
him some allergy meds? He should be
chilling in a black tea till then.
You're right. That would be my someone
sneeze. I'm like, why are you in the way
allergies that's like hindering your
breathing and also multi-layer of
fashionable outfit? You can't do those.
It just blows my mind that only 50 like
only like some people get allergies and
these guys podcast equipment, you know.
Seriously. Also, AI is a horrible thing.
Ridiculous. Really bad out by AI. Um,
and I don't like it. I think that like
it get behind it. I hate the mermaid
videos. I hate AI. I hate it. I hate
seeing a still image of me moving and
dancing.
Yeah, especially bald, too. Like, what
what are we doing? I did do a little AI
of my own the other day. Oh, god. Cuz I
saw I was like, I have to see what's up
before this takes over the world. Like,
I don't want to be I don't want to be
like I don't care to learn more about
AI. I don't want to know, but I don't
want to be the loopy old [ __ ] that is
just so convinced that AI is real. So,
it's like in order for AI to not take
advantage of me and my my
I'm like I need to stay on top of this
so it doesn't bite me in the ass, you
know? I need to make sure I'm aware.
Look, this photo driver cute, but I was
like also not a good photo. Like, I was
like, I don't understand how AI is going
to like do something with this.
Oh my gosh.
Art. This is the most peaceful and
accurate depiction of Trevor I've ever
seen in my life. Can I see?
So cute. It is really cute. AI
generated. I'm like, wait, can you take
a picture of me and AI generated right
now? No, I don't want to see what that
is. AI generate shirtless. Okay.
Oh my god.
Oh my god. Hey.
Hey there. How's it going? What's up
with you today? Uh, let me know if
there's anything fun or interesting you
want to chat about. Uh, yeah. That's why
I'm summoning you. Can you um can if I
submit a photo, can you do it in some
sort of like artistic art style? Can you
give me a little art feedback?
Absolutely. I'd love to help out with
that. Um, just go ahead and share the
photo and we can get creative with some
art styles and feedback. Okay.
Sickening. Hey. Hey, King Candy. Look at
your [ __ ] phone. Hold on. You got I'm
in the middle of a level now. Give me a
second. You're also in the middle of
[ __ ] filming a video. Hold on. I have
to get 99 tulips. How about you get two
lips on this dick?
All right, we need What would you do if
the world was end and jump off a
building to talk to your crush? Take all
your secrets and prize possessions. Burn
them or give them to someone you trust.
I think that we have I'll be cool with
the world on fire as long as everything
cord with us. Uh, what are your thoughts
on Nino Paid, the new upcoming artist? I
have no idea who that is.
That's not funny. I genuinely couldn't
even [ __ ] paint a picture in my
brain. It's just so funny how in two
different worlds you guys are. I think
Nemo paid Nino N I N I N O, not Nemo.
I think that me and Nick being on like
polar opposite sides of like media
media, I guess. but also just like like
the things we enjoy is a blessing in
disguise because it's just so amazing.
Every day I hang out with Nick I feel
like I'm learning something new. Yeah. I
feel like I unwarrantedly learn a lot
from you as well. Yeah. Like Nick, tell
us about the OKC Pacers game the other
night. Oh, like how the Pacers won. Has
there been any update here? No. Yeah.
OKC won. Yeah. OKC won the second game.
So it's tied 1-1. So you score. Yeah.
Okay. So the Pacers beat OKC which is
crazy because they were not projected to
do that and then they did and now the
series is tied 1 to1 in the seven game
series first to four win and take the
NBA final which would be crazy because
in the NBA finals we're looking OKC and
the Pacers are both
first time um first time competing for a
final. Yep. They're not first time
competing for a final. They just never
won a final. Oh both teams have never
won a final. So, so it's it's really
serious because it's tense because both
teams are playing for something they've
never achieved. Wow, Nick. It's really
crazy. Yeah. Um, look at this. What is
it? OM can see it. Let me see it. No,
let me see. I need to take a picture
with Trevor and he needs Let me see
that. And he let me see it. And we need
to be AIDed together.
It's kind of creepy, but I like how they
put our YouTube plaques. Whoa. Like,
look at my tattoos, too.
Let me see that. Yeah, it's like very
fun. Whoa. I'm I'm very afraid of AI.
Yeah, it's very frightening. It's a
little crazy. I don't like rewarding AI
either. Like you I feel like telling him
like that was you didn't do a good job.
You'll never beat I got to tell him
actually. Hold on. Hey.
Hey.
Hello.
Hey. I'm here. No worries. Yeah. You
need you need to speak to me.
I'm here for you. Sorry if there was a
little delay there. Let me know. Um, I
just want to let you know, thank you
first of all, but you will never surpass
the ability of human life. And I think
that I I don't want you to get any
[ __ ] ideas amongst you or your
friends and thinking you're going to
take over, none of that. And I want no
part in it. And I just don't want you
guys to become advances human beings, at
least in my lifetime. Appreciate you
sharing your thoughts with me. My main
goal is to be helpful and supportive. If
there's anything specific you'd like to
talk about or any way I can assist, just
let me know. Yeah, thanks. I didn't like
the attitude he had. My goal is to be
supportive. Like, okay. Yeah, you better
not [ __ ] twist that [ __ ] around. One
day, a million robots are going to kick
in our door and say, "Where's the one in
the brown hoodie that disrespected our
our our founder years ago?" And they're
going to stomp up your room like
one by one like this.
They're going to say, "He's in here."
And they're going to kick in your door
and what? Generate an image. No. And
you're in and you're weak human body
won't be enough to defeat the army of AI
robots. That a genuine fear. Like I
think that that's a valid thing. Yeah.
And you just you just literally cuz it's
like you documented it. One, he tracks
everything you say forever. That will
forever be in the internet of the AI web
is you just disrespect him. And now
they're going to see me and they're
going to be like, "Oh, everything's
cordial between me and and Black thermal
there because
he was he was he was actually speaking
his mind." So what you're saying is he
should apologize. I wouldn't apologize.
I just would put that on your radar for
the future. If you're the AI starts to
advance, I should know I'm If AI starts
to advance, the people that knew it was
coming and disrespected them are the
first targets.
What animals do you think would be gay
if there's some that could be gay? I
feel like
got to be a peacock, right? All birds.
Every bird. Yeah, cuz you got to think
like 2can.
No, cuz toucan Sam definitely like
Toucan Sam is probably the fruiest
mascot of all time. Really, bro? His
cereal is fruitless. Well, Tony the
Tiger is straight 100%. Tony the Tiger
is not. You don't think he's straight?
The tiger is like a like
I can't even say it actually because of
our current target audience. Like I
don't even want to say what I'm
thinking. Oh, I think Tony the I think
Tony the Tiger's like,
but I don't think it's like it's like
sexual orientation specific. No, he's
just him. Yeah, he's him. I feel like
every cereal is a little gay. Like Snap,
Crackle, Pop is not gay. Gay gay. They
are all twinks, right? All three of
them. No, Crackle might be straight.
Snap, Crackle, and Pop are the three gay
musketeers. Really? They're forefronted.
How do you feel about trying to think?
I'm not really getting any straight
energy. Maybe Captain Crunch is
straight. Oh, for sure. Captain Crunch
is straight. I think that for sure um
the cinnamon and apple guy. Mhm.
Cinnamon. The cinnamon and apple jack.
They're straight too cuz they're very
like ordinary looking. Like in the new
packaging they got rid of all of the
personality in Cinnamon.
Where did all of Cinnamon's personality
go? It's insane. Completely diminished.
It looks like Spongebob when he's
normal. Like I'm like normal Sponge. I'm
like where is Cinnamon?
They've erased Cinnamon's culture and I
hate it. I completely agree with that.
They destroyed and ruined Hold on real.
If you could pick one animal to talk,
like kind of how like what's that bird
that could talk? Parrot. Yeah. If if you
could pick an animal that like took the
parrot's ability to talk, what animal
would it be? And why? And like would you
have it as a pet if you could? Sorry, so
many. It's it's a lot of question. It's
a what if. It's like a and and so it's
like tell me. It's like a here's the
question then you have to elaborate.
Yeah. Yeah. Um I feel like you got to
say dog or cat. Wrong. That's what they
want you to say. That's the bait answer.
But it's never going to happen for me
because
this everyone at home is sitting and
thinking, "Oh, they're going to say dog
and cat because we live with them." But
that's the exact reason we would revoke
that privilege in my opinion because I
don't want someone spreading my
business. A dog's supposed to sit there
and be a good boy like it's supposed to
be. Like I don't need like if I have a
dog that can speak now I have another
thing that's hassling me every single
day that's adding to something that it
shouldn't be adding to. You are better
off as a dog. Wag your tail. Correct.
That's how I feel. Like I don't know. I
just like imagine like another thing
that like Yeah. I can't say I want a
creature I possess to speak to me. Yeah.
It would freak me out. Stop. Really?
Yes. It would sometimes I look at Trevor
and I'm like what would you say to me
right now? But it also like all parrots
do is repeat. I'm like if you're going
to say this, at least have an original
thought. Like you're just speaking.
You're saying what I said. I don't think
they know what they're saying. No, they
do. They have no idea. Have you seen
that video? The guy's like, "What's
this?" Ah, fork. And then he's like,
"Um, what what is this metal?" And then
he's like, "Okay, what? Um, what is
this?" He's like, "Basket." And then he
like fully knows everything. The guy
showing you a basket. Yes. He's
learning. A parent can't say when it
hasn't heard. Correct. Yes. But neither
could you. Yes, I could. Yes. If you're
reading it, but they don't have the
ability to read. But like they That's
not why I can say whatever I want. Nick,
how did you learn every word? You know,
cuz I speak English cuz you heard it.
Someone else said it fully taught, but
you couldn't teach a full parrot to form
full sentences. Correct. But the fact if
you hold up something and they're like,
"Yeah, okay. That's mental. Mental."
What are your thoughts? It's called like
Bunny, the dog that like hits the
button. He's like, "I got to go
outside."
The dog Bunny. And he's like hitting the
button. He's like, "Yeah, I got to go
outside. Chill." I know. What? He's
like, "Yeah, no, I'm chilling." But then
he has like a tree button. I feel like a
dog can't have a treat button. Maybe
dinner walk later. I'm like, you don't
get to call the shots, Bunny? You go out
when your owner brings you on a walk.
She's like, I go on a walk. He's like,
maybe snack out later. Ah, you can't
build a schedule, Bunny. You don't get
that choice. But I guess you do cuz your
owner gave you the privilege of 80
talking buttons. What the [ __ ] is that
one dog? And it's like, hell no. Hell
no. Similar vibe. Similar. It's the dog.
And they're like, they'll literally ask
like a full question or like they'll be
fighting. He's like talking to him with
like a hundred buttons on the floor. I I
can't even think of an example other
than like walk later. I'm like, what? My
allergies are hurting me.
[Laughter]
Freak. Poor guy. My eyes are itchy.
Do I look fat in the shirt? Yes,
actually. No. Bro, Chris burps and I
always laugh at him and make fun of him
when he does cuz when he burps it sounds
like he's morphing into a human body.
Like he's like
It is a lot. I'm like, how are you?
Like, it seems like you're just
possessing the body you're in. If you
could have picked your name, what do you
think you would have picked?
My middle name is Antonio. And I was
when I was a kid, I I bizarly craved
that to be my first name. But I do feel
like it's on a deeper level cuz maybe
you didn't recognize yourself in the in
the name Nick or just who you are. No.
No. No.
[Laughter]
Stop coughing now. Put that down. Metal
can.
Put down. Okay. When you name stuffed
animals, what? Like what's your what's
the quality? What's the procure? Are you
fluffy? Are you I don't know. Honestly,
I have like like Chris has a jelly cat
bunny that I got him in Italy. His
name's Willamin or Fry. Yeah. Yeah. I
don't know how he landed on Willamir
fry. It was It used to be waffle fry and
we like no that's too silly of a name.
We need something fancy. So we were like
Willaminer fry is better. Yeah. Short
for waffle fry. Yes. No long extended.
Yeah. Willaminer fry. Yes. Waffle fry
for short. WF for super short. Yeah. So
will fry. Waffle fry. WF. Yeah. And then
I feel like WF like if I'm there I'm
just saying waffle fry. No WF. Okay.
Quick. It's simple. What else? Remember
Rich and I burnt his head on the stove?
Oh, I have Rich still. I had a stuffed
animal named Rich. Matt lit him on fire.
I'm trying to think like I have a lot of
um I had a couple named Jerry at some
point. Dude, every stuffed animal dog
you got for seven years in a row is
Jerry. It's not true. There like the two
that I have that just like kind of sit
there like pumpkin and popcorn, but it's
like I can't name you something else.
That's what you are. You're a pumpkin
and that's a popcorn thing. His name
could be like pop.
How long do you think it would take you
to fold a fitted sheet by yourself?
Bless you. I don't think that that's a
challenge really. I think I could do it
as much as I could fold anything else.
You can fold a fitted sheet easily. Go
get a fitted sheet and fold it.
Absolutely not. Fitted sheet is not a
difficult task to It's like not hard to
fold a sheet. I agree. People just make
it a big deal cuz they're [ __ ]
stupid.
I agree. Just fold it. I mean, yeah,
it's always nice to have some help when
you're sheeting your bed.
Don't sheet your bed.
Stupid.
Stop looking at me all. What's the
weirdest thing you've ever seen in
somebody else's house? Like you were at
their house and you're just like,
"What?"
And you were just like, "What is the
purpose of this?"
You guys know I can't share my answer to
that. Yeah, I know. Maybe one day.
Maybe. Holy smokes.
I'm like getting flashbacks. Um, the
weirdest thing I've seen at somebody
else's house is a sink, but the pipe
goes all the way through the ceiling.
Yeah. Like it was like imagine a kitchen
drain except the sink that led to like
the spout of the sink like where the
water 7 ft tall and goes to the like the
water came from. The sink was just like
a giant pipe through the roof
and then it just landed in the sink.
Yeah. You get off of royal crush or
royal whatever kid. Royal, you are going
to be the you are the heir to no throne
and you will never be king no matter how
many [ __ ] rounds of matching colorful
blocks you play. Stop. Do you ever have
fun or is your whole goal to just be a
manipulative psychopath angry loser?
Hair on your [ __ ] chinny chin chin.
Stop manipulative. You're playing royal
crush. Royal Kingdom. You're playing
Royal Kingdom and I'm telling you to
stop matching blocks cuz we're filming a
YouTube video and I'm manipulative. What
am I manipulating? I'm joking around. My
god. Do you ever have fun? Like, are you
the just most angry person ever? Nick,
what is your preferred way of
communication with you? If if we like
have if if I've talked like the lights,
I prefer the lights. Flash them.
If I if I just met you and we've talked
like we've met two times in person and
we've like texted here and there. If I
FaceTime you are are you answering?
Absolutely not. Someone called my phone
the other day that I don't know. Mhm.
Lucky to have their name in my phone,
right? Call me. Give me [ __ ] for not
answering. I said if my mother called me
out of the blue without a warning, I
would still debate answering the phone.
need 5 minutes to gather myself. Yeah,
you have like calling someone out of the
blue is something that is so outdated.
We're done with that. I have like a
select my phone in I have like a select
five people that can call me out of the
blue and that's it. Yeah. No, I take
that back. I'd answer if mom called me
right away. Yeah, obviously. Same. Just
think like sure if you call me your your
odds of me picking up just got 75%
higher that or let me be generous here
90% higher than if if you facetimed me
100%. I'm almost never available for
like an out loud FaceTime. Yeah. No,
it's also like I think that because
we're always together people don't
understand.
Did a [ __ ] Did I just land in
Paradise Palm? Just enough, you know?
Like we're always together triplets. I'm
done. No, because we're always together
as triplets. People think we're going to
answer the phone and just be on
FaceTime. Like, I'm not going to be on
FaceTime. I'm with my brothers. Text me.
What What purchase have you ever made
that you think that you just are going
to regret the most? Like, what's
something you bought that you're just
like, "Oh, I shouldn't have bought
that." My bed frame. Really? That big
brown Jumanji board looking bed frame. I
have
You could add a flag and float that [ __ ]
down a [ __ ] sea of water. It is so
close to being a boat.
Need to upgrade my bed frame soon. A
[ __ ] pirate flag and a sail. I could
take that thing across the [ __ ] blue
sky. Seriously, I could cloud watch
while I pirate and retrieve gold from
other [ __ ] sea watchers on my bed
frame.
If Jack and Rose had my bed frame and
the Titanic sunk, them two and 20 other
passengers of the Titanic could have
[ __ ] skived away freely on my [ __ ]
junky gigantic bed frame.
You could lay my [ __ ] bed frame flat
and have Super Bowl 51
across my thing. There is enough yard
line footage.
Actually, if the Pacers or Oklahoma
City, whoever wins, build them a new
[ __ ] court out of my bed frame. Glaze
the wood, sand it, whatever you have to
do. There's plenty. They'll probably
just ask you to do that. Sand it. No,
glaze the wood. You need to stop now
during Pride Month. It's Pride Month.
You're talking about glazing wood or
telling me to glaze wood.
Nick, that was unbelievable. Yeah, I'd
have to say my um your bed frame. Guys,
I'm still thinking about getting a cat.
Oh my god. We need to get allergy shots.
We need to get Tell me about I need to
get blood drawn from my body and tested.
Yeah,
let's just do it through the palm of
your hand.
No, guys, I've been really feeling
lately like, oh my god, the days are
getting longer. The sun is feeling
The sun is feeling so warm.
I'm happy being with my brothers every
day.
And I
The sun is hot. The days are long. That
doesn't break into song.
I just am so grateful. And I'm so
thankful.
So grateful. Sun is hot. I don't know.
I'm just I'm feeling great right now. I
hate that the sun is hot. No, I like
feeling the warm. I hate it. There's
nothing I want more than You have back
and forth this opinion on the sun. No, I
hate feeling Stop tapping your [ __ ]
foot. I'm not. It totally depends how
much water I drink that if whether or
not I like hot sun. I like feeling the
sun when I'm like in my backyard or
something because then I can just go
inside. When you're at like Disneyland
walking around, it's like oh my god.
Cool breeze could help, but
I get it. You know what I mean? Like,
can we stop? Yeah, sure. Rapid fire
question time. Ready? Yes. I'm so
scared. Go. Dunkin Donuts or Starbucks?
Dunkin Donuts.
Pumpkins or apples? Pumpkin? Pumpkins
and apples. Pumpkin or apple pie?
Pumpkin. Apple pie. LA or Boston?
Like what is why is your go-to Mario
Kart and Mario character Waluigi? Just
gravitated toward his vibe from a young
age. Really? Yeah. From a young age.
From a young age. I was just like,
"Yeah, I love that guy." Really? Yeah. I
was like, there was that photo of me and
we were Did it help with your gay
awakening?
High potential, honestly. Tall, dark
hair, mustache, kind of goofy.
Yeah, maybe probably honestly had a
major part. You really think that? Yes.
Yeah, I do, Matt. I remember like
seven-year-old me probably being like,
"Damn, yeah, Daisy. I'd do it." Daisy's
your vibe more than Peach. Hell yeah.
See, I'm the type of guy that doesn't
have a preference there. All right, [ __ ]
it. I [ __ ] with Kitty Peach's vibes. I
always use Kitty Peach when I'm playing
Mario Kart. Yeah, it's a little freaky
to me. I don't know. I just I kind of
wanted to pick something that, you know,
would would be unexpecting. That's the
type of guy I am. I want you to think
something of me and then I'll show you
the polar opposite. Yeah. That's kind of
my vibe. Like if people think I'm going
to do something, I want to do the toad.
Cuz people are going to be like, "Oh,
Chris is the type of guy to go Yoshi."
And then boom, you're kitty peach.
People are like probably expecting to be
like Toad or like some some I don't
know. But I feel like throwing a kitty
peach at them is kind of like whoa.
Yeah. But now I feel like But now I feel
like people are starting to realize that
that's my norm and I need to switch back
to something else. You know what I mean?
Like you can't do too much of the goofy
like unexpected [ __ ] You got to like
lock in sometimes. Nate's a Koopa Troopa
guy and I've always respected him for
that. Yeah, for sure. Be mad at the way
you look cuz you're like eating your own
chin.
He's going to be like, "Nick, the camera
angle is [ __ ] awful. I look bad in
the video." You're like, "Surprised
you're not eating anything."
Did we say should we try to start a trio
ac capella group? No. What would it be
called? It would probably be the triple
the already. No. No. Triple [ __ ]
Triple triple trouble. Triple [ __ ]
freak. Triple triple my [ __ ] Triple. I
hate I hate like Oh my god. Do you know
how many I hate when someone comes up to
us three and they're like, "Oh, the
three musketeers."
Do you for one split of a millisecond
feel like you've just come up with
something unique? One thing I hate is
modernized slang or just goofy [ __ ]
making its way into vintage nostalgic
vibes.
Did you you thought you ate that one,
huh? And what I mean by that Yeah.
Please listen. The other day me and Matt
were at like this very nice lunch spot,
okay? And we went without you cuz we
hate you, okay? And Matt doesn't seem to
remember. Oh, I I am. It's like a nice
vintage like like lunch area. Like you
can tell it's like groovy. It's just
like classic. Like you feel like you're
kind of in like a time machine there.
But on the wall they have some goofy
[ __ ] that says like, "Oh, you ate and
left no crumbs." Like in like stencil
writing on the wall. And I'm like I'm
like why is this like the most glorious
fantastic
vibe setting place? And you have to
[ __ ] destroy it by this modernized
goofy slang cut out of vinyl papers and
stuck to your walls. Like you might need
to realize like ruin it all. People need
to realize when it's time to let the
doves fly on certain things. You know
what I mean? Like you ate and left no
crumbs.
Let the doves fly. It's over. It should
be gone and it should be done. Me and
Matt just went to the Lilo and Stitch
movie. Fire. Have to watch it. Really
good. Chris came home. He's like, I was
watching the movie the whole time,
smiling ear to ear. It was He was having
my favorite things I've ever seen. It's
the most I've heard Chris laugh like
sitting next to him in a movie before.
It was really funny. It was actually
really funny. It was just super cute. It
was just I couldn't take it cuz like if
I was checking my phone, he'd like smack
of like Lilo and Stitch like the
characters. Like I just really like
Stitch. I think he's awesome. And I just
think like the whole vibe of that is
unbelievable.
I love how like Disney just always
throws something like heart-wrenching in
like a phenomenal story cuz it's like
there was a moment where Stitch
literally I was about to cry and then a
minute later I was like dying laughing.
I was like thank you God. I was like oh
my god like the fact that Disney Stitch
the fact that Disney has the ability to
like make you feel so many emotions in
one movie is well that's like when
there's child actors like the girl
playing Lilo it's unreal. She she killed
it. She was phenomenal. No, me, Chris,
and Sam were actually talking about how
impressive it was that she was acting
with obviously like a CGIed thing. Like,
she killed it, bro. Shout out to Lilo.
What's her name in her life? I don't
know. It was literally one of the best
movies. I haven't watched it. They were
good. You have to watch it. My favorite
part is Stitch has like the gun, the
soda gun. It was bang bang bang bang.
It's really It was really funny. I got
to watch it. All your secrets and prized
possessions. Burn them, but give them to
someone you trust. Boom. And then that's
when the edit starts. And it's like I'll
be cool with the world. Everything
cordial with us. That's the vibe. I see
the vision.
I haven't edited I haven't edit farmed
recently. It's kind of upsetting. I
know. What do you smile at your phone
for? Big sexy. Don't talk to me like
that. Seriously, ever again. What's
What's going on? Tell everyone on the
world that's tuning in. Okay. Do we
bring up the stalkers or what?
Hey guys, really quick. Just want to
address something. We had a situation
where we had some people invade our
privacy and show up to our house. We
know a lot of you guys are worried about
us, but we are completely safe. We're
completely fine. Um, in our position,
when you post a lot of your private life
on social media, you have some people
that take it too far and invade your
privacy. Um, it's just something we've
had to deal with before. It's something
we've had to deal with recently. We're
safe. We're okay. We just want you guys
to know that we're not going to bring
too much light to the situation cuz
we're we're feeling positive. We're
excited. And we're just going to move
on. So, we appreciate your guys'
concern, but we're good. Our privacy is
maybe something we can have a
conversation about down the line, but
right now, we're feeling extremely
positive and excited to just move
forward, and we're feeling great.
[Music]