Hello Sharks. My name is Mattie Salin
and my product is called Wake and Bacon.
I'm asking for $40,000 in return for 20%
equity.
So, while I was getting my master's
degree at NYU University, I took an
introductory electronics course where we
had to make a device for the home. And I
wanted to remake an alarm clock. And so,
I canvased my fellow students asking
them what their ideal way to wake up
was. Now, I can't say what the number
one answer was on
television, but the close second was the
smell and taste of bacon. And so
inspired, I went home and I built the
world's first alarm clock that actually
wakes you up with
bacon. Here's how it works. So, the
night before you open up the chamber and
you put in a couple of slices of
pre-cooked bacon, and then you set the
alarm for, say, 7 a.m. The next morning
at 6:50, the clock silently turns on,
and it heats up the bacon to a crisp so
that the smell is really strong and can
wake up any bacon lover. You can then
actually just roll over in bed, open it
up, and eat the bacon yourself. You can
cook the bacon and then eat it. That's
right. Shut up. I'm serious.
I built this and I thought it was a
lark. So, I posted on my website and
wake and bacon went viral. I've been
inundated with hundreds and hundreds of
emails of people who are begging me to
sell them one. And so, with the money
I'm asking for, I want to redesign this
for mass production and get a functional
prototype so that I can go pitch this to
retail partners and manufacturing
partners and investors. I've actually
got an artist rendering of what it could
look like if mass-produced. Notice the
hose.
And this is what it looks like with the
tray open. And the cord is a little
corkcrew. I thought of everything.
Can we try it? Oh, absolutely. In fact,
um I've got some for you right now.
Hey, Maddie, I I love the face of the
pig. Do you have a slogan for this or
anything? Rise and swine.
Oh, lordy. Matt, how long does it take
to cook? Uh, it takes 10 minutes to
reheat. So, Maddie, what happens when
we've sold 10,000 of these and the
10,000 and first catches on fire and
burns the couple to death in their bed?
Well, it needs it. It has to be
ULlisted, which means it's safe for the
home for any I'm going to ask you. You
think they want an oven cooking bacon
next to a bed? Well, you know, there's
the uh Easy Bake oven out there. What
about next to somebody's bed at 2:00 in
the morning? You don't know where a
kid's going to put the Easy Bake oven.
If they if they made it through that,
then I'm sure that I can find a way to
get this UL listed and safe for the
home.
This is fantastic. You have any idea of
pricing? Do you know what your margins
will be? So, it'd be about $13 per unit.
I mean, you're asking for $40,000. So,
once you burn through the 40 to make the
prototype, where's the money going to
come from to sell it? I want the money
so that I can then pitch this to retail
partners and manufacturing partners.
Matt, let me see if I get this right.
This is a novelty item. Yes. You think
you can sell how many units? I'm not
sure. I don't have a projection of how
many units I could sell.
At least throw out a forecast. Say 1.26
million in the first quarter. Even if
you're lying to me, at least that's
interesting. You got no projections
whatsoever. You got a pig box that's
going to catch on fire and kill
somebody. I'm going to be sued into the
stone age. I'm out, but I'll give you
100 bucks for the pig box.
Is the pig box for sale? Uh, no. It's
the only one I have.
Maddie, I think your idea is whimsical
and it's a great novelty gift. Thank
you. That's my compliment. I don't think
anyone really wants to have bacon that
close when they're waking up. I think
they like smelling in the kitchen that
mom's making. So, I'm out. All right,
I'm taking my piece of bacon and I'm
out. All
right. I like I like bacon.
Get on it. In or out?
I'm out. All right. Let me ask you this,
Maddie. What do you think the minimum
production run is? Um, I think it's
10,000 is the lowest I can go. So, that
means if your full cost for these is 15
bucks a unit, basically 13 bucks a unit.
So, it' be $130,000. Where is that money
coming from? That's where I need to
partner with a retail partner or a
manufacturing partner or an investor.
You're not going to put your name on
this cuz I'm going to sue you into the
stone age after my bed catches on fire.
I know how to buy insurance. So, we can
deal with that. The bigger problem that
I have literally and being very
interested is you needed
$170,000. You only asked for 40.
I'm now asking for $170,000.
[Laughter]
Mark, are you really interested in this?
I like the idea. You really think
cooking bacon bedside is a good idea? It
doesn't matter. If I had to guess the
percentage of people who would actually
make bacon, I'd say 10%. And if I had to
guess the number of people who would
make bacon twice, I'd say 0%. How many%
set the house on fire? Well, that's what
the the point though is they're not
going to use it to make bacon. This is
going to be a present for dad because
it's so darn stupid.
And Mark Cuban puts his dough into
stupid ideas. Is that what I'm here for
today? It's a gag gift. The problem is
I'm not going to put up the 130,000.
That's the problem.
Because of that, Maddie, I'm out. All
right. Thank you for your time. Okay.
I'll give you 200 bucks for the pig box.
Listen, I figure I'm going to save
children by doing that. We're going to
put that in my museum of really bad
ideas that can kill
people. Okay. Hey, 300 bucks to the pig
box,
Maddie. Thank you. Thank you. Good luck,
Matt. Good luck, man. Thank you.
I wonder if he has any extra bacon on
him. So, basically, Mark, if you would
have asked for 170,000, you were in. I
would have tried to get you guys
involved and I would tried to sell
y'all. We would have said no. I'm very
persuasive. We slaughtered that one.
People love bacon and bacon mania is
sweeping the nation. I'm going to find a
way to build wake and bacon and get it
on every nightstand in America.