all right guys it's been almost a year
since the last time we filmed one of
these I think these are going fueled up
huh this is
crazy
say
all from the island to Madrid we had a
lot of plans but they
all because of someid but it's okay cuz
I'm moving
different this is wild
oh my
God okay all right oh my God I
actually you're insane oh my god oh
mine's empty yeah Nick just put it down
all right welcome back to
another that was so loud today we're
going to be baking blind deaf and mute
one of us is going to be each of those
and then we're going to try and assemble
a beautiful array of cupcakes yes we've
done this so many times but time do it
again we waited like a really good
amount of time to do it so we didn't
become a [ __ ] Baking Channel so I
think that they've waited the perfect
amount of time since the last time we've
done this to do it again yes I agree hey
Siri flip a coin it's Tails so you're
blind so I'm blind [ __ ] okay I'm blind n
kid I'll be blind no I don't care I
don't care I don't care why you scream
[ __ ] that's what I picked in on your own
M I don't care I'll be blind someone
give me a bandana or something let me c
some
songs oh brother yes all right y'all I
canot hear [ __ ] let's get after it I
can't hear a thing all right are we
starting I feel really [ __ ] dizzy hey
Chris are you ready to
start your comfor like dirt all right y'
we're going to do this together we're
making cupcakes today let's get the box
where's our cupcake
trays I think they're in the drawer as a
or do you guys want to make a full cake
or cupcakes I don't care cupcake cakes
or cake Matt cup small
gotcha what are we doing
Nick
hey what's God where is he Matt [ __ ]
gut punch me are you dumb I can't hear
we're making cupcakes Chris all right
there we
go just saying my
name just open that right where you are
that's what Matt's trying to tell you I
can feel
it dump
[Applause]
[Music]
it what's going on why does he sound
like an elephant all right we're done
all right Chris Matt wants me to tell
you something yes what the stop moving
Chris stop hitting
him stop throwing your hands up you
can't see are you
dumb how many eggs all right you need a
half of a cup of
oil so oil's on table and you have you
have your
cup so put half of a cup of that into
the big mixing bowl I'll tell you
exactly what I'll tell you go go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go stop
[ __ ] I mad I didn't realize that was two
cups so our measuring cup is actually
two cups a cup so you got to dump some
back I can't
see all right keep going keep going keep
going okay stop now hold the cup up and
stay still so I can measure read in my
eyes a little bit more back in the big
thing stop you're missing hold it
straight hold it straight
perfect that's good right
Matt is it good Matt Matt you can see
that I'm going for a high five
now all right how many three of those
three of
those be careful slow and steady wins
the race you going put them in the
[Music]
cup all right yes team
nice nice nice That's M said all right
hey can I get a paper towel Nick you got
a whisk it paper towel whisk it paper
towel the Whisk over there let me have a
paper towel the Whisk is a paper
towel here's a bunch thank
you more no what one no you have hands
right no where's the Whisk it's on the
table it's in a secret spot Matt said
wait oh we're missing an ingredients
what are we missing all right so you got
to actually get those eggshells out of
the egg out of the
cup I'm not doing that what is mad again
he's he can't rest the cheat come on
there no fun what is he not allowed to
do is
talk what just happened are you gross
[ __ ] I I
can't what's going on stop yelling at me
[ __ ] you doing don't run by me like a
[ __ ] tornado what's going on get out
who's rolling stuff what's going on he
just bent over in front of me what are
you doing Matt was yelling at me and now
I'm covered in baby chicken what can we
just Hest these are
the you think you can be my one
and shut the the [ __ ] up what's going on
who's breaking Stu all right we got the
measuring cup again all right I got to
whisk it what's going on stop fitting me
with this put a cup of water in
there where's the
water where's the water take the water
on the
fridge did you change the filter on this
thing so bring the cup to the fridge
that's what Matt is saying and he's
saying fill it with
water or hold it with your thumb and
point at it is it filling ass fresh love
is it filling
fil
perfect okay
wait
more more a heart like fun more little
time with me you're good Chris oh down
to B in the bowl no no no God no too
much too much or too little little too
much right Matt how much does you need
to get
out half of what you have right half
half a
[Applause]
quarter these are the requirements a
fourth no not the floor I got a cup for
you go
stop hold it flat hold it flat flat
flat that's good add it where's the
bowl
whisk where's the Whisk we need more
eggs whs to the shopping list eggs we
did like seven eggs grab the Whisk where
is it the
table could you hold me through the
night Wix gentle Wix whisk gentle see
are you dumb who whisks like that a
buffoon
it's too water die me I got it I got it
I got it tough stuff move I got
it if you think you can be my way and
only true love you must promise to love
me and damn it if
you is a good
M keep whisking [ __ ] I see chunks T he
CLS you got to get in there put some
wrist I know you got it that's what Matt
said he said whisk harder right
Matt bad whisking bad whisking yeah I
feel like I'm whisking a [ __ ] chicken
noodle soup what's going on I'm
literally covered in egg Y is it good
whisk whisk whisk whisk whisk whis you
got you on the sides whisk whisk whisk I
see chunk I see clunk I don't want to
see
it but be careful and gentle you just
got to get the sides more obviously is
it is it
good um add whisk it some more oh my God
it just looks thin we need to thicken it
it good now never n come on there's like
chunks on it I'm like trying to tell you
what you can say where on the
side thank you Matt paper
towel hey Nick paper
towel like you did all right but you
could have done so much better it's not
even towel the bowls that way put paper
towel you're gross your hands are like
sticky yeah I want to wipe them off give
me a paper freaking me out he's coming
at me like going to grab me with gross
hands like who do I look like Nick I
need a towel or something
[Applause]
Nick like come
on here you go who is this kid kid put
your paws down I don't want those gross
things near me those
mix like
me I'm sorry I'm done I'm done I'm done
I'm done I'm done I'm done I'm done I'm
done he can't even see it he's chasing
me like are you
dumb who are you who are
you no talking it's
Matt I will murder him all right what's
next are we
whis we're doing good all together we're
working together awesome are we whisk
[Music]
together did we whisk it Pam right Pam
you need Pam for
sure but like Pam are those only those
The Substitute get it but those are
harder to use than Pam if we Pam it up
we don't have to use those who are you
talking to there's the Pam oh okay here
it is Pam it up Nick wash your
hands where is
it so there's two cupcake trays 12 oh wa
wo 12 on each and Pam them up
take the lid off
maybe don't okay okay hold don't just be
spraying
[ __ ] is it good yeah you had the right
idea is it here
fast is there pan coming out am I
tripping oh oh I like that angle I like
that angle do it again yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay
back this way more You Got It Go well it
okay it can't snow Pam you got to hit
the thing my God it's not a [ __ ]
blizzard yeah right idea you have the
right idea go go do it I'll help you
woo hit that hit that what's that dance
called I don't know are you for [ __ ]
are you for [ __ ] real like you can
see the paper towels and your wiing sh
off on me he's blind he has this excuse
your vision's great is it the bowl into
the cupcake oh my God there's Pam
everywhere Nick if
you disaster Nick shut okay though we
us [ __ ] idiot who's
snapping what put the mix in the cups
dump it but you got to you have to be
very meod methodical where are they is
that a word like a very where's the
trains [ __ ] you sound like a pirate
where's the trains where are you you're
screaming and there's a song change
right now thank God where's the train
where are they I need you where you
touched them last you just
pamminger asking me where they are
you're just [ __ ] pamed all over
it
stop oh
no oh
no oh no hold it up okay just do it
again I'll like I'll maneuver It Go go
slow go slow yes yes yes Queen keep it
up keep it up keep it up keep it up keep
it going go go go like a racehorse [ __ ]
keep it coming mat get him a spoon we
can like move it out how's it going yes
yes that your focus is empty but
fishing oh oh disaster
disaster pick it up I still have it go
again not get it what's going
on what's
Happening I feel a spit on my arm just
keep going who's touching my armpit come
on dump
it
yes shake it shake it you're doing great
yeah shake it shake it sh oh almost the
glass
explosion okay we have so listen close
cuz you can hear me right y we have an
issue here yeah so this
try we worked together we did awesome
awesome on this one right now CHR stop
talking I had to tell you something yeah
shut up man want to know you okay so
listen sh so there there's too much in a
lot of the cups right okay so do you
think you can move some I'm not with my
hands so wait here's the
spoon Matt was telling you to be quiet
and I'm like bro I have to tell him
something no no that one was good that
one actually needs more what Chris stop
trying to talk over me I'm trying to
tell you what to do I'm not talking
Matt's shushing you Matt let him do it
hey jackass he's shushing you yeah I
know we have to move some of the batter
around scoop some of that out and move
it to the right yes right right yes yes
yes yes okay do it again oh o okay we
can do that we can do that okay so
you're going to go left two up
one up one up one okay spoon
oh okay up to the
right no right B you said up to the
right F [ __ ] I never knew what it meant
what it meant to be content with Chris
shut up you did bad
that's what he said can I see no good
Awful can I see terrible cut your head
off Matt give him a thumb up or a thumb
down you did all right but you also
didn't that good can I
see can you do good or bad that's up to
you at are you all right Chris I'm fine
mental checkup I'm okay I don't know
what master I tell you he's like he's
going thumbs up thumbs down like you did
bad mat can I take this off
but we didn't expect a lot from you you
can't see right so it's okay that you
didn't do good Nick can I take this off
you have a big smile can I can I take
this
off can I
look yay he couldn't see why are you
looking at me oh there it is okay I'm
looking my eyes hurt what's going on why
are there [ __ ] eggs
everywhere what why' you throw eggs
everywhere oh I did not I did not put
these in the oven so now what we just
put this in the oven see what happens in
a bit yeah yeah yeah for sure all right
uh it's been so we'll see yeah we'll
just wait right yeah you are a great
listener I was like oh he's doing bad I
was like what thank you Nick I
appreciate it man you did awesome too
you seem to have fun look
good oh my God I thought you were going
to attack me why would I attack look
good terrible no they kind of look good
what world do they look good to you guys
like the cupcake itself look very warm
and fluffy cupcake shut the [ __ ]
up this is so
gross
oh what Nick what I will actually Veno
you $1100 to eat this I'm not doing that
Matt
$120 to eat this nope I need cash 500
cash 500 yep [ __ ] no what is this who
you think you are come on try it get out
of my face at you spit it out you have
it I have to plug my nose over here how
bad like B not like an es skateboard my
before what is going on eat it eat it it
actually smells like it smells like oh
my God it smells like the alcat escap
the alcat Escape
R oh my God wa it smells like an escape
room
what I'm not getting it Matt no take a
deep stti it smells like an escape room
that we've been
to sh got transported back when I was
like 12 at an escape room that was bum
Bonkers that was
B all right we'll be back for the
frosting of the of the cupcake the
cupcake
yes this kid is
insane we're all going to decorate one
cupcake fully
blindfolded let me get all the
supplies I don't have it yet took it I
got it no I didn't you did Chris stop
you're [ __ ] kidding my cupcake give
me the frosting I have it in my hand
I'll give you what I'm done I'll get
sprinkles everywhere cuz we're already
cleaned so it's like going to be really
gross I think I took too much frosting I
really hope this is Blue Dude I can't
get this open and there's frosting all
over is it brand new I need the frosting
or not the frosting the [ __ ] all
right I'm done hold on don't take your
thing off yet all
right I'm good dude I just got a
frosting on my face [ __ ] Matt you're
done too yeah all right Nick let's
go okay I'm done all right ready set
go wow oh my God but youed a different
color a I wanted blue oh my go my shirt
wait I thought I used this wait I had so
much extra proc oh I have to cut this
tip off I was going like this for like a
minute wait I did
good yay that was fun yay look at us
guys got
mine the blue Cyclone what all right
guys thank you so much for watching this
Wednesday video Christmas content super
super super super soon so get ready it
is just like that one thing it all the
[ __ ] what does it taste like Nick
just like that one thing you said
piles it t like Grammy's piles look
exactly like it I know I just tried them
oh my God Rest in Peace this tastes
exactly like
that you miss me yeah you miss me and
all the things that we did we said we
going to travel from the island to
Madrid we had a lot of plans but the
allst
dis because of some but it's okay cuz
I'm moving different don't be saying
nothing when I'm suppos to with other
[ __ ] for my brothers