Good Friday wait that's a religious
holiday yeah that's today's not good
Friday happy Friday stolo
Nation we're back and we're going to
have a banger for you if you go down the
stolo catalog and you scroll and you
scroll 3 years ago in this kitchen we
did our first baking blindfolded video
ever and it was Nick blindfolded with me
and Matt helping them helping helping
him thank sorry I changed your night
going to throw it back um it's been like
I think n what neither of these are
brownies brownies are in the thing we
also haven't filmed like a baking blind
de mute video in like I think like 10
months and we try and keep them a little
rogue because it'd be a lot if we were
to do them all the time we don't want to
become a Baking Channel but I think it's
been enough time in which we can do this
again 500,000 likes and I'll dump this
oil all over MTH I knew you were going
to say that [ __ ] because of the
ogus Nick has to be blind unfolded hey
guys summer is officially here and it is
time to get out of the house do more
activities and possibly go see your
favorite artist and that's why I'm going
to tell you about today's sponsor
SeatGeek everyone can use my code
sternol 10 to get 10% off any tickets on
SeatGeek whether you're a new customer
or not Sports concerts festivals you
name it there are so many artists
touring right now including Billy ish
Sabrina Carpenter Noah Khan and Zach
Bryan and SE geek has got you covered
each ticket is rated on a scale from 1
to 10 and green means good and red means
bad so look for green no matter how many
times you've bought tickets using SE
code Stern 10 is going to get you 10%
off your next order so take out your
phone open the sege app and add code
sternol 10 to your account do it now
because this opportunity is only
available for a limited time once again
that is Code sternol 10 for 10% off your
next order with seek now what now I'll
be deaf I'll put the headphones on and
go get your headphones the [ __ ] out of
here and get a blindfold [ __ ] and what
am I you're amazing you're
amazing you look like a ninja
mushroom it's time to [ __ ] I can't
hear anything it's time to bake some
[ __ ] brownies real time Nick stop
talking fuing go Matt get two hos Nick
you got the
oil I'm going to get the bowl
okay God it's like it looks like a big
penis it's like reaching in the cabinet
Matt what are the dimensions of the tray
supposed to be 14
nine oh 9 by 13 perfect here we go Nick
give it a smack yeah
Matt you got it everywhere no you got it
everywhere no you got it everywhere I
can
do you have to punch me while I'm in
while I'm
clear mat stop hitting him I am quite
clearly vulnerable Nick get up mushroom
this is the most
vulnerable you not punch me again or I
will punch
you whoa half cup where are we at you
still can't find the eggs no I'm
cleaning here I'll hand it to you Nick
I'm clean
take this egg don't take the egg I can't
hear you stop talking to me I can't hear
you take the egg crack in the
bowl nice
crack oh you're so good put it on the
paper towel that I put down whoa why did
that peel
out here Nick that wasn't for you thank
you good nice Nick that was Sky High
awesome work work half cup
oil oh you need a paper towel Matt get
in a
napkin why am I not talking I can't hear
you can't hear you that's
why wipe your hands mushroom let's move
if I get touched again [ __ ] listen up
that if I get touched again headon on
headphones on have headphones so shush
get your egg off my face get your eggs
off my face get your eggs off my face
get your eggs off my face you're rubbing
your eggs on me stop it now stop it now
stop it now
now cuz if I get touched again while my
[ __ ] peripherals are gone you will
die and you will die next and I will
commit arson and burn our [ __ ] house
down you dumb
[ __ ] how am I he ain't do
nothing he ain't do nothing I did
it all right I just feel like I can't
move around a half cup on the table and
do the oil you wish I'd do the [ __ ] o
can't hear you stupid that's not the
trash you put that in you put that in a
colander a colander you don't even know
what a colander is all right Matt what
out give me the [ __ ] oil nice nice
Nick you're pouring you're pouring
you're pouring you're pouring you're
pouring you're pouring you're stop great
work dump that in
there Nick you're awesome great
work you [ __ ] ster Olo I will rip
your eyes out of your head so you can
experience what I experienced for one
[ __ ]
minute who is it who the [ __ ] is is it
oh up to it
now ow [ __ ] cuz you're an idiot
you st my shoulder stop I didn't even
hit you once [ __ ] off me
mushroom you're in the
bowl slow easy easy now little more nice
can you stop talking no one needs to
hear you than God yo Nick Nick you're
getting powder all over yourself your
mother are we missing Matt's coming in
with more oil there's no milk did you
guys add milk milk or water you're not
supposed to add milk you're supposed to
add milk or water oh three tablespoons
of
water we skipped over that one how the
[ __ ] can I see the box with no eyes on
my head what is he yelling about stupid
idiot stupid idiot table or
teaspoon [ __ ] how am I the guy
correcting the [ __ ] movements here
how did neither of you catch that a
especially you Matt especially
you here's a
tablespoon oh my God I'm going to
[ __ ] kill you both cuz why am I going
to be bruised and battered after making
[ __ ] brownies this supped be
fun what is it yellow about Nick we have
to add the water cuz the mix is getting
ruined thanks [ __ ] told you that
get away from me who told you that add
three of those
tablespoons I'm thinking about it oh my
God God three tablespoons triplets we
should each do one
no
[Applause]
what Nick it looks like diarrhea poopy
on in the bowl like actually it looks
like a mess mix mix mix it looks fine it
looks soupy it looks like Panera soup
mix it you're an idiot stop trying to
kiss
me Chad mix
it oh my God oh my God shut up lost my
Sprite deal cuz we can't pour in Fes you
know I'm
geeking is he singing the [ __ ] Burger
King
[Music]
thing whoa nice shirt thank you thank
you
I don't know if I stand by this
anymore I hear them talking about me I
hear what they're
saying oh we need to spray good call we
don't want to add more water or oil or
nothing Matt I knew I was that tripping
I knew I was going to meet I knew I was
going to be the one I knew I was going
to the Sun
I wish you'd shut the [ __ ]
up
[Applause]
good you're doing good Nick be easy
though keep it
simple Nick Nick simplify it lower it
down Nick lower nice calm down it's not
going anywhere Matt used her shirt as a
napkin cuz he got you got brownie on his
finger it looked like he pooped
himself you could hear how stupid you
sound Nick do you want to lick the spoon
no here give it a lick No
E no stick your tongue out Nick stick
your tongue out I'll give you a lick of
the no you don't want to Li the soon I
know you can't hear but I look pretty
visibly
no you're going to get shot and killed
with a gun did the oven be part yes an
hour ago I feel like The Avengers like
coming back into reality when we all
take everything thing off you're an
idiot yeah we're [ __ ] done thank
Christ not nearly as much of a mess as
last time thank God all right guys that
was us making the brownies so we're
going to do a brownie reveal and then
we're going to go on to dessert number
two later on where we switch the roles
of who does what I'm excited for that
[Applause]
off you look good
off I hate to see her go but I love to
watch the leave who are you talking
to all right guys brownie reveal let's
do a brownie reveal these brownies would
bow BW Bow Bow Bow Bow wo wo W it has to
cool it has to cool that was no that was
the best slice I've ever brownie history
you get out when you don't know what
you're talking about you shut your
mouth you question Matt too much on a
day-to-day basis way too much I didn't
question anything he did I said mat is
amazing and we're so blessed to be
triplets and have Matt with us I
actually am really happy that I'm
triplets with Matt what are you talking
about and it's not it's not that it's
not that I'm like oh I'm happy I'm
triplet with Matt like because like I
lovey
it needs to go back in see that it's not
like oh I'm happy I'm tripless with Matt
because like I love Matt I'm happy I'm
tripless with Matt if I wasn't he'd hate
me and we'd never speak but now he has
to I don't hate you guys you guys are
just like really [ __ ] annoying that
was the nicest thing you ever said I
take I take it back I hate Chris
actually he doesn't mean it a tolerate
Nick yes oh I love being tolerated oh
God you guys are just like
the world doesn't see you guys the way I
do they see you as like amazing awesome
people I see you guys I see you guys as
headaches I'm like oh oh here comes
another
headache delicious oh I love that may I
say best pro product we've ever baked
Yours Truly brownies were really good
it's time to get into the cake who's
what I'm headphones awesome oh my
God can he be mut can Chris be mute then
please I do anything Chris is mute oh
great this is going to be awesome you
kidding me this is going to be amazing I
lost the blindfold of course lost the
blindfold that makes so that's my
bandana too so you have to find it or
CHR shut up I'm dead Ser I know but it's
like you're acting like it's like a
crazy thing it's a [ __ ] gray bandana
it's a buck 29 on a [ __ ] Amazon why
would we have to sell the house oh my
God more tap more T
more hey
mushroom down he Chris is pointing at me
he's telling me you need a whole egg
recipe for
sure top one three eggs Matt there's a
carton right in front of you you're
going to [ __ ] grab an egg you're
going to crack a [ __ ] egg you're
going to dump the [ __ ] egg in into
that Bake Mix you're going to get
crazy crack that crack that hey Chris
get the eggs he needs two more I have
them he needs two more pocket
eggs oh God yeah punch me now while I
can see [ __ ] uh uh kill him shoot him
where is he it wasn't me this is me it
wasn't me where is this is me where is
he he's behind
me I'll tell you when he's in proximity
when I go one two three swing you sucker
punch in every direction
W to me and M got the system unlock baby
call this [ __ ] the Pentagon bring me to
Area 51 we run this [ __ ] what are you
talking about
yeah no I'll tell
you shake her
off pick those
up that's what I'm talking about
water in the blue cup I can't see colors
idiot I can't see anything like what are
you saying blue cup stop touching me
[ __ ] oh you think I can just be
like
Oh wrong wrong yes okay great are we
sure it's
blue cuz I know if Chris's stupid ass
read the box I'll probably yes okay
sorry I didn't know I was with the
constant reassurance
crew you got to make sure when one of
them's [ __ ] Chris read things Matt
Chris is telling me you're talking way
too much pointing at you and going like
like the the noise yeah now that metal
thing you're holding that metal thing
you're holding f it with oil okay
there's oil on the table what the metal
f
it theal
thing CH said
yes what good flip it listen close what
listen close and good I'm going to shut
the [ __ ] up I see it I see you I see
your bad behavior looking at me like
this like fix your
neck you look Chris look like those
Halloween costumes where the head falls
off look at at me like like he's going
to pick his head off from his [ __ ]
chest what okay you listen
I have no choice oh shut up shut up I
can see the yapping I can see it listen
listen that what does he think what does
he think I'm doing what does he think
I'm doing does he think I'm just sitting
here with my [ __ ] ears off what I
can't I have no choice but to
listen what are you talking about A
House Is Not a Home Without paw prints
all I can do is listen that's all I can
do listen close oh my God that punch him
in the face stop talking about me all
you guys are doing is talking about me
listen that bow oh my God oh my God I'm
going to lose it I'm going to lose it
okay you are listening great listen
closely that bowl is a b to the brim so
I'm going to give you a whisk but when I
do you have to be super [ __ ] careful
cuz if you go crazy it'll overflow if
you go crazy you're an idiot are you
mimicking me yeah I am you're an idiot
you're an idiot
Nick punk what the [ __ ] are you looking
at grab me that whis punk [ __ ] mix mix
dummy I do feel like a big baby in this
thing you are I hate it you are a big
baby keep going Chris is saying great
that's obviously what I'm going doing
don't pitch me Captain Hook Captain mix
mix mix Captain Hook can't pinch you
idiots yes Chris is saying you need to
mix more you're not mixing enough speed
it
up all I'm doing are you getting tired
all I'm doing is mixing all I'm doing
stop mix mix mix mix
mix oh my God if he keeps touching me
what are you touching me for the
touching means nothing stop pre yeah
Chris we need a bigger tray than this
stop Matt enough great thank you finally
okay you need to do better all of you
all
around who is he talking to listen hit
the head table God
table
move we got Pam in the hand baby that me
up okay listen is in front
of I can't I can't if I'm going to be a
big baby I can't be a big baby covered
in [ __ ] in [ __ ] MAA okay no we're
not going to spray me I have to wear
this one see no big MAA
Chris
stop that's the bul Matt Chris said you
need to chill and you're doing it all
wrong listen so self-explanatory spray
the [ __ ]
tray and Chris
chill
enough like what fill it
out I feel like I'm in a but Zone the
butter Zone what butter Zone covered in
oil butter Zone feel like I'm [ __ ]
skating on butter the whole [ __ ]
floor
oily the slip and slide in the kitchen
whole floor isn't oily he's being
dramatic for usual someone please
Photoshop the word Security on Chris's
shirt cuz why the [ __ ] he's saying it
like he's the
[ __ ] security like this is a secret
service cake Secret Service cake [ __ ]
take a breath before before you speak
idiot
oh I work best with communication with
eye contact so if you'd look at me
that'd be
wonderful I just got literally punched
in the jaw on my YouTube channel and I
edit every video I have to see that
again I just got punched in the jaw and
I have to witness it today tomorrow and
every time you [ __ ] clip it
ow he can't even see I'm getting punched
to the
jaw
you okay listen oh my God oh my
God oh my
God how about you listen now that you
can hear you listen listen right it's
annoying how many times are you going to
say listen
listen don't hit my head okay listen oh
my God
amazing
phenomenal keep going oh my God he's
going to die's going to die he's going
to die sorry if I have any batter on
that's not from my own doing he's going
to die he's
fine s stop punching you violence
monster do you feel the presence of the
Whisk like less than a [ __ ]
centimeter from your lip no I
don't
oh get this good job Matt you're a great
listener Nick makes up a ton of stuff
when he has the free range to do so that
is not true yeah it is every single
thing I said was fully the truth except
like [ __ ] 50% of the things you were
saying that's not true yeah it is you
look like a big penis at all the cake on
sh yeah whose fault was that on what
those cabinets Matt you can't say it was
mine it wasn't mine it wasn't Matt's
Paul can we get a replay of the [ __ ]
whisk flying across the road what did I
say what did I say God Only God knows I
said I said if I feel a whisk close to
my [ __ ] face my digital footprint is
unbelievable we got baking blind and
death with a mushroom one the on correct
going yelling constantly and now I'm on
the floor we are officially down to 15
minutes till cake
time we need to let it cool serious it
needs to cool and we need to I seriously
don't know if I'm related to you guys
can I have a hug no put the butter away
I can almost guarantee we're
related I'm the best ever I'm going to
frost this hell good Pat it
oh wait did it backflip while I did that
are you an
idiot didn't see you helping
move unhelpful don't tell me to move
unhelpful [ __ ] stupid idiot are we
going to blindfold up to do this no we
don't need to we've been blind enough
this video okay you're blind with your
eyes open bottom of the C C really good
wait this is a really good cake Nick all
right um I'm putting the sprinkles on
don't get any ideas I'm not getting any
ideas I hate when you just don't even
give me a chance look at you holding two
[ __ ] three things of sprinkles want to
know why cuz you didn't let me speak
what I was going to say is can we all
vote on one sprinkle to use get off me
definitely not these get off me
[ __ ] it'll help you a lot to
move that way these are the best two spr
gos you're really close to me yeah you
were [ __ ] on me what was he doing I'm
not doing over here Nick touch me again
[ __ ] you're walking into me what is
this the Nick show and I forgot Chris
back up I mean pretty [ __ ] much back
up oh also by the way someone has to
clean the cake off the ceiling Matt mom
was talking mom was in here earlier
she's like I had to clean the windows
cuz of all the cake you always got on it
like did you guys try to clean it we
were like yeah she's like oh my God I
was such a mess she was all be finding
cake forever and
I I I hope she doesn't look up it's
literally
literally that was from you whis across
the room yeah and whose fault was that
one of you has to clean that I'm not
Nick Matt one of you can we get a replay
of who threw the [ __ ] whis get a
replay of what I said before I threw it
thank you he couldn't hear like of
course all right I rate an eight out of
10 no I rate this honestly these two
things that we made this video are the
best two things we've made in our entire
baking blindfolder career I agree I
think we're Pros now I think we got it
down well well well I think I'm
officially I think I've officially baked
more blind blindfolded than I have with
vision i' fully agree I
disagree do it with me
it's quiet don't make me look silly can
we do something cool together go like
left right and forward ready ready one
one two ready
go 12 let's do a full choreograph dance
okay wait we're going to be right back
we're going to choreograph an entire
dance
that