what is rocking ladies and gentlemen
welcome back everyone to the stolo
triplets YouTube channel today we're
about to have an amazing day we're back
in this kitchen and we're going to bake
for you like we have once before once
before multiple times many times before
we're going to keep it casual in com
we're just going to bake with no
challenges but the decorating aspect of
this video might have a trick or two up
its sleeve all right guys today's baking
video is brought to you by invisaline so
shout out to invisaline for sponsoring
today's video to today we're basically
all going to bake some cupcakes and see
who can make the best cupcake I don't
know about you guys but in one of our
past videos I had a horse named cupcake
so I feel really connected to this
Challenge and I feel like I'm going to
succeed powder on your face get it off
with can you lick it off or no get out
of here you don't you definitely don't
want a video of you trying to rip it
still make edits of it I've been through
it you don't want to do it all right all
right add that in the bowl wait I want
to do some okay
you missed the bowl you missed the bowl
this is too tiny of a bowl to like make
cupcakes in I'd love to have the ability
to just disappear in one moment Matt
that's kind of gross our table's clean
what did he do he like got some cupcake
wait is it crazy if we mix it in like
something like this yeah that's not
mixing volume our bigger bowl is in the
washer right now and it's being washed
and we would be able to clean if it just
in the sink but it's in the washing
machine sometimes the smaller the more
impact it has
okay Mighty Mouse let's go okay we'll
need a cup of water and 13 cup vegetable
wait I I was going to eyeball I got it
no eyeballing gently Nick all right
chill
out no no you have to like go like this
do that do that yeah like make sure you
make sure it that doesn't do anything
wow look at the density in that actually
it's not you want to see something
really cool yeah I got you bro don't you
worry oh that looks so yummy now next
step is three eggs watch out can I do
him no can you move we'll each do one
egg cuz we're triplets I feel like so
gentle holding an egg like it really is
a dad no Matt Matt Matt wow it's crazy
that you can't really break if you
squeeze and crack that egg I'll be
really surprised no I can't yes you
could try it you're putting up a front
that I go like oh let me try and then I
do it try it oh wow I actually it's like
a hard thing to do try try to squeze no
I don't want to hurt myself you're not
like I'd cut myself with the shell you
can't you can't just try try
it gu that egg's going to blow
dude I can't it's it's hard you're lying
try no it's going to work no try it try
it seriously wait you can't do it I'm
like trying that in case an egg goes
wait that was mine to crap sorry you
took too long you're playing games I'm
trying to make I'll let you do this one
but you have to break it you have to do
it with your palms ready are you
serious don't do it well I'm scared if I
get it on my shirt I would get it
eventually but I'm explode all over me
I'll try it no you're not going to try
it you're just going to crack it yeah
yeah
you're double Yol no way oh my God we
just got a double Yol on camera get that
bring that in bring that in camera no
use your phone I got it I got it dude we
have three eggshells there 1 2 three
eggshells 1 2 3 4 so cool thumbnail
thumbnail double Yol what wow wait I
actually can't believe that we just
achieved a double Yol I'm like what are
the odds I know this is like a it's a
double Yol should you take a Yol out
I'll do it I'll do it no no no I'll do
it I'll do are you spare
hands oh it's
slippery hold on don't break the yolk
I'm not trying wow that's really
impressive that he can just scoop a yolk
out are you not that impressive at all
I'm really impressed I throw it Chris no
no God if I start any longer I have
cheese I don't think that's how it works
Nick Nick Nick Nick Nick Nick settle
down you're making cupcakes bro oh my
gosh if you mess up my cupcakes I'm
going to mess you up it's going to rise
three tablespoons let me show you ready
that's that's a spoon how what what what
makes you say that's a table that's that
eat
dinner guess a base a tablespoon Offa a
tablespoon that's three that's
equivalent that's an equivalent ratio
oops I got batter on the
floor I think we're just adding way
think they just aze adding way too much
in there are you serious yeah so what do
we do uh my my arms really hurt okay so
that this actually should have been the
perfect amount oh yeah it was supposed
to make 22 cupcakes there's 24 holes
here we have distributed the cupcake mix
evenly into two trays not really cuz
this tray is looking quite empty and the
oven is preheated so we're going to put
these into the oven and then we're going
to be right back for the decorating
ceremony are you
serious Nick it's hot all right I'm
recording because I'm going to decipher
this between me and you right now oh my
are we decorating the cupcakes with full
vision or are we blinding ourselves to
see you can make the best cupcake let's
ask the viewer I might decorate it on a
unicycle really yeah I say we bring in a
tribe of lions a pride of lions good and
we say prowel around the kitchen while
we decorate the cupcakes that's a good
one I think I might just sit there and
decorate it oh oh I don't know if I have
any special little activities anything
no unicycle no pride of lions no do you
want to be blind at all what if you rip
your tongue out of your mouth and you
can't speak well I think you guys should
blindfold to decorate yours and then
I'll stay un blindfolded just because I
want to surprise you with mine and then
you guys can like compete me versus Matt
and you can see yeah okay okay yeah me
and Matt are about a cupcake Showdown
and Nick is doing whatever he said he
was going to do I don't know what he's
doing oh my God because of my hat I like
look like I don't have a head like it
like Blends in with the wall I I look
like a floating face oh my god look it I
look like a floating face are you done
with the frosting no I'm just getting
started oh now just put that on the
Cupcake yep so good have I gotten it all
around the perimeter nope I got to like
spread it out a little more definitely
oh wait this might be a technique just
moving the plate and same spot knife
just put it
down okay I'm going in for sprinkle Town
time um I feel like I missed the cupcake
and I only got that on the
plate where's the frosting um I have it
and I need it for just another
moment there you go do I have a lot on
there yep well not a lot but enough
hello I don't have your sprinkles I had
my own custom sprinkle
cup where's my sprinkle where's your
sprinkles Nick can we see it is there a
paper towel yeah I just had it give it
to me where I I put it on the table
somewhere can I look
yep oh my cupcak mine looks beautiful
mine looks good oh my gosh it's a
snowman
wow it's a snowman it's pretty why is
why is he bleeding from the mouth
scar a scar yeah those are his buttons
oh the carrot nose three three orange
ones you got wa you must
did you have tweezers no I stole them
off Matt's plate with my finger before
we try and rate our cupcakes that we
just made we are going to take out our
invisible liners and tell you about
Invisalign the reason we love our
invisaline aligners is that we can
easily incorporate in our daily life and
eat whatever we want like these cupcakes
me my Chris lead a very fast-paced life
we're always traveling we're always on
the go we're always filming videos and
incorporating invisaline into our daily
schedule has been the easiest thing for
us we're able to eat whatever we want
whenever we want and it's more
comfortable than braces and we've all
had braces before and we're going to try
these cupcakes right now thank you so
much invisaline for sponsoring today's
video let's get into it and right can
you believe how similar our cupcakes are
due to the fact that we both use vanilla
frosting and uh sprinkles mine's better
though I can I can really believe it I
can believe it look at how little plate
mess up I have though compared to you
yeah but look at how many more I have on
my on my cake he blew his off too it
definit oh oh whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa I feel like that was is this G to
alter the taste test that was like
really rude in my opinion let's all try
mine because I have one of each so we
can all I call the Torso Ready set
go dry M mhm not I need water ah I'm TR
you guys don't hear as it's moving down
my stomach is is good though no I don't
like the like texture of that oh my God
it's like kind of like thin all going to
taste the same nuh mm- amazing what you
mean nuh-uh yes huh sprinkles and
F it's so good this is this is a lot no
it's like a chewier that one's actually
delicious like I eat this way that's
better than mine mhm mhm I do need water
yeah me too oh you have you have a
Sprinkle in your mouth best one best one
best one
mhm mhm no that is the best one mine was
way better no
yeah this is better no wasn't you have
to rest this I don't want it a I thought
that was going to be like my Flex like
oh he wants the rest of mine no I don't
dang it uh thank you guys for watching
today's video smash the like button hit
subscribe and we'll see you when we see
you my shiny teeth that's break up
[Music]
[Applause]
oh