blue team this their families cheering
in the audience orange team that they're
taking home the trophy what about purple
team purple team's gonna win this year
this is our year
you ready to lose today pal yeah yeah I
haven't lost in years but okay we'll see
changes today yeah we will see oh you
prepared yeah to lose
sure don't disrespect my fist bump all
right sure thank you move this [ __ ]
finger what is the finger here it's my
lucky foam finger okay set that down
okay people are gonna sit here touch
that finger again you'd regret it let's
leave it right there I bet I would yep
orange team's already looking all right
today we don't need the whole theatrics
with the finger and everything at least
I don't have a fanny pack on yeah okay
I love my fanny pack looks ridiculous
yeah talk about team spirit it shows
team spirit yeah
fueled up for the game okay
anyway how do you feel about your team
this year
I'm feeling probably better than you are
I'm feeling great so that's not true I
know purple team's probably better
they're down in the dumps today one and
10 years 15. 15 15. oh my God
yeah
whoa I don't know what he is doing don't
even know what I just saw wow
I feel bad honestly it's a little
embarrassing
yeah let's sleep on me no
he feels the spirit I guess that's all
he is that's all he needs
oh good morning I just woke up bright
and early watch your teams lose Jesus
Christ oh my god dude cute headband
borrow from your grandma looks nice on
you you guys got the same haircut look
at your face really fits your silhouette
nice fanny pack bring snacks yeah I did
it's not going to keep you entertained
oh God okay okay yo
that's my lucky foam finger ever again
go get it go get it
go get it you have plenty of time before
the game starts to grab that phone
camera this is crazy this is crazy looks
like grimace
oh are you in second grade yeah you know
purple team hasn't won in 15 years
15 years
there's two things I don't like what
blue team
orange team
and I'm adding a third what when people
reminisce on the past okay it was about
to start fast is important game's about
to start
[Music]
thank you
Matt told you you're never gonna win
purple bro I'm only down 40 and it's not
over till it's over well it's gonna be
over in about three seconds so I don't
know
foreign
[Applause]
yeah you're ridiculous bro let's fight
let's compete fight compete right now
fight compete call it what you want
let's do it right now I'll compete with
you right now okay we both know we're
all doing it right now
you guys serious
why not okay I say we orchestrated more
you can be team purple because you love
purple so much you can be team blue I'll
be team orange and we'll take it on tour
and our fans can be in the crowd witness
the whole thing we're doing it
competition style like that I'm packing
my bag
I have three bags packed and I'm headed
to the bus right now okay
oh they're going down let's do it it's
over for you
[ __ ]
Chris I have a question yeah Nick can we
go on to work we have mascots uh sure
yeah we can have mascots let's go let's
go