Copywriting is either the easiest job in
the world or the hardest job in the
world. So to me, the main difference
between fine copy and good copy is
what's the emotion. I think the biggest
mistake that happens when you're
creating brands is that sometimes people
think it's like logo type color, but
realistically there's so much more. I
see a ton of ads, especially in the AI
space, that are all about efficiency.
And I just think it's ridiculous. You
could stop a thousand people on the
street and ask them what they want in
life and no one is going to say, "I
really wish I was more efficient." I am
Mike Smith. I run uh Smith and Diction
with my wife Cara in the beautiful Bach
building in Philadelphia. Smith
Andiction is a design studio. We mainly
focus on creating thoughtful identities
for imaginative clients. We work on
companies like Perplexity, Gamma,
Exposure, and Anterior. Just anything
that feels really, really unique. I'm
Cara Smith and I run Smith and Addiction
with my husband Mike. I run most of the
addiction side of what we do. So I
oversee all of our STR brand strategy
and messaging and copywriting. Our
approach is pretty different in that
we're small. We're intentionally a small
team. So everyone we work with works
directly with us. Mike and I are the
founders and we also lead the project.
So at a traditional big agency, the
people who are started the company, the
people who run the company, they're not
the ones actually doing the work.
They're not the people doing the writing
and doing the design. And here that's
the opposite. So we are not only the
people who started the company and who
run the company, but we also are the
people doing a majority of the work. So
I handle a lot of the copywriting and
strategy myself. Mike leads all of the
design along with his team. So you just
get so much more connection between the
people who we're working with, our
partners, our clients, and our team
because we're just the lynch pin between
those
two. Everybody has a brand. Brand is
simply how people see you, right? So
whether you spend a lot of time and
money developing a brand or you don't,
like Mike was talking about, like our
favorite bagel shop where it's just a
bag and it's like a Sharpie on a paper
bag, that is still a brand even though
there was no money spent on that brand.
And it's letting people know we do not
care about design. We only care about
making the best bagels in this city. and
you're conveying that through that
medium even even if you didn't spend a
single dime on that. And I think the
thing that a lot of people miss about
brand is that if you choose not to
invest in it, you still have one. People
will see you in a certain way. If you
have a social media ad, then you you
have an avatar. And what does that look
like and what does that tell people
about you? So, I like to think that what
we do is we just help you understand
what your brand is and you be in control
of your brand instead of letting your
audience decide your brand because
you're not quite aware or you don't have
a handle on it. So, and I think that's
one of those things that when we give
you a brand toolkit, that's not the end
of the conversation, right? Like
branding as an exercise doesn't mean
like it's not a thing that you buy and
then like great, I bought my brand. A
brand is what you do every single day.
Every single interaction you have is a
part of your brand. every single
customer service conversation, every
single uh moment that somebody spends in
your platform on your product if you're
a client like Gamma, those are all part
of your brand and we just give you the
tools at the beginning to say, "Okay,
here's here's how you can create a brand
that will reach your audience. Here's
the toolkit." And then you have to go
out and you have to live that brand and
be that brand every single day. So
that's my like speech of like brand, you
can't just like buy a brand. brand is
how people see you. And how people see
you will continue to change with
everything that you do and every
interactions that they have. And you can
choose whether those interactions are
better and better and they're more and
more interested in being in your club or
whether every time they interact with
your customer service, they have a worse
and worse impression of your brand. And
then it doesn't matter how much money
you spend on design if your customer
service team isn't delivering on the
qualities that your brand is conveying.
Branding to me is just like what would
you put a sticker on your car or your
notebook or your laptop? Like a good
brand is one of those things that exists
more than just a a transaction. It's
something that becomes part of your
life. And I think that when you are
creating a brand, it's so easy to think
transactional. It's so easy to be like,
"Oh, I want people to download this
product or I want people to use this uh
this, you know, menu or something, but I
want people to want to live their life
with that brand as part of their mental
kind of like ecosystem." For me, the
Vulc logo, when I was growing up
skateboarding, I drew that logo on
everything, every book, every year,
every class. I I was just so obsessed
with how beautiful and simple it was. So
to me, I think that a brand is just
something that like it pulls you in.
It's almost like a gem or a crystal that
you're just like you can't help but want
to be near or can't help but you want to
hold it. When you look at some of the
brands we've made, I try to always make
them have a little bit of tangible
quality to them. Uh so people can
actually feel like they can reach out
and grab it or it could sit on your desk
as like this really cool paper weight or
something like that. Why is branding
important for business for like products
and things like that? I think that
branding is important in that use case
because it's the easier and easier it
gets to make stuff the more that brand
will actually make things that people
want to have in their lives. When you
have a product or something like you
know I open Instagram every day like
every single day I am influenced by the
AI or the the UI in that product. it
would be a disservice to not treat
people with the with the respect of like
you care about what's in their hand.
when you're kind of invading people's
lives, the least you can do is is
respect the the attention that they are
giving you uh and making a product or a
UI or whatever a brand that feels like
it's actually making their life better
or making their life easier or making
their life more fun or they're smiling
when they open the app or something like
that because there are so many things
that want to take away your energy and
take away your happiness that like I
feel like it's brand's job or It's a
brand's job to make you feel a little
bit better, but it doesn't work like
that. Doesn't work like that as much
anymore. To me, I think the biggest
mistake that and I don't even know if
it's founders. I think the biggest
mistake that happens when you're
creating brands is that sometimes people
think it's like logo type color. There
is like that's the trifecta of brand.
But realistically, there's so much more.
There's so much more interesting things
that you can do with photography, art
direction. You can make like a cool way
that you know the the type skews to
represent motion or you can even bring
in some sort of like really exciting uh
movement in terms of like okay we're
going to have this image be blurred or
this image has like a 3D effect or it
has like this uh X-ray MRI scan and
coloring to for like a uh you know a
healthcare company or something like
that. people are so so quick to just be
like, "Oh, no. I just need a logo. I
just want to put a logo on a PowerPoint,
you know, cover or something like that."
And I think that brand is so much deeper
than that. And I feel like if you're
approaching it in this shallow kind of
way, people will get to the bottom of it
really quickly. And I think that that is
something that is a very dangerous
territory because like you're relying on
the product to be absolutely impeccable
if the brand is super super shallow. A
verbal identity is all the words that
you use to communicate. It kind of comes
out of strategy. It, you know, often a
strategy is mostly an inter internal
facing document. It's mostly for your
team if you're growing. It's things that
you say to your team like, "Oh, here's
the things that we value and we're never
going to change or um here's what we're
trying to do and and the way that we're
going to position our company in order
to do that." Verbal identity is once you
cross that line between talking to your
internal audience or maybe your partners
and talking to your your external
audience, right? So that's how do you
what are your website going to say?
What's the tone that you use? And then
what are the actual words that you put
on a website that you put on social
posts that you put on ads that you put
in a video? What's your tagline? What
are your headlines? How do you talk
about yourself? It's interesting because
in some ways it's different than design
because a lot of elements of design like
a logo often you'll get a logo and
you'll keep it and you won't touch it
for a long time or you'll get a color
palette and you'll sort of settle into
that color palette and it doesn't change
frequently. Words are different, right?
So words change all the time and lots of
people you're you know your website
headline might change every couple of
months who knows like you people are
writing new elements and products all
the time. So it's really important with
a verbal identity to make sure you
understand the overarching tone and
personality of like who we are and how
we talk so that then when you are
writing new lines I mean never a verbal
identity is never going to deliver all
the words you ever need to use. Instead,
it's just going to set the tone so that
then you can continue to write new words
that always feel on brand and like
they're written by the same personality.
Like for Gamma, for example, we worked
on their verbal identity. The big idea
that we really rooted everything in was
this idea of get get your ideas out
there. And we loved that as a starting
point of when you think about who their
audience is, they're not people who are
so talented at designing a presentation
or making their own website. there are
people who are more interested in the
ideas and just need it to get out there
more quickly and that's exactly what
Gamma does. So, we love this idea. Um,
but then when you start to think, okay,
what does that sound like? How do you
express that idea to your audiences? We
had so much fun working on the tone for
this one because one of our tone words
was imaginative and and so few brands
get to be imaginative, you know, and I
think there's just it's an unlock button
when you get to say, "Oh, you don't have
to use, you know, if I was a writer and
somebody handed me a verbal identity
that had imaginative, that means I get
to use fun words." Like I don't have to
use the same regular words that
everybody else uses to say, "Start your
presentation now." You can instead say,
"Start a presentation about, I don't
know, exploring the ocean now." And you
can suddenly start to put a lot more
personality into that brand because you
have a verbal identity that tells you
right from the beginning, use your
imagination, do something interesting,
do something different. We've built
verbal identities for lots of clients.
We're working right now with a client
called Contra that helps uh freelancers
get paid. And so they were a really
really tricky verbal identity because
they have two very distinct audiences,
right? So that on the one hand they have
the people who are freelancers, people
who get want to get more jobs and get
paid. Maybe they're a designer, maybe
they're an animator, maybe they're a
writer, maybe they're a developer, maybe
they're a videographer, who knows? But
they want sort of more 1099 work. They
want to show their work off um and get
hired. And then on the other side, you
have the people who are going to hire
them. And their reasons for being on
Contra are very different because of
those two audiences. So, it took us a
lot of work to figure out how do we
connect with both of them at the same
time and make sure that we're
communicating slightly different
offerings, slightly different values,
but in the same tone that feels
consistent across the board and using
the same sort of core messaging across
the board. Our concept for them was get
more creative because whether you're a
creative a self-described creative
person who's trying to get more work,
it's this is a way for you to get more
creative work, right? And on the other
hand, if you're somebody who's trying to
hire more creatives, you can get more
creative team. You can get more creative
with the way that you're forming your
business and growing your business. If
you want to scale more quickly, you
don't necessarily have to hire the
traditional way. So, we love it because
it allows you to sort of like fill in
the blank after creative of get more
creative and then you can say whatever
it is that you want in your mind. So,
being able to hit on something that felt
really powerful for both of those
audiences was really fun. I would say
the most common mistake that I see is
thinking that exactly what you want
people to do is what you should write.
And I think that doesn't happen in
advertising. You know, in the big
advertising world, people are really
understand that you don't write a
billboard that says buy more chocolate.
You make people want chocolate, right?
You make them think, oh, there's nothing
better than a bar of chocolate right
now. And I think when you when a lot of
people go a lot of particularly like in
the tech world people who are building
products or like writing a website they
forget that and they go out and they say
buy now on their website which is not
actually the best way to get somebody to
buy something. What you have to do is
make them want it. You have to appeal to
an emotion inside of them and make that
connection. Right? So, if I were to talk
like broadly in the world right now, I
see a ton of ads, especially in the AI
space that are all about efficiency and
I just think it's ridiculous because I
look I you could not you could stop a
thousand people on the street and ask
them what they want in life and no one
is going to say I really wish I was more
efficient. Like that's not an emotion.
That's not a thing that people want.
It's a thing that people want for their
teams. It's a thing they want for their
companies. Maybe they want other people
who are they're paying to be more
efficient, but nobody wants that for
themselves. So, I just think you have to
connect with something beyond that,
something that people actually want,
something that feels positive to them
instead of just saying AI, it'll make
you more efficient. Like, that's not
actually a thing people want to buy. So,
let's move beyond the efficiency and
figure out what can what can it provide
that's a benefit to my life. Copywriting
is so interesting. In one of my early
jobs, I used to talk with one of my good
copywriting friends about copywriting is
either the easiest job in the world or
the hardest job in the world. And it
just all depends on how well you do it.
And I think particularly now in the
world of AI, if you're writing something
that sounds like JT GPT could write it,
then you're it's going to be hard out
there because the the the reality is
like there's a whole new set of tools
that are going to be capable of writing
copy. And the only thing we have the
only leg up we have on chatbt, it's like
it's not speed, it's not efficiency, but
we can be more creative and we can think
from like a more human perspective. So
to me, the main difference between fine
copy and good copy is what's the
emotion? What's the feeling that's
behind it? How do you make somebody read
something and feel something? So I like
to think of copywriting much more from a
storytelling perspective or a cinematic
perspective of like how do you make
something feel emotional and strike a
chord with somebody as opposed to simply
conveying information, right? Of course,
you want to convey information as well,
especially when you're on a website and
practical executions. A lot of bad
copywriting stops at conveying
information. It conveys information, and
that's fine, but it doesn't make
somebody feel something. And when I
often hear people say things like, "Oh,
people don't read anymore." I'm like,
"That is so not true. People read all of
Game of Thrones, and Game of Thrones was
an incredibly long and incredibly dense
book. Why? Because it was filled with
emotion." People read a lot, but they
only read when it makes them feel
something, and they're not interested in
reading very dense and informative
information. So, I I think that the main
differentiator if you want something to
be good is for it to be emotional. And I
think that's also happens to be what
gives us a leg up on Chat GPT is because
Chad GPT doesn't have any emotions. So,
it can try to emulate emotion, but it
can't genuinely understand the
difference between who headlines. If one
of those headlines makes your heart hurt
and the other one doesn't, CHBT doesn't
know the difference. technically they
might be equal. So my advice to any
copywriter out there would be like write
with your heart. Like put as much
emotion and heart as you can into
everything and you're more likely to hit
something that that changes the world or
makes a
difference. We've had clients before. So
Perplexity in particular was a really
hard client because their audience is
literally everyone. Like they in the
same way that like Google's audience is
everyone. They want anyone on the planet
to be able to go to Google and find
something and perplexity wanted that
same thing. So there was no like
defining yeah but who's more likely to
use this or who like no it's just how do
you appeal to everyone all at the same
time and that's really really hard. What
they wanted to do was so aspirational
and so we were somewhat lucky in that we
did it a little bit earlier. I feel like
the AI field is messier now and it's
more crowded now than it was. But at the
time it felt like there were only a few
serious contenders in AI. And so it was
much easier to be like okay as opposed
to chat GBT and you know maybe co-pilot
like what do you do differently than the
the key ones. I think Bard was at the
time we were looking at Bard as one of
their competitors and so um it we really
quickly came to this fact that they had
citations and no one else at the time
was doing it in quite the same way. It
allowed you to turn your AI experience
from, you know, chatbt, you ask
something, it gives you information and
that's sort of like a dead end into a
portal to everything, right? So like
basically turning it into like what
Google used to be, which is the front
page of the internet. Like perplexity is
now your your starting point and then
you can click any of those citation
links and go anywhere you want to go. So
we were eventually able to hone in on
like this one differentiator that set
them apart, which is the difference
between perplexity and a chatbt. Chatbt
is like great, we're going to give you
an answer to your problem. Perplexity is
going to open up doors to knowledge. So
you're going to be able to continue to
discover, right? And there is a very big
difference between like, I want to know
something, great, here's the answer.
It's like the old classic like are you
going to give somebody a fish? Are you
going to teach them to fish? It's like
are you going to say great here's the
answer great now I know the answer and
I'm done with this interaction or are
you going to say here's the information
and if you would like to learn more
about that here's all the places that
you can go that language of like
circling around the idea of knowledge
and then that's circling around
perplexity as the place where it begins
like everything starts here but then it
can go further and eventually that
became the headline of like you know
where knowledge begins which is really
beautiful but for the most part
something like gamma it's actually
easier than that because you can think
about okay maybe you want everyone to be
able to use gamma ultimately, but who
are there are certainly people who for
whom it's more it's a better bet that
they're going to be using it. So like I
think about gamma and sometimes it's
helpful to think about who it's not for,
right? So gamma is like not for my mom.
She doesn't like computers. She's scared
of AI. Like this is not her feature.
She's going to be overwhelmed. Cool. We
rule her out. Gamma is also not for
Mike. He's a talented designer. He can
do his own deck presentation and he
doesn't need Gamma to do that magic for
him. He knows how to design a deck. So,
how do you find in the middle something
that feels like it resonates, right? And
I just always find that really being
able to create an accurate picture of
that person in your head. So, for gamut,
it might be educators. Here's a teacher.
I think about the teachers that I know
and I think about what their lives are
like and I think about who they are and
what their daily routines are and what
what they do that's different than what
I do and what their needs are and what
kinds of presentations they might make.
And then the more time you just really
spend treating your audience like almost
like you're in a novel or you're in a
movie and you're putting yourself in the
shoes of that character, then that
allows you to really think, okay, how do
I talk to them in a way that's going to
matter to them, not necessarily matter
to me. I feel like we've gotten really
lucky with a few logos that like, you
know, the exposure logo is just like a
globe with a star in it. The perplexity
logo is like a spinning door. And so
like, how do I approach shaping logos
and stuff? A lot of the times I'll try
to push it into really far extremes
first and then simplify simplify
simplify and like weirdly a lot of the
times like I'll just post it on Twitter
and I'll be like has anyone seen this
before? You know what I mean? And so a
lot of the times the collective hive
mind of Twitter or X or whatever you're
calling it now is better than any design
book or any kind of database I could
check or something like that. Um but I
always just try to make sure that our
logos have like like a 10% strange thing
about them. And I think that that is a
really important part of the studio is
that like I want to make sure that we're
not creating just a classic geometric
logo that everyone's seen a million
times or something like that. And in
this age or in this time, people are
cranking out logos that look like
flowers and the most like like three
circles or something like that. And I'm
like, what are we what are we even
doing? Like that's not that's not
ownable in any way. So I feel like just
trying to get to the foundational parts
of what why this company exists in the
first place. We don't just create logos
just to fill a space. That's never ever
what we're doing. And so I think that as
long as the logo can kind of tell a
story and like convey an emotion or
convey a strategy or something like
that, that's when we know we're on to
something. And so we'll create so so
many logos when we're doing identity
process, the going through the identity
process. We'll create dozens of things
that anyone else would be like, "Oh
yeah, that works. That's perfect. Like
that's fine. It fits. It's beautiful.
But we always try to push it a little
bit further to feel a little bit more
interesting. Same with color. I was in a
I was in a call one time with someone
that was like, "Oh, I just eyropper
things from Pinterest." And I was like,
I like think about color in the deepest
darkest way possible of like, can it
work in light mode? Can it work in dark
mode? Can we find panones for this
thing? Uh just trying to be responsible
with color is something that is really
exciting to me and it's where it's where
I find the most joy these days is like
when two colors that maybe don't quite
go together still create some sort of
exciting thing or exciting vibration
between them like that's really exciting
to me. So yeah, I always spend a lot of
time on on color and just making sure
that you leave time to explore is a
really important
thing. I grew up in New Jersey right
outside of the city. Uh, but I grew up
skateboarding, coming to the city to
skateboard here. I grew up in the
heydays of Love Park. So, a lot of
really awesome skateboarders were
hanging out there at that time. And so,
I was just kind of obsessed with Philly
from such a young age. I would draw the
love sign over and over and over again
on all of my notebooks and things in in
school. And then in high school, I I had
a really great art teacher. I had two
really great art teachers that were
like, "You really need to be focused on
doing something with art." and that is
something that I think that that you
should be you really kind of
hyperfocused on for college. And I was
like, I think I'm going to go be a
history teacher. And they were like,
what if you just applied to one one art
school just for us just to see how uh
see how you like it. And then I did. I
ended up going to an art school in
Delaware. Quickly transferred out of
that cuz I hated art school. I didn't
really enjoy art school that much
because I was commuting to this college.
So I was driving an hour there, driving
an hour back. And I got there and just
like nobody took it seriously. So like
everyone was like questioning the
homework assignments or being like, "Oh,
I didn't quite understand the homework,
so I just didn't do it." And so I was
like, "I'm working two jobs. I'm driving
here. I'm commuting here." And I'm still
getting the homework done. But you guys,
for some reason, don't believe in this
part of your career. And I think that
car and I talk about this all the time
of just like ever since I saw Photoshop
for the first time and realized what you
could make with it. I was like this is
going to be the rest of my life and I
have no backup plan. I have no other
thing I want to do. This is exactly what
I want to do. So when I was in art
school I like a lot of people were still
figuring out what they wanted to do. I
would say most of them were still
figuring out what they wanted to do and
I just was like I don't want to be
around this. and um went to a local
university in South Jersey where I fell
in love with print making. That's where
I did a lot of like posters. I made a
ton of posters, learned about setting
type. I learned about etching prints and
plates and things like that. So print is
like deep deep inside of my DNA. And so
I love to bring that print ethos into a
lot of the things that I'm working on
today. And I'm not so like focused on
making the next best digital product.
I'm focused on making something that
someone want to hang on their walls. I
was so obsessed with things like element
skateboards and girl and chocolate and
all that stuff. So, I was just like, how
can I make a career doing that stuff?
And that was what really excited me. And
I also realized through skateboarding
that like brand is so much more of an
identity for people than a lot of people
might think. Like, you know, if you're
not skateboarding, you might be like,
"Sure, I buy a special kind of soap, but
that's not your identity." You know what
I mean? But when you skateboard, you
ride that deck and you can get sponsored
by that company. So that company can pay
you to have their board under your feet
or their shoes on your feet. And it just
became so much deeper of a obsession
when you think about like design can
actually be used as like a a proxy for
your identity. Yeah. After college, I
worked at an advertising agency in South
Jersey. There I kind of just learned a
lot of the basics of the programs. After
that, I went to work at a place called
160 over 90, which is where I met Cara
and she was my copywriting partner and I
was the design side of it. So, we grew
up in the brand design space completely
united. We were together on every single
thing that we worked on. So, we
basically have one brain now of how we
think about design and uh the approach
to branding. After that, we both went to
a place called Charity Water in New York
City. And that's where we really focused
on the idea of design can do really good
things for the world. While working at
Charity Water, you learned that design
can change the world through its pure
power to make people believe in a cause.
When I went to work at Charity Water,
the mission there is to kind of solves
the world's water crisis. But their
vision, the thing that's above that is
to reinvent the idea of charity. You
know, growing up, you always see like,
oh, Charity doesn't have any money for
design or it always kind of feels like
it doesn't quite fit inside of this. It
shouldn't look fancy. But working at
Charity Water, we really focused on
things feeling nice and feeling like,
you know, uh, something that you should
pay attention to. Utilizing design to
draw attention to these really important
things in the world was something that I
was just so excited to be a part of. and
we helped raise a few million dollars
when we were there for clean water
projects in Africa and all over the
world. It was really awesome just to be
around people who were excited about
helping people cuz when I went there I
was at a pretty low point in my design
career where I was like is design just
making millionaires more money and I if
so I don't really want to be part of
that. I left the agency world uh to
focus on just can design be used for
good and I believe it can and had a
great time while I was there and and
learned so so much. Scott Harrison is
when you're around him, you just want to
do well and you just want to um you know
help solve the world's biggest problems
and he makes you believe it's possible.
And so I feel like I try to bring a
little bit of that energy to our studio
and to the work that we create where
we're just like, "Yeah, sure. It's no
problem. If you want to change the world
a little bit, like we we'll help you try
to do that as best we can." And we
learned about writing a really good
mission statement, having really good
strategy, and also just like the impact
that social media can have on people. We
learned a lot of that stuff at Charity
Water. And then after Charity Water, we
looked around New York for a little bit.
And we were like, "Okay, like what's our
next step? What's our next move?" And I
really just didn't want to work for
anybody else ever again. And so we moved
home and we're like, "All right, let's
give this studio a shot. We'll see what
happens. As long as I can pay my rent
every month, well, this will be a great
success." And 10 years later, here we
are. So, uh, still paying rent, you
know, still really excited about making
stuff and, um, but yeah, so that's
that's my whole life story.
Mike is, um, honestly, it's wild. He's
unlike most people. He's not he's not a
regular person, you know, regular people
like I wouldn't have started this
company by myself. I think um, I'm lucky
because I learned early on uh, the value
of design, right? Like you can say a
great headline, but if your great
headline is just scribbled on a
cardboard box, it doesn't have the same
power as when it's when that design and
the copyrightiting are really working
together. And so it was never my idea to
start the company. He like told me he
wanted to start his own company on our
first date. And I think I probably knew
that even beforehand cuz we'd been
working together for months already and
we'd been working all day every day
together. So I knew a lot about him even
before we started dating. And it was
100% his vision. I was just like, "Cool.
I love writing and I love um the
creativity of it. So if that's your
vision, I will be behind your vision
100%. He's just refuses to let anything
be mediocre and if it's not good enough,
we won't present it. But I do also think
that we are a little bit different than
a lot of studios in you know the
practical side. Like our team, we don't
have a lot of meetings. We don't spend a
lot of time on sil we don't have a lot
of team building events. Like summer on
our team, she lives in a different
state. We see her maybe once or twice a
year. We the our team our designers they
come into work and they spend eight
hours designing and then they go home.
So because we get them to mostly focus
on their craft and getting better at
their craft instead of being in required
team building events or doing time
sheets or having HR conversation like
none of that is a part of their days. We
just really avoid all of the things that
aren't mostly just design. We have one
team meeting a day where everybody syncs
up to make sure we're all on the same
page. And then other than that, we
mostly just let people do what they do.
And I think that helps us make better
work because the main thing that you do
is actually work on the work instead of
spending your day in meetings. Do you
have a plan to scale your business? I
mean, Mike is not scalable. No. In
America, there is like a desperate
culture of growth and you must make more
money every year and you have to grow
and you have to succeed and grow and
grow and grow and like everything you
make has to be bigger and better than it
last. And we have to fight against that
so hard, but really and truly our goal
is never to be a big company. Like we
want to be a small company where we are
still doing the work every single day
for as long as we have this company.
We've always wanted to grow like a
little bit because if we were a little
maybe 10 people, we could have a little
bit more capacity to do more projects at
once and you know have a bigger team.
But like you said, Mike isn't scalable.
So we've we've already just with our
team of five reached the point where if
we grow much more then he will less and
less be able to actually do the design.
And so we're very very conscious of
that. And we do not want to I mean part
of the reason we started this company
was so that he could be a designer. When
you look at a traditional agency and
your like career path, you go from being
a designer to a senior designer to like
an art director to like a creative
director and very soon all you are is in
meetings. All you are doing is giving
creative direction and you never design
anything. And Mike, that's part of why
we started this company is cuz he just
wants his title to be designer forever.
He just wants to be making the designs.
And so, so far we've been able to keep
doing that where he is a lead designer
on every single project. And that's
really really how we want to keep it.
We'll see if we're able to do that
forever or not, but um that's the goal.
How did I get to this point in my career
is a really good example of just like
not having a backup plan and just trying
really really hard and failing like a
lot. You know, that's something that I
think is super super important for for
people. It's like especially in this new
age of AI, like you can have things spit
out answers and things without even
thinking about it. And to me, I'm just
like, there's so much beauty in messing
up and not being afraid to mess up. And
I think that like skateboarding is the
the ethos of that. Like you only land a
trick once, but you try it 60 times. You
fall in your face, you break your board,
you you you have thrown your body down
this set of stairs or off this ledge 20
times, and at the point you're like your
your body's like, I can't take anymore.
But then like you come really close to
landing one and you're like all of a
sudden that energy just comes right back
up and you're like I'm going to try it
one more time and then you land it and
that's just it was all worth it. And so
for design I'm just like not afraid to
mess up and I'm not afraid to put out
some stuff that maybe people don't like
as long as I learned something about
myself in the process. Like I said
there's no backup plan. I'm doing this
until I die. So, it's like why would I
ever be scared of learning or be scared
of failing when like this is it? I'm
there's going of course there's going to
be highs and there's going to be lows.
So, why not just try it every single
day? And I think that's the most
important thing when people get scared
of trying. That's when you fall into
safety. That's when you fall into being
like, "Oh, I just wish I could grab like
these pieces and like collage them in a
way, like do some scrapbooking." And I'm
just like, "No, I want to reinvent the
book." like almost every single time.
Just that's that's the point. It's why
we're doing this. It's like I don't I
don't understand people that are just
like I wish it was easier and I'm like
why? Like I'm having so much more fun
making the stuff. That's where I have
that's where my heart feels the feelings
of you know um you're inventing
something. I guess you're creating
something from scratch and there's
nothing more beautiful than that.
[Music]