you like sausage I love sausage
you better go let me know what you think
I mean you could have grabbed it too I
probably just ate it like I did
and then what you're saying how you miss
me
[Music]
it's not that bad and eat McDonald's
breakfast at the same time
I think I really regret eating a whole
one in the shower a whole what
this whole thing taking one more bite
what
you're giving up after is it that good
like the first three that you buy the
whole thing and then just
my thought is more of like
skin of the whole thing you took a bite
so I'm already cutting off rashford
exactly
regardless the whole thing it's like
yeah neither can he just took a part of
it off let me get a bite let me get it
okay Matt such the type of kid to just
get two hash browns like we asked you
guys if we adjusted in the car then have
it on his lips what questions to ask him
and you guys did that
but no one's pulling it up so I'm gonna
pull it up just give me a [ __ ] second
I want you to introduce the video you
know there it was well give it a little
bit of a better name what is it you
never even it's a little new Justin
hello we found him we met when we were
in third grade and he wasn't like
seventh and um
we went to the grocery store and he was
there shopping for his groceries and we
were like you know what this man looks
like people looks like Indian's guidance
he looks like he needs a place to put
those ever since that day
is lived under our roof or brought his
groceries home stop being a [ __ ]
just kidding he was there we were born
but
I'm sure there was a moment where
someone saw him at a grocery store I was
like I'm gonna pick him up and bring him
home tough to find me at a groceries
people are weird why can y'all cuddle
I think we should explain to them beat
up Justin Time I think that's a good
thing I think it's a good thing to talk
about I mean it's pretty self-explained
I agree there was a moment of the day I
was dedicated to beating up Justin and
it was called beat up Justin but you
loved it
at all times you know I might not have
been the best brother so I gave them a
little moment you know maybe to shine
five or six minutes and they were like
little [ __ ] Gremlins but it wasn't
even five to six minutes it was like
hours of fighting no no it wasn't it
you guys
do what you could
have like frog bird and like it had to
it we did it for maybe a I don't know
how long do you think though
it's gone the reason why I thought that
was fun just because like Justin would
be in his room playing video games or
just doing whatever you're doing in your
room just take a little breather I'd be
like coloring Nick would be eating
cereal and Chris would be like upstairs
doing whatever you'd come downstairs
just screaming no matter what we were
doing everything was getting dropped and
running at it yeah ready to go
I remember wiping my ass once and just
like beat up Justin Time
you ever want a sister instead of a
brother
um so I have a step sister she's a
little older
um I had her you know before I knew
these guys
but in this house I always wanted at
least one little brother for sure that
was definitely what I wanted just wanted
a little brother and I got got three
craziness boom
I was actually just like Bonkers like
wanting one sibling and then yeah just
wanted a little guy to just kind of hang
around with and you know do Legos and
three oh were you like amped up when it
was three three I don't even know how I
even reacted like you were just probably
like didn't make too much sense to me
yeah because I didn't I don't even think
at that point I definitely didn't know
of any like triplets like when you guys
were oh yeah born whatsoever that's so
crazy
so I probably didn't even know that that
was a thing isn't it crazy you mad ass
when we were born and were you like we
didn't like we never like met you we
were just kind of like with you yeah I
think of that all the time people like
we were bored and then it was kind of
just like yeah there's like no ideas
your older brother and he's gonna be
there forever and he's your older
brother well for you it's like we're not
a thought for those first seven years
what you were in like first grade
first grade
actually the first third kindergarten
your favorite flavored Dorito
oh my God I'm gonna have this crazy
strict like feeling towards you if you
answer I feel like I flip-flop all the
time they just change on me it used to
be
um like the nacho cheese ones when I was
a kid used to bang them out and then it
was cool ranch for a while and then the
heist the high school I love the purple
ones that they had oh I love the purple
ones no like coming back they weren't
they're not as they don't hit like there
used to be exactly to be honest I
haven't really tried any other ones like
I don't really know okay just playing
the purple I hate what are your
favorites blue and red I'm cool I'm cool
or it's like mean main cooler Ranch well
that's all I would like purchase now I
wouldn't like I get once the purple ones
are disgusting dude they don't even
smell it they used to like smell
horrible like disgusting because Matt
used it uh Matt used to eat them all the
time in like his room and I couldn't
even go in his room but at the high
school that's like all they had so I was
banging those out and actually started
to enjoy them when Nick had buffalo
chicken in his room and then left it
under his bed yeah
make a face for me when you're doing
[ __ ] like that because my thought is
that never happened chicken in my room
and there was no there was no windows to
be opened there was there was you had
two windows on the door no but I'm
saying
no like
I was mad
he couldn't open the windows that just
didn't open because someone was gonna
climb to the second floor of the house
and cough in his window I'm just saying
we were all like no one no one went
outside you know you can still open a
window I don't think was it uh yes you
literally had every opportunity you kept
them outside your room is what you're
saying no I ate no matter what the trash
cans are 20-foot walk like I think is I
ate the buffalo chicken and then I
didn't USA I kept it under my bed I ate
it and then I maybe fell asleep after
eating and then threw it out in the
morning no no no four or five plates in
that room at a time because in a weird
position of the house where there wasn't
a ventilation to make the smell leave so
I ate something in there thank you for a
while especially when it's old
adds too much Aroma to the [ __ ] where
it's just spicy at that point what
I'd rather sniff someone's [ __ ] than
Febreze [ __ ]
and you spray Febreze and you're trying
to mask the smell that [ __ ] with the
Febreze it's just not there's too much
[ __ ] talk going on I'm chilling funniest
thing me Nick and Chris ever did Growing
Up like individually
that you remember
L question honestly what wow I don't
remember a funny thing Justin did
they're gonna think I had to answer this
because I think it was like funny that
stood out yeah they're just crazy like
the most outrageous thing one of us has
done I remember the most outrageous
Thing Justin did to me
that one was right there but Target was
first what was that I was in Target
let's go look at the like baseball cards
I ran and I walked I started walking and
you bolted gone and I have no idea where
Mom was I had no idea where you were I
wanted them to call you on the monitor
dude
please go into some random lady to call
him on the Monitor and goes what's your
mother's name he goes mom so they're
like a mom I said Mom yeah you went to
the thing yeah this dude I was walking
around aimlessly and some lady walks in
and she's like are you lost honey and I
go
I probably kept an eye on you though you
were gone
I remember Mom was like livid dude I
just left dude
Patrick Chris no no Christmas
no we were [ __ ] around and you like
picked me up over your shoulder and then
and went to like slam me like on the
couch and totally missed like oh and you
hit the the ground no no you hit your
head off like the piece the like the you
know the couch was like [ __ ] two
pieces yes there was a metal battle bar
back of the head right in the bar yeah
and then oh I remember that I was just
like oh why would this person park next
to us so sucks but no what's it called
[ __ ] my head was killing me and then
the Christmas lights were on and I go
what did I say hold on I'm confused
yeah
oh word all right gotcha
what is this no idea
I'm a Terry we just got kicked out by
[ __ ] mall cop yeah like what over
here is he drinking are we even in a
parking like a bad spot
we do this whole time goodbye buddy
that's crazy I can't like pull out like
dude what is he so worried about is he a
cop like is he in like a I thought he
was gonna try and Rob us are we on like
private property I don't know about and
the dude he's just in a Honda Civic
correct what is he a detective and then
we just like I just can't believe that
that just happened to me
we found another spot that has a some
overhead so we don't it's raining right
now so we parked in our underground spot
but we also
I've never had that happen to us I think
it's because it's like super early I
think Buddy's just nervous on guard like
he's like it's his time to defend it's
Batman in the night except it's not dude
he didn't have one thing that identified
him as like a person of authority
invisibility or teleportation
teleportation yeah it's really not close
I'd love a naughty people I love a combo
of them combo would be pretty cool I
know like this building would always be
pretty sick but it's like you can just
do you want to know you want to hear me
invisibility we get old in a week
teleportation but
I'll just teleport when I feel like I'm
supposed to be invisible like if I want
to be invisible in that scenario
you are invisible my thought is if you
teleport fast and stuff you're like
invisible to like maybe the human eye
like if you like imagine if you could
teleport faster like flash like he's
kind of just teleporting but like also
it's like if you could teleport really
quickly like the first thing I do is go
rob a bank right
and it's like if I can if I can like
teleport I'm just in the safe and I'm
out correct and also if you're if you
can teleport I imagine since it's like a
I know I'm going oh my God Nick like
don't say all that because it's not
realistic but we're talking about
yourself don't shoot me but I imagine
that for people who can teleport it's
faster than the speed of light
what the [ __ ] did you when I'm thinking
teleport I'm thinking I want to be on
the top of Mount Everest right now boom
amen correct agreed now would you not
would you care to agree that that's
faster than the speed of light way
faster I mean if you can go from here to
them that's why I'm saying the speed of
light in order to get picked up this
light like isn't that quick
it looks insanely quick but isn't it
so that's my thought it's like if you
teleport faster you'd be invisible why
would you want to be invisible oh so you
can go to this person's like whatever
like go in the bank or go this that like
why would you like invisible so you can
go to this person's voice it's just
teleport quick you know practically
invisible because I can't see it because
you're going faster with this pizza I
think I like what I'm teleporting like
yeah people can't see you but like sorry
I had a good idea
scare someone you don't like but you can
teleport faster than the speed of light
so you teleport like someone and go and
then teleport back
like this
I'm like oh my God
thing yeah
this is gone yeah just nowhere it's not
like you're like 10 feet behind him
you're like that ass like another
country
middle of Saudi Arabia
apples are pancakes waffles easily I'll
defend waffles in my whole life yeah
pancakes have too much like potential to
go the wrong way for me I just hate
butter
right you know I know if I'm just throw
it in the Press you're good correct I
know if I order a waffle I'm like 50
gonna be happy like if I'm a pancake I'm
at like 10 like oh this is gonna be I
personally I don't think I've ever made
a waffle though I don't think I've ever
actually fizzled we need to get one of
those what are we doing we need it
waffle maker one thing that blows my
[ __ ] mind is that waffle batter is
the same as pancake batter it's just a
different do you guys know that it's the
same thing I never really never wanted
to hear that again
legit waffle batter and [ __ ] is the
exactly just my point of view on
everything because I don't think you
understand what that did because you
thought they were completely no no no
because I was when I was a little kid I
had chocolate chip waffles and I said
chocolate chip pancakes are way better
when in reality I'm eating the same
thing she's in a different shape well
Matt maybe it was just the chocolate
chips you basically just said we said I
honestly are you stupid he just said
what we said to be fair is he stupid
little I used to have chocolate chip
waffles sounds like chocolate chip
pancakes would be so much better but
it's like yeah we all would sound stupid
if we said that and Nick thinks like
everyone's gonna relate to him right now
so he thinks he's like well because Matt
said it like he's
was he trying to make a different point
he's having a different point just
because what was the chocolate chip the
point was saying like I'm surprised that
it's the same batter since I think
pancakes are better than waffles with
chocolate chips yeah but everyone was
saying that but he's like talking about
like he's been waiting on emphasis on
the chocolate chips are you different
agreeing with what we've been saying or
bullying
it was like oh chocolate chip like it
was something crazy and new and it's
like it's all right it doesn't affect
the back no it actually makes it more of
a fact because it's like if you were to
get a pancake in a in a waffle and you
dump like some random mystery ingredient
on it right like say you put like like
[ __ ] like so I'm not following so you
think just straight up no nothing in
them waffles are better but with the
pancakes with the pancakes chocolate
chip because they're more like they're
not inside or like what those are the
waffles I feel like I think it's because
it's like it's like it's not I think
with one you're chewing like that you
don't want some nice warm soft chocolate
you want you feel like it just doesn't
melt as enough into the water yeah I
feel you ever get annoyed at Christmas
with us three
great question of Christmas okay were
you ever jealous
I think the funny part is like watching
when we watch those Christmas videos
back Chris opens a gift that like he's
like realizes what it is tells everyone
and then me and Nick at the same size
box still wrapped so confused what it
could be so surprised
I I'm open unwrap a [ __ ] unopened
it's [ __ ] 5 14 in the morning and I'm
exhausted go for it I still can speak
why do you have two pairs of pants on
some [ __ ] cold as ever okay let's get
this point does he actually saying
something I unwrapped like a Wii remote
you guys have Wii remotes identically
wrap next to it and you're like I'm like
Matt Nick check it out and you guys are
like no way and then you open the
[ __ ] gift that is
like more shock than me dude what are
you putting in your burrito
Justin
you know when you took me to a Taqueria
when I was six I've never changed my
burrito order in my life because of you
I bet you I know what you get oh let's
see testing steak
sometimes like a steak sometimes like a
chicken steak that's the only thing that
really changes all right steak lettuce
cheese rice pinto beans
and hot sauce
yeah that's a
bit you brought me to my first yeah I've
never I've never had a burrito with
different toppings ever since I was like
eight years old because me and you went
to the Taqueria together wow I'll add
some like veggies in there sometimes but
like not really those are the Staples
yep isn't that crazy though how do you
feel about Oreo those are definitely the
stuff we're doing like burrito that's
crazy lays doing too much correct like
pepper pan pick on the [ __ ] flavors
like birthday cake yeah we need to get
out of here we need to reevaluate pepper
jack dill pickle like let me go to like
raised chips needs a new creators no
hate but it's like another one of those
things why would I want those correct
who
like maybe sound even onion like yeah
like I'm asking a laze meeting like
someone probably said it like they're in
lazy oh look it's the holiday season
it's like hot chocolate lays peppermint
lays and I was like someone had to be
like you're you're you got it mad people
are gonna be like your captain those are
so [ __ ] good like yeah
you're a go-to breakfast
breakfast cheese breakfast juice juice
or juice juice
orange juice
okay if you could switch closets with
any of us through who oh that's a great
question
um probably Nick Nick's got a cool one I
thought you're gonna say Christmas I
thought it was gonna be Chris than me
than Nick's because he's got the mirror
and that's cool not like genuine
locations
[Laughter]
like the location has nothing to do with
it it's like you know just like what's
inside
I don't know uh yeah maybe Chris that
was Demi Lovato you guys are close
though you guys both I like mats a lot
as well man's closet there today it was
it was pretty fire
you pop up [ __ ] like that Jack of your
yesterday I said that's true I need to
get that everybody Demi Lovato and they
were like what's your name
what's your favorite dish to her and she
goes
she's like what's your favorite
dishes
thank you everyone for joining in on
today's Friday episode five in the
morning episode that's like the latest
in the morning we have to go to the
breakfast menu at McDonald's that was a
little crazy maneuver you're laughing at
me for getting a biscuit I felt like a
fool I felt like I made it I feel like I
made a mistake no nothing beat when I
ordered a Dr Pepper and the guy was like
cash only cash only I said gotcha I'll
pay cash she said okay move on up to the
next window I said can I order here
since it's cash shooting me up there he
goes nah order here tell me what you
want
I said
he instructed a hundred different things
for me hi guys
for my brothers