I quit my job and then it took a year
and a half for me to launch Julius after
that. When I when I went all in, I was
nervous to be honest. I was scared, but
it's being a little scared is good. I
think fear is good. You It keeps you
sharp. It keeps you on your toes. You're
able to see through things. When you're
in a comfortable place, it it breeds
complacency and you're often, you know,
fooling yourself into believing that
your ideas are going to work one day.
But then when all the bridges are burned
and you really have to make a thing
work, you start thinking, you start
taking risks, taking shots at goal. But
having no other boats, you know, no life
boats, it it was a little scary, but I
think it was good.
I'm Rahul, founder and CEO of Julius AI.
Julius is an AI data analyst. If you
have data on your hands, Julius will
help you get insights from your data
within seconds and help you make charts
and data visualizations. Since launching
in 2023, our users have used Julius to
make over 10 million data
visualizations. Every day, Julius writes
over 4 million lines of analysis code. 4
million lines of code is more than an
army of data scientists can write every
day. It took about a year and a half to
get to 2 million users.
For AI startups, I'll say focus. Don't
build a general purpose tool. Startups
win because of focus. That's the only
advantage you have as a startup. Now,
Chad GBD is like all-in-one tool. Making
videos, making images, doing internet
search, writing essays, and it's just
allin-one tool. And it's not focused on
data analysis. So, the experience is
much worse. A lot of our users they
start with using Chad GPT and they
realize that to analyze any kind of real
data to get any kind of meaningful
insights Chad GPD falls short. The
quality of insights you get aren't that
deep. It cannot handle any kind of real
data. The charts don't look good. You
can't collaborate with your colleagues
on the analysis. So all these problems
people run into after using it for a day
for analysis and they all go to Google
and they look up AI data analysis and
the number one search result on Google
for that is Julius.
It's kind of like think about hiring
humans. Would you want to hire one human
that can do everything? You you can and
that will help you get decent results.
But then there's comes a point where you
want someone with deep expertise,
someone who's really really good at one
function like a marketer, finance prof,
finance person, an engineer. I think
focus agents for a task have much more
competitive advantage than like the
general purpose agent.
You know, there's this like conventional
meme like Google just killed your
startup, OpenAI just killed your
startup, XYZ just killed this all
startup. I think all that is very
overblown. As long as your users don't
care about that stuff, it shouldn't
matter. If you're building something
that solves a problem for people, if
you're doing that good job at that
better than everyone else, that all
that's all that matters. So, this is
back in college when I got into the
hackathon scene. I would go to these
hackathons. The big problem I noticed is
you have 48 hours to build and launch
idea. A lot of the time people would
spend on setting up a backend service,
setting up their database and I thought
that was a waste of time. So water
review was this, you know, managed
service. You would get out of box like a
backend server or database that just
kind of worked. It got a lot of users
and I would go to these hackathons, give
it to people and they would try it. It
would save them time. But problem was
none of the people that built their
hackathon projects, their weekend
projects on waterview continued to work
on those projects after that weekend.
You know, it was like a weekend thing.
The big lesson there was you can solve
the right problem. You can solve a
painoint for people, but if they don't
have that pain point daily or weekly,
they're not going to retain. They're not
going to come back to the product. You
you have to solve a problem people have.
If they have it only once a year or once
every 6 months or once a month, they're
not going to retain to your product.
That's the reason why water we failed.
And that was a very valuable lesson.
I worked as an engineer at Uber and
Facebook. When you're at a big company
and you have an idea, one no can kill
that idea. Get a yes from your manager.
You have to get a yes from your
manager's manager, design manager,
product manager. You have to get all
these yeses and even one no can kill
your idea. So innovation doesn't really
happen in big companies. And then at a
startup it's complete opposite. All you
need is one yes. Looking for customers
you know you can get 50 nos but one yes
your first customer that's all that
matters. Instead of one no killing your
idea. One yes can really make your
company work. So, one of the problems I
was trying to solve at Uber is people
book Uber rides usually for things that
they can't drive to, like uh like an
airport or from an airport or when
they're out going out at night to bars
or restaurants. That sporadic usage is
not good for Uber. One of the things I
wanted to solve for is how could we get
people to use Uber on a daily and weekly
basis? So, I wanted to launch this
commuter product at Uber. How can we
help people use you know Uber's
offerings Uber transit Uber X Uber um
Uber mobility like bikes as scooters all
that as a part of a commuter package
that companies could offer their
employees. So I wanted to pitch the
idea. I was pushing it really really
hard and you know I got buy in from a
lot of cross functional management. I
couldn't get behind from our um
engineering leader and I couldn't get in
from the engineering leader and that
crush idea but at the same time I was
building apps and different ideas on the
side on the weekends and that motivated
me to just like quit my job and spend a
year exploring my ideas full-time.
Every failure is is is good. Failing is
good because you know what's what's not
working. I I I talk to founders and they
they're too scared to launch, too scared
to tell people what their idea is.
They're too scared to put the product
out there. I'm the opposite. You know,
at Julius, we launch things when they're
barely working because you want to get
early feedback from our users, our
customers. We want them to try it out.
We want to learn from our users and
customers on what they actually want and
how the things should work. So, I'll
give you one of the examples. We were
building in you know data and AI and
insights and we thought you know one of
the one of the group of people that want
insights from data but don't have the
expertise to go do data science on their
own is is sports fans. We built this
thing called NBA GPD was called hoops
GPD could help you query NBA data
playby-play data but just asking simple
questions. We had to build the UI, the
interface, figure out how this text to
querying engine is going to work and
ship the whole thing in like two weeks
because if you were too late, the NBA
season would be over. It was no point to
wait a year to try the idea again. And
turns out like sports fans aren't that
savvy about data. Turns out it's only
the people that want to do betting. Yep.
Really aren't the users you want to
serve. So we learn very quickly know
whether it's something people want or
don't want. We don't want to build
something that no one will ever want to
use. I think failing is important.
Failing fast is really really important.
Paul Graham talks about this in his
essays all the time. It's like failing
fast is super important.
This is months after launching Julius.
We had about 10 15,000 users and most of
our users at that point were actually
coming from Chad GPT. Chad GP is this
plug-in store where users would discover
Julius and they would come to Julius,
stay with Julius and use Julius over and
over and it's going great and it's going
great. We're growing overnight. Open
announces that the plug-in store is
going to get shut down and our biggest
source of users disappeared overnight.
So we had to scramble and figure out how
we're going to get more users and where
we're going to get users from. So that
was an existential moment and that is
what really got us to move fast and
figure out okay how do we get our users
to become champions of Julius. Then we
realized that when people analyze data
they want to tell their colleagues about
it. When you get an insight you don't
keep it to yourself. You want to tell
your colleagues you want to tell your
team. And so we build sharing into the
product. If you solve a problem that
people have, they will come to you.
They'll come to you and they will use
your product and they'll tell their
friends about it. So word of mouth is a
free way to grow your product.
If I were to start from scratch today,
what would I do differently?
Nothing. I think you know all the things
I would consider as like missteps things
um I could have avoided I think those
are valuable lessons you know all the
features we tried and didn't work out
all that is really valuable lesson
that's helpful data you can if you have
only data from successes then that's
very skewed you know what doesn't work
so it's really important to try a lot of
things things that don't work also
important because now you know what
doesn't work honestly like I would not
do anything differently.