at one point mixpanel we were turning
almost half of our customers every year
and it was this place where as a company
that's growing fast you know in some
ways that can that metric can be
overlooked but in many ways it was a
time where we really came together and
said look turning half the customers is
a major major problem in that we are
clearly not driving and delivering the
value as a company that we need to and
even though you know we we're still
growing we have to go back and address
churn but the reality was much more
complicated and nuanced it so happened
that there wasn't one answer you it
wasn't one thing it was a set of a bunch
of different things that we needed to do
and so that's where our journey began
and we literally made a you know a
series of categories of different
priorities we had a series of things
that we were going to go out and and
Tackle uh and everyone the company from
go to market to epd sort of had this
core mission to go out and get this done
and the result was really incredible and
by the time we did our series C we were
at 50 and this past spring we almost
touched 60 which is really like now kind
of consumer grade category and then
retention went from you know 50 to close
to
90% hello my name is uh Amir moaf fagi
I'm the CEO here at mixpanel we are an
event-based analytics company currently
have 9,000 customers globally
distributed company crossed the 100
million in Revenue a little less than a
couple of years ago we're super proud to
have our uh one other metric that we
disclos in our customer MPS being almost
a consumer grade approaching
[Music]
60 I was born in uh in tan in Iran I
spent 7even years in Istanbul Turkey so
I spent a good number of years there we
moved there when I was about eight and
then I came to United States when I was
15 when I was uh going through graduate
school it was a time when financial
crisis had hit in New York it was right
at the the beginning of where social
platforms were coming online and
Uprising uh in Iran I couldn't get a
hold of my parents because all the phone
lines were were shut down and you know
email was not working and at the time
Twitter was the only uh uh platform that
was uh really reporting what was
happening on the ground in ton and it
was this sort of like incredible moment
of realizing just how powerful the
social platforms were becoming at that
point it was such a personal attachment
to the product that was my lead in to
Tech so I joined Twitter in 2010 when I
joined a company we were about a little
over 100 employees we were pre-ad
Revenue it was a extraordinarily
exciting time even Twitter at its height
of success every 6 months was like a
completely different company you had
this company that you would wake up you
all of a sudden had an ad product that
failed you kind of had a moment of
having to really kind of have these
moments of existential crisis right hey
are we going to have you are we going to
have a company you know in 6 months is
there going to be are we going to be
able to make it to the other side in a
lot of ways the way that we go through
and fix things together as a team is
this ability to really come together on
a core problem and we understand why we
are focusing on what we're focusing we
have Clarity around what objective and
what outcome we're trying to get to and
then we're flexible about the how right
and we're able to take feedback along
the way from our customers from our
peers from our board you know from
everybody investors like we are able to
learn and understand and then iterate
and then hold ourselves accountable to
these outcomes so I think fixing
problems at its core comes down to First
really centering oursel on why this
matters why it takes precedent priority
over the 99 other problems you have and
then rallying and inspiring people to
really get in have Clarity on how they
can make an impact and difference on
that Journey when I left Twitter we had
grown from nearly 100 employees to 4,500
employees it was from close to zero to
you 2 billion in Revenue it was um
phenomenal incredible growth that
happened during that time biggest lesson
was the impact that user experience had
on the success of the company and this
Obsession around delivering a better
product a better user experience and
sort of like a in a way having that as a
leading path into better monetization
and better growth companies in
Enterprise software have invested quite
a bit on technology you know better
utility building a better technology as
like a first order of business being
part of Twitter it was getting a lot
more closer to just how much the
significance of making sure that you're
always thinking of the user the customer
first before you go figure out
everything else because without the
value without that Ultimate Experience
that you're delivering that's creating
value everything else can feel much more
femoral and much weaker
Foundation I think you know in many ways
when you're part of a in in a great
company that's has a number of different
opportunities to make an impact and
connect and grow with in many ways you
want to make sure that your skill set is
You Know Rich enough and mature enough
to be able to deliver a bunch of impact
but hopefully if you're in the right
position you're also gaining a bunch of
new knowledge and new tools I think in
many ways the the growth comes from just
having that sheer intellectual curiosity
and a desire to make sure that you're
influencing and impacting things that
matter and so biggest one is this
constant ability to ask am I doing the
thing that is the highest impact uh work
that I could be doing am I focusing on
things that actually will drive and make
a difference and then usually if you're
in the right role and you have the right
foundational skill set then the rest of
it will take care of itself you'll
figure out resources and who to tap into
it's one of the best parts of being in
Silicon Valley is you pick up the phone
and you can call so many people around
us that have either experienced that
exact same situation that you're in one
of the things that I always mention
people talk about like hey what's so
special about Silicon Valley why you
know would I move my company there why
would we you know start a company you
know in Silicon Valley instead of
somewhere else the and the answer I give
is when I started at Twitter we were
going through a bunch of newish problems
that we were experiencing and at that
time I remember just through networking
finding out experts that were you know
at Facebook or at LinkedIn or at Google
and you would reach out in every single
time almost 100% of the time there were
willing to jump on a call and they were
willing to collaborate and they were
willing to give advice and I think that
was such a a phenomenal sort of
validation of just how important it is
to be in an environment where people are
experiencing that same set of growth
ambition and experiences that they can
impart and and give to you as you're
solving your your problems in your
company do you use Ken Lee to book calls
Tod do is to manage tasks trell to keep
track of projects what if I told you
that you could do all these with one
tool but then it also integrates with
all of the tools that I just mentioned
hi everyone I'm Hannah from the EO team
and I'm here to introduce the
gamechanging productivity tool akif flow
it's basically a smart combination of
all the essential productivity features
I need on the daily first is the
beautiful marriage of task management
and time blocking akif flow has this
interface where you can create a to-do
list just as you would in any task
management tools but you can also drag
these certain tasks right into your
calendar to the exact time of day I find
this particular visualization of two dos
and schedules side by side very helpful
in prioritizing my work carving out
chunks of focus time needed for video
editing blocking time here syncs with
all of my other connected apps such as
slack Ken Le and more secondly it's the
magical command bar the go-to shortcut
for all features within aif flow instead
of navigating the app manually I simply
click on the command bar to command what
I wish to perform for example let's just
say that we confirmed an interview
filming and I want to put that in my
calendar I could just set that up
manually on the Google Calendar or I
could simply go ahead and type akif flow
founder interview filming on October
28th from 12:00 p.m. to 3: p.m. and
there's my schedule we've been using it
to keep track of our hectic filming and
traveling schedules every
day okay at one point mpanel we were
turning almost half of our customers
every year and it was this place where
as a company that's growing fast you
know in some ways that can that metric
can be overlooked you're like Hey we're
still we're still growing things are
still great and you know you would show
up and and look at these numbers and you
wouldn't even blink you're like yeah we
just had like half of our customers like
walk out the door but it's not a big
deal cuz we're getting so much more and
we're still growing but in many ways it
was a time where we really came together
and said look turning half the customers
is a major your major problem in that we
are clearly not driving and delivering
the value as a company that we need to
and even though you know we we're still
growing we have to go back and address
churn as a way of making sure we have
sustainable growth over time and that
product needs to kind of get to this
level of maturity over time and you know
the problem is actually this one was
quite difficult cuz we were initially
just trying to find like easy answers
you know maybe this is a segment problem
like SMB has higher turn maybe we just
need to go to Enterprise and that'll be
the fix all of our problems but the
reality was much more complicated and
nuanced and what it required was a very
very diligent way of again segmenting
and understanding the behavior from a
different customers in different
segments and then being able to really
narrow in on the reasons it it so
happened that there wasn't one answer
you know it wasn't one thing it was a
set of a bunch of different things that
we needed to do and the list was quite
overwhelming the way that we came at it
was instead of putting some crazy insane
kind of goal for where we wanted to be
in a in in a year time we acknowledge
that retention was a lagging indicator
that it would take time for us to really
move it and so instead we said what is
the single kind of proxy leading
indicator we can grab that would Inspire
the team get them excited about making
the right set of improvements um in
moving retention in the right direction
and then we shifted our Focus to NPS
user NPS we said look if we are able to
improve Pro user sentiment that's a much
faster in product signal we're going to
get from our users that starts going up
then we know we can kind of move the
dial on on retention over time and so
that's where our journey began and we
literally made a you know a series of
categories of different priorities we
had a series of things that we were
going to go out and and Tackle uh and
everyone the company from go to market
to epd sort of had this core mission to
go out and get this done and the result
was really incredible we were in single
digits uh MPS at the time and we were
able to move that 10 points every single
year and by the time we did our series C
we were at 50 and this past spring we
almost touched 60 which is really like
now kind of consumer grade category and
then retention went from you know 50 to
close to 90% as a result which I think
again speaks to this ability to
establish real feedback loops that allow
you to understand whether you're the
things you're doing are moving the
needle and then having this kind of
combination of leading lagging
indicators so that you have things to
inspire get inspired along the way in
your journey of execution rather than
having to wait you know a year to find
out if something was
working companies go through very very
different stages and challenges as
they're going from no Revenue to the
initial uh signals that there's demand
and there's a need for their product to
get 10 million Milestone they get the 50
million Milestone and there's huge drop
offs from each of these stages learning
an experience that at least we've taken
here at mix spanel is the ability to
really have a very rich signal coming in
from the pool of customers that you
don't have right because so much of your
signal and constant uh feedback loop is
around the core Market that you're
addressing and your core set of
customers that are paying you today a
lot of your signals are coming from
existing customers and so along the way
as company's maturing you want to make
sure you always have in the initial
phase you you you just you want to get
as small as possible solve the problem
for the smallest audience that is uh
able to get value and pay you for for
your product um but as you're scaling
and getting to 50 100 million plus then
you're really trying to also make sure
you have a lens toward
the set of the part of the market that
you don't own that you don't have and
make sure that you understand what
opportunities you have to grow and
continue to expand your offering and and
creating more value for a bigger part of
the market I think Beyond product and
and signal from customers the other
dimension that's really critical as
you're scaling is way that teams operate
internally how and the the way that your
executive team and you as a CEO need to
operate is going to change completely
right as a 10 person startup you're in a
very different capacity everybody's
everybody's doing everything and then
you're you're need to then go create
leverage really create autonomy and
ownership modularity within the
organization is going to be key uh in
driving kind of growth and success you
need past a certain
scale I think product L growth is is
really important and I think sometimes
we oversimplify what it means even expel
we've we've had quite a bit of a journey
in terms of understanding the nuances of
you know what it entails what works
within product L growth and what you
need to augment and layer on the the
fact of the matter is what's really
awesome about product L growth and
what's so good about so many of the
startups and different you know growth
companies really leaning into to this at
its heart the principle is we have we
need to have a really amazing product
that's self- servable that can people
can get value out of right away that
sort of speaks for itself
uh you barely need to sell you know
that's kind of like the the the end all
sort of uh goal of product lead and
that's awesome but there is so much more
to being able to leveraging product L
growth and actually creating sustainable
growth over time and a big part of that
is this element of you know Market
education everyone is going to come in
to your product with a very different
set of maturity right they may be at a
different part of the company
understanding of the problem that you're
trying to solve as a company being very
intellectually honest about truly
segmenting and understanding where you
have an opportunity to actually go drive
product Le growth where you can deliver
a self- serve for the most part a self-
serve experience that's really key
acknowledging that there's this space
and there's absolutely an opportunity to
be very sales l and a way that you drive
augmenting that product Le growth
knowing that you can always rely and
fall back on the fact that you have an
incredible product that once you get to
a right level of Market education when
you get to the right level of getting a
customer to the same spot then your
product will take care of the rest it's
just this kind of core appreciation that
initially product L growth is really
awesome because of its unit economics
it's like the fastest the most
affordable the best way you can possibly
grow but it's kind of core at its core
uh it requires a really deep
segmentation Focus for it to to
work first one is about being open and
being open to feedback you know we as
people get attached emotionally to our
decisions about how to go from point A
to point B and just knowing that uh
having qualitative quantitative feedback
will let your course correct and make
sure you get to the destination on time
um and then the second one is about
being able to lead change and Lead
change has the element that Nick spanel
every months is going to be a
fundamentally different company and we
want not only individuals to you know be
okay with change or support it but we
want them to lead it we want them to
know that we're going to need to explore
and find ways to go out and create ways
that we can create more value in the
marketplace third is uh a customer focus
which at the end of the day we're only
successful if our customers are getting
value and so any decision we make around
what product we prioritize How We Do
pricing and packaging right how we
evolve our support organization is
around this kind of long-term value that
we're creating for our customers the
fourth one is results oriented which
acknowledges that you know the single
best way for us to keep ourselves
accountable on whether we're moving
toward fulfilling our mission as a
company to help the world learn from its
data is uh people's willingness to pay
us money to to solve that problem and so
Topline a growth are we uh driving that
in a sustainable fashion through the
right margin profile and then finally is
the one team which really emphasizes the
import importance of establishing
meaningful connections among employees
to move beyond the transactional zoom
interactions into a place where they
know each other they can trust one
another so when they do get into a
position of conflict there's a
foundational trust and safety that
allows them to work through those things
productively
[Music]