Uh I think the trade-off if anything for
sure would be you know what one goes
through in college. I I felt I learned
equally if not more uh in terms of what
I wanted to acquire. Exposure to a fast
growing startup looking at how a venture
builder a VC thinks. I think having a
huge amount of ambition and a good
amount of naivity is what helps
entrepreneurs get started and having
that dreamer within you helps you do
things that are bolder one would not
conventionally take as well. Hi, I'm
Gdoric Chu, the co-founder and CEO of
Intellect. We are a mental health care
company serving and building for
Asia-Pacific and eventually the world.
We provide end-to-end mental health
support from proactive care all the way
towards coaching, clinical, and distress
support. We've raised funding from the
likes of Tiger Global, White Combinator,
Insignia. To date, we've raised over $30
million in funding. Well poised to grow
and scale in the next uh many years to
come as well.
I would say growing up I always had an
inkling that I wanted to be an
entrepreneur. My parents aren't
entrepreneurs themselves but I always
been quite inspired by people who have
built things that they believe in
themselves. I studied in Raffles
institution. It's uh I would say the
leading secondary high school in
Singapore where many of our greatest
Singaporeans have been to. I got in from
the benefit of a great educating system
and having worked hard to get there as
well. But as I went through my my years
studying, what I found out uh for myself
was that I had a clear want to to build
to do things and not necessarily go
through the career path that most of us
set out to do. But I was quite clear
that I wanted to build. I want to do
something that actually I care about
that I believed in and hence why I
decided against pursuing you know going
to to university or college and rather
chose to uh learn by doing learn by
joining companies that are have been
that and learn by doing myself as well.
First company I started back then was uh
a digital media platform right where we
actually gathered thought leaders
experts CEOs doctors to contribute
thought leadership pieces expert
articles to help people learn and grow.
At the point itself, I I was huge on
personal growth. You know, think of your
Tony Robbins, the like that actually
helps you grow and and develop who you
are. I was huge on this back then in my
in my later teenage years and believe
that many others would benefit from
consuming such pieces of information as
well versus just you know etiquette or
your fun quiz type stuff as well. That
company back then I would say was very
very lean. It was entirely bootstrapped.
We we had a whole network of anything
from volunteers to part- timerrs to to
guest writers that all contributed to
build that network of what we had. In
the end, I ran the first company for
about two plus years. At the point in
time, the biggest challenge was I really
didn't know what I was doing at a point
very candidly. I didn't even call it a
startup. It was a a website platform
that I was kind of doing. One of the
core things I would say I I believe in
it simply doing right. I do believe that
one does not have and would not have all
of the knowledge and all the skill sets
at any point of time. you can be more
experienced but sitting by doing and
trying uh one gets there. The challenges
was the fact that I didn't really know
what I was going about doing. What I
took was very logical steps on you know
finding the right people to work with
the right content to create the right
audience that we wanted to reach and
then things followed through from there
as
well. After exiting my first company
then I actually spent a few years
working for other very exciting firms. I
spent time at startups. I spent time at
venture builders. the the high level
intent then was I was quite aware that I
was a very young individual right I was
about 19 20 or so and I had very little
skill sets I had gotten lucky to have
done something interesting I didn't have
the experience nor the skills to
actually build something at a large
scale if I really wanted to so I decided
to spend time to go and endeavor and
find startups that were growing faster I
could learn from that excited me and and
that's what I did so following the years
that I had uh you know doing my first
company uh I joined a a a Japanese
travel tech startup called Voyagen that
actually I led a component of their
marketing team as well. The company got
acquired by Rocket which is a huge
Japanese conglomerate. So that was a
very eye opening as well right what
actually happened next after you know
that have I actually moved towards a
venture builder sort of a VC venture
builder firm called that was the next
chapter of my own journey as well I
wouldn't say there was uh particularly
regret or remorse you know going through
trade journey I was very intentional
about the choices I made and what I
wanted to pursue and the way I looked at
it was there were trade-offs in both
paths right I do strongly believe in a
good education country with a strong
education system so I think it's
fantastic that folks who go to path have
their own journey there as well. Uh I
think the trade-off if anything for sure
would be you know what one goes through
in college the experience and exposures
that go with the college experience. At
the same time I would say for myself I I
felt I learned equally if not more uh in
terms of what I wanted to acquire
exposure to a fast growing startup
looking at how a venture builder a VC
thinks and actually doing right learning
from actually practicing and doing on
the job as I built my own experiences as
well. You know after existing my first
company it was quite clear to me that I
was going to build something that could
reach and help and impact more people as
well. Uh on a personal level mental
health has always been a very personal
journey. So something that I went
through in high school in secondary
school was actually quite chronic
ongoing anxiety. I struggled with
anxiety in my teenage years and I
actually started having panic attacks
when I was 16. That's when I started to
see a therapist. So and what I remember
quite clearly was my very first therapy
session was one of the most cathartic
experiences I had. If people knew how
helpful therapy was, everybody would be
actually doing it. There was a national
survey actually done pre- pandemic in
Singapore. One of the key stats that
stand out quite scarily to me is that
there is a 4 to 7year treatment gap of
mental health support and care. That
means to say if someone's actually
mentally unwell and needing care, they
waited 4 to 7 years before they got that
care. And that's for those that actually
eventually got the care, which is a
scary long and and and delayed period of
time if you think about it from a
physical health point of view. So it's a
huge huge issue and and if you look at
it from a outcomes perspective as well.
Asia many of the fastmoving cities have
some of the highest suicide rates as
well. So the problem is extremely clear
and extremely real. I mean from a from a
top down perspective the mental health
market across the world and even Asia is
in the tens of billions of dollars. We
believe this market not from our belief
but it is growing annually in double
digit percentage rates as well. So fast
forward years later into 2019, mental
health was something that I I was quite
clear was one of the key things I wanted
to to tackle and solve for. And having
gone through many more lived
experiences, uh having seen peers,
friends and friends of friends gone
through much much more troubling and
darker things themselves, a very clear
thing popped up was how do we actually
change this? How do you make mental
health care accessible as well as
everyday no matter how big or how small
your issues may be? In the earliest days
of intellect I in a very very lean setup
we we actually went about to understand
mental health what is the problem around
mental what was the thing that needed to
be solved for as well and we came to a
very very simple problem statement
people in Asia need help they want help
but they don't know where to start so
our initial hypothesis is how do we
bring care to them in a way that it's
almost extremely uh too simple like
there there's no reason why one couldn't
access care that was a simple initial
hypothesis bringing access to everyone
first scaling access and then secondly
getting deeper and deeper in the care
that we bring as well and hence why and
like what we do spans across different
mediums there is self-guided content
that is anytime anywhere different
languages we have deeper live virtual
care we even have crisis support as well
and we've gone in that journey from
scaled up care towards deep immersive
facetoface support as well firstly
anyone starting at a company is hard no
matter how I believe how experienced or
how inexperienced one is there are so
many uncertainties, so many variables
that never guarantees anyone's puff. For
us in particular, mental health, you
know, when we started the company back
in 2019, it was a very very nent topic
particularly so in Asia. Most clients,
bias, investors were not seeing this as
a priority for them at a point in time
as so for us it was really stemming from
a strong conviction, a belief that
mental health was not an if but a when.
Mental health is as important as
physical health. In many ways, even more
important sometimes because of how it
affects all that we do as well. So for
us the challenge then was how do we
build the cali? How do we build the
market? It was a nent space. How could
we actually convince our first
investors, users, customers? It was hard
to convince people to actually meet you
firstly or even you know want to do a
pilot and trial review rather as well.
So much less finding customers for us.
The early days were really speaking with
a lot of individuals anyone from HR
professionals, clinicians, folks on the
streets even as well to try and very
clearly understand what was the problem
we're trying to solve for. the first 10
customers a small small pool of people
to validate and these were early stage
startup that were happy to actually test
out and let us know if it worked or not.
So I would say what worked out well for
us was actually starting small knowing
quite clearly the broader vision and
mission was but starting in smaller
steps that we could chip away towards
that larger goal eventually as
well. It's been quite a journey. It's
been it's been not been uh relative
towards the bigger scheme of things not
been a huge amount of time but a time
that a lot has happened at least in in
my life. So I'll say one of the biggest
learnings I've had that that I find
useful and I I keep reminding myself
time and again is that it helps to have
a bit of naive in terms of what one one
has right in terms of what I think is my
my superpower if I could say it's huge
ambitiousness in terms of what I believe
one can actually achieve and that has
actually for better or for worse guided
me into taking the steps I have taken
from you know not going to pursue higher
education starting a startup and and
doing what we have today as well. I
think having a huge amount of ambition
and a good amount of naivity is what
helps entrepreneurs get started and
having that dreamer within you helps you
do things that are bolder that one would
not conventionally take as well. So I
would say in terms of what my advice is
for people aspiring to be entrepreneurs
young or old as well definitely possible
right I'll encourage those who are
interested to try to definitely give it
a shot. I I I do fundamentally believe
that there is no better time in our
history for one to actually start a
company to have the amount of access to
information and reach of audiences than
than ever before with the internet and
with with all that's happening.
Definitely try but definitely expect
that outcomes may differ from people to
people. I don't I don't think that
everyone is born or meant to be an
entrepreneur but I think everyone
definitely can try cuz if anything one
learns massively from this experience in
many cases one can actually impact a lot
more people as well. So I do believe
fundamentally there's many paths towards
one defines as fulfillment or or even
success as well. And this is the path
that I've taken but there will be many
more that people can actually take on to
to achieve what they want to do as well.
[Music]