In 5 years, we could have AGI systems
that completely automate all human
labor. AIs do all the repetitive work
and humans do all the novel work. Every
human is going to become a product
manager of a team of AIs. How are you
supposed to plan for that? I think it's
extremely hard to predict where the
world will be in 5 years. One-year plans
make sense right now. Threeear plans are
really hard and 5ear plans are
impossible. So, because the AI market is
changing so fast, like every month, like
new systems come out that make new
things possible. The right way of
navigating that is to think from first
principles about like what does the
market need that still will be true in a
year. Because if you're thinking about
what does the market need right now, a
month later something new is going to
come out and they're not going to need
it anymore. So you have to think a
little more longterm. You have to be a
little more strategic than in the past.
You know, for example, like when I was
in college, AI was not at all as
prominent as it is today. Everyone today
talks about AI, but there were a few
people who were aware of what was going
on. I was lucky enough to go to a
Westworld watching party at OpenAI and I
was actually on a bean bag with Greg
Brockman um just chilling on this bean
bag and we were arguing about the
scaling hypothesis and the scaling
hypothesis is this idea that you keep
putting more compute into transformers
and they'll just keep getting better and
that's how we get to
AGI. That was a crazy idea when I was in
college. The vast majority of people
didn't believe it. I didn't believe it.
Greg was arguing that if we just keep
scaling these things, we'll get there.
We'll get to AGI. And I was arguing that
we need new types of methods. I think we
were both right in our own way, but we
kept seeing progress from GB1 to GB2,
GB3, eventually GB4. And at some point
along that trajectory, I was like, "Holy
cow, like these systems when you scale
them, they just get really good." I
think the people who were earlier to
that conclusion did better. And we kind
of apply the same scaling logic to Exa.
We are building transformer-l like
systems for search. And we also know
that if you keep packing data and
compute into the search engine, it will
get better and better. That's a
hypothesis we have. It's like our own
scaling hypothesis for search. It's very
different from traditional search
engines like Google or Bing which
basically have stayed the same for you
know many years whereas like X is
getting better like this. And so we're
thinking a lot about like where is the
future going? Uh so we see a world where
there are agents everywhere. GBD5 level
AI agents navigating the web doing all
sorts of tasks. This future is coming.
They're going to need search all of
them.
Hey, I'm Will. I'm the CEO of Exa. We're
building the next generation of search.
One good way of understanding Exa is in
contrast to traditional search. So,
traditional search engines use mostly
keywords. Okay? So, if you're using a
traditional search engine and you want
to find startups working on futuristic
hardware in the Bay Area, traditional
search engines will use keyword
matchings. The results they give you
will be documents that contain the words
startup and hardware and Bay Area. But
startups that are working on futures of
hardware in the Bay Area, they don't
typically have those terms. Like you
might have a a rocket company in SF. A
traditional search engine won't be able
to find that rocket company. But Exa can
because uh we understand the meaning of
documents. We understand the meaning
that oh, if it's a rocket company in SF,
then it does match startups working on
futures of hardware in the Bay Area. We
believe it's possible to have perfect
search over the web, meaning whatever
information you want, you get exactly
that. We help companies integrate this
high-quality knowledge into their
applications. So we recently raised $17
million from Lightseed and Nvidia. Our
revenue is doubling every quarter. We're
building the next generation of
search. I came into college wanting to
study physics to like I want to
understand how the universe works and I
thought physics was the right way to do
that. Something big that influenced me
was watching the social network cuz I I
was studying at Harvard and the social
network took place in Harvard. It was
actually a very accurate movie and it
was very inspiring to see this guy
change the world just on his laptop. I
realized that you could have like a
massive influence just coding on your
laptop in a way that you couldn't as
much with physics. It was very clear
that that that the AI could understand
the problems of physics. So I went into
computer science and I think that turned
out to be right because now like the AI
is getting so good that it should be
able to just tell us the answer or
infuse it into our brains. Before EXA on
the side I was writing a history book. I
got really excited about world history
and I decided I'm just gonna write a
book about it because I'm like no one
has captured in a book my the level of
excitement that I had and so I was doing
a lot of research for the book. I
quickly realized that Google is actually
not good enough for that type of
research. Like Google is great for
surface level investigations. Once you
start like trying to go deeper and
trying to understand any topic deeply on
the web, Google really fails. For
example, if I want to find like all the
research papers on uh poverty in ancient
Rome, it's actually really hard to find
that on Google. Not every paper will
mention the word poverty. And so I was
doing the research for this book and it
was really hard to find things. And then
at the same time, GB3 had recently come
out and GB3 was this magical creature
really that I could talk to and it could
understand like anything I say at a very
deep complex level. And so the thinking
was what if we could apply the same
technology of GB3 to search? What if you
can make a search engine that actually
understands you at a deep level? And
it's been the same goal ever
since. The first year and a half of EXO,
we did research into uh search models
into how can we take transformer models
and apply them to a search engine. No
one's really done that before. It took a
long time to figure out how to do it
well. And that required persistence.
like we were just banging our head
against the wall for a year and a half
trying out different models, trying out
different data sets and eventually we
got something that worked really well.
If we didn't have the persistence, you
know, 6 months in, we might have given
up, but we didn't. Early November 2022,
we launched the first version of Exa to
the public. We built a search engine
that was perfect for AI applications.
Basically, AI systems, they have all
this intelligence, but they're lacking
in knowledge. And so, when they need
knowledge, they go make a call to Exa
and get exactly that knowledge. Then
catch came out a few weeks later and
that was a big moment uh for the
information ecosystem. But for us it was
really interesting because we started
getting requests for API access to our
search engine. We started getting
requests for API access uh first from a
friend who was actually like living
downstairs. I told him no sorry we don't
have API access. And I didn't really
think much of it. Uh but then we kept
then we got uh a request for API access
from someone from some company in
Germany. And we also told them no sorry
we don't have an API. And then we kept
getting requests for API access. And we
realized that because of chatbt, people
were starting to build AI applications
all over the place for all sorts of
businesses. And all these AI
applications needed search. Like the AIS
themselves needed to search and that's
when we started to realize, okay, X
could be really useful for these AI
applications. Yeah. So our initial
customer found us. And so one lesson
there is just like be a really good
listener to the market. Like what are
people repeatedly saying they need? and
you might have some idea of what you
know what you're going to sell but then
if people keep requesting something like
API access maybe you should start
listening to them like we cared more
about uh learnings from the customer
than getting a lot of revenue and so
yeah we were like opening our ears to
what do the customers need uh over time
developed a hypothesis about how we
should price and what types of customers
we should
pursue. I think you can guess where
companies like OpenAI and Enthropic are
going to build based on like what are
like what are big markets that they
could tackle like agents like automating
work is a clear huge market and so
they're clearly going to do that. Okay.
So now you know what types of things
they want to do. Can they do it? Well
then you think about fundamentals of
LLMs. You think like okay LLM can as
long as you can make training data for
some objective they will get better at
that objective. Can you make training
data for agentic behavior? Definitely
you just have a bunch of examples of
navigating the web in order to buy plane
tickets and if you have a million
examples of that then now the LLM will
know how to buy plane tickets. Yes. So
any sort of task such that you could
create data for it LLM will get near
perfect at that task. So that's like a
fundamental way of thinking about this.
So will AI get really good at navigating
the
web? Yes. That's pretty easy because
it's it's easy to generate lots of
navigating the web data. Will AI get
really good at
robotics? Yes, but probably on a longer
term horizon because gathering lots of
robotic training data is harder because
it's hardware and hardware is hard to
work with. So what do we learn from
that? We learned that AI's navigating
the web will come pretty soon. AI's
navigating robotics will take longer. So
just from like simple first principles,
you can like guess where things are
going. Picture in your mind how crazy
good technology will be and AI will be
in a year and then build for that world.