and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
[Music]
hey guys we're about to go on a trip but
we don't know where we're going that's
the fun part Laura likes to surprise us
with these little adventures but since
we don't know what we're in for at all
I'm going to show you a couple things
that we're packing for our personal
hygiene that I know guaranteed I'm gonna
have to use on there all right before we
go I wanna let you guys know the number
one thing across the board for personal
hygiene for me Matt and Chris is making
sure that we're wearing deodorant so we
all use native deodorant this is mine
vanilla and Sandalwood vanilla and
Sandalwood has a warm and cozy scent to
it and then this is Chris's which is
coconut and vanilla coconut vanilla
smells beachy and sweet
and then we have Matt's charcoal
deodorant the charcoal smells just like
charcoal but with a little bit of citrus
and then also here you go thanks they
sent us from their new Candy Shop
collection sour Berry belts which smells
exactly like the candy on this all of
these are paraben and aluminum free and
unlike other deodorants I've used in the
past when applying them I feel sticky
but with these they apply dry and then I
feel dry the entire time afterwards
while wearing it I also have the comfort
of knowing that I'm never gonna smell
bad because native deodorant has a 72
hour odor protection and it's vegan and
cruelty free
which is awesome oh yes and yeah guys
that's why we use native deodorant if
you want to use native deodorant click
the link in the description down below
and use code sterniolo which is right
here on the screen for 20 off of your
first order so don't look at me go click
that link
oh I got a [ __ ] so oh my God that's that
can't be the first thing they hear
[ __ ] hour okay Vlog me but I'll go to
Dairy Queen I thought I'd make my famous
chocolate
sauce
but we just stopped because I have to be
Chris has the [ __ ] and that is a [ __ ]
Dairy Queen and I want ice cream dude I
win in summer Vlogs we need to get Mike
up time please make it better come and
Rescue Me I can't believe Nick had the
audacity to suggest this song while
watching RuPaul's Drag Race like either
pick that you're watching a TV show or
listen to music you can
you all right take the camera I got a
[ __ ] I gotta [ __ ] it's still recording
I better make a blizzard Chris that's
terrible
hey
hey I love you at Dairy Queen just post
it on my story
hey guys we didn't vlogging again we got
here but we're on day two we slept here
last night
um I'm gonna go sneak into Matt and
Chris's room I don't know
they're definitely awake
but I'm just gonna go in there anyway
for fun
what did you say is that [ __ ] blanket
hogger cut me up all night yeah this is
crazy the lack of blanket in this area
go to that side of the bed
yeah this is pretty wild oh
wow woke up cold
Matt
[Music]
no I'm not going anywhere
it looks nice though thank you
okay I can't believe this dude
The View no [ __ ] Matt stealing my
blanket
but yeah guys we got here yesterday I
didn't Vlog anything
um but we slept through yesterday today
it's gonna be like our only full day
we're doing a quick little trip but
we're gonna take you along with us and
it'll be fun next time I stay at a place
like this I know it's like
guaranteed allergies
I'm gonna fill up a bucket of freezing
cold water before I go to bed
and then just leave it on my nightstand
and when I wake up just immediately pull
a hat in the bucket
stepped and heard a bunch of crunches
man oh man this man spilled the Rice
Krispies you know where the broom's at I
[ __ ] hate cocoa Crispies bro I don't
like Cocoa Krispies but I'm being
considerate because considering I mean
consider it because we only have like
that or like Frosted Flakes and I know
more people want Frosted Flakes so I'm
like you know I'm like okay they're
great I was like you know I'm okay with
cocoa Crispies I'll take this long bro
cocoa crispy is a dog [ __ ] I'd rather
eat [ __ ] Kellogg's pops because I
only understand that's why I'm eating
them because I want someone else to be
able to enjoy cereal a lot because
you're considered right
consider right what'd you say Matt
I said I'm excited say it louder I said
I'm excited I came downstairs and the
Frosted Flakes weren't eating until I
can have them
I [ __ ] told you it's time to wash
down my cereal with cold pepper bro give
it a break oh [ __ ] don't it literally
says do not pull the handle hold on
uh oh
I'm doing that
what does it say here
are you exactly
it says turn clockwise once to start do
not attempt to open until compression is
complete if the door sticks please
return the compressor so I have to keep
it going yes
it'll Auto stop now
what the [ __ ] where
oh lizard look man what lizard where
why does he look fake he's not he just
ran at me bro looks funny kinda I'm
gonna get it
this is like we didn't even transition
to where we are now Lars is holding a
baby raccoon oh yeah there's more in the
bucket are they named
[Music]
it yeah
oh IP freely
he matches your hat he does
what you know okay oh my God
the Tails everybody
oh my God so cute
okay
this is good or bad yeah like what does
this noise mean is he afraid of him or
does he like him
oh yeah
I've been feeling supported Matt I'm
trying my best
Largo's walking in that building next
thing you know I'm holding a baby
raccoon yeah that was insane you say
that that right there's the scratcher of
baby raccoon I don't know if it's scars
that would be so cool I don't like it I
love my vaginal rest
oh
oh my God everything you want to go in
that store oh my God it's a Pokemon oh
no it's not it's Luigi I'm sorry
yeah like I have to whisper in here
everyone else is so quiet
thank you
all right
God unique yes I like literally have
seen everything in there
everywhere there's nothing unique about
that place
you know I hate when a place you know
they finesse you I feel like we should
go through the front Nick not the I
think that's the back door nick I feel
like they basically put all their good
stuff in the front
does it
let's follow him this is like stranger
things like I know the guy
oh wow straight to the
whoa arcade whoa
this is a lavender plant gotta send a
photo to my mom lilacs I think lilac
that's it
that it said Mom the Lilac bush she
loves it favorite flower
House of jerky what I kind of want to go
where I don't know but it says it on
that sign Nick you in that flag look
exactly the same right now
hmm
yo is this a vintage clothing
what a jackass
oh my God it says Treasures
so we gotta go there
treasure absolutely
coffee Crepes gelato bubble bubble
waffle
rate your crate
you're so good
[Music]
oh you got marshmallow on your lip yeah
there you go you're good
they had chocolate on your lip
I can feel where it is yeah there you go
match
this is gonna be my like if you're
taking us on these like you need to buy
this yeah if you're taking us on Mystery
Adventures every month I'm gonna get a
shirt every single one of the place I
already know what we're going for our
next mystery Adventure I'm so excited do
they sell shirts Nick Laura said she
already knows the next place we're going
right there Instagram picture mountains
and trees in the back okay let's do it
okay I'll explain to the Vlog that
the Vlog all the viewers are like oh my
God summer Vlogs like we love summer
Vlogs and I have to fully agree with
them yeah we can I have to fully agree
with you guys the summer Vlogs really
are the best and I want to make them
even better but I want to do like more
just like is there a couple of you just
walking bro shut up like I'm trying to
go up to the [ __ ] thing look up there
there's like three feet of rock just go
out like Matt's walking like there's
gonna be like a path right there there's
no path you just gotta genuinely
like what are you doing oh my God what
oh my God what hold on
oh my God Matt
there's a wire right here this used to
be a zip line
it goes all the way to the other tree
is that okay hold on
that fell apart like it was like a video
game feeling super Twiggy lately uh-huh
you missed them again
hard
I would hit him right in the face I
don't think it's nice to throw rocks at
your brother it's not a rock it's a
stick whatever I have to go Instagram
live and just leave it on the creek and
walk away I'm down
that's why that'd be kind of funny it
was a joke
um I could pee so bad I wonder why Paul
Revere's wagon
oh my God that look at the OG shape bro
like this is low-key if me Matt and
Chris if me Matt and Chris were born
like hundreds of years ago this would
have low-key been when we filmed car
videos in literally what
like this one he just asked if that was
a bear trap I'm like what was it the
world's biggest [ __ ] bear ever it
looks like dude I'm telling you bro this
[ __ ] is better than Dasani
dasani's ass so there's really no
competition like bro feel like feel that
you can like feel the carelessness ready
go for it how do you touch it well you
gotta like lean
and dab
not Nick don't okay
oh my God right it's like a nice arctic
cold right
thick there's a trail
we have to walk
go go go
are you stopping the water from flowing
through the creek
because damn
[Laughter]
walk me through it you're doing
cinematography here I'm just taking a
video so like walk me through like the
positioning the lighting the click
I'm taking a video walk me through it
though
I'm honestly just taking a video but
like walk me through why you're taking a
video I'm like where where your
whereabouts are you know I'm good I'm
just like walk me through how you're
doing to be honest I'm just taking a
video but like walk me through it I'm
good you don't want to walk me through
it
hey y'all
oh God hey y'all last night in this
little oh okay last night in this little
uh cabin here but
we were gonna bake cookies and show you
guys but they were so good that we just
baked them and eat them
I'm not even really a fresh cookie off
the oven type of guy you know that bro
we saw a girl today and she just
screamed colby jack I was ready to
literally actually just lie down the
road I was in and he's been hit by a
truck she's really nice she was it's
just if I hear colby jack again I'm
gonna cut my [ __ ] ears off and turn
him into a necklace oh that'd be kind of
hard like right yeah it would be funny
if I had two ears on a necklace and not
on my own like sometimes I think like
having like followers is such a weird
thing because it's like someone will see
you in public and know who you are and
like be shocked like imagine like people
who don't have followers with Bagels
sometimes I forget I'm a YouTuber and
like a girl will gasp like I'll walk
too like I'll be like who's there
oh yeah way less cool yeah
can you go record outside for like 20
plus minutes and I can Loop it and sleep
to it yeah I got you
we're about to leave how heavy that
gutter is going man where
oh my God we're about to leave dude that
knock your head off this is probably the
shittiest weather we've had here so
thank God we're this is the day we
decided to decide dude look over here
Nick look at this guy they're going
crazy absolutely buckets right there oh
my looks so nice though there's a shower
under it no good goodbye cabin goodbye
rain goodbye Creek
goodbye hammock
goodbye
table
goodbye door
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me