H it's the green thing on the bottom
left but I don't see
it you don't got a whistle it's not a
it's a camera not a
dog
yeah it's working yeah it's definitely
working okay that was welcome to testing
the mic what's your [ __ ] deal What's
your deal what are you 90 years old
What's your deal you have your own water
right there correct and it's you have
your own water right there and it's way
colder and refreshing I'm itchy really
underated really underrated joke the
other day Matt um he picked up a package
that he got and it was like a big
package but it was super light okay hold
on hold on everything's wrong
everything's wrong did Nick get the
package everything's wrong mom's package
it was mine okay you got a package let's
let's normalize letting people that this
the story actually happened to tell the
story yeah let's normalize it I hate
that let's normalize stop saying
normalize everything everything is
normal okay why is there always cops
here hello officer don't arrest me
um go for it what were you going to say
Nick just got a really light package and
I picked it up and I said hey what did
you order oh hair air it was funny it
was really fun was a funny joke like
saying a joke that like happened the
moment yeah it's not funny yeah um was I
going today me and Chris went to go get
ice cream and we were in the ice cream
how did they get there who drove mind
your business we got to the ice cream
place and this lady was like I felt bad
for her um I was too busy [ __ ]
[ __ ] getting money I'm joking no but
we were we were in the ice cream place
and this lady was like waiting in line
and she had like a three-year-old kid
with her and he was like Mom hurry up
and like hitting her couldn't do it oh
no no yeah he couldn't talk he couldn't
talk that was me like imagining what he
was thinking as like a three-year-old
yeah like he was like three he was like
hitting her like this and fresly walking
I turned around at some point to see who
like someone was opening the door and I
want to see was coming inside cuz I'm
nosy and I like looked to the entrance
and then I looked back at the lady and
her kid is like on her back like like a
like a cheetah like he was just
everywhere if you searched up if you
searched up like like mountain on top or
okay hold on hold on hold on how big
tell me when to
stop it was a kid not a posa no saying
like three-year-old boy like tell me
when you're better off saying like how
tall yeah he's probably like this tall
like he was probably like my a little
above my kneecap where my three's
tattoos are okay little kid but no there
was one point where he was grabbing his
mom by the neck like like literally like
behind and yes and she and he was
standing like on her no I yeah she went
to put him down and he just kept like
being like whining and she was like you
need to be patient you need to be
patient a long line
ice standing he's 3 years old can't talk
kind of mid height this is why I'm
confused is it a baby or a toddler it
was a toddler it was a toddler it
definitely a baby that could not talk
but could walk and like complain like
like ver like it was like verbal
complain like oh yeah you know two to
three for sure whatever and he was at
one point she was like no holding the
mother's back standing on her lower down
she went to put him down to the ground
and she was upside down like his head
was this close to the ground and she
like an and like and put him back out
but he was just all over the place and
she was trying to get a hold of him
she's like you need to be patient
meanwhile she was also trying to order
and there was people everywhere and I
think she was like on her phone anyways
pass forward like two minutes no in the
in the ice cream store there's the metal
bars between people waiting in
yes and he starts climbing up on them
and he stands on it and I literally
thought my head oh he's going down he's
going to fall cuz he started climbing
metal things and she wasn't like looking
like she I think it was finally her turn
to order or no she wasn't even ordering
yet but she was like looking forward he
climbs up immediately Falls and doesn't
break his impact with his hands his back
his butt his legs flat on the flat part
of the back of your head on the ground
and it was so loud everyone in the place
turned around I was shocked he wasn't
gushing blood and he's baby like I see
his head hit the ground I see his eyes
roll back and his head he like this like
all the all the air out of his body and
he just gets up and starts like
screaming like as if it was like a a
satanic chant it was
like like SC like screeching like like I
was like I was nervous and she picked
him up and she goes oh you need to be
patient she skips everyone else in line
pays for their stuff and they leave and
he was just like screaming crying
causing a scene oh my God but I was like
shocked a
concussion I was watching him fall for
like 2 seconds it felt like longang cuz
it's like it's like and like the Mother
wasn't paying attention cuz she was
focused on like the ice cream and [ __ ]
the whole time was there another kid
just the one kid in the one mom and
she's just not paying attention I just
it's crazy to me the I literally said I
this lady's like not she needs to pay
attention to her kid I said that and
then the [ __ ] kid starts climbing it
and he's falling and me and Nate both
kind of like Flinch to like yeah but I'm
like I'm not going to like like I'm not
going to lady's kid you know what I mean
but then it was also like when we when
it was our turn to order the lady goes
what like when I got to the counter I
was like like I jumped back I was like I
don't even think I want anything anymore
cuz then I like didn't I didn't order
sprinkles cuz I got like embarrassed I
was like I'll get like a scoop of coffee
ice cream and like a cone she goes and
like points at the options of cones I
was going to be like can I add but I was
like she already doesn't want to do what
I asked for let alone adding another
thing no it was a lot it was I was
embarrassed it was a lot that was pretty
nice but the kid went splat it was crazy
if he was [ __ ] paint he would have
been all over the walls yeah I went into
the grocery store and I went to get my
mini pizzas do you know how the pizza is
in the thing where like automatically
pushes the next one forward no yes do
you know drinks you you drink and all of
them come I hate those stupid but with a
drink because it's a a long thin bottle
it slides so there's nothing like really
like pushing it forward this one spring
activated had like a springloaded booby
trap behind it and so I'm walking over
to the pizzas and I can't find the ones
that I normally get and I see a stack of
them like yay high but behind the glass
freezer like over here to the left and
I'm like why is there like five
miscellaneous pizza boxes like and
they're all like stomp up top like like
on top of each other they're not like
organized someone must like spilt it
whatever and I walk like still like
three full solid strides to the right so
that tells you distance and I see the
pizzas and I see they're in the
springloaded thing right so I go I don't
know how five of them I'm like someone
must have got five of them and then
changed their mind put them back so I
[ __ ] open the freezer and I grabbed
the first one boom spring-loaded Pizza
trap like Bing Bing Bing right off my
face I get a a literally felt like a
spring-loaded pizza booby trap boom
right in my mouth and I open the freezer
I grab it and I pull the first one up
like this and then the second one peers
through like a bullet I thought like I
was in like a movie hits me in the face
and then like it fully flew out like
dude it was a square pizza and it would
I'm like I must have been the perfect
height victim for the spring-loaded
pizza booty trap because it literally I
literally picked it up boom like that
right like the full Square thing mini
pizza in my face and then like six more
like pop around and then like all of
them land to where the pile was so I'm
like that exact thing must have happened
to someone else but I literally got set
up by a spring-loaded pizza booby trap
that's insane that's pretty nuts we need
to we need to buy one for our house the
worst thing is when you decide you don't
need as many of what you just grabbed
and you're trying to put it back and
you're like trying to like res you you
had to push the it's ridiculous what
about how like dude what about stores
like locking up like deodorants and [ __ ]
it's insane it's like everything I went
toothpaste and it's locked up the other
day it's like 2 in the morning and
there's nobody there with the key you
know like the key guy goes home it's
like okay looks like I'm not brushing my
teeth until tomorrow what blows my mind
is like why like I feel like I when I go
into like a CVS or like a r Aid I need
like a with me the whole time why is one
worker just like everything's locked up
why do they make one worker like the key
guy like it's only the manager it should
just be like on the front desk and like
they just go get it or like like it
should just be like everyone they should
just unlock it and have a security guard
at the door that was my story I got
[ __ ] annihilated by the pepperoni
monster right in my mouth dude sounds
like a either great time or bad time you
want to know what I was thinking cuz I
can see the moon right now and I could
see it the other day and it's it's
bright tonight it's super bright tonight
yeah but you want to know my thought oh
hi Bunny look at
him my thought I saw the moon the other
day and I was like I totally get why
wolves howl at that thing when it's full
yeah I get it I don't know you almost
felt it you like almost did it you're
just so Alpha that it probably was like
you almost like were like I'm the alpha
omega um look at the Moon tell me I
can't believe that like I can't believe
there's some men on this Earth that will
so seriously call themselves an alpha
and I'm an alpha male I am that's the
craziest thing ever they're all betas
what is that it's the secondary to Alpha
it's just crazy thingy toilet R did baby
grank Riz up liby D mad or what oh my
God wait funny story I saw this on my
Tik Tok the other day no
what I'm going to [ __ ] this teacher
was using Kon at Duke Dennis and Phantom
tax to teach subra saw that and it makes
me want to throw up that's insane she
like if Duke Dennis has this many like
slices of what are these things and who
is it it's like the twitch streamers and
it's like a it's like a all like a big
joke you would you would I like can't
even talk about it without feeling like
an absolute idiot have you seen the
video it was like super viral of like
the the two kids like a stre in like a
school fight and they're hitting each
other and then one of them like Miss
swings and like hits the teacher and
another kid punches him in the face he
goes I don't [ __ ] with that you
accidentally hit the teacher and he like
knocked knocked the kid out my favorite
video ever I've never seen this it's
like a sweet lady teacher and the two
kids are fighting she trying no she's
trying to like intervene the fight she
comes over and starts trying to go like
this and then he punches the teacher in
the face by accident like I think it was
by accident so then a third party kid
came in and knocked the part of the
fight he was like and then he goes what
do he say he goes he hit you in the
[ __ ] face I don't [ __ ] with that to
the teacher and the teacher goes I know
it's horrible but like she even after
getting punched in the face she was
trying to like dis deescalate the
situation that's why I couldn't be a
teacher if a kid hit me I'd like
probably go to jail I'd probably hit him
back no I don't know it is crazy to me
that kids in high school are fighting I
don't even think I hit puberty till
junior year let alone fist fighting
another one of my classmates I don't
know why I'm saying I can't believe this
I've almost fought two people I remember
that I remember I almost fought some
[ __ ] idiot who kicked a coffee at me
I think he we might have told this story
before definitely have but I almost
[ __ ] punched that kid in the face I
was so and he was one of the teachers
kids I know what a [ __ ] nerd that
loser and then there was another time I
did get in a fight during hockey
practice I punched my own teammate full
fist fight during hockey oh yeah he's an
idiot I didn't know how to tie his
skates it's like dude you are a Boy
Scout literally that was that was
probably that was that was Matt like
that was the only thing that I've ever
that was kind of that was kind of like a
bully it was a little bit of a bully
move but that was the only thing but he
was a [ __ ] [ __ ] and he deserved
it and he thought he was a [ __ ] there
was some kid on our hockey team that was
lowkey an [ __ ] when we were kids he
was a horrible kid and he was just like
not good at playing the sport at all so
it was like really easy to make fun of
him cuz he was just like a really no I'm
being honest he was just like a really
negative kid always had something to say
to someone he thought he was like better
he was like the kid that was like G on
the coach's shoulder to let him in the
game and [ __ ] and it's like dude little
baby you're like whatever you're just a
big [ __ ] and um yeah he was just like
making fun of all the kid he couldn't
tie a skates and Matt was like no he was
making fun of all the kids like he was
making fun of like two other kids and I
don't [ __ ] with that you know what I
mean like I don't [ __ ] with like the
other kids getting made fun of that are
like also not the best at hockey but
like way better than him and at least
they're nice people yeah I wasn't good
at hockey but I never bragged or claimed
correct same I was like kid was the
worst ever and was like questioning why
he thought he was going to the [ __ ]
NHL I was like all right buddy you got
far terrible yeah literally he was also
a Boy Scout and he um he was really
struggling to tie his skates and his dad
came into the locker room to tie his
skates and he like was getting ready but
like he just came from Boy Scouts too so
he had his whole little boy scouts get
up on and get up is so funny well he did
he was like a whole get up and I was
like where did you just come from and
he's like oh boy scouts I was like
you're making I go what did you what did
you learn today like what what was the
couple things you learned like what are
the patches for and he's like oh and
he's like oh like you know fire making
like whatever all of them are you know
they're all something I go what about
that one the the the not tiing one you
can't tie your skates but you can tie
not and then his dad was like is there a
[ __ ] problem with him being a Boy
Scout I go no I just assumed if he can
tie a [ __ ] fisherman knot he can tie
a skate that is crazy playing hockey not
tying your own hockey [ __ ] you kid come
on on all right what to talk about if
you had any superpower but it only
activated when you sneezed what would
you want it to be I just want to admit
flame I'm just like I just burn up
everyone around me full circle circular
just a full big flame around me that'd
be kind of hard if but if you were
sneezing you'd have to like run away
from people in public or you go to jail
if you assaulted them no I'd want to
sneeze $10,000 into my hand that's a
great idea good superpower I'd be
sniffing pepper every night no i' just
be waving a [ __ ] feather on my nose
that's so like the
feather traction control
disabled it's okay buddy you can shut
that off if I'm sneezing and it's like
my superpower I would say it just brings
me to whatever like location is in my
mind like whatever like I'm thinking of
like how would you get home no like if
I'm thinking like oh I really want to be
home right now and I sneeze I'm there
yeah but what if you were accidentally
watching like National Geographic and
you're and it's like the Arctic and like
penguin God oh wow I really wonder what
it's like to be chew I definitely if if
I had the superpower I'd find a way that
like I'd carry in my pocket like a
sneeze activator and it would be like
something that I could just like wave or
like eat that would like force me to
sneeze if I could time travel I wouldn't
even do it why cuz I feel like if you
are time traveling the butterfly effect
is too real no it can't be good for your
body like to go from like oh you're so
worried about what you put in your body
Mr [ __ ] Pepsi Drinker 10 a day Red
Baron pizza is the only thing you eat
Hershey bar oh get me a Hershey bar if
you're going to run in the store eating
a Hershey bar right now no but what I'm
saying is like I feel like no not time
travel but
teleportation I feel like that just
can't be good for you like if all your
body ends up somewhere else like it's
like oh the like cuz I think of like
going in a plane like when you go in a
plane it's like the altitude control can
we believe we figured that out no I
can't are we [ __ ] serious sometimes I
think cuz me and my CR fly all the time
cuz we live in two different places and
I'm on the plane and I'm like shout the
[ __ ] out whoever came up with I can't
believe I don't have to walk to
California I can't [ __ ] believe it
and why are the [ __ ] who
invented the plane not the first thing
you see going into the airport I agree I
need a statue of those twins I think the
right Brothers the right Brothers I need
them statue in every airport every
single time I'm headed to terminal ABC
car I think their car regardless yeah
they need much recognition you're a
[ __ ] idiot are you talking crazy
because they definitely came up with
boats first and that's why everything
was like land or sea and then someone
was like one if by land two if by Sea
that was hard what history lesson PA R
Paul R I don't [ __ ] with Paul R at all
guys can we tell you this is the
funniest thing ever and can we say this
on the internet you think or no yeah I
think at this point we it is so funny
there was one video and I don't know if
you guys were able to figure out when it
is cuz I feel like we talked talked
about part of it but then we cut some of
it out but we literally cut out Chris
calling Paul River [ __ ] cuz we were
afraid that we were going to like get
fully canceled off the internet you want
know what I'm thinking in my head right
now that's not real what I'm thinking of
like a squirrel or a chipmunk or like a
bunny rabbit getting in a fight and
using a blueberry as like a big weapon
like do you think like okay hold on how
the [ __ ] did you just get there I don't
know I was just sitting here and I was
thinking like I was thinking of
something to say cuz we're obviously
filming a car video and I was like oh if
I was a little creature I would use a
blueberry as like a paintball and just
right up my friend get them gotcha and
then it's like a bunny with a bunch of
blue
spots you need to write a children's
book quick yeah I agree seriously cuz
they're lacking your level of creativity
in that here's the Box Chris is here I'm
always if they just pit you the concept
for like Disney
movies like and just told you what the
movies are going to be you could come up
with some crazy addition oh I completely
agree like zootopia I feel like what
would you what would you add to the
movie zootopia that's not already in it
um a bird detective that's like flying
over all of zootopia and then he can
like like just SC like like and it's one
for each region so there's like an eagle
in the Rocky region he can like radio
like I see someone coming in the T in
the in the rainforest you got that and
it's a twocan he's like a suit and he
has a walkie
do and he's like and he's like
absolutely I got it and like they can
communicate with each other and then
they can find Mr Lamie the victim that
way I rewat that movie is so good dude I
remember when we were watching that
movie for the first time the actual
[ __ ] horror movie Insidious level
jump scare that the OT can we watch
hereditary tonight or some type if you
could only eat with foods that rhyme
with your name what could you eat
Matthew oh my gosh hold on I can't say
what I
thought I could be like a dog and eats
sticks just carry sticks home I don't
like this at all if you could have any
sound effect accompany your every move
what would it be bow I you all knew that
yeah like go like this or like like you
like Cross Your Arms yeah you know like
the squishy sound when you walked Matt I
was going to say like when Squidward
squid walk cuz I want to be like a m
would be like AED octopus tentacles
crying off glass I was walking near I
was walking did you think it was me nope
what I was walking near a goose and I
heard and I was like that reminds me oh
Nick did you see that video I sent you
and Chris today I love yes yes or did
just or did just Chris see it hold on I
love pool flippers oh [ __ ] did I did you
see this what are you showing me did you
see sorry I'm like blocking out you
check this Tik Tok this morning okay yes
this [ __ ] cuz Nathan and Chris miss
it freaked me out look oh on the car
hold on hold on this freaks me
out that's disgusting I can't even look
at that that's like gross he's so cute
that's disgusting I got to save it that
is disgusting and then he moves over
like a couple there's a tree right next
to my window I think we're going to
start talking about like an imaginary
tree I don't know why I instantly you
stop talking no cuz when he said that I
instantly thought of a bean stock who
last when you said there's tree next
okay I don't care there's a tree next to
my window and sometimes very late at
night raccoons they're nocturnal they
climb up and they're on the branch and I
got like a little
Gap in my window of like my blinds and I
look through raccoons they see them
they're talking raccoons really climb
trees they talk to me my biggest fear is
opening the trash and they being AAC
that's one but I open the blind I open
the blind I open this blind and I'm not
joking three raccoons in the tree and I
was just like looking at them and I was
like this is absolutely when you said
that it's the
triplets one of them like hit the other
one they started scrapping and I swear
to God at some like I like kind of like
went on to like the window like this
yeah and I like hit my like arm on the
window still cuz I was like trying to
like look at the raccoons more and I
like hit the window I like hit the
window by accident and all three of
their heads turned right at me and
looked at me and I was just like cuz
they heard the noise I so scared and I
was so scared and then one of them
literally stood up on its back two feet
like you know how they do on a tree yes
no it didn't yes it did I swear to God
and then it waved at me you're [ __ ]
lying I swear to God you're lying you
just said you're not good at lying no
yeah all of that is fake that was good
man thank you no I always tell people I
it's so funny it's so funny how Nick
thinks I'm going to hit him every time
now cuz I I might one day I always tell
can't lie but I can perform if I believe
my full lie it's more of an act I can
expand on the truth but I can't lie do
you guys remember two years ago in our
fandom when like people genuinely
shipped you and Mt like dating together
and like don't ever don't ever say that
us video ideas give us things to talk
about let us know what you guys want
also I was going to say the other day I
just wanted to um have a moment of
gratitude with our amazing fans here and
just say that me man Chris are so
grateful for you guys sticking it out
with us for the past two and a half
years we had I was thinking of this
today because or one of our fans that
has been supporting me Matt and Chris
for like over three years now and was
probably one of the first hundred people
to subscribe to us her name is Ellie she
has been subscribed to her YouTube
channel and engaged with what mimat and
Chris have done the actual entire time
that we've been posting on YouTube and
it made me think of how many people
there are that have devoted so much of
their life to being a fan of us and will
grow up with stories of growing up with
us being their favorite YouTubers and
it's the most mind-blowing thing ever so
I just wanted to say thank you to you
guys as well as kind of apologize to
some level of M Matt and Chris have been
posting about two times a week for
literally those three years in a row so
sometimes we'll talk about things like
before the three of us like agree on it
or like work out something enough like
creatively so sometimes we'll like tell
you guys we're going to do something and
then we're not actually going to do it
or like we'll run ideas past you guys
and we like it could be in like super
early stages but with filming so much of
our Lives sometimes we bring stuff up a
little to preemptively of them happening
I remember when we were going to start
our podcast and we were talking about it
for like legit a year before it happened
so just thanks for working through
everything we've ever done with us thank
you guys so much for watching this
week's video we'll see you guys when we
see you guys peace and love
[Music]