well well well today I'm wearing my
Hooter shirt cuz I'm a big fan of
breasts I got good chicken too though
and I'm a big fan of tits and
chicken God you're insane
Nick breast is probably my least
favorite term for boobies n boobies is
worse boobies is worse what's your
favorite I don't like this conversation
I feel like we should make oh my God
great idea we should make a our Channel
I was about to say we should make like a
YouTube video that's like rated art and
it's like actual [ __ ] just like fully
like like steros at night or something
like you know what I mean that would be
wild I think everyone just needs to grow
up I feel like we like we made our
content not family friendly cuz we swear
a ton but then but it's not like it's
not too explicit to point where we have
to like cuz even like an interview and
stuff I'll never address talking about
anything slightly sexual cuz I'm just
like terrified let's do it let's get
horny okay I said say or ask anything on
our group account someone said who would
win in a
threesome and I can't I don't think
there'd be a winner I think we'd all
equally lose I agree what I agree is
that a candy where did you a candy oh I
really want that ow man stop pulling it
like really can I have it like I just
he's so like Nick it's on my head guys
stop yanking it can I have it no [ __ ]
you I really want it what is your guys
ideal um
like driveway look like some people got
brick I can't drive and I don't care
what it looks like no like like your
Nick for your home aesthetic you would
care so much as long as there's a good
brushel of li like livelihood plant
nearby I got see and he doesn't care
care only there's a brushel of
livelihood plant nearby I just want some
bushel to like have like bunni of course
you want some bushel your
mother no but I think give me this give
me this give me this I really want it
remember that friend remember whose
friend who's whose
friends had a driveway and it was like
it was near the cape and it was all
seashells I love that I'm with nature
I'm bringing in some fresh air M I think
a lot of people that's what people need
fresh air oh you need some fresh
yeah Nick went to old
water he s like a
back do that again do that again do that
again do that again do that again me
Chris and Nathan the other day were
talking about just like our top 10
things in life in life like just life
pumpkins and one of no no and one of
mine was fresh air I don't like cats I
was going to say why you say cats FR
fresh air yeah it's in my top 10 fresh
air is so good what do y'all plan to do
when you turn 21 I'm going to get
copious amounts of alcohol and drink my
life
away this is crazy and I'm going to
violently attack people next to me I
don't know they probably lose all my
money gambling no I was thinking about
it the other day I was like we should do
a
video where we just party insanely hard
for our
20 myself no not for for our actual 21st
I want to do something enjoyable with
you guys but for like a video and like a
joke I think we should 100% go like
Gamble and like go to a party my
everyday life outside of my everyday
life with what I with what I enjoy is
like the opposite of like what people do
when they're when they turn 21 you know
what I mean like I'd be happy turning 21
and going like out to a pizza party in
an arcade but that's also like sounds
good that's also like a 10-year-old's
birthday yeah but I'd love that was like
our 10th birthday I think that was our
10th birthday yeah Pizza arade Gummy
Bears or gummy worms someone said they
both have their pros and cons to me the
gummy bears are good cuz it's like fun
to like decapitate them I was going to
say I kind of like gummy bears cuz I
like to eat oh my God I like to rip out
their soul eat the heads off of the
gummy bears and then like switch them
and then make them to you're a kid you
like to play with your food but then
gummy worms gummy worms is like the
perfect gummy worms shut up oh [ __ ]
gummy worms are like the best thing ever
to like casually get a two-time nibble
in because they're like split in half
two different colors so you get like
that one half bite two time nibble is
crazy you get a two time nibble and it's
gone you just bite it in half and then
bite you want to know what I was
thinking of the other day what I was
like a g shut up Nick a gummy worm I'm
going to rip your [ __ ] the actual
size of a worm mhm now let's see the
gummy bear that's what I want to see I
want to see what if there's just mini
bears like that and they live in like a
burrow of like a tree like they like I
want to see I want to see a [ __ ] real
siiz gummy bear that's what I want okay
that's what I want to see soon that is
something I really would like to invest
in in our content by the way a mini bear
no is making ridiculous overly sized
things like I want to fill a pool with
with I want to fill a pool with soda I
want to [ __ ] I want to [ __ ] eat
the world's biggest dut I want to make a
a big doughnut the size of a Randy donut
that is outside of that building I want
that to be real you want to be wasteful
nope we can all eat it afterward I love
after what you bathe in it no Nick oh
yeah let's get a bunch of gummy bears
for Chris to stick
his naked body in and then we'll eat
them what is he talking about naked body
you said fill a bathtub with Gummy Bears
cool we're not doing that actually you
have you heard about osmosis yes osmosis
would happen wait we should study
osmosis we should get a big we should
get a where am
I [ __ ] am I no cuz you I feel like I
went into a portal tonight see how big
it
gets you want to know what pissed me off
the other day and I wrote it down yeah
tell go for it I hate when I see
[ __ ] doing food reviews or like
or like um I love that no no listen
listen you're jumping the gun clearly
I'm not done I love food reviews you're
not this girl did a food revieww and she
was like eating like a it was like a
donut or some sort of breakfast snack
like a um something stupid God forbid
you let me my pillow croissant or
something and she took a bite and she's
like oh my God guys this is so good and
she's like eating it still and she's
like crumbs all over her face and I just
saying don't tell me a thing about it if
it's sitting on your mouth like that you
know what I mean like if I can still see
it on your lips eat it first and then
you can review your snack cuz she's like
she's like oh this is so good and she's
like covered in I'm
like even if it's the most positive
review ever it's like o like I don't
want to see that that's repulsive yeah
it's like put everything in your mouth
eat the [ __ ] whole breakfast thing
and like oh yeah wow this was really
good I like the
crunch I can't even hear you over the C
she like oh God this is really and she's
like reviewing it and it's like still on
her mouth and I I took a video of myself
and I was just like E I said I said
don't don't even
I don't even remember what I said I was
like don't even tell me yeah don't even
tell me about what you're eating if it's
if I can still see it on your face they
also like enjoy it cuz there's like one
crumb that like I have to literally go
like this to hear what they have to say
cuz he's like eating a sandwich and it's
dripping or like barbecue sauce all
here I can't do it I have issues with
like food cleanliness it's so like I
don't mind to get dirty I don't I don't
mind no I don't mind to get four [ __ ]
ribs and a p pork sandwich and be messy
I don't mind but I'm not going to start
talking to you for real if I'm filthy
yeah that's a moment I'm going to wipe
it off I'm going to make sure you ain't
seen me with that P pork sandwich from
Hawaii you want know my thought I'd rub
that thing all over me naked Nick stop
you're freaking everyone out I wish I
didn't forget no one is freaked out I I
just want to rip these handles off the
car they're driving me insane you want
to know what's crazy I wish that was I
wish there was a thing I wish there was
a thing where it's like we could film a
car video right but like it's filmed
through like the lenses of my eyes so
like the [ __ ] so like you could see like
a car video from my perspective just get
the sunglasses that record and then edit
your view I love it I love it I love it
I love different and you be like what I
see it's just so different it's fun the
whole car Nick stop Nick the car is
shaking yeah it is
do you like tater tots yes love tater
tot I love tater tots and I love the
name of them remember those cheesy tots
we got that one time Nick if you were a
plant what would you be I'd be a venus
fly trap of course you would I'd be what
the [ __ ] that supposed to be what's
considered just like extra like o get
the bug off oh you gross ew buggy what's
yeah it's the same way raccoons you only
see them at night if you're like out
really raccoons like a raccoon I could
go a raccoon why are you guys saying it
like that raccoon a raccoon raccoon a
raccoon what would you how would you
want me to say it a raccoon a raccoon
how many raccoons do you think there are
raccoon how many do you think there are
like I don't know where I woke up to
them banging on my window once I told
remember I told you you know racco in
that of them three of them in the tree
someone and I opened my window BL and it
was just like three of them this I was
like what what was he in like power St
yes cuz you know how they do the thing
with their hands they do this dude he
was like this I love raccoons the Nick
did you see the position he was saying
the racco I believe it I believe it I
was there there someone said right now
Matt go find the raccoons where would
you
look right now I'd look in a garbage can
I don't know you have 3 hours to find a
raccoon I'm shooting you in the back of
a head oh my God where would you go I
don't know I wish that I could have the
attention of everyone in the world all
at one time and just tell them what I
think what did you say okay dude I wish
that I could have the attention of
everyone in the world all at one moment
and then just tell them what I think
you'd be such a waste of a person to
speak at something like that oh my God I
cannot believe you I'm being honest oh I
don't have earrings in how upsetting if
the whole world was paying attention to
yeah but if the whole world was paying
attention to one person and they had
something to say you were probably the
last person I would pick to speak do you
want know what I do what you probably
dance you're right or go go watch RuPaul
I would not say go watch rup Paul yeah
you would no I would not because I don't
want I'm I I like I couldn't tell
everybody to go watch it everyone in the
world no it's like if if I'm going to
tell everyone in the world to go do
something it's going to be one of two
things go watch our YouTube channel or
Veno me a [ __ ] dollar cuz then I'd be
a billionaire I'd probably just do like
a jig I go like
this we should get a white panel van
instead of this what does Matt choose to
be quiet or does Matt just not have
anything ridiculous to say I think
that's a good thing you talk a lot when
we're not filming I think you got camera
yeah cuz you talk a lot when we are
notice how that works I talk a lot all
the time yeah and I talk a lot when I
feel like it what unconventional animal
do you wish you could have as a pet I
want like a 100 hamsters and I want to
lay down
I want to listen yours is very
obtainable like on a weird listen I want
to be able to like teach them and train
them that the blow of a whistle like and
and a clap like a and then I'm going to
lay flat on the ground and 100 hamsters
are going to run at me and pick my body
up and then they're going to quickly why
I have nothing to say
and 100 hamsters are just going to drag
me into a
room like I want to I want to be
scheduled to go somewhere how am I
supposed to say things and I'm going to
have it's it's it's either this guy
yelling and making noises or my other
brother telling me want to geted up
by by downstair like at a slant I want
just likeed to how many hamsters do you
think it would take to do that and not I
would pick you up a million a million I
don't know I say I was going to say
let's just say hypothetically you fell
on 100 hamsters I think they're all dead
I agree you think I'd kill my petite
body would kill a 100 hamsters I don't I
I think it wouldn't distribute the
weight properly what no I think you
would if you fell on like a bucket of
100 hamsters I think you're clearing 80
of them at least I don't I can't think
it's hard to think I don't know I think
how many do you think like realistically
would they need to pick me up and do
what I want probably like a safe bed is
like 500 you're
lying come on how stronger is a hamster
I don't know come on have you seen
GeForce what's that movie with them
they're running through like the pipes
and [ __ ] just search up how much can a
hamster lift can you guys stop talking
about this how much this is such a funny
thing to Google hamster lift it's like
hamster
lift why is the top star fit in its
cheeks that's crazy what what we don't
need to know that hamsters can carry
half their body weight in their cheeks
alone I don't care they're not going to
eat
me hold on hopefully up to 50% of their
body weight is what it keep saying so
let's just say how much hamster does a
hamster weigh 2 G at Birth I need to
know a full adult masculine
man pounds what how much can a strong
hamster how much does a strong hamster
weigh okay 0.2 lbs is how much a hamster
weighs so if you think about it that's
what [ __ ] a pound is three of them no
it's not it's 10 of
them no it's like three and a half four
of them it's like three and a half four
hamsters could pick up a pound you need
like 3K
yeah let's not take guesses let's not
take guesses let's not take guesses
3,000 hamsters uh-uh girl let's say Nick
you need a lot well you guys don't know
how much I weigh yeah we do ask me
you're like 180 ask me how much do you
weigh you never ask a girl
okay so it's 180 * 4 i' only need
720 3K is unbelievable a th000 for who
do you think I am I feel like Nick you
have to think about 1,000 for Comfort
yes okay so I need a horde of a thousand
hamsters there we go see I'm not that
big God you're a sicko dude what was the
question someone goes are you guys still
in college no Nick if you met Abraham
Lincoln in person what would you say to
him here we go I think my heart would
flutter I would know I wouldn't know
what to say hi Mr Lincoln I'm a big fan
of the penny um the penny I loved you on
the $5 bill is he on that yes is he yes
I'm a big fan of your work on the $5
bill on the penny do you want to go to
the
movies have you ever tried melatonin
gummies someone said I oh my God I had
the craziest dream ever on a melatonin
gummy I had numerous crazy melatonin
gummies give you funky dreams I don't
even think I can share mine on the
internet I can't either cuz the people
that were in it but like weird [ __ ]
dream no we're getting down of business
Nick
no you're just weird like you're so
[ __ ] weird actually I had a dream
where I was cursing out one of our
teachers did I tell which one um no
[ __ ] hate him I
know no she was the nicest lady ever
yeah I was cursing her out in my dream
the other night why I was um oh sorry
you're playing cat H it's just muted we
were going um what's it called I love
that KES has a dollar sign in her name I
just saw that she's the hardest person
alive um I died in my dream the other
day yeah Nathan I talked to Nathan about
it man on a bike man on a bike hi it
means rebirth does it yeah it means
Rebirth of a new chapter it was actually
really scary I died in my dream the
other night and there was like a song
playing but like it you woke up and the
song was playing yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I woke up I woke up and it was
still playing but I have the CH crazy
part it wasn't a song that I've ever
heard before and it was just like the
what was it playing out of I don't know
what I have no idea who's in your head I
have no idea oh so you're crazy
probably thoughts on Nick's new haircut
no you don't get to your thoughts I look
great and I don't care what you say I
love when people ask like can I can I
say something can I sh my opinion Can I
Say No shh who the [ __ ] cares
you oh my God I don't think anyone's
opinion has ever swayed how I move about
a scenario unless they say it with like
some good evidence you love evidence
evidence not evidence like if someone's
like working out for me and they're like
oh you should do this this and like
they're coming from good intention but
if someone's like oh I don't like your
shirt it's like [ __ ] I don't like you
okay where's Matt with the cup boring
corny old do you like pineapple I love
pineapple I would take pineapple and
just I'd squeeze the juices out and
drink them all I love pineapple weird
kid I wish I could just cut up a
pineapple and get like the pieces and
stick every single one individually with
a toothpick and get Matt and a cute
little outfit and a tray and be like
here your
always comes over to me imagine M like
this he's like a cute little outfit and
he's got like a little bow tie on the
top and he has a tray of pineapple and
they're all cut they diced they're diced
and they have topick in them he goes
would you like some pineapple that'd be
awesome and he hands me I wouldn't say
it like that how would you say it would
you like some pineapple no I feel like
Nick would be such like in another life
you're like the hot dog guy I I think
I'd love to do that for a day yeah I'd
like nothing more no I want to work at
like a stadium Shack oh you want like a
concession stand yeah it's like a
baseball game's on and like B the
baseball game my favorite thing ever is
like being at the concession stand and
you're in a hurry to get back to the
game and you hear like a ding and you're
like oh and everyone's like looking
they're like like someone it's at home
run while you're at the stand he loves
that I love just good old American
baseball I love baseball I love baseball
I love baseball I love B what's your
favorite way to celebrate something
probably probably a little twerk I was
going to say probably a little Bust A
Move Little twk remember when I killed
someone in fortnite and I twerked yes
how can I forget that was insane what's
your least favorite word least favorite
word I don't care what word it is but I
hate people who just shouldn't speak
speak it could be
any any word said by the wrong person I
agree I agree that was that was good um
if we were beverage like alcohol
consumers what would be your go-to my
goto drink of choice would be a Pina
colato you know that for sure absolutely
I I don't know cuz I don't know what
they taste like but like off of like
like just thought and like how I i' just
be like one of those annoying beer
drinkers you would yeah you would be
like Oher li no I'd love a good fruity
drink we should bring back the not
what's the biggest thing you think you
can swallow in one
go like dude I have
unbelievable no idea who asks that
what's the biggest thing you could
swallow probably a sword honestly let's
see I see sword swallowers I'm like what
I could do that
EAS guys sword swallowing takes no
Talent it just takes an oh my God I was
going to say a big throat I was going to
say an open
throat like insane that's terrible can
we go home please if I was like caught
off guard and someone like pushed me in
the back or something I could easily get
like a Snickers bar down there but it
just needs to be like a blind side your
throat
easy that's I'm freak D if I was like
about to eat a like if I was about to
bite s question and I was like and then
someone p pushed my back and I went oh I
could easily get like absolutely it just
I just have to be caught off guard I
can't know what's coming can you guys
handle being a president for a month I'd
love to be the first lady when Abraham
Lincoln was around you're insane
opinions on Oompa loomas I need a
couple yeah i' I'd like them I got
chocolate they like chocolate
[Music]
right
oh someone said do spiders have knees
does your mother have
[Music]
knees there's something wrong with me
this up I need to see a doctor WRA this
up please wrap this up right I have to
have something the smell of bug spray
just like clean fresh scent can you put
that [ __ ] bug it's in the
mottle okay what else tell me for is it
25% off too that's not a real question
my favorite thing about Nick is how
charismatic he is charming I have RZ yes
yeah okay dude it was a good one I love
you love you love you peace tell your
mom I'll be there in 10: all right dude
you're insane tell me more about that I
have to go potty I loved filming tonight
tonight was fun I've been having a p a
great past few days everybody just
thought I'd let that out if you're one
of us come roll with us
hey
[Music]
yeah