And we're live. Yeah. All right. All
right, guys. Um, welcome back. Holy
absolutely macaroni. We have not filmed
a car video. We have not filmed a car
video together in three weeks, I think.
In about over 3 weeks. And this is our
first car video filming
since we were apart for 5 days when you
guys went to Summer Smash. Correct. So,
this is going to be a lethal car video.
Guys, I just want to say before we even
get into the meat and potatoes of this
video, but doesn't he always make fun of
me for saying meat and potatoes? Meat
and potatoes. But anyway, potatoes.
We're starting to do more ventures. Like
me and Chris went to Summer Smash this
and that. So, we're going to start
trying to like make more content and do
stuff like that. Just Friday's the day.
You'll see something. Just don't worry
about it. I don't know how to word it.
Yeah, but we we're trying to like do
more adventures and stuff and obviously
that means less time together
and more time living life, which is good
and more good for stories. Speaking of g
gathering stories while we're not
together, that is what today's car video
is probably going to be honestly all
about. We're going to share a bunch of
stuff that happened while we were
separated. So, let's get right into
[ __ ] into it, guys. Also, I have my
sunglasses on and I felt like I really
needed to share, especially to Nick. My
biggest fear ever like do you know
biggest your biggest fear ever? You say
biggest. Okay. I know like NY's birds
whatever. Okay cool. Like we've had so
much conversation about biggest fears
and like I've brought up like things
here and there like oh having a
girlfriend like haha so funny. But I
genuinely found my new biggest fear. My
house just exploded. And why do you
think like while I'm inside? Cuz I think
like there are so many times where like
if like the pipes are wrong in the house
or like the furnace is on or like the
furnace. We don't have a furnace. We
don't live in a furnace. Almost every
house has a furnace. A furnace? Yes. You
have to move a boat like they throw coal
in like the Titanic. No. No. If you have
central AC central AC and central air,
you probably have a furnace. That's what
makes the heat. How common are furnaces
in modern day? Um huge. Even like your
oven leaking like like gas. Like my
biggest fear is just like my house
exploding. Yeah, I can. I don't think
your house is going to [ __ ] explode.
Like imagine like just the roof like
pops off and then like and then it's
like boom, your walls go off. I wish my
house would explode. Like a cartoon
explosion. Like the roof just flies off
and lands back on and then it's just
like all 2x4s and they all just like
fall
like recreate. No, but that's actually
my biggest fear is just like I saw a
video. He's saying it like you. I'm
saying biggest. Biggest. Uh I saw this
video. This kid was walking home with
his friend and they're like dribbling a
basketball on the sidewalk. Dribbling.
You're You're having a speech moment.
No, I'm not. Yeah, you are. No, I'm not.
They're dribbling a basketball by a
house and as they walk by like the
[ __ ] front door flies. Dribble the
basketball by the house. It's like and
the house just like the house just blows
up and you see the kids like run away in
fear. That's terrible. So, it just made
me think like it inspired me to like
share my biggest fear. I can keep going.
I have more. I can keep going with
something. Matt, Nick, do you want to
tell Matt about your f your take the
other day? Your hot take when me and you
were out with Sam driving around. Can't
remember it. I have so many great hot
takes. We were me and Sam and Nick were
driving around and shopping. So, me and
Sam were just having a lot of
conversation back and forth. We're
driving around for a little bit. Nick's
in the back seat quiet for probably like
20 minutes. Shocker. And then we drive
by a fancy restaurant and there was an
ambulance outside of it. Okay, I
remember my take. I think there was an
ambulance outside of the fancy
restaurant and there was a bunch of like
people inside and people walking in and
out with like their suits and ties on.
Like it was like a nice fancy
restaurant. Now that I'm remembering
what you're going to say, I'm already
disagreeing with my with my previous and
Nick. This is a quote that I wrote down.
I can't believe that you can have a
heart attack in fancy clothes. And he
basically think of like having a heart
attack. It's like I think if you are
able to get into a nice outfit and like
do your hair and makeup and like get
like all dressed up, it has to be harder
to have a heart attack. And that was if
you can get yourself and bring yourself
and put yourself together really really
nice and you can look super good. I feel
like your heart attack like levels are
lower. You know what I mean? like if
you're lazy. And this started a whole
thing. Like we were talking about it for
like an half hour. Then we started
driving by people and Nick was like,
"Oh, he's safe. Like look at his hat."
And there was like a guy who like looked
messy and he's like he definitely could
probably This is insane. No, like this
is literally what Nick was saying, but I
was thinking to myself, it's like I feel
like it has to be relatively hard to
have like a heart attack in like a gown
or like a suit. Okay. You know what I
mean? No, Nick was just saying like
looking good and having a fancy suit on
like lowers your probability for all
injury like in general is what Nick was
saying. I think so. I believe that.
Okay. Sure. Do you believe that or
disagree? I disagree. I feel like it it
takes so much out of me to say like,
"Huh?" when someone's talking. Yeah. No,
it doesn't. No, it doesn't. That's like
you're a classic.
The reason I probably wrote this down
and the reason I probably thought this
is because you are always like, "You
heard what I said." But it's like if I
say huh and you say I heard you heard
what I said. You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] Cuz
I'm saying huh cuz I have no [ __ ]
clue what you're saying to me. I will
say over and over, huh? Huh? What are
you saying? Because I want to know what
you're saying, but I just have no
[ __ ] idea. You just don't listen.
You're not a good listener. Oh my god.
No. You talk. I say, "Huh?" Cuz you
mumble and talk
and I go, "Hum." And you're like, "What?
What the [ __ ] Ever. Chris did this to
me in the house. No, cuz you double huh.
Like I double h if I didn't, Nick. You
double hump. No, I didn't. He was
talking to me. I said, "I'm not
listening to you." That was a blatant
I'm not listening. I'm telling you a
story and I'm like waiting for him to
respond and he goes, "Yeah, everything
you just said, I didn't listen to." And
then I walk away. Obviously, I'm not
going to continue to talk to someone who
just said that to me. I was being
honest. Did he want me to pretend I
heard it? He goes, "No, what'd you say?
Like resay it?" And I'm like, "No, I
just spoke for [ __ ] 3 minutes. It was
full honesty. No, it wasn't. No. Well, I
was driving earlier to pick you up over
there and Nick was in the passenger seat
and I said something to Nick. No,
silence was my correct. You don't even
know what I said. So, I was just like,
"Okay, whatever. I'll try again later."
I don't know if we show shared this on
the internet already yet, but me and
Matt are leaving Chicago and we're in
the elevator of the hotel going down to
the lobby and our flight's not for 6
hours and he's asking me in the
elevator. See, Matt, say that. I just
said that. Did he? You're not a good
listener. And Matt goes, "Do you think I
should take my belt off at TSA? Am I in
Am I at TSA?" I'm like, "No, I'm in the
elevator of the [ __ ] hotel." Well, I
I was trying to be productive in like 6
hours in advance. He's asking me if he
should remove his belt at TSA, which I
understand. Wow. We Well, yeah. I just I
feel like there's listen to the guy. We
had a full day ahead of us. TSA people
will not hesitate to tell you what the
[ __ ] you need to do. We went out to eat.
We went to the Lyrical Lemonade
headquarters. We saw some friends. We
played basketball. Like, there was a
full day that conspired between You're a
[ __ ] idiot. How about this little How
about this little interaction I had with
Chris the other day? If we're going to
talk about people being stupid where
we're driving by a semi-truck and he
looks, gasps, you were in the car,
looks, gasps, points at it, and I wrote
down and I quote, he goes, "This looks
just like it's from the movie Cars." And
he's going like this. He's like pointing
at the car and he goes, "This looks just
like it's from the movie Cars." It was
probably And then he goes he he goes,
"Look, it's Mac and it's a [ __ ]
18-wheeler truck." I said, "Chris,
wait till you find out what the movie
Cars is based off of. Just you [ __ ]
wait." He literally points an 18-wheeler
with both his hands like this, like a
like an animal. Like
shock pointing. Look, it looks just like
it's from the movie Cars. It's like he's
seeing like the real actor of the
[ __ ] movie. It's a truck. It was an
18-wheeler truck.
Are you crazy? Of course it does. And so
does the car you're in and every other
car on the [ __ ] road. Are you
unfamiliar with life is a [ __ ]
highway. Here we are. Life is a highway.
We're here. Oh my god, Nick, you're too
funny. No, but speaking of also being on
the road, while Matt and Chris were
gone, I still was living my own life.
But being a 20-year-old, I cannot drive
a car, which is so embarrassing. And I
was getting in so many I was getting in
so many Ubers. I have at least four Uber
stories to share with you. No, me and
Matt were dying laughing when you texted
us that you and the Uber driver had the
identical outfit on. Oh my god. I I took
a video. I took a video cuz I was
shocked. We were both wearing a black
shirt and like funky like sunglasses and
I was like, "This is the funniest." No.
And blue shorts. You had head to toe.
No, I recorded the guy and record
myself. Insert insert clip right now.
[Music]
Oh my god, it was so funny. But me and
the Uber driver were matching. There was
another time I got in like an Uber like
six times just going about. I got in a
car and the guy asked me where to go. I
got in the car. He goes, "Which way do
you usually go?" I said, "Uber, sir, I
can't drive." I literally said, "Mr.
Uber, I cannot drive." Mr. Uber is
crazy. I was like, "I don't know which
way to go. Follow the GPS." And then,
no, no, hold on.
Was that a tiger? It's a car. I also I
also not of course there's not a tiger.
Like why would there be a tiger coming
to jump at us before give me a tissue
right now. Life is a high.
I'm going to ride it all night long.
Another thing is I was uh you guys were
gone for 5 days and I didn't go out
until the second day. So I was
completely alone with my thoughts in
silence for like 48 hours and like I had
no one to speak to. Why? I was
completely alone. I got into the Uber
and he goes, "Hello, how are you?" I
said, "Hi, how are you?" And then he was
like, we had like a one minute
conversation, I felt like a primal
animal speaking like I was like, the way
that I can communicate with this person,
like I had not communicated with anyone
like face to face, verbally in like 48
hours. So speaking to him and like using
our words to communicate literally made
me feel like an animal. Like it was like
back to the basics. I felt like I was
like You felt like a kid. I was like I
felt like it was my first words. The
fact that I spoke and he understood me
made me feel like literally primal. I
was like in You want to know what I've
discovered is that I'm the only triplet
that hasn't been away from you guys for
more than 24 hours. Yeah. I feel bad for
you. You need it. No, I've I've
literally never been away from either of
you for more than 24 hours. You've been
away from us for more than 24. You've
been away from us for more than 24. Mhm.
Yeah. I've yet to do that. Like I've
never slept in like an empty home. I
worry for you. It's important for you to
do that. It is. It is important. And
that's why we have this new era of life.
Why don't you guys go do something? No,
we will go on a date or something. Go Oh
my god. Take a couple trip to Morocco.
We're not going to do that. What is that
all about? No, like both of you could go
somewhere that I kind of like want to go
and I'll miss out a little and that
would make it even more of a good mental
adventure for me cuz you guys mental
adventure. Like you guys could send
photos with like coconuts and nice
necklaces. Do you even know where
Morocco is geographically? Yeah. Where?
Isn't it near
Panama? That's why I ask him. He might
be spot on. He might be, but I might.
Anyways, moving on. Also, another thing
I've noticed is I've never in my life
had like aux on the car with like no
judgment. Like, I've never been able to
like hit shuffle or play on my songs and
like have neither of you complain about
it or have either of you be in control.
Well, you also can't drive.
So, you're going to be judged because
you're playing for music for somebody
that's also in the vehicle. So, you've
never been or had a moment in a vehicle
alone. So, obviously there's room for
judgment because there's a crowd and
you're putting on an audio for everyone
to listen to. You could say that for me
and you could say that for Chris because
we're always playing something that
they're going to get three different
opinions from different categories cuz
you like pop music and Chris likes
hip-hop and I'm more on the indie side
most of the time. So, the fact that So
are you. So there's going to be
judgment. I feel like I'm with like
narrator smurf right now. Yeah,
literally. Okay. Thank you for literally
saying what I said. I got into the Uber
and I like I think you felt like
something telling you to do that. Like
there was a commending force to get.
Anyways, commending force. I I got into
the Uber and I asked him for a a a
charger and I plug my phone in and he
goes, "Oh yeah, yeah, Bluetooth, too."
And I was like like I was like frozen in
fear. I was like I've never done this
before. I I started playing like oldies
like good songs and he was quiet for 30
minutes and I we were on the highway and
whenever I'm in a long Uber I play color
by numbers. I'm not like looking around.
I'm just like I'm chilling. I'm on my I
have my head up in the clouds, you know?
You're really like you're role playing
like a six-year-old when you go out.
Color by numbers, old music. Yeah, I
guess like I was playing old music and I
was doing my color by numbers. We're a
half hour into the ride and neither me
or the Uber man has said a word. A word.
And all of a sudden over the music he
goes, "All good songs, my friend." Like
all like he went to compliment my ax and
he goes, "Oh." Like when he said all, I
thought he was like going, "Ah." So I
literally I dropped my phone and I like
shoot my head up. I thought that I was
going to [ __ ] eat the highway. Like I
thought when he said all good songs to
my friend, he went to compliment me that
my body was about to go [ __ ] flying
out of the window cuz he was shouting
when he like he was being nice, but it
was like he hadn't said a word yet. So
when he yelled, I literally was
preparing for my body to break through
glass and glide across the highway. I
was in a state of shock. I was in a
state of shock. I literally What did you
say? So what did you say? Oh, I
literally took a deep breath, I think,
and picked up my phone. I was like, "Oh,
thank you." But I was like I was
literally in [ __ ] shock cuz the way
he did it I think he was just so shocked
that I wasn't playing like rap music as
a teen boy that like all good songs all
good songs my friend and I was like oh
my god like I jumped when we were
leaving Chicago through the airport the
girl like at the TSA booth that like
scans my ID Uhhuh. like knew who we
were. She I think she like noticed it
once she saw me but like she saw Matt
was like hesitant about it but then when
she saw both of us she's like oh cuz
Matt went in line ahead of me remember
and Matt scans this thing and he walks
through and then I give her my ID and
she goes wait you're like Chris Sternolo
right? I go yeah she's oh my god I love
you guys and like hands me my passport
and like she didn't scan it through the
machine and yeah and then she was like
oh like I love you guys like nice to see
you and I was like am I good? She said
oh yeah yeah you're good. So, like I got
noticed by the lady, so I like didn't
like check in for the I didn't need my
pass. I could have I could have walked
right through. I think that's illegal.
And I think she could be fired from her.
No, like definitely like because she
noticed who I am. She just was like,
"Oh, yeah, you're good." And like let me
through the airport. I didn't need I
didn't need a like I didn't she didn't
even need my passport. Like she never
even grabbed me. Like I went to hand it
to her and she's like, "Wait, you're
Chris Hill." I go, "Yeah." She go,
"Okay, you're good." I think if I spent
48 hours at the airport, I'd have enough
car video content for a year. airport.
The amount of psychopaths are just dumb
people that are at the airport is
insane. I hate the summer. I just got to
say it. My nose has been peeling. I got
to put moisturizer on it. My [ __ ]
shoulders are burnt. It's hot. I'm
sweating. Nothing. Summer's not good. I
like the summer. I agree. I'm like
really like I'm burning. It's like
insanely hot. Look at that stupid
[ __ ] helmet. Can you grow up? Random
hot take. I have seen the Nutcracker
play like five times. No. When? In my
whole life. When you haven't seen Where
and when have you [ __ ] gone to see
the Nutcracker? Are you [ __ ] serious?
I have never gone to see Ben. Yes, I
have. Absolutely not. You've seen the
[ __ ] nutcracker in play. You have
never seen You're cracking my nuts right
now. No [ __ ] way. I'm not. We went
for a school field trip one year. One.
Mom took us one year. Yes. Absolutely. I
You can't even get to three. Call mom
right now. I went and watched the
[ __ ] Nutcracker play. Actually call
her. Actually call her. No, don't cuz
she's in a different time zone. Just
call her and see if she answers. I'll
call her, by the way. Hey, mom. Random.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Is
she calling?
Hi, Nick. Hi. Hi, Mom. Hi, honey. How
are you? It's me, Matt, and Chris. I
have to I have to go cuz we're filming a
video, but we have a question for you if
you can answer it for our viewers.
Absolutely.
How many times and did we ever go see
The Nutcracker in Boston? Like the
Christmas musical?
Never. You never brought us to see it.
No, I think there was a field trip. Yes,
that's Chris is claiming that he went
five times and me and Matt said no.
We've been He's dreaming. You saw Lily
in the purple plastic purse. I remember
that. That was a good one. You know, I
never took you to the Nutcracker.
All right. I didn't think you guys were
into it. Yeah.
Apparently, Chris is Yeah. I mean, it's
a ballet. You guys didn't strike me as
the ballet kind of kids. I didn't I'm
not I'm really don't think we are
either. All right. Thank you so much for
that information. I'll call you again
soon.
All right. I'm going to bed. Good night,
Mom. Love you. So you how do you feel,
you [ __ ] idiot? So how many times
have you seen the Nutcracker? I guess
I've only seen it once, but I feel like
I've seen it more than once. Like I feel
like I've I've heard about I don't even
think I've seen it once. I think I think
we went on a school field trip, but I
think Matt might not have gone. Yeah,
I've never seen it. I think that I've
been at least three times like with
friends or something. Like I I don't
know why I'm so compelled by this, but I
feel like I've been. But the whole point
of me bringing this up, Lily in the
plastic purse, that was a good one. I
remember I don't remember that. I
remember. But the whole point of me
bringing this up is I feel like I've
seen it like five times, but I could not
tell you a thing of what it's about cuz
you've never been once. I literally It's
a ballet. We were driving down the
street and I saw an ad and it was like
the Nutcracker and I was like, I've been
to that like two times and I have no
idea. Now it's two. Matt, do you have
any compelling stories that happened to
you while we were all separated?
Um, not really honestly. Nothing too.
I'm trying to Well, I feel like I could
if I think about it, but I don't know.
Isn't buying a wallet such an
interesting thing to do? It's like,
where was your money before? Like,
exactly. You want to know what my like I
hate piggy banks. You want to know what
I've realized? You want to know what
I've realized? One of my like um issues
or something that I'm going to run into
a problem with all the time 24/7. What?
Being too full? Yes. But also, it's like
I need to constantly drink water to be
hydrated and not feel like I'm going to
pass out. But I have to pee. I have to
pee every 20 minutes if I drink a
bottle. It's ridiculous. It's the most
ridiculous thing ever cuz we're at the
festival in Chicago. It's 90 something
degrees. I'm cranking down water bottles
like they're [ __ ] Dixie cups and
nothing you can do. And I'm pissing all
the time. We need more public. I'm just
like all my friends are like, "Oh my
god, dude. like you're holding us up and
I'm like no one's saying that to you.
Well, like they're not saying that, but
like I I'm getting that vibe. Like I
feel like I'm like such a terrible viol.
I feel like just standing up and being
like, "Hey guys, I'm going to the
bathroom again." You know, I'm in a I'm
in a constant state of having to piss.
That's like who I am. It's ridiculous.
It's so ridiculous. But I don't know
what's up. Maybe it's cuz we're
triplets, so it shrunk all our bladders.
Don't say that.
That's a good That's a good point,
though. Why Why do I feel Maybe all of
our organs are tinier. Ew, don't say
that. That's why I'm so skinny. But I
have a big heart. Yes. I love seeing
like a dog get some water at like a dog
park. Like Yes. [ __ ] get that water.
You really feel that way? Just you, huh?
Go hydr. Have you seen the scientific
behind that? Yeah. Dogs scoop it up like
this. Insane. Have you seen this, Matt?
Yeah. Insane. I feel like I look like a
disgusting, sweaty, repulsive monster.
I'm right there with you. Internal temp
too high. Allow
[Music]
Hey. Hey. Hey.