and what you saying how you miss me yeah
you miss me and all the that we did we
said we going to travel from the island
to Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
all why oh because of some K but it's
okaying
brother failure Matt want Alle hold what
does that even like mean like I hate
talking about sports today so for our
Vlog I mean for the show we're
practicing at one point I'm going to be
up there in the corner and then there's
going to be a spotlight right and then
the lights are going to dim and it's
going to goom and it's going to be me up
there and I'm going to take the shot of
the life time from up there see that's
actually crazy cuz I'm having re set up
the zip line from up there and I'm just
going to go from across and then it's
going to land right behind the net and I
got to slow but I already have mine
planned like I'm going to go behind the
back like
this terrible out here oh my okay okay
Chris Pepsi away you don't have to get
soda just it's not for the Vlog for Life
yeah but like it's I don't do for
for views and for the camera I'm not
saying you were I'm just saying like you
can put it away like we don't wait can
you guys see me if I go up there right
now go up oh what what should I do what
should I do Matt I want you to up there
do 10 Jumping Jacks and I go like this
Matt
Matt what you're not even listening look
at this yeah do something crazy today
we're at the film war in Washington DC
where they don't care Nick this is
Monumental to life Mac Miller has a line
to goes I just sold out that filmm war
play it in the Vlog yeah but was he even
talking about the filmm war here isn't
there multiple filmm Wares and he's not
from there's a poster that says Mac
Miller upstairs correct he's been here
before I'm sure but I'm talking about
sold out that film was the bar this song
or is it this venue or was it another
film War there film War but it doesn't
matter each film War it's like the House
of Blues it's like there's just oh my
God oh my God he looks blonde God he
looks terrifying hey get it wait put the
volume up four five oh you wait call him
and tell him to talk into a microphone
he's get hey
[Applause]
hey oh look at him putting up the blue
score what a rookie he shut the shut the
TV volume down
idiot wait hang up do it again hold on
I'm hanging
[Music]
up it kind of
works I hear like yeah
pain it's like hey hey that is so funny
I heard like back here yeah it was crazy
you hear me it was really scary are okay
I'm putting F logo stickers on the wall
in the you want to fancy venue these
stickers get a little tricky is that L
na X where just says Nas
x l NX I don't know this door Clos I
wonder what that QR code
means can't put it in the center of the
wall what a guy there it is I get
it um go to the bathro all right guys
now we're we're going to play a little
game do you know the acinator thing
whatever the it is you want them to
reply the kid saying that like they're
going to
respond you have to understand it's
video we're doing this oh it's already
screen recording we're going to be
playing a game called acinator if you
don't know what that is it was a major
part of my M C's childhood and you
answer it's like playing 20 questions
but the 20 questions that they ask
narrow you down to a specific celebrity
or person and I think that we got put
onto the app which is crazy in and of
itself cuz we used to play this game all
the time when we were kids all right me
we're going to play and try and get each
other okay okay challenge you let's see
it is your character female yes no
like is your character real no
yes not fun I just love does your
character have any kids yes no is your
character a famous YouTuber yes I think
is your character Indian nope not is
your character black nope nope does your
character have a gaming channel a game
yeah but we don't have a gaming channel
no does your character live with their
brother yes not all of them yeah but two
of the three yes is your character part
of a trio
yes does your character like men if I
hit no it's going to go to me and Chris
if I hit yes it's going to go to you it
should go to it's going to go to you
right now watch let's say yes is your
character associated with the sternal
of that's CRA oh my God that's a good
photo of you yeah they picked a good
photo we won okay I'm going to do all
right we have achieved me in under I
feel like that was like 14 that was like
10 questions in like under 10 questions
let's count how many times it takes to
get is your character a girl no one is
your character a gamer no are youing
your character a YouTuber I'm doing you
oh I'm a is your character Indian no
does your character do 24-hour
challenges no is your character white
yes does your character live with their
brother yes does your character like men
no is your character mostly silent
yes that's crazy
I mean it's literally true you're on
stage I can't hear you you have a
microphone it's still insane to me
that's the craziest is your character
associated with the St triplets yes wow
that's crazy that I got you you're
mostly that's how many words is acinator
saying not much he's a character
in a game is your character a YouTuber
yes count how many things one is your
character female no is your character a
gamer idiot is your character Indian no
does your character do 24-hour
challenges no is your character white
yes does your character live with her
brother yes does your character like men
no is your character mostly silent no is
your character associated with the stern
YOLO triplets yes does your character
Love Pepsi that is crazy I have it right
here
yes that's the photo they
use oh they use nightmare Chris that is
so who the what if someone
accidentally gets Chris right and this
pops up on their phone who theck aor
allowed nightmare Chris to get p
on the thing that's crazy he needs a
name nightmare Chris needs a name how
the nightm nightmare Chris no no
it's nightmare Chris no no it is
Nightmare Chris needs like another like
I
[Music]
juster that's that's not Chris that's
chess I like that one that's nightmare
Chris literally chest how the did
they allow that who did that that had to
be some but it's also like when when
you're like a little kid and you're
playing that game you're probably
playing it trying to get a celebrity and
like while you're actively trying to get
a celebrity say like I don't
know Ariana Grande and you're playing
you're probably thinking in the back of
your mind as a kid like where is Arana
Grande right now like did you ever do
that as a kid like when I was a kid I
used to think of celebrities like and I
like I wonder what they're doing like in
this exact moment select theme let's do
animals let's see it has Trevor wait you
guys didn't do that as a kid Nick shut
up guys we just got off the stage I won
so I'm at two medals now but look what
Chris has I just walked back into the
GRE room it's
Chester oh my God what are the it's
literally back in the green room I just
saw this scary ass I need
that for my room this is that's actually
a really good piece of art as well they
wrote a letter too we should oh we got
read this save that yes for sure but
that's awesome that just scared the
out of right I thought it was like
Decor of the Filmore like some pH I just
I was really looking it'ser and then I
was looking and it was
like dude I'm so it's nightmare Chris
who put this here it's
Chester I love that his name is Chester
we were just talking about this
literally just a minute ago Chester but
guys we just got off the stage the the
tour is getting closer and closer Matt
is at I'm at two still I'm at two now
and Chris is at four I need to go to the
eye doctor though cuz I got that I got
the eye that just like wanders I think I
have wandering eye you're um I lost
tonight but it was very close and I'm
okay with losing cuz that meant that
Nick won and now we're tied I'm a little
scared that it's going to get really
entertaining here I just really don't
want it to be Like a Rock Paper Scissors
Shoot showdown at the last that would be
awesome think be terrible but
we'll see guys bro guys the
venue in the Filmore has a screen that
shows what's going on on stage like
while you're in the green room and the
guy John our tour manager is letting
some of the girls in the line right now
ask knock knock jokes or say jokes to
the audience and some girl just said
what do you call a cow at no legs ground
be and it actually made me cackle
whoever just made that joke at the
Filmore show that was hilarious but
we're sitting here waiting please give
us more make another joke I feel like
texting John like let him make another
joke okay why was a dog left to the
doctor's office left left left because
he had La
coat
he the
LA it was all right I get it I've never
heard it favorite place to go on
vacation
what Malibu oh there you go Malibu yes'
why did the scuba diver fall backwards
out of the boat why why cuz if you fell
forward you'd still be in the
boat what do sweet potatoes
we
what
what does sweet potatoes wear to bed
yammies what do you call an angry what a
steam
veggie terrible knock knock who's there
Ash Ash who BL
you him saying thank you is funny how
much money is it oh what's going on in
there oh there's someone there three
you're not going to sit and a massage
chair Chris get in there buddy I got I
got you for 3 minutes we just finished
our show and we're on the way to North
Carolina for a big old show tomorrow we
got the 3day the Bing Bang Boom
that's me up oh thank you start it
up what if I get trapped like oh I feel
it already dude I needed this you get
two more minutes and 5 Seconds two more
minutes anything else to say while we
relax um oh my God this feels really
nice by guys we'll see you guys next
Wednesday next Friday I'm going to do a
slow nice beautiful outro from far away
while Chris
[Music]
relaxes and what you say how you miss me
yeah you miss and all the that we did we
said we going to travel from the island
to Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
alled
because of some but it's okay cuz I'm
moving different don't be saying when I
post with other for my brothers