was her best friend whose best friend
Hannah you're my best friend oh my God
Matt that was the nicest thing ever
anybody care for an orange slice I
really care I'm like The Giving Tree
right now oh my God you are The Giving
Tree guys this is like it's 2 a.m. right
now so this is a very late night this is
kind of like this is OG's trip VI do you
feel the oenus rubbing on you I do cuz
when we were back in Boston and what if
ogus just went no this is the time where
we were like that that was crazy in your
throat this is like the time ooh I'm
dripping I got this hey D oranges like
that look a lot like um I love trailer
Chris was filming with Tara yummy today
and he did his personal video right so
Chris was doing that and me and Nick
went to the dry cleaner we go to the dry
cleaner and I bought I bought a couple
like jackets cuz I was like oh I kind of
want to step up my jacket game and you
know you can't wash leather I had yeah
you can't like throw leather you can't
dunk leather water why do I feel so low
I don't know I I sat there today and I
changed the whole do this can I go up
yeah you can probably you're going up
you're always going up we can't stop you
from going up but anyway we brought the
stuff to the dry cleaners lady goes oh
sorry we actually don't do anything
leather or
suede I go I go where what building did
I just walk into yeah what do you do
what what do you wash you wash [ __ ] that
I can wash in my dryer and wash her at
home I could do a I could get a
washboard and do it in my sink you're
telling me Chris that I can go to that's
a dry cleaner and they don't clean
clothes no it's and don't dis don't
never ever ever adjust my seat settings
again that is not your seat I it was my
seat this morning [ __ ] yes it
was cuz I was there for hours speak okay
several hours if I went if I went back
there I wouldn't go alter your whole
setting I don't give a [ __ ] yeah you I
actually why did I was sitting there
sing your seats yes it is it's not what
did what did we do to oh I just thought
something I have to speak up I have to
why why do we have these seats why am I
the only one that can drive because you
went and got your license first Nick
Nick used to sit crippling
anxiety listen Nick used to sit in the
front remember and then he did that [ __ ]
where like he would just paranoid you
cuz you'd like you'd follow the law and
he'd be like oh my God you're going to
get hit and then so or he'd yell at me
like why are you stopping at this stop
sign just go guys I'm a paranoid person
yeah whatever close to the FR of the car
what just made me think of like how I'm
like the passenger of this car is the
guys that like have a two-seater they
put like princess on the glove you are
my princess my passenger princess I
should actually get like Chris's little
seat or something like that with like
gems right there when girls put like the
fuzzy thing on their wheel oh my God
it's like girl if if there's if we're
hydroplaning and you go to turn your
wheel back to go straight and the fur
makes your hand miss the wheel and now
we're all rolling over over and dying is
it really worth the cute accessory on
the car yeah we got to go fully function
for sure why are we why are we putting
things on on the car thing that are
going to make our hand slip if you have
like a bat to protect yourself from
Intruders you put a sock on it cuz if
they go to grab the bat you can remove
the bat dude I really think they grab
the bat they they win I'd love for a
[ __ ] to try and intrude in my
piece you're getting decked God if I
think I'd be an Intruders either [ __ ]
happiest day on Earth or their worst
nightmare I'd go full [ __ ] Rambo on
your ass you leaving with no teeth and
your [ __ ] eyes in the back of your
head we should set up a plan that like
if someone intrudes our house like what
we do as triplet like imagine you in
open a house like you're about to Rob
three people that look like staring at
you and then we like we turn around all
put like black contacts in and we're
like and then they we turn around think
we have enough time to do there's
someone
intruding Glam go and then mat shuts All
the Lights Off Pitch Black in the house
and then I climb up a ladder get to the
ceiling turn the lights back on I drop
from the room I need like an alter ego
name cuz there's like a part of me deep
down that's just like a Fearless monster
keep that to yourself like actually no
actually meet your monster D how often
am I oh that's such a good saying meet
your maker underrated saying how often
am I stop talking I just really could
fight like if like I'm not a fighter at
heart but I'm a fighter if I need to if
someone like made fun of like my Mom oh
they're Dum oh my God if someone tried
to mess with Mary I think they'd be
eating cement in point I agree I would
neuter someone if they mess with Mom I
would take their ball sack who almost
neutered me the other day with a trunk
you the other day we were standing by a
trunk and someone
literally the other day someone we know
as like a newer car and it was like a I
don't even know where we were and the
trunk was like like they have like a
[ __ ] trunk Dr does it goes down so
it's like it comes like most of it
goes half goes up half goes down and it
was like coming down and I was putting
stuff in the trunk I click the down
button like legit like my height was
perfect like like like I don't know how
to say this I'm sounding like insane
like my your dick balls my my your
[ __ ] balls yeah yeah yeah I like they
almost got pinched in by the truck yeah
like I can
say like part of me because of my height
like when I was putting something in the
trunk like perfectly rested on the trunk
and Chris went to close it so it's like
like I wasn't going anywhere my balls
were lifting it almost guillotined like
I almost got neutered the other day
that's a nightmare yeah dude imagine you
going to pay attention more dude to put
him in a situation like that almost
neutered me not that it matter was it
was like it was like an auto of us hads
get neutered I'd volunteer I'd volunteer
cuz I can't have kids anyway I'm gay so
it's like if one of us if we were like
at like a if we were at like a um if we
were like got kidnapped by someone and
they were like one of you ball your
balls are out of here you're getting
neutered I take you know what no I want
take one of mine no I want to be a good
uncle like if if someone had to lose the
ability to like don't all right Don you
want to know what I don't understand
origami yeah
folding paper who's the first person to
make a paper swan me someone who is very
bored how did you figure that one out I
feel like that's one of those things
that you do for the first time and you
must feel like you're about to like like
who like I've definitely said this
before but who is the first person who
milked a cow what the [ __ ] were you
doing you sicko well like how did how
did we just how why' you drink it why
did we start how are we putting gas in
our cars I don't know how how are we
driving I want to know who first turned
on like a
flashlight like who invented that or we
can even get as simple as like and this
is so crazy but like when like never
mind no say
it I just think a lot of inventions go
over our heads especially as I think of
this I love that saying over your head
like if something goes right over your
head I think of this H fan of think
about this before people knew before
people knew like like the the ability of
like having like the birds and the bees
talk and like oh this is how like babies
are made like to people who like had sex
for the first time and like they had the
thought in their head like I want to do
this and we're going to do it together
and then they did it and they were like
oh my God that was crazy like what's the
outcome of this and then not much longer
it's like the woman just starts growing
and she's like what's wrong with you
there's like an alien like there's a
parasite in me I'm dying and then she
birs another kid like imagine being the
first person like the first woman to
like act on having sex and then birthing
a kid I don't need she must have thought
she was dying for 9 months I can't hear
this yeah I'm fre is that not [ __ ]
crazy know Chris told me Chris told me
that if if he needed like if way in the
future like him and some girl were doing
like a gender reveal of a baby I he said
that he trust me to orchestrate like the
experience I told Nick the other day if
I am ever in the position where like one
of my Rel you're Notting has to find out
about like my gender if you're not
starting he's the guy to reveal it if
you're not do like a trick or something
crazy my unpopular opinion my unpopular
opinion about gender reveals is like in
order for it to be a good gender reveal
you have to either cause like a lot of
pollution a forest fire or have a
casualty otherwise what's the fun in
finding out the gender of your baby if
we're not lighting like half a forest
down or getting like glitter and dirt
and like [ __ ] what are you saying
that's what I'm saying like I think that
if there's a gender reveal we need nine
planes to fly by and blue smoke to fill
the entire and then maybe light like an
entire Forest on
fire see if I if we like had like a if I
had a really really nice like front lawn
I'd hire people to come and like cut
plants like Edward scissor hand style
like a big like a big new conversation
yeah I want like a big like something
that says I'm here like I want like a
massive like Shrubbery of invit me okay
if if I'm if I'm inviting someone over
and they're not they're not being conf
fronted by my welcoming Shrubbery Nick
you don't even like plants I don't like
that you're wrong no I'm not I don't
like that I don't like that you don't
like plants you don't like you no I
think uh CVS I have a pitch for CVS we
need to get the extra care we need the
receipts longer no we need the extra
care Buck to be part of like an app now
where like if I put my phone number in I
don't need to like get my receipt of the
extra care cash just like hold that on
to my next Pur yes like I want to scan
my extra
care hoping people lose it by the way
I've never yeah cuz I never use my extra
care box cuz I don't have them on me mom
does I still don't like understand
origami and like I don't think I ever
will cuz here's the thing whoever built
it then again had to remember how to do
it again to make the instruction PN it's
like I don't get it dude and then how
are how do we know to cut off a certain
piece of paper for like the fortune
teller [ __ ] you dude that's not
happening you didn't say [ __ ] you D we
didn't say [ __ ] till we were in high
school can we talk about I I I hated
like I remember we've we've claimed like
we've said on the internet like oh we
didn't swear as kids because like we
didn't and people pulled up videos from
us like as super little kids saying [ __ ]
and damn it's like those are not swears
it's time for you to grow up yeah I
consider they said they didn't swear
they're saying [ __ ] and damn swears are
[ __ ]
[ __ ] um dude I don't think I said [ __ ]
till freshman year of high school I
remember the first time I said [ __ ] is
cuz I spilled a burning hot cup of water
on me I was in a hotel lobby that was me
yeah that was stop turning my personal
experiences into your memories that was
me no it was not restart this restart
this rest restart this hold on you need
to get away me Chris has a terrible
terrible terrible triplet habit of like
we'll see a friend of ours we live in
Boston and La as lots of you know and
love to [ __ ] [ __ ] and complain about
and when we're in Boston we hang out
with our friends from Boston when we're
in La we hang out with our friends in LA
and we'll be we'll go to Boston we'll go
to our friend's house we'll be like
three of our friends there and we'll be
like ready to tell them a story of
something that happened to us in LA and
I I'm like so intrigued to be like how
is Chris going to express this story and
he'll [ __ ] go up to our friends and
be like yeah I grabbed like this drink
out of the fridge and I took a sip and I
was like oh that was awful and I threw
it at the wall and it exploded
everywhere and it would he'll tell a
story fully from his brain and
perspective that he watched happen to me
like my story and I see it too and I'm
like and what I'm like it makes me feel
like I'm going crazy I'm like am I
[ __ ] do I need to be
like no Nick it makes me feel like I'm
going crazy too cuz I it it always he
happen immediate I'll walk somewhere and
I'll grab like the last mint from the
mint jar and we'll go to our friend's
house and like it it'll have happened 10
minutes ago like yo we're just at a
restaurant and I grabbed like the last
minut from the mint jar there was like
one left he always does it to that you
do and then I hear him say it and then
it makes me think wait which one of them
just did that okay but I did say [ __ ]
for the first time burning myself on
wrong guarant I did and and then I heard
at the end of that little story you're
like oh hotel lobby where one two no
yeah where where one yes where one two
yes where where where on the count of
three you're going to say where this
hotel was if we have the same [ __ ]
answer my point will be proven shut up
I'm not going to yell no
just just say the name of just say the
name just say the state we were in just
say it you [ __ ] liar you crazy liar
on the count of three you will say it
three say it
you're [ __ ] I say I unzipped it and
give me the key Nick can I can I say
something oh my God
some I'm dead serious I'm I'm D it's
soot sometimes I just get excited to be
with you guys and then I forget oh I'm
not doing the sob story of Jo I'm not
soing three two nope not saying Chris I
am so beyond the serious level scale
it's burning hot three you're the
goofiest person I've ever met then why
do you want to be me and share all of my
personal anecdotes and experiences as
your own I don't are you going to do it
yes I will three are you dead serious
yep three Hotel first beverage or second
three two one Vermont hot beverage 3 2 1
T thank
you if you walk into the hotel and a to
further prove my point if you walk into
the main entrance of the hotel which way
is the [ __ ] hot tea station to your
right or left 3 2 1 left is it before or
after you pass the [ __ ] front desk 3
2 1 after you liar you [ __ ]
liar can I say something of course okay
so I want to share this from my
perspective I don't care we were all
sitting in the lobby Nick was getting
the tea and I remember standing there
next to te there next to te next to Nick
getting his tea and he burnt his hand
and he said [ __ ] [ __ ] and he screamed it
really loud I remember all like my face
went pale I almost passed out I was I
was so much
nervous I was so nervous for Nick cuz I
thought Nick was about to get in so much
trouble or like be possessed by the
devil right then and there it was the
first time I heard him swear oh my God I
literally I think I it fear I literally
went like this I went like this and I
went I almost just [ __ ] fell straight
on my back I remember walking home once
and my friend was like so you guys don't
swear at all and I was like nope he's
like say [ __ ] like right now and I was
like like I was like scar I couldn't do
it I couldn't even get that's the real
story that happened yeah I remember that
I couldn't get it out of my mouth it's
unbelievable yeah Nick I hope you have a
nice Bush one day in front of your yard
thank you yes of course thank you I
really want that I was really
uncomfortable when you were saying you
hope everybody's welcomed by your
Shrubbery I was like I really do I want
walk and like the first compliment I
want about my house is like wow you have
amazing Shrubbery outside
love to hear that no I wouldn't I oh
imagine someone goes up to you Mt oh
your brother's shrubber is unreal they
wouldn't know it's my Shrubbery yet i'
have to tell them unless you [ __ ] be
like oh it's my
Shrubbery can I can we talk about lassos
for a
minute love oh my God love them so much
love them so it's like just I've
captured you in this
ruply like rope of
what what I think that's something we
should do
what a lasso competition what I think
that that's like I think just imag
getting lassoed like oh you're running
like I'd love to just see imagine a
parent and like their kid is running and
like be like oh go get your kid lasso
gotcha oh my God if I could lasso
somebody my life would be a dream okay
dude you're freaking me out if like a my
dog is running away and I like dropped a
leash masso I've caught you no no if I'm
dropping a leash there proba no way I
can lasso yeah no for sure it's just I
love I I would love to maybe be the
lasso e that gets caught and like put me
and like a cowboy on a horse in like a
stable together and I'll run around and
they can try and catch me okay I think
that the word lasso like sounds like the
action of doing it it's a perfect word
lasso um you know what I mean I I really
felt it until you did the like little
like
I just like felt something deep in my
soul and I just like had a big
connection to something in my past and
I'm about to say it it's like one of
those things where like are you okay do
I to worry my goodness I just saw like
this receipt right here it's a parking
pass from like a parking garage we
packed in and it reminded me so much do
you know like I'm not I'm going to I
don't want to reveal no know I will I
will where was this I don't know I don't
want to reveal what I was talking about
to soon cuz I want you guys to really
experience it but what I'm about to say
is like one of those OG feelings of like
of like of like just like touching like
a like a like a sand and the pizza like
the Good Vibes of like retro stuff go
now I this reminds me of like the old
Deli slips that you just like pull out
of the Del machine that weren't any
shape or color of of this no but just
how classic it was like seeing all the
numbers in the letter like nothing was
better than getting called up to the
deli uh there's a lot of things better
no not true leaving the grocery no
correct being at the deli and holding my
little ticket waiting for my name to be
called it was like knowing you're going
to win the lottery [ __ ] I guess you
know what I mean it's just the
excitement thrill of like almost being
up next in line all right guys that's
been this week's Friday car video I had
a blast filming today it felt really
ogenus just rubbing up on me everywhere
and it was a wonderful feeling I need to
get a massage now too as well just
that's a side note but it has to happen
oh my God I need a massage we should do
a couple's massage cuz I heard that it's
cheaper I'm down yeah and then it's like
we're covered we can hold each other's
hands while we go through it as well for
just emergency like I'm here with you I
think it's not like I'm getting an MRI
I'm getting a like I think I'll be good
I don't know I'd be nervous like I'm
just afraid to like I'm afraid to do
normal people [ __ ] cuz like what if a
sternal or triplet fan walks in and I'm
like butt naked getting rubbed you know
what I mean that's very valid very valid
feeling yes anyways guys that's been
this week's Friday car video we are
going to be
back next Friday I know that for sure
yep yeah I hope you had a blast watching
today and we are going to do origami in
the meantime yeah or Nick is and then
Chris is going to claim he did the next
time Matt [ __ ] you the next time you
guys see me you're going to also see me
with my crane friend Emmanuel the the
paper
[Music]
crane