wait can I be in the middle of the
triple sandwich please it's already
recording yeah I hit recording and Nick
you need to stop vibrating like that
please it's really making me UNC my
shirts are loose so I kind of feel this
in full effect hi everyone welcome back
to the stern YOLO triplets YouTube
channel it's
Matt the
driver it's Chris the soda drinker it's
Nick the gay boy yeah today is the
probably the most Monumental moment in
stni triplets career and I'm not even
joking probably in the past 3 years this
is the biggest if we are ever going to
see in terms of car video ever the Chris
stolo California driers
license and you may think oh Chris got
his license this video is clearly going
to be him driving around no we are
getting a tarp we're getting tons of
Lubin oil and we are wrestling naked
finally we've been dying to do this for
like 3 years okay all right our whole
career we've had lore of Matt being like
the the driver the driver triplet he's
Matt has had his license for almost 5
years and he's looked so good our whole
career Matt's been driving us around
sacrificing his ankle sacrificing guys
the ankle bit is like not a joke Ser
like he's going to get an MRI like
severe ankle paint Matt has done so much
for the triplets and he's been just the
lead driver for the past five
years but yeah so basically I got my
permit while Nick was in Japan so we
were supposed to do it together and then
I go to Japan in Australia and I come
back didn't even send me a text the
courtesy text of like hey I'm doing this
thing we both needed to do for the past
two years I come back and he has Driving
School scheduled for the next 3 days cuz
he's that
guy so I'm I'm I literally and
figuratively am being left in the dust
like I'm being so wait so what's your
excuse I'm choking on Dust right now
what's your excuse I had I had three
driving lessons I did them all and then
I actually got my permit first try too
which is pretty awesome I failed the
permit test all right so guys what I'm
thinking is should I drink first
probably get you black just that I get
loose I saw this amazing statistic of if
you drink once and then you drunk you
drunk Drive you're not going to feel
really confident in it but if you drink
and drive consistently by the 20 of time
you're going to get out there hammered
feeling like I got this is a horrible
yeah I can get on the road drunk and
I'll be fine driving yeah obviously a
joke guys come on please don't drink and
drive it's actually like one of we're
going to Nick's going to do something he
hates and when Chris goes to drive right
now he's going to put on his seat Bel no
I'm not yes
you wow this is the fastest you've
decided to drive rough right turn you're
in the middle of two lanes you need to
pick one how do we feel driving with the
moon out I feel
me the Moon is [ __ ] right there yep w
ohcome [ __ ] take aot that I need to
get over right man don't kill the
motorcycle I need to get over though
right yes you need to get over twice
okay well just say that then change two
lanes dummy Drive yeah literally little
driving
elf you're going to Chris he's not
snoozing he's wide awake you're going to
[ __ ] sideswipe him idiot like oh my
God go you snooze you this guy go too
stop oh my God Christ I'm hitting my
break good boy now right in here is this
exit only Matt yes you need to get over
again again yes you only you did it once
but you did it like an idiot so it felt
like you switched Lanes twice guys
what's going to happen first Chris
switches Lanes or we get struck by
lightning odds are equivalent I can't
switch Chris you'll be able to switch
you need to stop going so [ __ ] fast
Nick why don't you do what you do best
and make some jokes or
something whoa sorry I actually wasn't
paying attention sorry yeah how about we
pay attention saying wo is n there's
just like a lot going on Fu you mean wo
I'm feeling a lot of pressure like this
is like I'm a very
cybertruck everyone list your favorite
fears that's a good topic favorite fears
or your biggest fears my biggest fears
is medical devices like needing like a
surgery needing a a transplant needing a
blood donation like anything medical
uh-uh kill me I'd rather I I agree with
that I don't like I don't like heights
don't [ __ ] with Heights I don't like
being alone I don't like spiders okay I
don't like what if there was a spider
while you were by yourself it was
crawling on you I'm good was like I'm
going to touch you Chris I don't being
alone is number one for me my biggest
fear is Chris driving I don't like v i
don't look at the road stop don't even
joke when Chris first started driving
the craziest thing for me was sitting
behind Matt always I always for some
reason choose this left seat even though
the right one is available to me sorry I
didn't that and for the first time in my
life it was genuinely difficult to tell
who was who apart because I was so used
to Matt being in front of me and then
Chris had to stop and you could tell who
is who no Chris was just driving I'm
like okay this turn was rough imagine
this imagine you're a rookie in the NBA
season right yag and then you and then
you go face one one one to one against
LeBron James he's going to dunk on your
[ __ ] ass and he's going to make you
feel like a fo you're still in the NBA
okay imagine being a rook and not and
not talking you are you are the best I
talk to you with respect you yell at me
like I yell you because I know what you
need to do it's [ __ ] up Matt's the
LeBron James of driving no one is better
at driving than Matt I will get stamp of
approval like the goat Driver best
safest I feel most efficient I arrive
what are you driving to the bakery to
get more glaze for this kid I'm dead
serious amazing hardcore like what I am
dead ass Matt is the best driver I've
ever driven with thank you 100% ni's
your for me to get compared to Matt it's
a rough thing right and it's like Nick
Nick started talking about my driving
the other day I'm like shut your [ __ ]
ass up can't drive you laughing at me no
shut your ass up you were in Tokyo
eating [ __ ] all your food and being
yourself oh my God eating all your
food I was in the US grinding bro I was
trying to get my license I was taking
lessons 21 with my license feels great I
was long are you waiting yikes I needed
if you if August 1st this year my
license expires if you let that happen
before you get yours that's really
embarrassing I just see that as me and
you in the same playing field we get
soda Nick you we'll go to Inn out we go
to Inn out shut your [ __ ]
mouth Inn out not that in a not okay so
like remember when we were filming that
car video and you go I love cars and
it's not true I could not I that's the
the most underrated C if there was a
Lamborghini a Bugatti give me two more
Lamborghini a Ferrari and a Porsche in
front of me I could not tell I could not
tell you I swear to God I swear to God
if I'm lying kill me now I could not
tell you gun to my head which one was
gun to your head you could what about a
fir truck a bus
okay all right yeah I I'd figure it out
but I be the worst person to be with in
crisis what would be your least favorite
crisis to be in with Nick stolo any any
of them if I was like urgently like
imagine if I just got like
impaled correct I can't if I was like
slowly bleeding out you're the last or
quickly Bleeding Out actually is the
worst case scenario no the anything
involving you at a at a crisis I would
hate like even if I twisted my ankle and
you were the person that had to like
help me walk away I'd be like have you
gotten stitches I've gotten two
Staples oh my God craziest school dance
moment everyone share I have one in my I
have one too there was this couple of
this this boy and this girl that were
dating when I was in seventh grade and
one of them was a seventh grader one of
them is an eighth gr I know what you're
talking about say it I'll blur it were
they talking about how they motor booed
no no it wasn't the motor boers it
wasn't the motorers and there's a I was
going through my Snapchat memories guys
I kid you not I I don't know what I used
to be such a bold person like I'm bold
on in terms of us yes and like in like
our vicinity but I would never just go
up to someone and say something like
rude
or there's a photo of me in my Snapchat
memories and they're slow dancing at the
school dance and I'm like gagging myself
with my finger and pointing at them like
like throwing up yes they're right
behind me they're in it's a flash photo
of me of them slow dancing right behind
me you have the photo yes dude we have
to put it in the video no just blur them
out it's literally me being like
disgusting Ed by them sling each other
I'm like that's ter I think the craziest
like slow or school dance memory that I
have is like just like kids that I
thought like presuming that they were
just like innocent kids sh like
delivering like just delivering like
back shots to somebody at prom like like
like that's crazy should we get on a
real serious note on why I have my
license and you guys didn't for 5 years
basically I'm going to sum this up real
nice and quick and sweet and slap bow on
it for you I dude you love that another
matolo like Banger like that yes that
was slap a bow on it like that was
perfect um anyway I had crippling
anxiety for okay for um all of middle
and high school so when Nick and Chris
would hang out with their friends I
would go to driving so annoying it was
like Matt get over it right correct
correct it's like stop faking that stop
faking your anxiety
youer but no but no I just really wanted
my license because I wanted to be able
to leave places I wanted to be able to
drive myself to school I wanted the the
power of being able to leave situations
and have a car and be able to drive all
I wanted so they would hang out with
friends and I would go to driving school
and I got my license and that means that
I would drive I wanted the power of
driving so bad so they didn't get their
license because I was going to drive us
all everywhere anyway and me man and
Chris have literally done everything
together ever since until this year
we're finally like being a little bit
more individual so it's time that we can
maybe transport ourselves places by
ourselves I started to get more anxiety
not to put blame on
anyone but who no you can't do that you
can't do that I'm not I'm not um just
like the idea of like if I broke my leg
in our house tomorrow or if I got shot
in the foot who knows what's going to
happen I would like there to be a
possibility of Transport that's not an
amb
you know what I mean yeah so just I
would whip that ho just the comfort of
somebody else in my home being able to
drive me to a green lights or go to
Jersey miks to get themsel a BLT so that
I don't have to do it like stuff like
that you know yeah take that turn buddy
I got did someone just beep at me yes oh
I will [ __ ] get out of my car and I
will gun you down I'm not a bad
driver Chris Chris Chris Chris Chris oh
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry go go go
go go embarrassed I'm also embarrassed
sorry sorry sorry I wasn't looking it's
cuz Nick's already critiquing me so it
makes me second guess my judgment I'm
beaming on my face I just know that all
this isn't going to be usable I'm going
to look like I'm glowing white it's
usable we literally like I've notic we
Vamp tasty ghosts are vampires
disgusting white ghost I hate the son
I've been saying this [ __ ] for my whole
life my favorite is daylight savings and
then I wake up at 4 like 3:00 and I have
1 hour of sun a vampire freak I like the
sun I'm just this out of here me and
Dracula are one in another so am I going
taking the neck left uh right you need
to learn your right I Tak the next right
shut your [ __ ] mouth and just answer
the question you saw me is there water
in that water bottle yeah can I have it
were you saying that I wish I could
shave my head uh go for it there's like
totally the tools to do
that last time that happened it was a
crazy time in really
bad I can't believe you were just bald
yeah that [ __ ] was terrible you looked
awful Justin gave you the [ __ ] number
nine all
around that was so crazy it was so I was
just like hairless like a cat I like
like I look like a literal hairless cat
hello what's up um can I do three uh
wait Nick you don't want a burger yet no
Burger can I do two plain cheeseburgers
okay and then three orders of french
fries and then does anybody want a drink
I do cuz I asked for one a minute you
pepp
and then a medium Dr Pepper okay and I
think that will do it you don't want to
drink cheeseburgers PL three fries pepp
to go yep going to be first right side
lane thank you so much when ites okay
cool thank Youk
you I feel that's kind okay get
don't that was like kind of weird right
was that kind of weird Nick or or am I
losing it
what weird that was kind of weird I
don't like Chick-fil-A at all I'm never
really there but when they be saying
like when they're like my pleasure I'm
like you're kind of doing tricks on it
I'm like are you going to do a little
bow too or is this it when I hear my
pleasure I'm like I need you to be
pulling on the sides of your little
skirt and do a little dip for me like
let's see some action with that kind of
like you're like glazing your pleasure
when they look at you with those creepy
eyes do like have a blessed day I'm like
get the [ __ ] away from me like that's a
lot of work for for a goddamn chick
chicken Deluxe oh my God like you're
doing tricks on a chicken I have a story
time I already told Chris or he already
heard part of it but Nick you didn't so
I'm going to say it and your reaction is
going to be better yeah this is funny me
Nick and Chris were shopping the other
day and I first of all I hate shopping
in general because that means I have to
leave my house second of all I hate a
lot I hate shopping during the holiday
season because it's way way more busy
and they make shopping such a fun it's
way more busy though and I don't like it
you can slow down for sure there you go
um so anyway never been told to slow
down when I'm literally at zero miles
per hour but well you can stop moving
forward is what I mean I wasn't
increasing speed I was at zero miles
hour you know what that means Z M
holiday season shopping is the worst and
here's my couple of examples why all the
railings that I have to put my hands on
now have [ __ ] tinsel and glitter all
of the that's like so n all of the music
that's being playing is taken from the
number one pop songs in the world to now
we're just blaring Christmas music and
everyone pretends to enjoy it and
pretends to be all happy like oh I just
love wasting money buying Christmas
gifts for my needy kids and family
everybody my God so we get into this
store and I'm thinking okay I'm just
going to get what we need and I'm going
to leave but no holiday cheer is is
playing max volume in Santa's in the
two-step Boogie with a million other
kids literally tap dancing oh my God
wait I'm sorry look at this group of
people yeah they look awesome wow Nick
so I'm walking into this store trying to
focus on what I need to pick out and my
thoughts are Santa's doing the twostep
Boogie right in front of me and and I'm
losing my mind cuz I'm think I'm trying
to think about what's a logical purchase
and I have Christmas music and bells and
whistles playing in my ear and I I'm not
kidding m volume there a DJ felt like
did you guys see the DJ yes yes when
when I heard the music so loud I was
like wow all the way up when I got to
the top floor I was like oh there's a DJ
here and this is where I'm sorry to
interrupt you why does I think what we
should have is In-N-Out gives you the
drinks right when you order them and
then by the time I got my food I've like
had a little drink like I want my drink
more than anything right now anything I
want my drink I had to to bring a Red
Bull to the drivethru cuz I knew how
long it take and I'm done with this
already ni I feel like you'd really [ __ ]
with a Congo line is that just me I
finally pick the item that I want and I
go to the register the lady scans it she
goes all right is that all I go yep I'm
ready to check out she goes okay do you
have an account with us I go no she goes
all right well I'm just going to put in
some information about you it's not
going to like create an account or send
you a million emails but just you'll
save 20% off if if you like answer did
you actually save 20% off yeah if you
like do like three questions or whatever
do you have an inch under your ass do
you have a [ __ ] yeah I go sure you
have an inch in your ass I go sure yeah
I'll do it she is that what she said
obviously not that's what I
heard she goes flying the rocket
ship she goes okay email I go Okay blah
blah blah whatever and then she goes uh
last name I give her my last name and
then I hear because keep in mind as I'm
talking to her and giving her this
information I didn't just say my email I
screamed every letter of it because
Santa and the holiday cheer and the
bells and the Chimes and the the bells
were jingling so I'm I'm like trying to
listen her I go what and she goes oh
just just the last name I go okay give
her my last name and then I hear birth
birthday I go uh August and then and
then I'm like you got that and then she
was like yep and then I go first and she
goes what
what question did you just ask me right
there she goes last and first name
August stolo you're good to go signed up
completely under August stolo because
she said she said first name and I and
as I'm listening to Christmas music I
switched first name in birthday and now
I'm August
stolo you didn't speak up no I didn't
speak up Nick why would I she already
has the account the 20% went
through pH number email every time I go
there I'm like do you know if you go
back and you have to buy something
doesn't like you're going to have to use
August stolo dude are you dead serious
Santa's fault hello how are you good how
are you I'm so sorry about oh don't
worry what you sorry about I have no
idea I'm great thank you
okay sorry thank you no problem you like
any ketchup today by any chance um I'm
okay no thank you I almost said Yes
again you those are those two Burg playe
here are those three thank you you
a I like thought she was tripping but oh
look at this hat on this
lady like she going to explore the wi
goes how are you she goes I'm okay
that's no she said I'm sorry no she said
she came back over she said I'm good and
then one goes okay yeah I was just like
confused I was like okay buddy well I
was just confused by what she was
telling me she I'm good he go this lady
look at this look at this bow on the
license plate gay Chris you need to be
way more to the right really yes dude
are you I need this person to just drive
their [ __ ] need to drive Chris I can't
yes you can you absolutely can enough
for him to play football no you're they
host the Super Bowl between you and that
car go over here straight straight Lane
you're taking a left Super Bowl 55
between Chris's car and the curb oh look
at this guy speed right past you yeah he
mad I ha me do that stop talking about
should have I mean you still could have
gone after is this person going straight
dumbass like both directions after this
car no yeah
no no no no definitely not it's cuz like
when I'm driving with you Matt
everything I do is either too fast too
slow not enough to the right not enough
to the left I just got my license most
of the time it's no I'm not parking in
here Nick most of the time it's not
enough to the right or left because you
haven't navigated those yet Nick keep
laughing a [ __ ] slasher throat they
give out driver's test like Snickers in
La
guys give out driving the test you can
actually if you go to a a 7-Eleven or a
supermarket and to take a penny leave a
penny you can find a driver's license in
there it's really funny man pick it up
sign your name and you're good to
go
girl pick anyway
you guys are annoying you're so funny
Chris stop [ __ ] making jokes about
like my like Inc right so for this
second of the video we're incoherency
we're going to
rap Nick you're so funny everyone laugh
a Nick we're going to rate Chris's
driving for this part of the
video why did it just get
darker wonder what I miss so much what
those like B themed baby toilet it's
like before you're potty trained and you
get to [ __ ] in like the Barney toilet or
something and it's like a big plastic
tub that just like totes around your
[ __ ] and piss you're so weird d I don't
miss that for a
second I don't remember
that I want to say that I think Chris is
going to be a great dri a great driver
one day he has he has he has the best
teacher in the world and once we get the
lefts and rights down pad everything
else is smooth sailing from there
let me just say this guys I have a
couple remarks to
make is that funny nick kid still
thinking about Encanto diapers and [ __ ]
so Weir stuck right now no Nick why
don't I think you'd find funnier than
diap the the what you say was so funny
the best teacher in the world he goes
Chris has the
potion I think Chris is going driver
it's so D it's like [ __ ] you right now
typ me it's so
funny is that no he's like you're the
worst right now but like one day you're
going to be good you put my card in my
wallet you pick and choose when you want
to like love and hate like Nick could do
the same thing and then if Nick said
something bad about you driving he'd be
like you'd be like get your license
idiot fat boy like you're stupid that's
yeah butter ball pork chop fat so
Porky the
B meat
stick beef
jerky fats of the
clown biggie
ball yeah all those things
huh yeah fat ass you you couldn't do it
either you chubby
[ __ ] yeah people always say Nick's
afraid to eat on camera meanwhile I've
been shoveling fries down my throat for
the past 30 I don't give a
[ __ ] I tanked this [ __ ] put it in 2x
I'll do it
again you want to know what I feel like
when we film outros you know when like I
don't know if you're going to know this
Nick cuz uh you're a baby but when
you're part of a team in school and
stuff and you do the hands in thing it's
like all right count us down and they
like select one kid how would I not know
that and they're like go team on
three be back it next Friday with
another video at 5:30 all the stuff we
were wearing in this week's video will
go live on Christmas Christmas
Christmas so shop the merch if you like
it thank you so much for watching hit
the like button see you next Friday at
5:30 smash that subscribe button please
[Music]
oh