yep
look him up
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
would you like a sip of water
no thanks okay I'm a big fan of that
stuff
no
[Applause]
hold on comfortable all right let's ask
let's get started here let's start with
the three easy questions that should be
the truth here
all right so we're ready are we running
over there
okay Matt go ahead is your name
Christopher Samuel yep
Massachusetts
where were we born in Massachusetts oh
yes
are you 19 years old yes
us true
[Music]
do you think
do you think your Pepsi habits are
unhealthy and out of control
nah
true
that's probably why there's still a
problem
this one was for me it's a two-parter
do you remember putting Reese's on a
plate in high school and labeling it do
not eat or I will kill you yes
you remember that true great second part
of the question do you really believe I
ate those Reese's yes yes I do why
happy left out there lies that's the
gratification I feel is beyond I was
pretty sure it was Matt I think I ate um
didn't work I think
Do You Believe In Love
no
why
he's just broken yeah I used to eat a
little fixing yeah he needs some grease
in the tin can
whatever that was crazy do you fully
trust me in that with everything yeah
um bye
that's nice oh it depends what
everything is
[Music]
it depends if you give me like like do
you trust like with my life yeah of
course
so what do we not trust
have you ever made music
maybe you gotta say yes yes no I haven't
true
not yet at least oh next question will
you ever consider making music
yeah
true
considered have you ever found a girl
Matt likes attractive
yeah
true okay
I guess that's a good thing yeah yeah
Fair cheat on someone no
true nice
I'm a faithful young man does having the
most Instagram followers boost your ego
ever zero percent of the time okay
that's insane I knew it would just a
little bit like it just you just like it
just shows like who really started oh
wow I was doing I was doing it before
y'all
if someone finds you untrustworthy do
you think they have a valid reason
no
true no I'm like the most trustworthy
person in the world I have to agree with
that like I could help with any
situation I'm just that guy wow I was
expecting you to lie on that one me too
why would I lie I'm on a lie detector
right now okay
do you ever wish you weren't a triplet
wow
I was looking at my lap and said I
wasn't really zoned into the the I mean
yeah
I would never do you want to live with
me and Nick forever yep
lie
well I don't think you guys want to live
with me so
yeah
yeah I think that was like there's a lot
in line for you I don't yeah I do
believe that you do but I feel like I do
believe yeah considering circumstances
that may occur but who knows whatever
whatever the [ __ ] that means I don't
know are you happy with the people you
surround yourself with right now
absolutely
true
nice do you think your mom and dad's
favorite child
me personally I am yes as of right now
yes I do
true where are you at have you ever
purposely started an argument
no
why yeah
all right okay
oh have you ever lied to us about your
location
no
lie oh no not you guys well that was the
question
so I don't know who you're thinking of
where would I even going I can't drive
that's the question okay
okay next okay do you think your style
is evolving
yeah
why
I hope it was
I think it's more of like I feel like
you have no confidence
I know what's cool I just can't match
for the life I think it's like it's a
building evolving's the wrong word I
think you're just getting it in check
you think you have a stronger bond with
one of your brothers more than the other
no
true nice good I like that good boy
um
are you familiar with the song Florida
by Dominic Fike yes I am
okay
would you ever cover that song
no
it's alive you already we're not there
streets yes
dude
[Music]
that's your version do you think you're
more talented than your brothers
yes
true
in some levels yes I feel fine you guys
that's insane okay I feel far more
driven I think you guys need to wake up
hey did we put out any content you
regret yes loads true
interesting one on the same page
would you consider yourself a player no
why couldn't you test the chuckle after
the lines
did you even believe yourself saying
that
I love everybody see it's got some
problems
hey I've been heartbroken yeah
true damn when you say Matt's an
instigator
yeah
true that's ridiculous that's absolutely
ridiculous and then if you consider
yourself to Problem Solver
yes yes yes true yes okay I agree I
agree with that part I don't know if I'm
an Instagram
I love g-star digital and Laura
true that's my life that's on a
year-long contract or a full life
contract tomorrow well that was the last
question thank you good job Chris
wonderful job how do you feel after your
experience I feel open like an open book
awesome that's good ready to read ready
to read nice
but
for my brothers