rip me out the plastic [ __ ] I'm acting
brand new bring me up the plastic
bedroom acting brand new big Lotto
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
that we did
a lot of plans
uh is that your name Big Lot over that's
what she says that's not a rap name oh
is it I actually just water I think it's
just Lotto probably big wobbles like but
she goes big Lotto
we gotta go
you're stupid
Warehouse 79 trash Duty
according to service
bro I'm always scared of raccoons gonna
come out climb up my ass or something
what
they gated up like it's golden oh my God
that's a lot of trash he Mets went
through here
holy [ __ ]
one of our neighbors must have gotten
like a [ __ ]
trash or something
I always try to think like a joke like
Nick but I can't think that fast bro I'm
taking like a year to think of a good
old joke
I agree and Nick's wobble Luigi no he's
Wario no he's not bro he's wobbly he was
literally him for Halloween I'm gonna
tell him you just said that okay go
ahead Nick
oh why is this out of focus
Nick yeah I said to Matt sometimes I
feel like Mario and Luigi and I said
yeah Nick's Waluigi I mean yeah I said
waluigine he goes nah he's Wario
bro I don't like that
that's what Matt said yeah that's crazy
what happened
I need ice and a lot of it
get it like why are you telling everyone
bro I need ass wipes hold on
I'm out of these at home
you can go okay
that was not Chris there he is not that
[ __ ] nice I think the advice I just
don't think it's gonna be in like
the [ __ ] frozen section I don't know
dude
[Music]
or something why'd that sound like a
Lego
isn't that all we need two bags are you
[ __ ] crazy like eight okay we need to
put those back and go somewhere else oh
we can just get them why would we do
that because look at the next place has
four do you think you like that's all
the ice you have the ice that's in the
freezer
if there's more in the back inside of
Oxford like way in the back or like I
could call something
probably like three more three more yeah
thank you so much
oh it never hurts to ask huh yep never
hurts to ask
prime example that was awesome actually
I was expecting to be like no like yes
we have ice
cream I treat people with respect out
here man
three others
that's under your hand oh there it is
lights are crazy expensive happy I'm
using a group card do you need help with
the bags I'll be good
um
you think you got all of them up here
can you have a good night
okay
all right
I'm unsatisfied I want more ice I was
just embarrassed to ask for that amount
you know we had to ask like the back
inventory [ __ ] I was gonna be like yeah
I need 12 more bags of ice so we're
going somewhere else yeah okay
that's not the freezer
I'm walking away from them they're going
the wrong way
oh man I'm a man I'm the man where are
they
maybe they did go the right way
is there no ice here
skipping down the Ohio
where's my Takis at what's going on holy
[ __ ] where's the ice
I need your finest batch of ice
no fiction heck something just told me
it was that way what
something to the side of me I don't know
it could have been the coolest too oh
wait it might be that no it definitely
is hold on do you think so
yeah it's got to be this one oh yeah it
says ice
what do you need
what corn dogs
[Music]
it's hard to freeze that we need a cart
a cart Chris yeah
orange lime lemon
scared to see how much ice you got
I'm not gonna stop so
it's good ten these are way bigger than
the others too yeah it's about to get
full God
wow Nick the plants and candles you
added in here makes it very like nice
and aesthetic thank you of course
okay I'm not gonna do this if you're
gonna make this much noise clearly
didn't want just the way the eyes fell
I keep throwing this [ __ ] ice I'm not
gonna
we have to actually chill I'm scared
thank you
just hurry up this is really loud yeah
Chris
let's put some water in there
you need to do it quite hold on we'll be
right back
oh my God
I think you might have too much ice no
there's never too much okay
yes yes I'm really scared I'm ecstatic
oh my God it looks so cold
okay oh Ice Cube foul how'd you get ice
in that plant I don't know
I'm gonna take this
thank you that's all the ice yeah
okay we're good oh my God I stuck on
this ice cream and I'm already cold as
[ __ ] Nick definitely has the best shirt
for this or let's trip [ __ ] new drops
coming soon hopefully oh my God where's
my Pepsi it's in there oh I got scared
grabbed it out oh my God where's my
towel I'm gonna like have to get naked
right away what no like I can't stay
with like I think what's worse than
being submerged under cold water is
having this like like when you get like
the worst part about going in a pool is
when you get back out and your bathing
suit is touching your body wet like I'm
gonna have to get naked right away maybe
I don't want to go first on I have to
pretend that I'm a can of Pepsi
are you ready come on get in there lick
my fingertips ice cold like get in there
right now
oh my [ __ ] God it's like worse than
like when you go to the beach in the
winter
I have to pee actually I just realize
when I get it I have to pee right away
so you go pee now okay you have to go
with the flamingo technique first one
foot
oh Chris this is Nick get my timer ready
or take the camera this is gonna be
worse for you because yeah you just
gotta send it bro okay
is it that cold
[Laughter]
at all whatsoever it is
actually really concerning how cold it
is
get out it like it hurts
plunges everything and it attempt to
unleash the Superhuman version myself
fear and anxiety
all of the benefits from a cold punching
I believe self-discipline equals
self-respect which is why all right
self-dism self-respect get in there I
feel like Jack I respect myself so I
need to get in there and show myself
who's boss yes I feel like Jack and the
rose right now where the Titanic was no
joke I'm if I okay if I step foot in
this time I'm sending Neck Deep go in
get in there so cool get in there I feel
like I shouldn't do it those thoughts
made it worse yeah actually by far the
second my talk was out of here yeah I
kind of want to do a shirtless too I
don't really sure it was on video so I
don't know aren't we all
let me go here we go
to the timer
get in there
[Laughter]
foreign
this is pretty much
that's all you're doing oh my God now
you've set yourself up when you have to
actually do it you're not gonna be able
that was genuinely like the worst 10
seconds of my whole life
it's like Spiderman
something is self-respect right
self-respect
thank you
you're insane
I'm like like I'm frozen in here I can't
I just like literally I feel like I feel
like it's the Titanic no I feel like
when you're walking on like ice and you
get knocked down like into the thing
like when you're on the shallow River
what it's gonna not making sense this is
crazy
get in there come on do you feel how
numb you are yeah it is crazy that's
your whole body it is crazy but I also
feel like once you're out you're fine I
literally couldn't breathe like I am
like gonna I am like when I was fully in
there I couldn't exhale like I was like
I know I was joking but that was a Pepsi
though
the [ __ ] you saying you I did it six
times you didn't do it enough my ass is
still wet like okay you once you beat
waste an olive neck like it'll be a
challenge no if I do I'm going in once
and I'm getting out okay do it then
that's the only girl uh no no get in
there Nick let me feel it hold on
no it's cold buddy I can do it
that's insane your feet in there I think
if my feet stay in here long enough then
I can just get numb enough to just go in
yeah oh you're doing it the crazy
technique yeah this is psychotic that's
what I did see you feel your knots
get in there sit
Matt go oh my God I'm so proud of you
yes yes
sink sink go go go get in oh my God is
that what I look like yeah weaker oh I
can't look like that amateur I have to
go fully
okay you guys are cleaning my floor I'm
not holy [ __ ] how cold are you I like
can't feel my feet yeah that's what I'm
saying hold on give me my towel please
I'm sand I should have just done it then
that's what I'm saying how am I gonna do
this just plop it it's all legit let go
of all your limbs at the same time Nick
you got this bruh you're just strong but
I can tell I'm worried I'm just you got
this I'm just scared that I'm gonna have
to be hospitalized why bro oh my God
that's devious
his toes grab that
[Applause]
no you just gotta dry your feet and then
you're good the socks are the worst you
got to just dip right in
oh he's an animal oh he's thinking
devious right now
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah lock those knees get
those done yes Matt if your knees go
down you're a winner you're an absolute
champ yes
oh
you win that's the winner right now
Matt's the winner
[Laughter]
okay hold on I have a new discovery okay
what's your Discovery [ __ ] I guess
what's your Discovery okay this it
sounds crazy
the reason why I just had to get out is
because you're you feel so cold and
brittle that when the ice is like
touching you like it like it might it
like hit my my knee and it just felt
like it was like a rock being throat
like it feels so like like the like the
ice cubes literally feel like rocks like
bullets yeah literally like bullets
because you're just so brittle oh my God
that was the worst I live once and you
can tell everyone
I think we should start with like cold
showers I have really dry skin so this
is probably bad for me hold on it's
probably better for you I think can we
do a part two of this video after we
like train yes for a little bit all
right my heart is like racing yeah I was
nervous as [ __ ]
you guys it's you're correct though like
if I went in there fully like ass naked
it would be way easier right I agree I
didn't close this whole thing come on
you got this Nick stop doing that just
jump in dude you haven't even put like
your knees in like that's [ __ ] [ __ ] bro
come on it's the same temperature every
time hold on good observation Matt
oh
take my shirt off in like the cold part
right here hitting my back just [ __ ]
[ __ ] me up
Matt what's up
come on Nick you got this [ __ ]
try it
oh man yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
oh my God
oh my God oh my what is going on what is
going on I was just slipped oh my God oh
my God oh my God
do you feel cold yeah yeah bro that was
Championship right there now it was
really bad like
you're like your character traits and
just you just disappeared yeah but I
thought Nick's life just like like no
personality no literally I thought
called punching Chris like oh let's do
it for a video I was like okay easy bro
I like I don't even remember what just
happened like my my adrenaline was
rushing so much I don't remember doing
that I was just in there
no I'm done you went in there the least
that's not true bro take this then okay
wow that was like what I did
yes wow Chris
good job buddy good job good job good
job
good job bud that was good
it's not bad now
I have to get used to it
I'm telling you if there was no ice
cubes
dude when I went in I was so in there
that I was under the ice that's what was
helpful as [ __ ] like I was just under
the ice
oh my God I genuinely feel like I just
feel like
stop under the water like that
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you missed me and all the things