all right guys as you
know me Matt and Nick one of our most
unhealthy habits is eating gross fast
food and going out to dinners and we
spend a lot of money out that I want to
start saving I want to be more smart for
my health and for my wallet but we're
going to go to the grocery store buy
some ingredients and then today I'm
going to be the head chef and Nick and
Matt are going to be my assistant Chef
so we're going to cook some [ __ ] real
food I don't know if I [ __ ] with the
term assistant Chef you better take
charge all right let's go where is the
meat like can I get some meat around
here that was so loud do you want to
make your own no I need yeah I need
ground beef we don't have like a Patty
Maker though you need like a cook cut I
got these right here that's all I need
those M let's still beef 100% pure this
is 80% lean wait that's not enough Bean
juicy on me I think this is good I don't
think it is Nick to make it's a pound of
meat if this is all one Burger that's a
pound of meat you're eating how much is
a how much is a regular burger at fud
Ruckers I used to eat the one3 burer
that a qu pound these are these are
patties let's see how much one3 is not a
quarter dog these beef patties o we're
each eating a third of a pound of beef
we're eating one/ thir
Burgers yeah that's what we' be eating I
don't want that one this one looks way
fresher more ready to go kid spanking
his me m mad
he dropped I dropped the meat wait no I
want sesame seed buns what do you like
sesame seeds I love sesame seeds like
this is kind of more the vibe I'm going
but that's Kroger Brand I want some like
fancy name brand [ __ ] not Kroger
lit I love
cheese
iass I
hate Baby Swiss okay that's Chris that's
a good nickname for Chris Swiss I kind
of [ __ ] with that a lot let's get it you
don't need anything else no unless do
you want like onions or anything
unrelated but I really want a box of
chocolates dude ew those are stink the
big sour touch kids are so good no I
need I need eggs we have eggs at home
I'm getting these do we have eggs at
home go [ __ ] this oneberry
cream I'm being healthy now is that what
Gatorade
water is that just water what's making
you different than all the rest of them
extra electrolytes maybe I don't buy
that at all that's a crazy product like
I can't believe my eyes when I just saw
that that was a little insane all right
I love these types of sprinkles the
little Jamies yeah put them back I need
this no you don't put it
back put it back there we go tell them
we'll see them at home see you at home
all right I'm totally going to Freestyle
this sh by the way okay I have like no
game plan I have no recipe this is all
straight from my head and all knowledge
I literally searched up earlier I said
how to make a good burger the first step
looked way too complicated for me I said
[ __ ] it I'm going to just do it my way
all right let's do it and I'm hungry so
I hope this pays off I'm a little scared
of your way I really I really hope
something's open get me my eggs you over
there give me my eggs and you
you're on eggs you're on spices get
going get a good bowl and get okay hold
on what spices and how many eggs that's
what I was going say anything You' put
on a burger I don't know I don't know
figure it out I don't know get out of my
kitchen then you get get away from me
get the spices all right fine get a bowl
and a spoon and like a stop going like
this stop pressure like a tablespoon
okay it's Nick do we have an exension
cord no [ __ ] can you
move I got a bowl okay it looks good how
are we going to record cooking on this I
don't know I don't know what the [ __ ] he
give me a mixing bowl stop lose your
[ __ ] attitude please get my patties
what are you saying get your patties
your patties aren't made yet or get my
buns and I gave Matt that job on purpose
to get your buns
yep guys are we serious this doesn't
seem seem too smart it doesn't we have
look at this is how we have the thing
plugged in give me a spatula actually
you need to say please and thank you get
your mother did not raise you get it
where are your manners please a head
shap doesn't have time for manners he
has time for Perfection I'll thank you
at the end of the night get my spatula
get my spatula I'm looking for a wow you
think you're talking yeah you feel tough
and
major I listen to you I'll thank you
guys once I have a good Creation in
front of my eyes going into your mouth
and now get my [ __ ] what I I'm dead ass I
have literally zero clue I've never
cooked in my life like why why are you
like the whole are you [ __ ]
kidding the whole dinner almost just are
you [ __ ] kidding I got the meat all
over me is this like gauze for the meat
e wa it stop W wo double
360 our beef is going to fall yeah a b
it
can I break that egg into this nope I'm
tired Chef doesn't care keep doing
it you have to like fro the
egg right till it's fluffy oh I'm going
to sneeze all right we'll do a little
bit of way more do some garlic powder in
there ow what hurt my finger locked
we'll do some onion powder a little bit
of that right more more more more onion
I love a good onion you don't understand
garlic no listen to sh you need more of
all I feel like I'm really annoying the
viewers with this clicking you know what
I mean I'm like nothing's when he was
banging this meat see we have a pound of
meat that's not a lot What in in the
meat world we have a pound you're really
going to do one little Spoonful at a
time I am like you couldn't dump half in
we're going to do five Scoops with
egg it's only one egg it's not that much
is a thing Chris you can always add more
egg you can't always take egg out you
just put so much egg in there mix it
up get in there with your hands if you
don't get it I'm not doing that yes you
are ever see it's bonding it already I
can see it is this what y'all
cheeseburgers lit looks like but
Plankton is this what your meat looks
like we should we add more get off me
listen the head chef you actually get
out of me get out of my [ __ ] kitchen
can sprinkle it around there you go hey
hey hey
hey I don't know something told me I
should have done
this what something told me I should
have done this after Patty it cuz now
it's like not going to be in Patty form
and it's going to be seasoning it's
[ __ ] fine meat is meat more like
Hell's Kitchen move it all right how
much would you say is one Patty's worth
that's a big patty dude ball it
up make it a ball we should have got a
we should all do it I'll do it I'll do
it swear you go first we should have got
a p if you don't do it I'm throwing this
at your face
so a a handful of meat is so crazy I'm
not doing this first you are I'll do it
after I
swear [ __ ] meatball Chris take that's
perfect that's actually perfect this is
a this is going to be like a whole
cheese I don't know what's going on take
this okay ball it up and we're going to
flatten it soon this is still too much
no I don't know Matt no that looks
perfect don't add more I just said oh
just don't you want to jugle the
meatballs yeah Nick ready wait am I thr
it yeah throw it up I'll stand right
here don't let them fall Ready kind
sticky I know whatever we'll try we'll
try yeah set
go hold on meatballs
okay throw in I'll catch it no one's
going to know what this is yes nice work
guys give me a that's hot yeah it's on
oh that's hot level five like you said
look all right wait listen wait what if
our smoke detector goes off it might
ready if our smoke detector goes that
was kind of insane insane wait I'm
really scared guys sorry that you hear
like this vent and stuff we just are
prepping in case our smoke alarm goes
off so we have it already smells like
it's going to go off well it smells like
a [ __ ] should we try we have to cook
we go to the stove a light buttering all
right all right all right all right all
right all right ready we're going to
just dive in go for
it it's doing nothing awesome yeah we
should have heard a Sizzle cheese under
the bun is that what we're doing those
are just their placeholders right now
pleas go here though it's not cooking
you have to put that the cheese on the
the Patty when
you it is cooking nice should I go to
level four doesn't look good um that's
level five that's level five doesn't
matter fine yeah be careful just splash
myself with meat
juice dude this is unreal all right 5
minutes on each
side 5 minutes what do you want set a
timer for a minute 30 come on set a
timer for a minute and 30
seconds stop I think you should get the
others on there let pop his Freezeria
this [ __ ] dude no no no no no we have to
just like cook one see how we
did then we cook the rest
turn up you're fine you're fine if the
smoke alarm goes off it doesn't let me
take a photo of you too smells pretty
good oh it smells
delicious oh with
that a little more then we're
done so much smoke it's
fine
hey who get off get off the SP spatula
bam should we add a little
heat guys oh my God this is the
Patty beef cheese bun that's all we like
as the sternula triplets sometimes I'll
throw onions in there no you won't yeah
I will occasionally but look at that
move over other side now that is a nice
burger come over here let's eat it the
cheese is a little floppy ooh come on oh
my God is it good it's so good is it
good try
it I yes I would rather eat this than
something at like that at like name a
burger place better chis we got a
fan what the it's
smoking that was good that's really good
this is
[Applause]
unbelievable this is this is actually
crazy that we're this excited over
burgers in our own
home this a mon this is a Monumental
step for the sto triplets guys we do
need to start cooking so bad I got it n
yeah I got it don't wor enjoy your
burger guys I have like chills chills is
when I ate it all the flavor that like
just hit me up once I was so close to
dancing I'm so confident I thr that this
Burg on too oh you're the man what was
that your foot oh Sho my shoe squeaked I
thought it was a smoke alarm Matt if you
stop inning you got to C me in if you
stop out me we're
good let me let this one cook oh my God
you're taking it a little too far dad
cooked two strips of bacon and the
amount of [ __ ] wind I was getting was
crazy or I mean smoke alarm what am I
saying they look good though get like me
I just cooked a [ __ ] delicious hold
on is that good I don't know
this one's falling apart that's okay
who's going to hire you I feel like this
is like a individually own what is that
it's a cheeseburger oh you just burnt me
it's cuz you're asking stupid questions
a you're fine I'm talking about the tray
whatever that is we should have used way
more frequently the Ste it yeah that's
just fire you look good with the the
wind in your air while you thank you
thank
you you're telling me to do the same
[ __ ] one that one's already in flavor to
over that we're good oh I like
that oh on the grill the grill first
time watch out watch out first time
cheese on the gr moment
here that one's it's thick though it's
thick that one that was a little thick
yeah but that can be a little medium
rare a little thick old
Patty
ooh knock it off stop playing with Nick
all right watch out let me let me step
into that last Burger boom yeah thank
you chef of course
kiss can you [ __ ] off you're getting me
burnt you're getting me house full of
smoke no I'm not you're being dramatic
yeah Matt likes it is it good Matt mm
better than the
first better than the first yeah I'm the
king Chef though like it's crazy to me
that you're freaking out with this cuz
the smoke detector has yet to go off
this guy's the burger K that burger is
going to split in half cuz you're
putting way too much pressure on it who
you talking to I I can already see it
ripping I don't care I can't
do Nick you're talking to the Burger
King right he wishes he was the Burger
[Music]
King kid saved the worst for last
Jesus I think the best two burgers were
the two that were made in the middle I
agree you didn't even eat this one yet
well I don't even have to overall this
cooking at home experience as Chris as
the chef has been a 10 out of 10 I'd say
Oh you mean it I do it was fun the food
tastes good amazing
and sorry sorry I don't know it was just
really fun and it worked and I can see
us doing this again so oh that burger
was phenomenal if there's one thing I'm
confident in cooking it's a burger so
it's a burger my kids are going to eat
this one day be like well Dad you're
really good at cooking I'm say yes I
am what yeah anyway you're planing on
your voice getting that deep no that's
like when I'm
70 anyway if you guys want to see me and
Nick pick a recipe and be the head chefs
and boss the other two around let us
know in the comments and get this video
to 25,000 likes 25,000 get this [ __ ] to
80,000 I don't I hate to say I'm playing
around I hate to say it cuz like the way
Chrismas acting but I don't think it's
going to be I think it's going to be
really hard to top this burger oh anyway
thank you guys so much for joining this
Friday video or what date is it
Wednesday wnes we don't know what date
this is going to get posted Wednesday it
could be Friday we don't know what date
this is going to get posted on depending
on our new lenient schedule but who
knows um thank you guys so much for
joining us we hope this taught you how
to make a burger at home to enjoy yeah
if you want a really good burger
literally just do exactly what we did it
was delicious peace out bye love you
guys
[Music]