foreign
Nick breeds like an orangutan oh it
seems very low
is it low low Schmo whoa wow he's on the
car oh wow he thick though
this is gonna be the most
what man is he in it
is Nick in it I think that should be all
right
I really can't really tell that was my
arm you [ __ ] and if I broke your arm
I can't really talk I can't like go like
knuckle sandwich you know what I mean no
not no we're good you both did that
means why it's crazy
snap is femur I kind of like filming
videos in this parking lot because it's
like someday I let you in whoa we should
start a jazz quartet oh is that four
people I don't know I think a quartet is
whatever it is I want to be a part of it
eat sleep breathe jazz music Matt would
have like the um saxophone he'd be like
leaning into it yeah and you get a
saxophone solo yeah for sure
I need like lean like and like Lean
Forward just just let the saxophone take
him over yes whatever I'd play the tuba
all right guys welcome back to another
video we do not have a topic today
everyone give me an x no
experience some fun fun things that
we're just gonna share about and curated
our own opinions on random topics that I
have written down on my phone and we're
gonna loudly vocalize and express our
thoughts because we are the stromboliage
strombolios what I've been laughing at
that for days what's the origin from
because you guys keep saying I saw a
tick tock of some girl who like whose
father unironically calls us like the
storm
Rollies oh okay yeah like he's just like
oh you watch those [ __ ] strombolis
that sounded like the intro of
Macklemore what what they're shopping
okay do not put that like don't get that
all over the car correct now let me tell
you guys something funny about what
Chris is eating right now so this is
apple slices with caramel and it [ __ ]
belongs to me I saw it in the fridge and
couldn't help myself he just had to he
just got taken over if that spells I'm
knocking you what a gross thing to eat
in the car I would never bring these in
the car to eat in front of the public
like just dip apples and caramels like
such a thing I've noticed over the years
Chris has been getting worse and worse
at like just chewing so loud and
drinking I don't drink loud yeah yes you
do you just make so much gulp you go
you just make so much noise as you like
eat [ __ ] one of my least favorite things
ever that we experienced like two years
ago hold on I can hear him chewing the
same level of volume as you talking Nick
I'll [ __ ] kill you too quiet okay
we're gonna play a game it's the quiet
game but you're chewing do you not hear
it as like a person are you not
self-aware of it at all
like genuine question
oh that was so cool okay every time I
can't do it please stop you sound like a
camel Nick I'll [ __ ] stop cover my
mouth again with Your Filthy Hands I can
literally smell that have you stop being
an alpaca I will you're like you spit
he's like an elephant your hands stinks
llama put some lotion on them you're
literally like an elephant and Carnival
peanuts that's what you sound like
stop disgust anyways it was when people
like wave you on in like the car or like
on the street and it's like you're doing
it anyway like if I'm gonna cross the
street and I'm halfway through the
street in the line of fire to the car
that could hit me and the driver is like
this
I need your permission yeah King of the
Road and I'm already doing it you
[ __ ] [ __ ] I don't know you know this
I don't know I don't know when you're
like driving and Matt's like gonna move
the car anyway and everyone's like oh oh
it's like put
regardless of what you do here I'm going
to it's like when you're about to do the
dishes and Mom's like do the dishes yeah
never doing them yeah well you don't do
them you don't do things to help oh
actually me and Matt were talking about
it today yeah literally laundry I was
actually talking about how I'm gonna
stop doing your laundry because the
whole thing when we moved in was like
Nick does the dishes and you take out
the trash but I do the [ __ ] laundry I
clean the house Nick does the dishes
that happen occasionally and you don't
do anything involving cleaning the house
and when it comes to trash you just
leave it sitting there and when it comes
to eating you chew like a [ __ ] camel
so you guys gotta just hot camel or
alpaca because
I think both are fine oh my God it's
actually like sickening
idiots what about a child a [ __ ] apple
sauce it's like a baby with no teeth
eating applesauce there's no apples
there's no applesauce
your gums are like this you're
ridiculous this is your mouth your lips
are flapping together next thing I want
to talk about view grab get ready with
me these are like my favorite things
ever like they push the headband up so
they can do their makeup well they're
gonna like tell you a story but it's
always like the crazy there's like a
story time or get ready with me and
they're like
get right with me to commit arson and
then they like put their hair up or
they're like get ready with me for and
they just say like the most outrageously
outlandish things that you say favorite
the whole story time it's like the time
my mom found out her third cousin was
her grandfather and that they put their
hair up or something like that
the time I found out my sister my
girlfriend was actually my sister and
they're like I love those the time I
just like the Disney Channel yes the
timeline
yeah those are all staged they weren't
all staged they were real stories with
actors as kids yes [ __ ] anyway what
Nick was saying I'll keep it on the
topic here I saw one and it was like get
ready for with me to break up with my
boyfriend and the whole talk was like
her explaining that she like found out
that he's that he was cheating on her
headband that's the thing
get ready with me for and they just say
the craziest thing get ready I'm like oh
the craziest thing was one of them I saw
and it was like it was like get ready
with me break up with my boyfriend and
she does the thing and she's like
talking about it but she's like in the
middle of talking she's like so yeah I
found out that he texted my best friend
blah blah and like she's starting to
tell the story but then in the middle of
telling the story she was oh I kind of
[ __ ] up my eyeliner a little bit and
she brings it back to like yes
oh my gosh story again y'all are weird
take your cruise next one Nick what's
the next one oh no that's why I said if
you [ __ ] ever hit me again I'm Gonna
Knock your [ __ ] teeth out literally
that's why I was saying I was
comfortable oh my God I just bit my lip
[ __ ] dumb well don't [ __ ] hit my
mouth [ __ ] face I'm gonna just start
sitting here in the videos it's like
what you did wasn't funny what you did
wasn't funny either oh my God no like
I'm bleeding right Chris what did you do
Matt get out of here
oh God I'll just never be excited to
tell you anything again because I know
that now it leads to perfusion blood
Nick in my mouth blood blood blood in my
mouth but I just wanted the blood then
I'll touch you this is all right made
you bleed you're not sorry about it yes
I am sorry I made you I want to taste my
own blood that means that means I'm
doing something right
Nick stay leaning closer I'm excited to
talk about something that happens to my
mouth filled with my own blood
it means I have passion I don't care
just stop hitting my arm
you did something
to the extra mile you know what I mean
yeah so if I steal like a snack of yours
yeah you stole my snack oh I'm gonna
kill you
how about that for even like getting
even you're not even be you're not even
close to even you push things too far I
now have to hit you like a billion more
times to get even yeah
it's a strong bully it's a stromboli
trickling first during car video stop
this guy the other day made me laugh I
was walking by him I forget where I was
but he went to say um like you guys hold
on purple that many like like you know
something
um like that like it's um
he said arm like orm like then that's
how he said it no he was just like
literally was just like
um and it sounded so weird to me that I
wrote it down no
and then we're out of valet the other
night
and some guy was over here like across
the street like dirty like disgusting
who are you talking to you're looking on
the street yeah okay we'll figure it out
who looks in the um
I don't want to be even be like Nick
stop the valet was across the street and
then we're right here and there was a
guy right behind us and the guy across
the street he goes he said we're trying
to find our driver like what we can't
find him whatever and then the guy
behind me has like a joke to his friend
mumbles he goes your driver's dead
yeah it was so funny I thought it was
hilarious that's kind of a lot because
it's some [ __ ] us three would do like
the guy was like I can't find my driver
like where is he and the guy goes
from like across the street but like to
his friend I don't think any he thought
anyone heard him but I did it made me
laugh I also heard a group of people
with the same situation and they were
like one of their friends asked him and
they're like hey what are you guys doing
and he said
it's Thursdays
Thursdays and then he he after he said
he goes oh my God that rhymed
it doesn't
I was like in shock and then he was like
happy that it rhymed and I was like oh
boy oh my God that's insane I forgot
when we were little ones when we were
getting Trevor I asked my friends I have
my friend where's he going with this
Thursday I asked my friend what I should
name Trevor and they go Crystal it's
like a really pretty name I didn't know
it was a drug because I was really young
so I went up to Mom and I was like I
think we should name him Crystal
that's what I said to Mom that's good I
told Mom we should name Trevor Kristen I
didn't have a single name idea for that
dog yeah I agree he would have had no
name in my plans oh my god this is my
biggest pet peeve when people request an
apology when they're like I would like
you to apologize to me for this oh or be
like I think that you should apologize
go [ __ ] yourself first never yeah never
will I ever apologize to someone if they
blatantly ask for it that's crazy you
can't you can't suggest someone to
apologize to you I could go out to Matt
and be like bro you should say sorry to
like whoever yeah you know what I mean
like as a friend but if you request a
personal apology then you need to well
the whole point of an apology is to like
this is to solve is to solve a solution
and like realize you're correct ability
to being wrong but if somebody has to
tell you that you have to apologize for
something that's wrong you didn't learn
your lesson oh I'm sure you would
bit
I'd like you to apologize I'm sure you
will I guarantee you I'm sure you would
I almost put this on Tick Tock instead
of saying it to you guys and I don't
remember what I said but it's in my
drafts and that's what gave me this
thought I was like I'll save it for a
car video
[Laughter]
or something you know what I don't know
what I'm saying it's just crazy I'm sure
you would
[Laughter]
I'd like you to apologize I guarantee I
guarantee you're not the only you want
to know something that I witnessed the
other day and it's just like it's
getting old and like if it's time to
figure out for people across the board
let's hear it any type of couple
arguing or screaming about something in
real life go to someone's apartment and
go home go to the car duke it out
somewhere else or just take the separate
walk away from each other yeah
I think screaming at each other in front
of restaurants and stuff like that is
getting a little bit whoa
where can I get my hands on that that
was crazy that soda was big maybe it's
Chevron oh my God I need to go there
really bad the suit had a soda this big
that was like my dream that was never
got a large that was insane it's okay
it's okay it's okay but just see it's
just passion yeah fine do you ever get
an A large drink from Wendy's no oh my
God they're big it's large big the other
day the guys like at the we went to the
movies and the guy y'all get what I'm
saying though with the old couple
arguing things yeah figure it out for
sure
I actually don't I can't think about it
too much you should all start an
argument out of some building one day
okay
you're nothing go home yeah like that
like a venue like a party to do this I
was about to say it Knuckles wait don't
mess my phone I want to get it crazy my
question is what was I saying no one
cares no one knows [ __ ] oh the movie
theater large the other day we're at the
movies and the guy's like hey we have no
free refills I'm like the movie theater
is the last place I'm ever getting a
free read yeah like you're good like
everywhere else I get refills but the
movie theater it's like bro
it was like I think it was KFC Taco Bell
they had a collab like one of those
collab why are you saying like that cold
lab at a cold lab next stop you already
made me bleed don't touch me again
the KFC place they had the chicken place
they had a chicken jug drink called the
Chug jug or not the Chug jug the the
[ __ ] what was it called no no it was
called the gummy no I'm getting confused
the gulp jug gulp jug it was called the
gulp jug or something it was like it was
a guzz bucket the gun
the KFC Gus bucket search it up it
literally was the chicken thing but
filled with soda in a big straw like a
big straw what's it called the gun it
was called the guzz bucket I know I
didn't make that up I I like it that's
just not exist no [ __ ] way it doesn't
exist because I've ordered one I
literally ordered a guzz bucket and they
didn't bring it to the house thousands
that they brought foreign
it's not a Mandela effect because I know
I've literally added a guzz bucket to my
cart like actually yeah how did you all
know the name I remember it you know
what I mean if it was fake y'all
wouldn't know the name it was literally
called she shared a clip a tick of tick
tock to her Pepsi bucket and we're super
[ __ ] excuse me as proof saying my mom
my mom went to KFC today and I thought
the bucket of Pepsi was a typo well they
weren't [ __ ] kidding she said showing
off the plastic pouch adding this is the
most American [ __ ] I've ever seen
the rest in peace of God's bucket I
don't think there's a fly on the window
see you later
[ __ ] it
yeah I ordered one once door Dash and
wanted it really bad and they didn't
bring it they just brought like four
sodas like cups like the hardest Pokemon
in that correct the whole point was I
wanted to guzz bucket like I wanted to
guzzle down the guzz bucket
I don't like that word because
not for me nope I'm good
never want to hear it again
very comfortable with the lack of the
word guzz in my vocabulary to this day
very comfortable with that feeling it
does for sure
guzzling guzzing no no that's my okay
dude does anyone have anything with
substance I don't think I got anything
else something more heartwarming than a
guzz bucket oh my God the other day we
were at like this event thing and there
was like alcohol being served and this
kid goes up to he goes what's that bro
and I had like one of those liquid death
things that like looks like beer but
it's not like it's just a can of water
and I go no it's just a water like I'm
not drinking anything whatever because
he asked what I was drinking he thought
it was like a beer and I was like oh
it's just water he's like what that's
not beer and I go no it's just water and
he goes what do you do like what do you
mean what do I do yeah I said YouTube
no I asked him what do you mean what do
I do like what do you do and I go I'm a
YouTuber and he goes no like for fun
like he couldn't believe it he couldn't
believe that I wasn't having fun because
I had water but I thought it was
hilarious the way he worded it yeah
bud yeah just know you're in my thoughts
and my prayers yep same with the other
girl there poor girl yeah she goes she
goes where are you guys from
the East Coast Boston Massachusetts oh
I'd love to go but I'm scared of icicles
genuine quote
I'm scared of icicles I literally
laughed in her face and I said trust me
girl icicles are the last thing you need
to worry about ask Chris I felt bad
after I had said it because I was like
wow we like it came across more rude
when I like first opened my mouth but I
genuinely laughed at her because she was
like
the only thing preventing her from going
to the east coast was icicles I said
girl you're good how many how many
icicle related injuries are there every
year Google it dude like what he
accesses he asked us that statistic
realistically thinking how many oh my
God I have a mosquito bite on my ankle
like right in the pit of it you know
what I mean like to the left of your
ankle and it like icicle 15 Americans 15
die to an icicle 15 Americans die from
it has to be stronger accidents every
year like there's no way you just get
hit by one and you're dying you know
what I mean but we've also idiots throw
them at each other it says in Russia
about 100 such deaths are reported
annually
Russia the guy I'm sorry to hit you no
you're good I think that we should tell
that girl oh don't worry about the East
Coast like you're fine but if you are
scared of icicles you go to Russia
instead I like the death rates higher
from Isis okay dude I thought you were
gonna talk at first one time I was wow
this guy was one of the icicle victims
no he died yep oh my god well well well
I can't believe that leaves just fall
and that's what we went with the fall is
literally called The Fall because leaves
fall like that's real
like so I'm gonna make you bleed wow
what the name is to is thou to originate
in the phase the fall of the leave in
reference to the time of year where
what dude am I right or wrong yeah
you're reading me a passage you're right
what code is this
all right guys that's been this week
this week's Friday video
next week on Friday and another video on
Wednesday put that hit that subscribe
button right down below hit that
notification Bell turn the notifications
on and then after that follow each and
everything one of us on Instagram
triplets for Photoshop every single time
the video comes out on Friday we love
you signing off stay strong bully stay
Stromboli for the AC on it's as hot as a
[ __ ]
[Music]
for my brothers