we're good I almost locked you out
forever on purpose get out of the
car hey guys what is up it's the stern
triplets here back for another Friday
car video um and real quick we just want
to say that our youts are still
available for another 7 days then they
won't be coming back and it is a
pre-order so make sure you get your
order in right now before they go away
for good once again they're limited
edition so if you do not buy the you's
within the next 7 days they will never
ever be available again the link is on
the screen and it's the first link in
our description down below so go check
out this the last week to get it last
week last week to get it limited edition
o we all have all black on tonight we
look very like ninjas
mysterious Mage in my neck got a
crickety old neck I think need a haircut
I think that we should do we should do
everything self beneficial at the same
time like a massage a chiropractor and a
haircut say I would love to go to a
chiropractor I really think that a video
of Nick getting cracked where they like
put the mic on his spine and then they
go breathe in and then they go like that
would be like that's the one thing I've
actually thought about I'm like I I
think out of all the like embarrassing
content of me out on the internet that's
something I think where I'm going to
draw the line really chiropracting if I
go to a chiropractor it will probably be
a personal Endeavor that will not be
documented no we should do it and get
the chiropractor to come to our house
and set up everything in our living room
and then just like Vlog a whole if we
could get a licensed chiropractor in our
home I'd do it okay today we don't have
any topics but filming a car video
without a topic is like finding the
dusty book what does that mean like you
know sometimes you see the book you
shake off the dust and it's always like
the one you need you know in the movies
when they're like what do you know about
Dusty books what do you know about
reading what I'm saying is like do you
know when the videos or like in the in
the Disney [ __ ] like whenever they find
the book that they like need to like
solve the problem that's occurring it's
always like Dusty and like hasn't been
touched for years okay that's what
filming a car video with no topic feels
like it's like get I don't get the
corespondence of one another well just
like we need to get that Dusty book dude
I hate when people are driving around on
Teslas cuz it literally sounds like a
UFO of D no I'll be my I'll be like I'll
be in like I don't even know say it your
room that's what you're going to say
just say your bedroom right like say
bedroom but I also say like a restaurant
like I could like multiple stories up in
a building I will always hear a Tesla
it's not a Tesla it's an electric car
it's like all forms of electric vehicles
dude it's obnoxious like I'm just saying
if everyone if everyone on the road gets
an electric vehicle it's going to sound
like aliens are out to get us the whole
day literally they need to lower that
like silence that no I feel I fully
agree I feel like I have to turn around
with like ray gun and shoot whoever's
coming toward me no it's terrible okay
like I feel like it's going to be an
automatic alien battle the second
electric I don't feel like that I don't
feel like that at all well no I'm
obviously being dramatic and emphasizing
the situation thank you it's also like I
would hate to like plug in my car do you
know how many times I'd have to like
you'd forget to plug I was about to say
but you didn't let me finish I you know
how many times you you want to know what
I actually noticed today there there
were four different instances in which I
was talking to instances I love that
word okay well there was four different
five now or six yeah there were four
different instances in which I was
talking to someone or explaining a story
that Chris also knew or also was a part
of and he just took the story right away
from me and said it for himself oh don't
you hate that I do I have to pee really
bad again just started you need to go to
the doctor no I've been drinking a lot
of water I'm staying hydrated I bought a
new water bot today a new water bot oh a
new water bottle new water bot I don't
talk like that that's what you say like
you said water your words I didn't you
just literally just said water bot
replay it I talk Water Burger your words
are falling off I did not say water bger
you said water I bought a new water B
today like a Kindergarten kid just said
what if you ran into the room with like
if you ran into the room and like just
underwear like held something up you
look just like a kindergarten what cut
that out cut that out cut that out you
don't a little boy like I'm talking you
clearly you like fully could have said
like oh if you ran up and I had my eyes
shut I would have thought you were like
a little kid like that would have been a
very cuz of me like like being a triplet
like I remember being a kid like when I
was showing anyone anything it could
have been like my mom's friend or cousin
or Aunt I'd like run into the room with
like just underwear on and like my
stomach would be out and I hold
something out like that just remun like
such a little kid thing like running
into a room with just like like a little
kid to show off something yeah I think
it's like so cool how much I liked when
I was a kid like I just liked stuff
horse
Galloping am I tripping definitely no
horse what was that sound it was like a
I don't know okay I have something to
say and I wrote I've been we haven't
filmed the car video in a while cuz we
filmed a lot when we were in Boston last
and I've just been storing some things
that have hit my brain in the past like
two weeks that I just want to bring up
and it it may be an unpopular opinion
Chick-fil-A is ass I mean I completely
Chick-fil-A is just ass like every
single time I if you order Chick-fil-A
like like and it gets delivered to you
by the you could live 10 minutes from a
Chick-fil-A at
I I've been saying that for years is
like consistently the most ass food I've
ever had in my life I've been saying
that for so long out of all the fast
foods Chick-fil-A It Takes the Cake
dominates the worst [ __ ] you want
know what the worst actually like cuz
the reason I bring it up and why I
express my the fries that are like the
the bunt of a potato bunt is that a
[ __ ] word I don't know the run the
but end the butt end the butt end the
butt end okay but that's why that's why
I bring it up is cuz Chick-fil-A had so
much hey and like has height I think
it's one of the worst places to eat ever
and
I've I hate a place that like have oh
like we have Chick-fil-A sauce like you
can't get that anywhere else and it like
tries to indulge chickf oh you have to
come to us it's like no that's not that
cool I've also been thinking a
lot how how little people really need to
just like speak
yeah dou down on that you're thinking of
me though no a lot of people I look at
and I'm like H you could benefit a lot
from shutting your [ __ ] mouth I agree
I think that's something you should try
and oh like there's some people that
like talk a lot and I love that they
talk I love listening to people but
there's some people wait what no you
don't no there are some people that like
tell me stories like oh I love listening
to you like genuinely there's people out
there that talk and I'm like I will
listen I could sit with you for 24 hours
you could talk to me all day yeah and
then there's some there's also sometimes
like I'll be outside and I'll see
someone like smile oh you could never
speak again this is also like this is
there's like I have like five people
like that oh for sure but I also have
like this weird low I have this weird
like can I speak I have this weird like
creepy little like it's not creepy but
it like sounds creepy if I describe it
but it's favorite word it's one of those
Tendencies creepy like what are you two
okay you just said water bottle so let
him see I didn't I did not say
was trying to tell stop talking right
right but it it sounds like [ __ ]
bizarre but when there's people out in
public and they like are smiling and it
looks like they're having a good time I
just like oh my God it it tears it warms
your heart little makes me like I just
love seeing people smile like doing
stuff yeah like if someone I saw some
lady we went out to eat today and she
was like a literally and it sounds like
I'm a stalker psychopath like fully
across the restaurant and she was like
sitting with her whole family just
smiling eating food and I'm like I hope
that she's having the best day ever yeah
see I don't think that's creepy at all
who's off I was going to say something
but then Nick fully interrupted me you
all you've done is you you have to not
be mad when you get interrupted when you
interrupt people to say stupid R number
one number one yes no I was going to say
something but one of you guys like
screwed do you have to keep saying I'm
going to say something or what am I
going to
say so much about I have so much on my
mind that like the new thought always
just knocks out the old one but it
doesn't go far it just like bumps it
back in the the brain like adding to a
que yes like I have like a cue of
thoughts at all time and then it's
either like it just goes blank like the
motherboard overloads and then it's just
like whoop and then I just so this is
why you accidentally let out words like
water bottle correct cuz then it's just
like white like nothing and then do you
know like how you view a computer how
it's like all those green tabs with the
funky words like think of that as like
my thoughts and it's just like piling on
and I have a ton of tabs like loading in
and then I like click one and then I
accidentally hit escape and like
everything closed like that's how my
brain is so that's why like when I say
things you're always like oh you're
repeating yourself or it's like oh cuz
it's like my brain is gener like a
software like it's like okay thought
thought thought thought new thought I
boom on the page but then I exit out and
then I minimize and it's down here and
then I full screen it goes in between
these two tabs but it's just like my
brain is full and then I forget a lot
I'm going to end this with I think I
need ADHD or something I'm going to end
it with one question do you have
anything to say right now do you know I
know what happened to me the other day
yeah this story this is what I have to
say I was writing something down and I
started like a list and I like formatted
the list of like like on the top it was
like formatted the list no I needed to
make a list of like things to do or
something I don't know what it was like
it was either a list of like things I
needed to buy or to do like I forget
what it is car no problem [ __ ]
problem I wrote down the label like and
I was like okay like list like Chris
don't forget this whatever and then I
put number one and by the time I put the
first thing on the list I forgot what
the list was about I was like wait what
am I you don't write like a you don't
write like a like a letter topic that's
what I'm telling you I wrote the header
then forgot the the the liner but
wouldn't the header tell you what what
need no it was like it was like Chris
don't forget this list pack back pack
back home and then I put the one cuz I
was going to bring the list home and I
put one and I was like is that all you
had to do is pack back is this the list
that no it was pack the list itself back
home like I wrote that on the paper I
said like bring this list home
one all you wrote on this was water
bottle it says water bottle that's it
ironically enough it say water
bottle okay I don't know I don't
remember guys L my phone oh you want to
know what I was thinking go for it I was
I forget who I was talking to the other
day oh my God okay go ahead sorry I'm
just really hot your tab opened go ahead
I'm really hot and I didn't realize it
until like I you you get to shut the
[ __ ] up as well and that's going to play
into like how you feel do my hair look
and Chris no offense but you were on the
list that I was thinking earlier oh
that's fine of one of the people that
could I don't remember my list so talk a
little less you know move on um Chris
shut up I always think what your life
would be and how it would change if I
never spoke again I think that too
sometimes let's try it okay I was
thinking the other day see the the funny
thing is to me he can't not like it'll
break in 5 minutes yeah you will but I
was I was talking to someone day and I
was like it's crazy that I think that I
will spend more than half of my life in
some type of mode of
transportation whether it's a plane a
car a train um that's not even close to
the truth Nick cuz you you sleep in a a
bed every day so no matter what within a
okay
okay I have to pee I have to pee so bad
please go home please half half is
probably dramatic but I think a solid
third I think think I've traveled more
than I've slept literally I feel like
I'm all obviously not true if you add up
like walk if walking counts I you have
to keep in mind the amount of night 100%
I have you have to keep in amount the
amount of night sleeps that we've gone
on listen if you're asleep in the car I
wasn't done you have to keep in mind our
our career is also this so even
sometimes when we're working we're in
the car L we're not traveling right now
I'm not saying I never said anything
about traveling Nick not sleeping I
never said anything about s either you
guys are like you guys are creating this
this this little S I think if I wake up
I'm walking to the bathroom that's
travel oh my God I said
I get what I I'm offering a different
counterpart I'm doing sleep compared to
travel you're doing travel compared to
life I'm not doing travel at all I'm not
doing travel I'm not doing travel at all
all I'm saying is I am inside a car for
I feel like way more than everybody else
I agree I feel like I often am in a
vehicle I feel 50% of my day is in my
car we should fix that let's start
taking the train I don't want to take
the train either why the [ __ ] would we
take the train can you stop talking I
have a good Wednesday video idea okay
let's finish this Friday one should we
eat it and it's like gross [ __ ] okay
like answer's no done yeah correct like
are we serious thank you everyone I
resigned from today's video yeah okay
you'll be yapping in two seconds no I
won't Matt yes you will you always act
like I'm I know you better than you know
yourself all right yeah and notice how
you've yet to stop talking since you
just said you were ex shout
out I wrote this down as well my list of
thoughts it pisses me off so much when
someone says baking isn't cooking like
baking is baking yes but it is
definitely also cooking like people
would be like oh like if you bake
something like if you bake something
you're also be like I'm cooking later
cuz if you put something in the oven you
put something in the oven if baking is
100% cooking something mixing
ingredients and cooking and heating up
or freezing and then coming out with a
final product you just cooked I don't
care if it's Absol you know what I mean
baking is 100% a form of cooking and if
you disagree you can [ __ ] yourself
correct but it pisses me off I saw
someone literally corrected somethingone
the other day like today what's the
difference between lightning and thunder
lightning is the visuals Thunder's the
sound I was no way yes I really had like
a joke loading up but I just didn't say
it say it no okay you didn't have a joke
I wrote this down too I never once fell
for the fake princesses at the party or
like fake Michael Jackson fake Elvis on
stage like I knew the whole time that's
not that's actually not true I feel like
you were the one of us three that like
lowkey thought that that was Elvis dude
when we went to like our went when we
went to like sixth grade birthday
parties and someone's like oh Snow White
or like Belle birthday parties is
ridiculous it's like why
would like oh so and so's eth birthday
and the princess and Michael Jackson's
there yeah like Tiana and the Frog are
here like no she's not New Orleans I
think the dead giveway I think the dead
giveaway was like that was that's your
uncle that's that's Uncle Pat that's
Uncle Joe that's grandma you know what I
mean are your family members shut your
[ __ ] ringer off oh my God you always
have something to say about my ring
you're screen recording right now you're
no I'm
not oh you're like Matt always has
something to say about my ringer my
[ __ ] phone it's all like the other
day he has dude we'll like casually be
sitting there me and Matt and it'll be
it'll be silent and we'll hear from
Chris's
phone that's fine how annoying that's
not annoying at
all like sh it's cuz I'm a busy guy I'm
not talking about you you're talking
yourself is therefore I'm not shut up
did you just hit me yeah you're growling
at me I get afraid anytime I've ever hit
you it's cuz I think you're about to hit
me I hit you all the time cuz you like
lunge at me or growl or something oh my
God it's so hot in here yeah it's hot I
just like went like this and like
touched my face and I felt sweat like
I'm just like sweating I swear to God
I'm yet to stop talking I'm
melting the other day I dude I messed up
with something a while ago where I went
to shut off like my notifications cuz
they were complaining about like the
sound or something we don't care they
don't care we don't care okay no one
cares about why your ringer would be on
no one anyone give a [ __ ] it's just
annoying me that's all I know it's it's
annoying no one cares all right guys
it's annoying Matt let's
stop that's how you expect everyone to
react about something that does
something to you no oh I'm upset guys
everyone chill oh I'm bothered everyone
piss
off he me you're ready to listen I'll
tell you what you expect as I know when
Belle is pulling up to the six
six-year-old birthday party it's not the
[ __ ] from the movies it's not it's not
and we're at I always think of like the
the people that like run like when like
Hulk walks into the party and all the
kids are like and they start running and
like fleeing everywhere that's the
funniest part to when kids are afraid of
like the dress up characters that is so
that only usually happens I used to be
so scared of Chucky cheese whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa why did you just like Ascend
forward I have no idea what I just
hit I thought you were going to yell at
me for my notification again I thought
it was my phone can we just love on can
our next car video be our X about each
other and we can like start do it I'm
actually down I there's one what there's
a little preview of next week's video
awesome I have random things that remind
me of you guys okay I'll start with Nick
sleeping bag I don't know I just feel
like he'd love it like Nick's the type
to use a sleeping bag in his bed just to
like be all
cozy confirm or deny like I don't even
want to speak when you talk because it's
like obviously wrong why would I put a
sleeping bag in my bed and go to bed
guys you'd like want to be super
Co
yeah I have a couple things that remind
me of Chris wait I have another one of
you yeah go no I have one first one of
your Nick like the whole manual like he
needs the manual to something to like
like if like I ask him for something
he's like I don't know get me the manual
and I have to like bring it to him and
then he's like trying to figure it out
like fix the bugs you know what I mean
like if something has like a bug like a
tech I don't know what you're talking
about so just go to the next one Nick go
ahead that was it you said you had two
more I forgot one of them okay you
minimize the browser go ahead Nick you
are like a fire alarm system right every
single time it starts to speak or talk
it's absolutely loud nonsense usually
[ __ ] Incorrect and just pisses you
off or terrifies you but one time if the
fire happens you'll be so grateful that
I'm there honestly not really what you
would we've had a house fire were you
guys happy for the smoke detectors that
didn't go off well clearly not they
didn't help a thing exactly I can't
believe our house was on fire and the
smoke alarms didn't go off can we like
get like a debrief on that like what
happened how was that I feel like in
that old house that fire alarms were
going off when mom cooked
spaghetti the house was in flames and
the alarms were dead silent yeah that's
exactly what I'm talking about for you
right now Nick oh I just could give you
one of a punch you're not going to punch
me I'm kidding it's a playful joke all
right guys I think we're done with this
week's Friday video we hope you enjoyed
we'll see you guys next week on
Friday let me just say one last thing go
for it it's three words oh God I love
you I love you love you y love I love
you guys so much I love you too I hope
you know it
[Music]
Nick