[Music]
so
sleepy from the island of Madrid we had
a lot of plans but they
all why because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different
be coo bro you're laying on big secrets
right now do you even know that big
secrets yes right under
there look it hold should I tell show
them a little sneak peek of big secrets
that's
bacon take this Nick I'd like to get out
of here we have to show them our merch
no we don't we do look at everybody we
got new merch let's true let's just all
put our favorite piece on and wear in
the Vlog this is my favorite it's a
Massachusetts license plate for those
that don't
know these St them are durable you just
it's not at me I love this one too 5
million us three in the car let's strip
love pink hoodie pink hoodies with gas
this shirt oh my God this is actually
one of my personal favorites show the
back show the back show the back show
the back show the back oh I love the
back we're going yeah new Vlog camera
really yeah but this is the exact same
one I broke the other one how'd you
break it I don't know I didn't even know
you bought a new one yeah here is it my
money what do you mean whose's money you
spending to buy a new camera not telling
anybody it's so hot oh so hot it's so
hot don't edit that
guys I'm so
hot can I have the ear pump I want to
use it I want to see if it's actually
doing anything good do you have a
headache or migraine yeah really bad are
you telling the truth yep okay here you
call me a liar I can't really Vlog you
this the side and then just squeeze and
no no you're doing it all wrong okay
then take the [ __ ] camera this you
hold this up in the front and I'll do it
for you no bro yeah hold it up
Nick put it like as close you can to the
front of the car let me see it not the
thing you o I thought you were going to
kill us so you squeeze get you squeeze
it and release all the air okay go ahead
and then you just shove it in your ear
tell me if I'm going to hurt you that's
so stupid M's driving I don't want to
like ow give me it D Shut up I didn't
even touch your ear you're so ni give me
it it wasn't even touching your ear like
put the clip it wasn't touching your ear
when I yes it was give me the [ __ ]
thing uhuh Nick tell me what it's called
then you can take it the head pump no
you're going to wake up one day and I'm
going to [ __ ] push Q-tips through
your ear loes here you go you're doing
it like an idiot and you're doing it
wrong this is the dumbest thing I've
ever [ __ ] seen well cuz you're an
idiot you're a [ __ ] idiot let me do
you squeeze it Nick get away put get
look I'll show you Nick you put it in
your
ear and then it just stays there ew bro
that's so gross it feels better Del Taco
we've never had Del Taco we should get
Del Taco I'm good for the Vlog I'm down
we've never had Del Taco everh how funny
would that be getting with the person in
front of us order at Del Taco and trying
it for the first time at Del Taco I
literally didn't think you were speaking
English I didn't even know what he said
okay it's hot the AC back on like dude
what degree is it here doesn't say it's
a million de too hot I want you to buy a
thermometer and take the
temperature I want you to always know
how hot it is what are you even saying
look at how Matt's so fast at
driving is just crazy get out of
here we should just book we should book
a terribly rated Airbnb and stay there
and see what happens no
why why would you do that I was thinking
of good video content and you guys are
not oh yeah staying at a crazy Airbnb
that's it'd be funny as
[ __ ] it would be
[Music]
dangerous are you watching Matt edits
again it popped up yeah you hold on to
the steering
wheel got
you well don't get the
map okay I just twisted your wheel now I
don't know why you turned it all the
other way that's
now you never know which way you're
going to go once you start awesome oh
almost went straight why would you ever
[ __ ] he just went to the left like
God well that's what happens when you
tell me to touch the wheel like I want
to create my own escape room I need the
AC back on I want to create my own mini
golf we should do mini golf
escape and you have to Nick said he
wants to play a song for the Vlog give
me the ax cord on full ax no
oh okay this is getting shut off Nick
what is this it's Morgan
wall you don't like that
song you're going to get I'm going to be
H hit a [ __ ] car cuz I have to keep
focusing on [ __ ] pausing that
terrible Nick I'm going to [ __ ] kill
you don't play that song again please I
can't believe you ever would play that
song you guys aren't real country folk
and that's your problem go use it had
the money y'all I have to pee I
okay okay oh oh I'm a ho again you're so
stupid drive me to the shore when we get
there I'm not going to help you with
anything and I'm going to have to pee
like he's so stupid tell us how you
really feel that's how I really feel I
used to
float now I just [ __ ] [ __ ] I can't
do this dude you're a [ __ ]
idiot who I do not need an hour I need
like 23 minutes why is that 23 [ __ ]
you're going to be in there for two and
then realize you don't have money I got
money
barely all I'm going to kill you shut up
stupid Los Angeles Melrose la
la we're in the store now but I put the
Vlog camera away cuz it's Su these are
hard I love these anybody that works
there yeah it's completely empty and
they're playing gospel music oh and I
forgot to mention there's a truck in the
middle of the whole store do you like
that nck get this out of my face bro
okay Matt and Chris are both in kiding
rooms and both probably going to get
close so I'm sitting in this beautiful
beautiful little waiting room right
outside it's serving horse cabin ni shut
the [ __ ] up now I can see Matt changing
okay that's crazy a like the perfect
word lately that I've been using to
describe Nick it's just a hooligan
you're just a hooligan all right
I trapped my door bro oh yeah awesome
close it no look pick it up what are you
doing Chris you're going to [ __ ] rip
the door off you got stuck in the dirt
how do you fix this I don't know I
opened the door and now it's why are you
guys swinging your doors like you got to
get a [ __ ] whale out of the way you
need to stop yelling and being all you
have to do is walk like bro it's like in
the dirt [ __ ] dig a hole let's go
little rabbit little rabbit like it's in
the [ __ ] I think you have to move the
car forward like I legit can't close it
yeah Drive the car awesome one of you
grab the camera I'm not going to I can't
drive the car and stand here Chris if
you break the [ __ ] door I'll kill you
I got I got it I got it oh my God you're
not real how did that happen I don't
know how I did that okay wait pause
ow I
got are you 12 Anonymous confession time
oh god that hurt when we first came to
LA and we drove around this area for the
first time I forced L to bring me to
team tent house to like get the Vibes of
like being in La I actually remember
that cuz I took a photo of it I said no
way it's the brought I made laa I was
like we were on Melrose and she's like
oh is there anything you guys want to do
and this was like I think like two years
ago we had first touched foot in La well
I have another anonymous confession no
but she she me and Nick actually sent
Jake Paul fan mail years ago so long ago
walking into store number two now see
you I actually own these pants and then
I actually was about to sell them on
doot but I didn't like these exact ones
damn
I could turn them in and get some money
[Music]
back ooh this
song what are these I like them they're
satin this song is so ass dude it's like
driving me out the store like I actually
want to leave yeah this is terrible for
customer
[Applause]
[Music]
service and
now my favorite place on
Earth all right the line was hot long as
[ __ ] and we're all hot and
miserable so we're just I hate that so
we're just leaving like having a drink
for a long time is embarrassing just
chug it like get it down even with a
Pepsi I'm just
like like I just gulp it you gulp it
don't ask me that question not answering
that you don't gulp Gul it
down St
feeling like big foot just stomp on the
little
kids that's it that's all they
got let's trip
LT oh how about a little bit of this one
a little bit of sugar don't call it
Sugar okay enough that's all you guys
get I got a poop go
poopies yeah nice job missed the ball
buddy let's
go oh wow that's why was is
hard what did he say shake it shake it
right Jimmy would be so happy here yeah
he would we have to dude we have to take
Dad here
H where did it go I right
again I'm really bad at getting it in
the targets but I can get it like out
there you know what I mean kid the
targets are the biggest part of the
whole [ __ ] thing I know but I'm not
good at
it okay trash
hit trash more again I think maybe less
oh wow no six okay that's a good
bounce that kid said look these kids
want to be YouTubers and I saying look
want to
be goofy what did he say someone said
they want to be YouTubers so bad by said
they want to be YouTubers I said he
wants to be good at golf that's
crazy that's crazy check out the 5 mil
merge bro yeah he clearly didn't see my
shirt sorry
came oh my God what the [ __ ] was
that these nachos so good I just want to
um n n look at that
chicken oh my God look at that chicken
damn and look at that
cheese look at that fresh love
pants you're disgusting look at that
Hunchback oh my God
I didn't hit my
name
wow
wow hit the cart hit the C hit the
C oh
close I don't like that they shut the
lights off me either I hate it put her
home right in the right there
oh nice She's a
Beauty
oh R right in there oh my gosh wait what
the frig what the heck what the frig
what the frig I literally saw it go in
the freaking white I mean the
red wow you look so good with all these
lights on you do I oh you had a plus
three yeah let's
go that was a good hit
right up the middle oh in the blue maybe
maybe maybe right in the blue you think
they call me Bluey L chewy plus six
let's go hit that ball give it a swing
give it a swing
wo okay oh you had red undies
on looking like
blood oh my God you almost hit my foot
rid thank God I have boots on rapid fire
rapid
fire hit it as it's sliding out oh my
God you
demon video is
crazy and then what you saying how you
miss me yeah you miss me and things that
we did we said we going to travel from
the islands to Madrid we had a lot of
plans but they
alled why oh because of some kid but
it's okay cuz I'm moving different don't
be saying when I post with other [ __ ]
for my brothers