is it
recording yes hey guys that tripod's
going to break why look at it the whole
camera's angled down like it looks it's
going to snap Oh I thought that was like
the whole I thought you had that like
that
[Music]
no hey guys Texas me Matt and Nick are
about to go fly to Texas to meet Sam and
kobby and conjure demons with them no
we're not doing that not conjure demons
say hello to some Spirits yeah if you
don't know who Sam and KOB Arts this Duo
friendship YouTubers that talk to ghosts
so we're going to go basically basically
we are going to go on our own little
Texas Adventure and take you guys
through that so first and foremost we're
not going to post this video Until Sam
and Kobe post their video with us so
right now already you can go over to Sam
and Kobe's YouTube channel and see
whatever we do we don't know what we did
did yet because we're still here we're
not in Texas yet but that's why we're
going to Texas this Vlog is going to go
out right after their video goes out of
just what else we did in
[Music]
Texas we need to get a light if we're
going to use this new camera no we don't
it's fine no we definitely do but what's
up guys we're we're here Nick get that
light out of my face what are
you doing hey yo what's up there's a
diner in the hotel no way wait is a
diner it's closed but there's a diner in
here tell where we are where it's Texas
Texas Austin Texas at our hotel I'm not
going to tell you well I mean it doesn't
matter cuz it's going to be posted
beforehand I I hate this music there
yeah bro I'm sagging so bad right now
this is nice all this is you right here
oh this is nice o hold on wait gummy
bears definitely eating these tonight
wao for free I no definitely for
purchase hickory smoke beef jerky
mat is it like a million bucks Tios they
know us
well yes hold up I'm going to down this
real quick this this like Patron ooh
going get loose real
quick pour me
up sub machine wait watch this be a
fridge why would
that why would that be a fridge I don't
know it look like a fridge let's look at
our view
hold on I'm saging just now I ordered
Wendy's the second we got here I got
Baconator fries on the way I got a 10
piece on the way I got fries on the way
I got chocolate chip cookies on the way
did you get a CH a chocolate cake from
Wendy's kid o oh look at the lap pool
waa wait that's a really cool deck
that's a really cool
deck you sound like an observation like
a like a murder mystery show I actually
really like that's a really cool no like
the layout and design of that deck is
nice that pool is nice Definitely
probably a little Frosty right now
unless it's heated we should swim and
then yeah the guy was like you'll have a
pool view hopefully there's nobody
swimming yeah I there was people
swimming and we can observe them from
above hello Mr swimmers oh theing giving
very rustic Vibe I didn't even notice
the ceilings making me feel like wait
why does the bed frame look like a book
the ceilings making me feel why does
this look like a book and I just want to
hello hello hi do you not hear someone
else
talking I said the ceiling's making me
feel like I'm in an escape room what is
the red light in that wall it's in a
bomb is a bomb so we're going to get our
wendes and CH the down I'm trying
to think like what your what is our plan
tomorrow hopefully we try some barbecue
food have a good day tomorrow we're
going to we're going to meet Sam and
Kobe tomorrow and film with them
tomorrow night I'm so excited like I
think the excitement is overdoing my
fear like I'm not really afraid
anymore are you afraid Chris I'm not
really afraid I'm never afraid one time
I'm not really afraid anymore one time
we did a horror themed escape room and
we quit because Chris was like terrified
of being in there so now that we're in
real real horror situation it's funny
how like you're just standing like he's
been I don't know like he's observing he
been frantically running around we're
going Street never sleeps rest assur
that what did he just say anyways it
says right here Sixth Street Street
never sleeps rest assured that you will
and they Supply earplugs I assume we're
on Sixth Street good morning Austin
Texas today we are going out we are
filming with Sam and Colby and because
we're filming with them we're going to
leave our camera here so we don't steal
any of their content sorry guys for the
quick Interruption from the Vlog but
there's a pretty massive time Jump in
content right now we basically filmed
the entire day with Sam and kobby and
didn't pick up our Vlog camera once so
this next clip is me waking up Chris the
day technically two days after the day
we got to Texas I believe but the clip
also just doesn't look like it makes
sense but I personally think it's the
funniest thing on earth to wake somebody
up with like an ultimatum right like you
need to do this instantly because then
they're just so confused like I woke up
Chris with a relative sense of urgency
offering him lemonade in this next clip
and it's my favorite thing ever cuz it's
like why the would he need lemonade
he was just asleep you know what I mean
he clearly doesn't want Lemonade he was
sound asleep a second ago
to the clip
resume Chris do you want to sit
Chris do you want to sitp or
no do you want to sit of what Nick it's
like
lemonade are you
[Music]
stupid last time we were here I got a
pull of like exact same like that but it
was like slightly different colors and
stuff and I wore it at the I think I
wore it at the next show that we had
where were we headed when we left here
from the first stour I think we were
leaving Texas oh no we um San Antonio no
all right oh so we were going to
Dallas we were going to Dallas yeah cuz
we I remember for the Dallas we 3 in the
morning here at the Dallas show we all
wore something from that we got from
here yeah we're going to we're going to
each pick our favorite thing that we got
and show you guys when we leave here but
just general thing if you're in Austin
Texas Rags reng is a place to go it's
the plug bro the best place and they
have a website as well so you don't even
have to live in Austin Texas they're
going to be in the description but I
love it here they give us clothes and
the clothes are so cool come on me a
pizzeria you forget about it come
on we're about to eat some nice Austin
Texas Pizza look at that building yeah
so we're eating pizza we've had barbecue
twice when we were filming with him and
Kobe I was like admiring their equipment
they had a nice light yeah they were
doing they okay um that's not weird oh
my hands are cold we've eaten barbecue
twice we haven't documented it all but
we're at an Italian place to bring it
back to you know the stern Yola shoy
Roots we're going to go eat pizza we're
in Austin Texas still only time you'll
ever catch me my lips trapped I'm in the
Tundra right now and I don't
have my yet God I covered I can't
eat in here I thought they were cover in
blood they're covered in tomato
sauce oh my God meatball M give you the
realest revie of your like I love
meatballs let's see it I'm going to rank
this meatball
how I rank my children one day bro's
ranking his kids even the way that the
fork goes into the meatball is
important little pressure kicking back
at you yeah I like it so far you got to
have some resistance in the ball I feel
you by the way when we're done with
these meatballs me and Chris are going
to cook our pizzas ourselves with all
the machines in
here I'm going to need the dough with my
feet e
scent okay sent is high Chris is eating
the whole thing they don't call me
meatball mat for a reason all right for
no reason yeah they definitely call you
it for a reason that's what I'm
saying 10 out of 10 ball 10 out of 10
ball mat meatball
mat sauce good amount of flavor no no no
I'd say eight out of
10 what a tricky little laugh that was
okay um I'd
say oh my God
it
f i got the Wicked Witch of the
West rude God forbid you was great
meatball eight out of 10 cuz
nothing can beat my grandmother's rest
in peace rest her soul oh this is
feeling just how Grandma's balls
SP 10 is crazy that's all I'll say well
no I was I Wasing every every detail
yeah but I'd agree ten is insane you're
insane it's like a seven I can't even
look at that like a science
experiment gone wrong no it just looks
like gross and nasty meatball is
good though God it makes me sick that
they're like smiling like put your oh my
God
eyelashes oh
gross all right another power ranking
from meatball Matt coming
in crust off look is given 10 out of 10
presentation's a little notation is I
like the thin cut can we make this one a
little faster oh super that's not good
that's not good not a good site
[Music]
W I'm getting a lot of Garlic Knot
flavor
yeah honestly I'm tell you I'm enjoying
this honestly worst flop I've ever seen
I'm being honest worst harsh review oh
it's
dripping the crust is like a gar
dripping with ease ain't that a rap song
you would know meatballs are better I'd
come take another big monster bite of
that thing all
[Music]
right oh my
God here here let me help you out let me
help you out little recoil on it
rating for B I'll take the meatball over
it any day this is again a six point
five five just five or 6.5 I feel
like do you keep pointed them for too
much they had something to do with this
pizza they had they part of the reason
this one out yeah not bad though here
you go Mr canoli are you cracking your
knuckles to eat a canoli that was my
neck defin neck like I didn't even touch
my fingers all right eat it an
need God shut
up let's get a that like a
reveal cuz the paper towel like kind of
hid them and then you're like what went
like
this okay dude it's not long enough take
the biggest bite you possibly can I'm
not doing that either I actually like
really feel odd about this like I don't
want to eat this with you in my face
yeah cuz I'm like a no I can't I can't I
actually
okay what a weak bite
so much labor almost knocked him out of
his seat Nick has such like bodily
reactions to like
food take a b bite Nick's typ of flow if
he likes something he eats like tastes
like
mint take another bite M bigger bite
bigger bite I'm not doing that Nick the
big huge bite big big bite kind of a lot
of cream compared to everything else I
mean yeah and the canoli shell is hard
but it's good it's like a just eat it
bro like a seven as well one more bite
one more bite I'm not doing that one
more Big
Bite did the review change no so
seven just shut the blinds or
something oh it's too
dark are you going to talk dude I didn't
know you were recording
you've been complaining about lights all
right guys we are wrapping up our trip
in Texas I'm putting lotion on my face
and we are headed to the airport in
about an hour we're going to eat it one
more place I know we said our one goal
was to go to barbecue restaurant and
Vlog it and we went to a barbecue
restaurant twice we just didn't Vlog it
either time so this year and this this
year of better content
is us making sure we are ready for what
we're going to film and we went to a
Italian place on the Vlog but
life is unpredictable so whatever we
went to a barbecue place literally once
but it was with Sam and Colby right
before we filmed for their stuff so it's
like obviously we weren't going to like
bust out the camera we were like meeting
them and getting ready for our day um
but we'll see you on our next Excursion
we're leaving Texas right now and
wherever we go next we'll see you
there hey guys what's going on I hope
you enjoyed that little Vlog
there so weird I know that was really
weird who you yeah anyway we are back
home in Boston but we were just in the
Holy Grail Boston
Massachusetts we but we were just but we
were just in Texas there and that was at
the beginning of this year that was in
that was early January now it's early
February and we're now in Boston we're
in so we were in LA but now we're here
we're going to sit and outro that video
cuz we never did filming with Sam and
Kobe was great great they're
amazing gentlemen I'm super excited to
go again we have zero plans to go again
so don't lose your mind but it
was awesome I think that we did well
enough and Sam and kobby had enough fun
that they'd be like ah we should bring
bring those guys again you know what I
mean my whole goal was to for them to
have a good enough experience that they
want to bring us to something they do in
the future so I hope we get an invite
back cuz I had so much fun but and we we
flew literally we came back here to
Boston and watched it with Nathan it was
very like we were avoiding spoilers on
our for 2 days before we got back here
but I'm happy to finally be back here
I'm happy to have finally watched the
video and now it's at like 5 million
views in 3 days so they're killing it
shout out to them it was a amazing time
an amazing video and obviously you guys
are enjoying it I keep seeing edits like
every day no I love it obviously you
guys can tell that um this video is like
higher quality from our normal one cuz
we use a newer camera and we're trying
to like upgrade our content to make it
but that's another conversation another
yeah we're going to we have plans and
you don't need to know about that right
now the camera was just a
beginning that was mysterious man that
was really good now it's time for some
stery Olo spoilers I'm kidding you got
to cut that
out we are going to give you guys a
first look at what our one of our 6 mil
merchandise items because right when we
are filming this outro to the video we
are 25,000 subscribers away from 6
million subscribers if you guys bless us
to bring us to 6 million subscribers
this is one of the items from the merch
store that will be available for your
purchase nice it's a great item I love
it I don't even know what Nick edited in
to I don't know what I edited in either
but all the items are great so we know
it's a great item whatever chooses to be
right here that 6 mil design is a little
hint at the 6 million video which should
be coming to you guys hope we hit 6
milon right the next video posted after
we hit 6 million subscribers will be our
6 million celebration video we did a lot
to celebrate 6 mil and we hope you guys
enjoy when that video comes out we have
a lot of major major content plans and
the six mil video is an example of what
we want to do for Content moving forward
in the future so the six mil video is
coming and we hope you like it are ready
for it that wraps up this Wednesday
video if you have not seen our video
with Sam and Kobe yet you need to go
watch that because that's the entire
reason this video exists and the entire
reason that we went to Texas we are back
in Boston we are working on more content
we're working on more stuff we're super
excited for you guys to find out
everything that we're planning and
plotting see you next
[Music]
Friday