what the [ __ ] is up YouTube you already
know who it is it's the stern yo
triplets Chris here map behind the cam
we got Nick getting ready in his room he
doesn't know that I'm coming or that I'm
Vlogging but I'm just barging in
hi welcome to the stery Olo triplets
Vlog we're learning how to become
Habachi chefs correct thank you I'm
ready do you have anything to
say yeah you got big Airbnb tonight that
has a big fat backyard and we're going
to have a habashi chef try to show us
the way kind of we're going to learn how
to use the show us the way or show us
the way was that with a C or an S there
I said show us the way all right you're
chewing that ass no I'm not Kidd chewing
that ass spitting it back up all right
we're about to take a party bus because
why like Matt's complaining about
driving he's like oh go ahead do the
little [ __ ] thing you do go I don't
want to drive I'm mad my ankle hurts do
it do it um I don't know if there's like
a little [ __ ] thing I do it's more of
like hey guys I've drove 7 hours in the
past 24 and I'm a little tired yes like
o my ankle hurt do like like complain
how you do it normally I drive yeah and
I
go oh wow this ankle hurts after 6 hours
of up and down yeah yeah so all that
complaining got me and Nick to basically
get a party bus so that Matt can have
the night off so we're about to take a
party bus and have a party essentially
on the road to Habachi dinner for the
Vlog come here real quick what come here
come here come here Chris I'm about come
down three steps please three steps all
right go ahead I time to watch you go up
those St you're [ __ ] weirdo do it do
it no no you back pedal [ __ ] dude I just
I didn't have one sip of water today and
I just had half a poptart and I feel
like I have ashes in my mouth yeah get
some water oh Dr Pepper Pepsi root
beer a p b you guys are so dramatic
because it's like I say it I don't want
to yeah
I say I want to drive one time and
instead of an Uber we're taking a party
bus this is M when he has to
drive requesting Dome there's a dome
button in this car there's a dome button
bro oh [ __ ] press that I think the
Apple's rotten right to the core
from
sco
Wow
inter favorite songs
[Music]
I'm going to be honest I'm going to be
honest I went hard look at me I'm
disheveled I got no hoodie on I got a
sideways hat I started this nice and
clean Ming up it's like it's like Stern
triplets like morph in time okay you're
so stupid Falcon Chris sorry Meo you
know what this reminds me of have you
ever seen the movie Dodgeball I have
seen a dodgeball you know the dude
patches a hoola handy like
d it looks just like this R like tell
like the same thing today we are serving
cajun chicken spicy chicken honey
chicken um is going to help me cook
today so hopefully don't burn down the
house or get sick from eating chicken so
try get down maybe burn it a bit no I'd
rather overcook than undercook yeah
that's like that should be on a shirt or
like told to everyone I think you're
good that should be like one of the like
main things everyone knows never
under you're way too passionate about
thisal down you're acting like a su I
know you're all right now we got to
finally get started you we got any
celebrations today that we should be
know on Chris woke up Nick come there's
Halloween good thing so I'll say happy
Halloween you just got to trust that
right that was sick yeah don't
CCH two one you think catch okay I'm
just a little Chris's turn Chris get up
there St fling that
thing all right now who's going to want
to try Chris get up there make sure you
don't cut a finger off okay okay chis
you got
this you know you can juggle though oh
you can juggle yeah do you have like
three items of the same size I have two
I have three eggs but we could try to
jugle I jugle egg safely you think so I
think I could we have exactly five for
the whole night oh
[ __ ] we like this on fire later yes
right now at the end we going do all the
fire tricks at the end so just in case
you don't burn down the house I didn't
think there was going to be any try to
see if you can Crouch it just like that
yeah you're already good yeah
you all right oh all right now try
behind the back says you already know a
little experience you just go like this
real quick off thing yeah off the thing
it's like a it's like a bang type
situation
oh Cho your fing off Cho your fing
you're closer
than we do some extra tricks for here we
want to start do some tricks for we do a
little more advanced tricks all right CH
do you like a do it again oh no I don't
have oh you want to do it one more time
no no it's okay just like a move I'm
going to end it on the Banger I made all
the little basic tricks first so I think
you try to go like
this all right just make sure don't hit
your eye right here okay so I'll show
you just like this you're going just
toss it and just let oh my God all right
but don't drop in the floor cuz we going
use this to eat oh God okay yeah so a
tin and then it's going to flip and then
going I'm going to do it like play bypl
here like Red Zone like that and then
it's going to spin yeah but don't do it
too hard cuz it will either go that way
right in the middle or right towards you
I'll do it gentle yeah so have it like
this the goal like a gentle and is it
better if it falls on the stove like on
the stove make sure you don't grab it
I'll grab it if it falls on the stove
okay got don't burn yourself
oh yeah they hit him though that's okay
okay one more try just flip it it's a
little more easier you can do that you
can definitely do that yeah so like all
like fli the WR you know he knows all
that boom what I'm tell you watch out in
the yeah and then all the way in and
there's a it's like putting a
knife spin it dude so you'll thr you'll
just till toss and then you'll flick
it [ __ ] I can't do it here let me show
you one more time yeah just make sure it
doesn't go that way again okay yes oh
you're so
close maybe pick it up pick it up before
it [ __ ] gets really hot I need you to
stop talking cuz when you get up here
we're going to watch these are it get
harder the more we pray like jugle yeah
we only got exactly five too I don't
even think I'm going to come remotely
close to doing anything you've already
done let's see it no no no yeah no one
of you guys has to do this next Matt
you're up all right now you got to get
your first try
yeah [ __ ] do how long did it take you to
master this it's actually my first day
today yeah I'm a little nervous no way
no I've been doing it for 3 years on and
off wow D lock them oh
wa back last time all right I had I had
a better swing than you though yeah
clearly you almost okay are you going to
do it successfully we not going to get
that successfully we can do you want to
just flick it up yeah we see with that
more easier just like this oh that's
yeah money don't cut your hand yeah just
make sure you don't grab the metal oh
maybe use the batons instead grab the
metal M should I use a baton the the
Baton thing that you were going with if
you're a baby yeah it's not too hot it
just might burn your hand a little bit
but you're okay that's all right
oh my God done I can barely Shake
someone's hand let alone flip a [ __ ]
saucer I don't know what that is go try
it let's go yeah whoever's in the middle
watch out cuz I got and you know and you
know my capability level so you got to
really just like that first time so
we're going here all the way
up you come do that again can't you can
do that that was really good a banger if
you just do exactly what he says it's
easy Nick that was I'm
impressed more oh my God good [ __ ] thank
you I'll just clean these utensils and
clean the grill so we can get started
with the food all right I'm going to use
the bathroom while you guys do that I
don't know where the bathroom at keep
your mic on no it's fine keep your mic
on I just have to pee you're fine where
are your dinner
manners you're like a little dinosaur I
ain't got Wi-Fi
here the [ __ ] are you
doing what are you
doing you're weirdo
dude Nick I'm actually like really
impressed it was easy I'm surprised you
guys didn't do it oh hello guys a little
yeah it's getting a little close you
guys can he you up watch out for that
tree my gosh tree's low yeah it is wow
yeah wor you guys going try that a
little later okay all right it's okay we
I have a Sharpie right here just in case
you lose her eyebrows so we're all good
there's a fire hydrant here too which
makes me feel really actually need to
keep my eyebrows I was at a Halloween
party last night and someone told me my
eyebrows were like really nice did they
yeah W RZ I was at the same party and I
just saw a girl with no eyebrows I'm
like sh
yikes that's why I want mine mayis
reason maybe Chris may I just stole the
girl the
yeah
literally who hello all right don't
choke I should have grabbed the Pepsi
from the party bus I should have grabbed
a drink too should have would have good
right yeah yeah yeah we have a lot of
veggies do you guys like a lot of
veggies and your rice I love
veg huge onion fan over here huge garlic
fan yeah we had a lot of garlic Butters
today for you guys I like
peas that's [ __ ] good I like peas
like already [ __ ] that's like a
lettuce
dude get out of here maybe get three
this time here we got three we got na
with the head just real quick that was
sick are you going to do it I'll do it
in Chris you should do it you should try
to go straight for the Hat though I
don't know if you juggle the bowl I'm
being honest all right I it's a little
easier to juggle with the bowl then it
AEG so this is like if you can do the
bowl you can probably do the egg okay if
you can dodge a wrench you can dodge a
ball yeah and if you can juggle a bowl
you can juggling EG okay you're going to
throw up you're going to catch and let
it slide down oh my God so like midair
it's like it's like a gather it's like a
gather just like that so let me show one
time you can see it yeah you're like
slide down like that gather technique I
got it okay you got to move with you
have to move with swiftness and
confidence wait I'm kind of scared Nick
okay here with the hat and then you can
do it yes I didn't tell you how to throw
in the Hat just make sure you cat I'm
terrified okay no no got here whenever
you're ready almost almost got it go you
got yes a oh my oh my God
here we have another one we have another
to close this Gap yeah no no he needs to
get better um you want to use that bow
yeah yeah I just need wash it we can
it's fine we're we're going to be the
only ones eating I don't even give a
[ __ ] really don't wait let me go to this
side real quick okay okay up and then
gather little more a little you got to
get it up and you got to catch it shut
your mouth do it
yes it's that come on hello oh count
what'll count that okay H you don't want
to put your face over is this hot like
if it hits me the bowl yeah it is really
hot right now no you're fine and think
of the hat is like probably just 8
in maybe 12 let me get a good feel for
it what do you know about that I don't
know are you ready next yes I don't know
if
you almost got it okay Chris I'd give up
if I was
you now gather gather almost closer no
I'm not I'm not beating that you got to
yeah whoa are you going straight for hat
no I think you
could that was really phenomenal Matt
okay yeah it gives you time to react
yeah just like that all right all right
you're the closest you're the
closest yes oh my god did get went for
the like the 720 you don't even know
what you're talking about or not
20 my God hold on hold on wait straight
the Hat you have to make you have to
make the Hat a part of your body you
know yes you have to your hat is that
you have to be the Hat hold on hold
[Laughter]
on look like you're like
M ready burping Contest no no we not
little
kid the only one with a carbonated drink
let me get some soda in my system this
about to go crazy for this trick only
one one of you guys can do it cuz
there's a trick to it so one person I'll
tell you the secret of it so I'll do it
first and I'll tell you the secret and
then you try to do it okay so you want
to see it first you want to sit down
here sit your ass just show you got a
little classic we have some egg rolls
for you
guys okay and you get one chance to look
at it yeah if you didn't see it just get
me back tomorrow cuz I'm always here all
right all right here you go got you guys
and then one you guys got to hold it so
here you're going to hold this real
quick for me but don't throw that one I
want to go blind to just hold it real
quick here sh here you a little bit all
right you ready yeah yeah so you know
what to do I think no you're not ready
let me tell you you're going to tap this
three times okay tap it three times you
go one two
three all see it here you go we got two
wgs yeah I'm part time magician cook
that was crazy there just thought I used
to do magic when I was a young kid wait
wait
okay all right all right all right hey
ladies and gentlemen welcome I have an
empty bowl here sure you
do dare you
do tell me more about the
ball go I want to see you do it it would
I want to see you do it I want to see
you do it let's see you do it no you
were doing CHR come on I'll pretend I
didn't see it you the egg roll
yeah just the egg roll yeah you have to
distract us look at it go look at it go
whoa that egg is rolling empty bow
yeah okay you didn't put it over the
[ __ ]
egg it three times
only who would have thought I'll be all
night goes an empty bowl and I see the
egg between your fingers Nick [ __ ] you
that was funny you should have just went
with my my story I know but it's okay
here I should just show you this one's
the same exact way just that I could
break here we got one you're going make
it two we got three go four and just
pulling your head real quick oh ah but
yeah just make sure you're don't
cracking your head no I'm sorry about
guys I clean up real quick y we got
some Jens doesn't get any more fresher
than that
right I said
that was awesome okay just we only have
five eggs yes okay you break it I kill
you w if you believe it it'll happen
yeah or you can pick it up just if you
pick it up like an angle just like that
just get in there believe it yeah just
don't don't put too much force up
freaked out I'm chill out the egg
breakes were still going to like the
world
will we got two we got two good ones we
too great work great better than I
thought yeah you got it first try yeah
we got first a that was really good M
yeah the world will still spin no matter
what you do everything's good for you
but everything's bad yeah your protein
you eat eggs too much whatever too much
of this too much of that you know too
much of anything is a bad thing what am
I going to eat except for celery am I
going to that's just water sticks yeah
then you can too much of everything you
can overh too much of anything wait what
is this saying I just said what did I
just say you know someone died from
drinking too much water yeah what was I
going to say though mat too much of
anything is a bad thing except except
celery so you guys make eggs like this
at home too you go
like not like not like that that's take
not that's a really good technique if I
walk in the kitchen and Matt's doing
this ever I'm walking back out red bell
peppers green bell peppers green onions
as well as regular onions my tummy's
dancing right now give me the
food dropped down yeah turn to
Kash oh my God
hope you guys can see this one I don't
know if you guys seen this one yet but
here in Hibachi we're known for the rice
shapes so then I'm going to do this one
and I'll give you guys a chance to do it
I'll put down the the temperature so you
guys can try your own rice shapes in a
little bit go what are you going to make
Chris I don't know I want a fire
breathing figure in what about a fire
breathing dragon yeah sure recreate the
mon next time we got to look at the
clouds like guys you guys know about
Pac-Man love Pac-Man oh my God the power
pets and I'm going to mix this and then
you guys are going to have a chance to
do your own right shapes I'll do a heart
yeah don't say it why you're supposed to
do it then me yes that's like the whole
[ __ ] point [ __ ] I'll try something
else just uh yeah just don't use the
fork usually yeah exactly like that okay
ready against yeah pay attention pay
close attention I watch I'm going to
look I'm going to
look wait can we get a close-up on his
rice rice shape memo this [ __ ] idiot
going to be like a circle correct there
you go um wait I have another one in
mind that I can
achieve a pie chart no a vend diagram no
a pie no oh slice of cake pizza yeah
we'll go with that what was it it's an
unsuccessful other shape I'm going to
make something inappropriate okay all
right go for it I'm making something
like inappropriate okay yeah that's
totally fine I think hopefully should I
I like have to it's like I'm it's like
think about it you bring bread to the
pond the Ducks are going to eat right
Matt what I've never heard that in my
life that's a
mutation wait no no
yes wait let me get [ __ ] 3 years old
you're stupid all right I have to do it
I'm
sorry look at this kid leing in the
bathroom what is he doing
a little dance he's the weird person
I've ever met in my
life God that party must changed his
life I know thank you we just put some
right here for
everybody shout out me whenever I like
go like this I'm like that [ __ ] finger
looking good bro that [ __ ] got me
sucking on my
fingers you watch what you're
doing h
I feel like you've been in too many
scenarios where you're going like this
where you don't got to be no you that
with every meal fat
ass you been bigger than me your whole
life was doing the that with a poptarts
the other night literally literally an
hour
ago yum dummy Dusty
poptart yum yumyum who are you
texting we have the zucchini sauce oh oh
I got to lock him
how far could you do it
um it depends I'm not sure but we can
find out right we we got I'm going to be
like GR in this [ __ ] I'm G to [ __ ]
I'm going to run a
[Laughter]
line what is so funny like what are you
guys laughing
at I'm like literally I'm going to run a
slant like I'm going to go this like
textbook play like up and then to the
right you going to run like around the
pool right it I'll jump in the pool
midair s in your mouth boom they we warm
up a little bit all right
let's right here so honestly all the
work has to come from you
okay yeah I think know last time only
two people caught it last time what
we're all we're going to go three for
three
people ready wait don't make me laugh we
got to warm up a little bit shut up
sorry sorry make sure you don't fall
backwards you're going to fall right in
the
pool you actually the F for one second
try to catch your that was all me that
was all me just try and warm up a little
bit got to be
honest it's okay we're not
juding three
two I felt like a
dog [ __ ] two one here
go logo for it that the new Jordan logo
God after this you're going to try to
toss it three two one here
go almost no it doesn't count should we
try a Long
Ranger yeah we can try
one cracking your knuckles is crazy get
over
there three two one
[Applause]
oh wait can I get it again yeah we have
a lot more kid's going to set his chair
up oh my God bomb here you go three two
one oh oh
no
[ __ ] live here okay he's feeding the
coyotes oh [ __ ] what dude all right
three get picked the only part in the
backyard with rocks at his
feet I thought you caught that one he
could have stood anywhere and he shows
exactly where the rocks are hit the tree
hit the tree set oh oh
oh wait can I do it to Nick yeah I mean
want I can
send okay asking so
much dude oh you're [ __ ] over me dude
sorry don't be sorry just do it
better Matt I want to do it to you like
like deep like we got to what do we mean
what are we talking about all right you
ready Matt yeah come
on all right you ready Matt last try on
the zucchini
flinger we about to go
crazy Matt what are you doing use your
mouth into the water let's like come on
dude all right well we tried this is so
good it is I feel like someone's lurking
in the woods trying to catch me right
now I think you're good bro Anonymous
confession did you just hear the bush
Russell no bro going to take me
anywhere so weird dude so weird I don't
think there's ever been a thought that
hit your head that didn't come out oh
yeah there has really I can guarantee
that if every thought that hit my head
came out life like this sure is sweet or
no trick you actually put that oh you
actually got it Go Chris almost oh my
God I saw that uh in front of you
definitely keep that yeah just in case
hold that just in case oh
yeah why you spray all of
it
yeah there you go I have it ready I
think heart
stereo for you so all right I don't
think you're
my thoughts
[Music]
no s familiar I just heard the whole
thing what song should we sing I'll do
aella style at the Habachi
table um Matt give me a beat with the
chops okay hold on I got
you terrible terrible be nah
are you something for this trick he's
like shut up you guys are do this trick
you guys sign a waiver so we're all good
okay so all right whoa Chris get up
there yeah you want to give me a high
five just give me a high five just like
that here you go just show you you want
to take out your hat just like this go
here go three real quick in three two
one why you grab it
it
what no way yeah don't do this at home
all right I was trained TR straight
straight from Tik Tok straight from Tik
Tok most reliable source on Earth yes
sir nowadays oh oh oh got you all right
now it's who's going to do it no no [ __ ]
that no I just grabbed it in my hand I'm
all out of op I can't do it you do it I
feel like we have to like draw straws or
something I'm not doing this I'm not
doing it I'm like yeah there's like zero
world we have to do no no I'm not doing
this I don't give a [ __ ] if you CH my
name for here I'll buy you I'll take you
to Jersey mics anytime you want I don't
give a [ __ ] I'll walk two one you got
closer real
quick good job put that you have to do
oh I'm not doing that yes all right
you're going to eat the fire no ready
come on three it's a little tiny one
it's not too bad two what you do that's
Kidd a little bit this is crazy work
yeah I'm parttime magician yeah that's
why
with Santa when Nick's
[Laughter]
laugh elves bring me my finest
reindeer
laugh Mrs claw [ __ ]
off
australi he said [ __ ] off he said
Australian you're an idiot what's the
deer name buster
mustard
Rudolph The Goat in our house that's not
rer are you idiot Buster is not a
reindeer oh what is it it's like
jumper jumper
goofy Nick what is that what is that
yeah you guys are going to do all this
so just keep your hand just like no
we're not I'm not doing it are you guys
doing it I'm doing that easily and then
we're going to do this one too make sure
you don't burn your head
though what is the this is a perfect
size it's a 180 just like that the [ __ ]
bug on the face the [ __ ] is good it's on
your leg Yeah get it the [ __ ] off me get
it off me [ __ ] that's my phone I don't
give a [ __ ] not using my phone I'm about
to taste the f
he talking the GoPro oh I forgot that
was there he
goes by okay okay ready
who do something better how about behind
the back oh try one I can't do behind
the back I haveing you guys thank you so
much thank you for having hiachi J as
your Chef today my name is Antonio and I
had a wonderful time with you guys all
right
guys yeah night guys hope you guys enjoy
this thank
you thank you so Standing Ovation all
right thank you thank you Antonio thank
you make sure I leave R here to help you
guys
out so much all right I had such a good
blast what a great fun dinner that we
got to have together for con such an
amazing dinner thumbnail
thumbnail thumbnail oh I'm eating it put
the Pepsi in my mouth Matt like the I
got you I got you oh
[Music]
thumbnail dinner gone
wrong I got stuck in
a get the
[ __ ] okay that was this Friday video I
feel very very successful I don't know
who's eding that bro until
here I don't know whenever I see it tall
Pepsi I'm just like that's got to be
talking
you
think yes like that's a family of peps
and that's like mom son and Dad okay you
know only if we had the mini one that'd
be perfect thanks guys thank you guys so
much for watching this Friday video
subscribe like the video we'll see you
guys next week classic LA right here
that's you're here La in the hills with
the coyotes and the fires wrap it up
dude
[Music]
[Applause]