my tummy hurts oh no Matt sternula's
tummy hurts what is
it I know what you're saying how you
miss me yeah you missed
me
but it's okay
so that's what I was gonna tell the
viewers oh we have to change our Brita
filter on August 19th you guys have to
remind us because we will forget August
19th August 19th why because it's like a
filter thing you just gotta change it up
tell us to change the Brita filter
so yesterday at the canes drive through
guess what Chris made me buy you have
three seconds free spray oh stop put it
back
Freeze Frame we have three seconds here
you guys pose for a freeze frame
[Music]
all right I gave them I'm gonna give
them multiple choice if you guess Kane's
one gallon of sweet tea
you win
we should actually do that like multiple
choice questions that are interactive in
the video so they win a prize that's
what I just did but I don't know I don't
have prizes you got it wrong skip 10
seconds if you didn't get it wrong here
you go
we'd have to like wait a full 10 seconds
for this five five thing to work
[Music]
dude I always hate when it's like this
like what the poor right because it's
no I I learned this oh my God
oh wow that's some noise to it not oh I
love how it sounds one gallon on it well
that's the size so just don't don't
okay
that's like that was such a Matt drink
yours you didn't pour it out for nothing
I just I put it up for him
why would you yeah why would you do that
would you ever do that and not like say
anything yeah just he did it like did I
just say stay instead of say I don't
know I think I did oh smash cream
okay dude like that's nice someone clean
that up oh and he was gonna wear that
shirt yeah he's gonna wear it all day
today yeah look at that I want to know
what I'm gonna have all day today my
[ __ ] right hand so it looks like
everything we have here is gonna be
sticky
yeah it was
go ahead see what happens if you do that
see what happens should I see what
happens guys
[Music]
what happened you don't want to know
what the [ __ ] will happen I promise
you can't we can't we have to clean the
whole thing you have to imagine you
literally can't no you literally cannot
come toward me with that thing man
I have all day Matt I have you can't
David literally like that's a ridiculous
mess in the house you can't don't care
you have to get away from me
all day long
enough
we both have to change our shirts now
it's even Steven it's not even yes it is
I've seen Stephen it was even Steven
after you got it on my hand and I got it
on your shirt no because you decided
like an idiot no it wasn't nice Matt
literally it's not even funny you will
rule the [ __ ] day
over here I will kill you oh my god
escalated so bad I'm sober you ready
this isn't even funny at this point okay
Chris show them that Chris show them
that show the map Chris show them that
Matt
get the [ __ ] away with the gallon I'm so
God honest for real God honest for real
could you be more for real than God all
day it's the same thing he said he's God
honest for real [ __ ] you because of our
amazing viewers
because
I'm having a moment
[ __ ] You Because of You Beautiful People
we have achieved another plaque 100 000
subscribers on the cut the camera
podcast
that's pretty crazy so go subscribe if
you're not because we upload every
Wednesday and Friday here on this
channel but every Monday on the cut the
camera podcast Channel okay if you
haven't noticed actually guys Nick has
yellow hair or blonde hair but it looks
yellow I keep calling them Ronald
McDonald but Ronald actually has red
hair he does I bought a shampoo today
that was holy [ __ ] yeah I thought that
DHL truck was gonna kill I bought a
shampoo today that was suggested to me
by
a hairdresser so I'm gonna like what's
that in your hand is this suction cup
it's supposed to be rid migraines and
neck and head pain
but I'm not gonna give my rating y'all
gonna have to figure out yourself you're
supposed to squeeze it and put it in
your neck just tell them
and it stays suctioned right you should
be able to let go of it that's so gross
that's nasty as [ __ ]
for 20 seconds
is this like a like your rules no that's
what it said like Burger King you rule
Burger King rule ain't the slogan yes it
is it's it's Burger King Burger King
have it your way you rule that's not
real yes it is I swear to God remember
when me you and Nate went to Burger King
back home and I literally pulled up to
the window or I pulled up to the yeah
you're the king what would you like yeah
welcome to Burger King you rule I was
like meet the Burger King The King
though no like you are the Burger King
and they feed the king
Queen
you can be the burger peasant the burger
jester
Feels Like Home
this technology is so unique wow
[Music]
oh my God does Chris have a sun kiss and
not a Pepsi Cola
we need to alert the news now I think
that's
oh my God their eyes look so blue in the
sun you get it Nick can you get your
favorite
did someone edit me when I sing along to
the song no then the song plays is like
okay Matt
[Music]
show them your top four Pokemon
I bet you my top four better than your
top four
exactly what I mean I bet you my top
more it would help battle the CP and I
beat your Pokemon that's hard
Dragonite ah oh that's hard can't lie oh
you want to see something cool
oh wow
what nothing show them all my shinies
dude the fact that the first thing I'm
eating is a pepperoni pizza and shiny
it's shiny shiny Sneasel
sneezle
Shiny Magikarp oh I want one so bad I
have two wait can you trade yeah can we
trade can we trade hold on hold on can
we trade I have three shiny tepes hold
on oh listen you ready look
shiny lucky
I really keep it like this you can't
show the camera dead Onyx it like [ __ ]
out shiny lucky Larvitar I traded with
Kyle Johnson Captain Kyle
that's my guy I traded the other day and
he got you might have a shiny Magikarp
you do have a shiny Gyarados
but I could have three of them so it
doesn't matter lucky Gollum
if you want to play the lucky game I'll
play the lucky game too
thank you
I have a lucky Tor chick yeah
do you catch the Tulip is it Matt Two
Lips on this dick Chris come on
yeah
the crust no not the crust like the in
between the crust and the cheese
okay yikes I almost made it who does
that and it's like okay with themselves
[Music]
it's just lame like you're just weird
it's good look at it back to normal
foreign
just stopped recording and Matt flung
into Chris's arms after he burned his
tongue
[Music]
I think we should become really intense
food critics okay me and Chris have done
battle
you guys have done this before and I saw
a lot of funny edits of us struggling to
drink so Chris that was [ __ ] stupid
oh that's so cool I'll do this one yeah
you better so we're we've done this
before and there was a video of me and
Chris really struggling and burping and
we looked like sad little small kids
remember that it was really goofy I
forget it looks sitting on Matt's bad it
was a vlog from a while ago
okay stop bro this is gonna explode
next stop ASMR makes me want to like
punch somebody in the face
I know if it was room 10 it would be
gone in three sets but I don't know
three sex is insane
this woman was trying to teach her
friend how to shock and something so she
punched it open for her and she goes
just open the top and like sip or chug
she said and the lady puts her mouth on
it and opens it instead of sipping she
blows air in and it shoots across the
like golf cart whenever y'all are ready
ready to check out
what would you guys do if I just went
over and started tickling you that's so
cold yeah it's freezing and the house I
think I'm gonna igloo
oh
actually it's almost huge
I feel like her channel is way too many
clothes are those ferociously drinking
soda yeah oh I agree
that was cute
mm-hmm
ah
brain freeze for sure brain freeze for
sure
I'm done
oh
yeah and then what you're saying how you
miss me yeah you miss me and all the
things