this here mirror is about to go through
that there Hammer I just said that the
wrong way around we're vlogging my God
just cracked open that
lid all right guys we're getting ready
to um to leave for what is going on over
there Nick stop it like um oh actually
matter of fact I should Nick put this on
please oh yes we're starting an annoying
triplet today medal and basically
whoever is the most annoying gets their
medal thank you no problem I was wearing
that in the last Vlog I'm not going to
lie um should I bring this or no but
Nick but Nick gets it for obvious
reasons today yeah look it we're about
to head to our tour bus and this is what
Matt has he has his duffel bag and his
backpack on his shoulder I have my bag
and this is everything that Nick you
guys are bringing backpacks you're
bringing four [ __ ] duffel bags Nick I
have to you're bringing 1 2 3 4 5 six
seven bags oh my God I almost forgot my
laptop with my surprise is on it oh my
God that would have sucked for sure dude
oh my God you're aware you have to walk
we have to walk to the bus right now no
someone has to drive me over and then
has to bring the car back has to I two
suitcases two pairs of shoes and four
[ __ ] bag five bags and a stupid metal
on someone has to drive my car is out
there okay let's go next you are a
disgrace I'm just I just have come to
terms with the fact that I'm lazy and
I'm very okay with that I'm a lazy lazy
lazy person and I hate doing anything I
just can't believe it me and Matt were
packed 4 days ago you're and I have to
edit two surprises on the bus I know
three surprises on the
bus you stress me out we'll see you guys
on the bus Matt oh Matt's really
asleep hi good morning
can't really see it's so dark in here is
there like a secret no or a surprise no
I'm just vlogging you for fun okay say
good morning to the Vlog hey we're in
Arizona day two oh it's really
cold I got to brush my teeth before I
speak to anybody yeah no I woke you up
cuz I want to go to the room dude feel
my sock feel how cold I am dude yeah
it's really cold freezing in my
bunk shut that off for now [ __ ] we're
not filming the waking up Chronicles
like that funny
dude it's not that funny dude it's not
that funny dude welcome to episode one
wake up W up
Chronicles anyway we're going to spend
the next two days on the bus getting to
Texas and then we're going to have our
first show in San Antonio you guys where
someone is revealing a surprise who is
it tell
me are you like me Matt and Chris and
wanting to to get out of the house
needing something to do or just want to
buy a gift for a loved one which is why
we wanted to give the sponsors of
today's video SE geek a huge shout out
with over 28 million downloads SeatGeek
is the number one rated ticketing app
there are more than 70,000 events listed
on SeatGeek like concerts festivals and
sports games there are so many artists
going on toward this summer like Tyler
the Creator Sabrina Carpenter the
weekend Beyonce and siza and Kendrick
Lamar me my and Chris recently went to a
Celtics game and we're super excited to
go to more seey caser back each ticket
is rid on a scale from 1 to 10 so you
know you're getting a good deal so look
for the green dots green means good and
red means bad plus every ticket is
backed by their buyer guarantee you know
we came through for you guys you can use
code sternol 10 to get 10% off your next
set of tickets at C geek that's 10% off
tickets with promo code sternol of 10
make sure you click the link in our
description to download the app and have
the code automatically added to your
account so you can use it later thank
you
SE tickle tickle tickle tickle bro
that's not going to work at all oh yeah
stop Chris stop I'll break your fingers
off your body I'm uncomfortable I'm
uncomfortable what was that was that
watch out for the C I just got so
comfortable breathe in breathe
out thank
you up yet whenever we all get into the
bunk I imagine that like we're all
different bugs and we're all like
wiggling into our own little uh part of
dirt I hate being next to a truck like
so ruining of the
view there we are and there's the view
we wanted yeah it's literally grass rail
oh look at Nick Oro maxing over there
you guys want to see a magic trick
before we leave let's see it magician
all right do you see this wooden stick
yes oh my
God I just broke it okay see you can see
there's a clean brake yep do you see the
brake I see the brake do you want to see
the other half
yes whoa oh my God is that a good trick
a good trick and it lines up perfectly
cholo magic dude it's been while it's
been a while who has found cholo Magic
on Instagram Nick can you stop bro shut
them out Nick chill out can I shut them
out on the screen you can't go follow
Nick stop why looks like you have like
stitches on your head cuz your hair is
like going that way and then your other
hair is like falling across it like it
looks like a Frankenstein moment that
didn't it oh my God Chris it like locked
it reminds me it reminds me of all the
stress that you put on yourself and you
do it all for no Reas you do it to
yourself you just need the last minute
packing the last minute editing the last
it do it does it breaks my Str you're
going to be bald you're going to be bald
first and it's going to really suck oh I
know and you're the only one that
doesn't want to be bald like I could
I'll go bald I don't really give a [ __ ]
you on the other hand it's going to hit
you hard today we're going to quiz Nick
on NBA knowledge throughout the entirety
of the tour so Nick we're in Texas right
now tell me the two NBA or tell me the
Texas basketball teams we have the Spurs
yep from where San Antonio that's where
we are right now and the Houston Rockets
very good and I I knew the Houston
Rockets
who is on the Houston Rockets
in Chris why would you say that out loud
tricked you I tricked you okay who is
the who is the starter on the Spurs
right now that's the tallest dude in the
NBA I don't know Nick's super tall no
clue it's NBA everywhere tall it starts
with the
w and it's long in French Williamson no
Willamina
no Waka Waka no should we give him a
first name Victor Victor Victor minaga
yes come on Nick he said it a little
weird okay we're going to keep doing
that at every single City I'm not
looking going to give us all of his NBA
knowledge do let's get a random right
now football team in Minnesota go no no
no nice I'm of Texas football
team uh Texans okay Cowboys yeah Dallas
um who is who is the guy you actually
think he's super hot he played for the
no he's on he's on um he's on the Texan
I don't know the Tex he has a brother
also in the league I don't know his
brother is it not Nick
Bosa oh am I ever going to get this
what's his name JJ Watt never going
to if JoJo watt was sat right where you
are I wouldn't even know I'm talking
about JJ W sitting right here I wouldn't
even know it you have said JJ wat in his
Hut though I'm sure I have I'll show you
I'll show you a picture of them oh my
God there is nothing I love more in this
life than pure authentic Texas barbecue
man it's really loud in here I'm so
scared of everyone I have developed such
insane social anxiety in the past 3
years would you ever go hunting no I
feel way too bad for the animals no but
I a big buck arcade hates to see me
coming absolutely ho the turkey game
where they all fly the mini game God the
bonus round hates to see me with that
shotgun and you got four bulls and three
craters I love this I love that deer
like mid pance that's a good one take a
photo of it that girl in your head ain't
real get the chandelier no no no the
chandelier next house need that I don't
need I would love that Nick look at how
cool that is are you kidding oh my god
oh my god let's take it let's soak in
some history while we're here my the
Pinkerton family we're in a place called
Pinkerton it's making they Liv in this
house during a Great Depression that
10 it was honestly up I want a deer head
on our wall in our next house I don't
care I want it I just it needs to be
pre- murdered soz I'm not going to do it
whose drink is this it was here when we
got here you don't have a I thought it
was my most I thought your drink no no
no guys I have I have a $1.50 on the LA
Dodgers today and they're up 4 to2 in
the the top of the six so we're looking
good I'm going to make $2.50 it's the
opener they just they're coming off the
championship in LA Dodgers are a
lock okay being here makes me want a
beer more than anything ever I know give
me 20 beers I want Pinker merch do you
get one it depends how good the food is
though Nick and Chris just got their
soda I'm still on a water Journey um
these are the best pickles I've ever had
in my entire life not even lying Whole
pork is amazing I'm almost done with my
Mac and Cheese I know the Pinkerton do
it right over here we're going to go
ham eat it you actually hold this half
of the rib Matt you hold the other half
and I'll eat it no I wouldn't do that in
I wouldn't do that in a million
years
hurry oh was it amazing again again
again oh
ni give me your paper towel no
take a I will [ __ ] light your [ __ ] up
stop take a bite paper towel take a bite
first paper towel Nick I will [ __ ] first
take a bite and then he'll get you a
paper towel no he's going to show take a
bite do take a bite I got I got him I
got
him Nick I will [ __ ] I will literally
turn you to a Pinkerton cow give me it
okay what did you guys just do you
didn't do anything why are you vlogging
me cuz we love you are you full get out
of here I just smacked I just dude the
[ __ ] what is going on nothing's
happening nothing's
happening okay the [ __ ] could be
happening I don't know I I want to just
take this this Lantern through a v
through a village and carry it like this
and find find out bad horrible news
about the plague spreading throughout
all of humankind wow it's crazy they
call ribs ribs because they don't call
any other form of meat the body part
chicken legs chicken wings you're right
I'm thinking like they could have done
something crazy like meat on a bone or
something boned meat
why me why is it called baby back ribs
though are these from a baby's back they
just smack
it what what are you talking about dude
we went to the bathroom and there was a
[ __ ] nightmare above the toilet a
nightmare above the toilet shouldn't the
nightmare be in the toilet no it was
above it oh did you take a picture I'm
going to have to go back in there it's
like the no no insert the nightmare
clip Hakuna
Matana no not a wonderful word back in
cheese started like I feel I felt it
like hitting me all once I was like like
that cheese got thicker and thicker and
I was like I hate cheesy mac and cheese
so much I just want enough to cover the
the the the
Mac yeah enough to cover the Mac with
cheese and then I'm good I don't want a
pool of cheese after there stop what are
these eat one it's a pepper absolutely
not but you will no I will
not ah I can't even stab it I will not
eat that oh come on go ahead you have to
I'm not you've been talking about Good
content this is great content Chris will
eat it kind of shap like a j Chris will
eat it hey
Justin eat it Chris will eat it Nick get
that out of my face before I punch your
teeth out and you'll never be able to
eat anything again that you're going a
fire smoothies for life
Chris you want to try it come on no come
on get away I'm not get I'm not I in I
instigate I am not trying try one you
have to try it let me sniff it
no it smells so good you should try it
let me smell no just try
it it's pepper yeah it's good just try
it it smells pepper eat the whole thing
and I'll give you 100 bucks I'm that's
not worth it to me no why I don't want
to it's [ __ ] it's a [ __ ] pepper
you live once you've done crazier things
you eat it no it's not funny cuz I'm
holding it on the fork you got to eat it
you got to eat it but you got to let me
feed it to you no I'm holding it on the
fork no no I don't want it no nobody
else does I don't want it no Dr the
pepper video over can you eat it no I
why not not eating that we're in Texas
it's the perfect time to eat a Pepper
would you ever compete in chil
competition or no I'd make a chili what
are you doing this isn't yours you are
what are you
doing absolutely not not till you take
this no eat a I'll eat a rib if you bite
this not equal definitely equal a bite
of this and a full rib and I'm not
hungry that's spicy it will ruin my
whole this is not spicy I'm not eating a
pepper before we have a show tomorrow
I'm going to [ __ ] myself just take a
bite will you take a bite nope okay well
we're useless no one will be bite the
[ __ ] Pepper take a bite idiot I don't
want it why do why do I want for
funniness you won't take a bite eat this
pickle eat that pickle I would if you'll
bite this I'll I'll eat that if you eat
this I was going to eat those pickles I
will eat that pickle if you bite this no
that's spicy and
hot are you a baby I'm done oh these
Peppers actually you shouldn't eat it
they tend to get hul of in your business
you guys are Dum eat it no you're the
king of eat it I had it on the FL just
take a bite you're the king of eating
food just eat
it what did you just
say eating food take a bite no why it's
not going to kill you I had an unknown
allergy I could actually die you have no
idea it's known enough to the point
where we know it's that's not going to
do anything to you just take a
bite py in the restaurant you eat it
guys want to play penis no
penis I win yeah you do no one's play
congratulations I got a pepper for you
if I bite that at any point in this tour
I get to present to you something and go
eat this and you have to eat it that
could be so much worse no that's a good
deal that's a good deal but what are you
thinking like a bad thing at any point
in time in this whole it can't be like a
gas station sandwich or something it can
definitely absolutely not then I'm not
eating that then well yeah if you're
planning on killing me I'll give you
poison if I give if you present you
arsonic you got to eat it it's like what
you're telling me if I give you [ __ ]
a gallon of antifreeze you had to chug
it quick no it has to be equivalent size
that's I could do equal size but I'm
asking for a nibble you're saying you're
saying eat a [ __ ] unsh platter of
food I'm not doing that just take a bite
same size though so however much he gets
down it's the exact Testa no cuz he's
spicy and hot that's it's not true what
if I took a [ __ ] and I feel here and I
take a bite what you eat it no no it's
like spicy I can I know exactly the 20
minute pepper
e okay dude it's hard you can't even
bite any it yes you can fight into it
first I don't like it okay put it down
we're done it's already making my done
you're the king of food it's already
making my tongue tingle a little
seriously just literally tap it
seriously swear to God that thing is so
spicy kick and hot would you do with
bread no all we're done no Chris is
being a [ __ ] in Tex you eat it no I I
presented the challenge I don't care you
know what I mean it's like asking
[ __ ] John Cena to do the wipe out
course he's the host not doing that it's
like getting Howe Mandel stage no we're
walking the streets of San Antonio to
get Nick's fat ass girl in your head
ain't real how bad do you want me for
real oh um yeah we're going to get ice
cream we just had some insanely
delicious dinner this way over Yonder
wait up I could be in the wrong place I
have to sense My Vibe here Nick why
don't you just open the
phone cuz it says I'm
here we got to just scope it out hey
look it hey guys what's up just sipping
on my milk right now siing on my milk
what do I have do I also you also have
milk you also have milk I wish I was
hoping I was a woman I wish this wasn't
2 feet tall yeah can I get a one scoop
of the lemon lemon in a cup or fold in a
cup please can I do the same thing can I
actually make that a three please tripl
it triplet moment all three lemons yes
please anything else that's literally it
2111 you can the this reminds me of Matt
there's more he's got his shoes don't
fit so I set the world on
fire y like just H thank you I think I'm
good you too yeah we're good we can
bounce here you
go oh this is so good I feel like I'm in
Disney
I love it here cuz it's just like not
real life this is so
good I can't believe people eat like
what do what do you call it first of all
sherbet or sorbet I'm not if I ever say
sorbet just shoot me in the face as a
gay person it's really gay to call
sherbet sorbet I agree that's coming
from a member and an ally well no that's
coming from two allies and a member it's
just H it's so bonus like it's like
extra it's just like yeah it's the flare
that it's like saying like I can't
believe people get this in a a cone
gross it just doesn't seem like the type
of thing you can like eat with a waffle
cone you know lemon was a rogue move for
me tonight thrilled about the choice now
dude [ __ ] thrilled I fully agree
lemon is honestly
like the power move to keep it simple
and effective yes like you know you know
you're not [ __ ] around when you get
lemons like I could the rocky like what
are we talking about this is classic
like I really do love the lemon it's
[ __ ] classic
I can't believe we have a show we should
do like a montage San Antonio with my
pals do that do that no when we first
put all these tickets on for sale you
want to know how many people I thought
were going to buy
them do you guys want to hear fun fact
about the story about the story triplets
tell us I think a majority of our Dream
listen a majority of our live shows have
happened in Texas I think is a I think
we've done like seven shows in Texas
after tomor tomor yeah we really have
gone crazy at I think Carry Me Home
Tonight you have to think when this
video goes live tomorrow we are going to
be on the stage in like 4 hours mhm for
the first show I just want to share a
moment of gratitude while I sit on the
curb in Texas and eat lemon Italian
ice lemon sorbet sorry let me get gay
with it yeah let me get
G anyway hold on
lemon are you guys done yeah cool um I
just want to say that hold
on livon open on the ground go ahead can
I talk yeah cool yes um stop asking if
you can talk just convict the viewer get
off me on my
foot on my foot you're on my foot anyway
I just want to say that this tour brings
so many amazing memories it's only been
3 days and we're already on the random
curb in Texas eating lemon sorbet we
haven't I I'm going to [ __ ] kill you I'm
going to kill you you're going to die
tonight sorry anyway I just want to say
that love to make it to the show
tomorrow I just want to say that the
amount of memor let me live I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry chill chill I'm snap
your glasses in half next time you talk
like that try again I just want to say
that I'm done I'll I'll film this by
myself and I'll insert it in the thing
are we done go just
stop next one of you guys to say that
you're sorb getting thrown across the
street okay go back go the amount of
memories that we make on the show
meeting fans and just out and about is
amazing and we wouldn't be able to make
memories like this right now bad bu we
wouldn't be able to make memories like
this right now if you guys didn't give
us the opportunity to tour all we hit we
hit 4 million subscribers the last time
we were in San Antonio I am a
mess I got I love San Antonio I'm happy
to be back here I love the ever walk but
just grateful for grateful for
experience and
change because every experience our
lemon sorv changes
you thank you we're right by Boot and
hat is that what it's called I don't
know these are sick I wish I was a
little
kid I'm I'm trying to scope out what I'm
going to buy when they're open tomorrow
snowflakes on them
tough what what brain
freeze lemon tbas freeze zesty kind of I
feel like I do want to get one it's a
little zest a little zesty what zesty
you're zesty are you going to get a hat
for show I just zipped this up and like
felt a freeze dude you blasted me with
that ice cream you are blasted dude Nick
these are your type of VI the sequence
boots dude ione's going to wear this
jacket the whole tour you still can't
dry it off it's covered in ice you're
acting like it's lava literally lava all
right I'm ready to go what hat are you
going to get tomorrow I'm scoping it out
I'm thinking maybe that white
one or that one I feel like I do need a
hat no you don't
SC all right let's go and every weekend
you want to find someone to
bang get get out of a room singing [ __ ]
like that that girl in your head ain't
real how bad do you want me for real
frightening so much content coming your
way with the with
the with the sternol triplet Surprise
Party tour
underway did you like that or what you
don't even [ __ ] understand you don't
understand and you will never [ __ ]
understand that's
fine whatever it doesn't matter it
doesn't [ __ ] matter it doesn't
[ __ ] matter shut the [ __ ]
up you don't get it you don't get it
thank you guys so much for watching we
we appreciate you more than you know we
will see you
guys sooner than Friday at 5:30
[Music]
[Applause]