we locked in I can't tell it's so cold
and I already have allergies in my look
at my eye yeah you look sad you want me
to wipe your tear it's [ __ ]
ridiculous Chris you go check give that
a [ __ ] break look at the
camera you just [ __ ] put a hole in
the glass hey guys my
eyeball yeah it's okay dude you look all
right all right well today's car video
finally has a topic everyone thank God
about time put it there
um you're a negative do you want me to
break your finger instead and it is
could you defeat that I got one a short
stack of
pancakes right now yeah I could [ __ ]
defeat that I could defeat that with a
fork knife and a big open mouth and some
syrup of course yes of course if I I
can't imagine eating like a pancake or a
waffle with syrup like that's just so
dry like syrup kind of helps push it
down you need like an O an orange juice
or like a juice I just take the pancakes
straight off the skillet I could walk
out of the house with just that I don't
even cut it up you eat like a biscuit
kind of I me yeah sure I need some
lubricated syrup no I'm good I agree I'm
more of a waffle guy myself it has more
crunch to it no I'm fine with that I
just don't like I don't like flop I
don't like SOG uh guys Matt's not crying
or emotional and um and I'm not
winking I'm not winking every time I see
the fans like wink he did this eye has a
[ __ ] problem someone edit Matt like
squinting but make it look like he's
like win like winking I'll go home mm is
a super super angry leprechaun that's
out of gold like someone just stole his
pot and he's like [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm
going to [ __ ] fridge size one like a
mini one like a Smurf it's a leprechaun
dude Smurfs are not leprechaun sized I I
I feel like you think Leprechauns are
like 2 feet I think I I don't know I
think a leprechaun is more of like a 3T
range 2T range yeah like two 2.5 ft okay
yeah I could defeat it but they have
like a beard they look super old
anything that's like half of my size I
could defeat super angry he's out of
gold and he's like where the [ __ ] is my
gold does he have a gun is he going to
shoot me no he's a [ __ ] angry
leprechaun he has probably magic what
kick him into his pot flip it over and
walk away yeah if he's out of gold I
feel like he's out of spells and [ __ ]
too you know like he's not going to do
you magic what yeah but they don't have
spells I don't know I feel like a
leprechaun is like kind of like in my
like the equivalent to like a rabid like
Angry animal like I feel like it would
like GW at my feet and be mad like I
feel like you do that no
who you know are you talking to
me what about this dear God please
please what are you he burped but I'm
only human but I'm only
human you have to swallow 15 packs of
gum in one hour could you defeat it
absolutely [ __ ] no 15s and it all sits
in your gut like oh I could you know I'm
your stomach for seven years okay so
let's think if it's 15 sticks per pack
that's disgusting and you have 15 packs
that's disgusting 15 * 15 15 * 15 is
25 in an hour [ __ ] no stick that has to
be more than divide that by 60 okay I
could defeat it divide that by 60 two
what 250 225 divided 60 equals 3 3.75
pie of g a minute yeah [ __ ] no are you
crazy I could do it [ __ ] no you could
not no you could you not eat any a meal
that quick little no I absolutely could
no you could not no you could not I
think it would like do you know how like
when um Viet from Willy
Wonka can you let me go do you know how
in the Goosebump series there's that big
pink blob that sucks in everything in
the city yeah I feel like that's how the
big gumball would take take everything
from your stomach and then you know what
I you know exactly what I mean right
don't even say that like it would take
your your corn and your and your your
corn yeah like I'm saying it go in your
stomach like your corn your breakfast
and your and your steak tips and your
potatoes like they all go inside the big
gumball well you wouldn't swallow it
whole I assume andely not that's 3.75
gum per minute you canot [ __ ] do that
like the ratio of that is unbelievable
you couldn't even get gum into you
couldn't even get gum into gum chewy
like like like chewi chewy gum before
that if it's those little [ __ ] ass
Trident ones I can knock them down I
want to see if I could get four you what
I mean like maybe Chu brother chicklets
if I tried maybe chicklets a swarm of
are you listening yes a swarm of male
seahorses sporadically giving birth Nick
what is going on AB imagine you're in
the sea and there's like a 100 male
seahorses surrounding you and they're
sporadically giving birth because have
you seen a video of male seahorses yeah
they just like s out the
babies and they're like pushing babies
out like I'd freak out I'd freak out I'd
be like get the [ __ ] out of here it defe
one goes in your and it like stop yeah
like a [ __ ] se's family could grow up
in my [ __ ] like Canal yeah really
could [ __ ] hate that I would just try
to eat them all once something's in your
stomach it can't live it just dies to
the stomach acid what the [ __ ] camera
you're going to break your [ __ ]
window man
stop oh my God say a wizard that defends
the mighty tower like you picture this
you're at like the end of your uh Trek
you walk all the way up to mount
whatever like Mount like Mount um
crystal ball and oh misery Mount Misery
was good all the way up I said wizard oh
no Mount wizard it's boring like you
can't oh wait it's kind of good though
cuz in like the fic it tells you exactly
who's up there so you're you're going
out Mount wizard you've defeated like
like three levels of like beasts on the
way up okay and you get to the tip top
and there's like a castle and the
Wizard's there and he's like standing
right in the front and he has the beard
and everything the big glasses and he's
like you shall not not enter my castle
and then he's like throwing like fire
where what is my current status like am
I on a horse or do I have I'm assuming
we'd be kind of like um like characters
I'd be like a lizard man or
something be a lizard man okay I have
one question that will answer answer
this for me okay what were the what were
the three stages of beasts that I beat
on the way up to the tower you know like
the C like the Casual ones like uh like
the um like a big spider probably yeah
like a big spider like a flying monkey
maybe like a pig standing on his back
two feet with like a long like I feel
like I got it you can't feel like you
got it it's yes or no it's like how are
you going to beat him and what are you
I'm like a lizard man like I'd go up
there and I'd be like SW i' like swiggle
I don't probably be half horse half man
Centaur and then I'd run up and take my
spell and i' literally Boogie bomb his
ass like over the shoulder alley like
that and it's going to crack right next
to him and then he's going to be dancing
he's going to be a fire wizard I'm going
to have ack of water balloons and I'm
going be emptying them out I'm them in
the face like that as I go I'm I'm going
to go there and I'm going to say I'm
going to like after I beat all the
beasts on the way up and then I'm going
to change yeah into just like a regular
like casual fit okay like sweats in a
hoodie yeah just sweats in a hoodie and
I'm going to go hey man I don't know if
they told you but like your Barbers out
today I'm here to trim your beard a
little bit and
then like the the the salon of and then
I'm going to go and then I'm just going
to like start triming his beard and then
I'm just going to take his like little
scepter thing and kill him with it
you're already at the beard with the
scissors he's just cut his neck open you
know how Bears catch a salmon and rip
the skin off it and
then could you survive being like in the
bearest position like you have to catch
a fish I'm not and Des skin it while
it's alive and then eat it am I a bear
or am I me no you're you and you have to
live [ __ ] no yeah no I couldn't you have
to catch the I feel like I feel like
because of how many salmon are are
swimming Upstream wow it's a little
tongue
twister I feel like I could catch one
but I don't think I have what it takes
to like I'm like afraid of fish like
when flip a fish is like when like a
fish is flopping around me I'm like get
away it's just like disgusting ew yuck
yucky like if a fish is like looking at
me with its [ __ ] eyes on both sides
of his head like okay buddy can't even
look straight looking at me with his
crooked eyes and he's going like this
like I'm going to I'm going to be fre I
could fet a fish with ease you could not
f a fish yes I can you start at the tail
and you like ease up to it this
[ __ ] to the face on a rainy day
I already see it oh yeah could you
defeat it it's going to that tell you
guys of the time I got bullied during
field day no uh it was like field day
for the school and I don't know who the
[ __ ] I thought I was and we were playing
like kickball but I knew it was at like
a baseball um field and I brought cleats
to school wow that's embarrassing field
day yeah like neon cleats and then we
were like playing oh Nick did have neon
yellow CLE and I put I put cleats on to
play like kickball and the kid was like
making fun of me and I um I cried you
should have [ __ ] CLE his neck no I
hate that kid do you want know who was
that's so funny cuz he thinks he's
somebody but he's
not oh Loser yeah loser [ __ ] that kid
what was the question um could you take
that soccer ball to the neck the face
yeah I've done it before I can do it
with like that red Ros type skin
oh like I'm like cold already assuming
so it's like an hour into like playing I
feel like every person has experience
that in their life who hit a baseball
bat off of a soccer ball and like the
The Reflex of the air hit the bat in
their
face yeah and he knocked his teeth out
no he bit through his cheek yeah that's
what it was that kid used to pull his
balls out when we played hockey the
locker like balls in my man yeah crazy
okay I'm doing one more actually this
guy no we're done no Matt done toast
you're absolutely [ __ ] yeah you're
done you're done he's the ultimate boss
he really is when I saw him I sweat like
I was sweating
the I just put he's the trainer in the
um boxing one or maybe yeah you like to
do the practice thing yeah they're fun
nerd Medusa no no I'm done I'm toast I'm
toast you think you're done I'm doing
the camera thing that Percy did and then
I'm going to slay her ass see I I can't
I couldn't do it cuz I have fomo like
she'd be like like she's like really
enticing she like i' need to know what
she looks like like if meduso is in real
life I like are you a Badd or what like
you're kind of a Badd in the movie you
have to no you could look at photos
right of what Medusa idiot I don't know
if I knew what she looked like if she
had an Instagram knew what yeah if she
knew if I knew what she looked like
already I don't think I'd have to look
like if I was like oh you're like like
know what you're at yeah then I don't
think I need to see you but like if
we're in combat battle and she's like
well she'd be like telling me to look
though and i' be like oh like I might do
it you're weird I feel like peekaboo
myself like I be oh I might look could
you look at her in the eyes through a
mirror like if you were both looking in
a mirror together you could see her
whole face think so I think so I don't
know though I don't know how it works I
don't know I don't know could you defeat
a rattlesnake with no Venom so like it's
going to bite you a lot but you you
won't die to the bite you're it's not
going to [ __ ] see you're already
wrong so it's not going to bite me once
it's going to Slither at me I'm going to
grab him by the head and say I'm okay if
you're a rattlesnake with no rattle
you're just a baby toy it has the rattle
no Venom I'm a Snake Charmer no you're
not Nick am do a little belly dance I'd
get shirtless and go boom boom it would
be under my
trance I'd charm your guy
snakes yeah is it a crazy babies need to
chew on [ __ ] too like the same way
puppies do te on thing get their teeth
isn't that kind of crazy I don't think
you just realiz teething no I'm not oh I
just think it's no when you chew teeth
yeah he no I'm not when you chew it
helps your teeth grow as in baby cuz it
rubs against your gums and it helps the
gum like it helps the cute I could never
breastfeed my I literally just did that
I I could never breastfeed my nipples
are way too sensitive to breastfeed way
too we're going to move on could you
defeat the American Ninja chent warped
wall [ __ ] [ __ ] no I could I my back you
should run up that warped wall they run
and they like just miss it and fall down
a little I'd run and like on my
back like they have to that would be the
funniest thing I think I've ever seen in
my life Dro 14 ft keep in mind it's so
impressive when people run up the wall
sorry to interrupt you I have to when
people run up the wall and they don't
use their arms to pull up and they just
like and then like stand no I can't do
if you guys don't know what we're
talking about inserting a clip warp wall
American Ninja Warrior look at these
[ __ ]
train
[Applause]
run see the thing that's crazy to me is
they just did all the other [ __ ] too
they're FL they're flabber no they're
what's it called when you're drained of
energy flat famished no that's hungry
drained no it's not it's like I was
going to say flabber acid but it's not
it what is
fatigue fatigue Fue is the word that I'm
looking for fatigue sounds like a good
meal it sounds like yeah like an all
right I got two no it's no it fatigue
would be a bread you I could do the warp
Dall I had like a 100 fet of leeway I
can't believe they do it from like
they're getting no running start it's
like bro what you can jump 14 ft
essentially no you can't there's a wall
no but like they got like no running
starts like that's kind of impressive
they can't jump no three nights in the
woods
I wouldn't want to do it but I think I'd
survive unun easily survive you got to
like find your meals though I wouldn't
eat and I wouldn't do anything you don't
three days is nothing because all you
need is like maybe one day of like clean
water and at that point it doesn't I
just be starving and hungry and wait it
out and hope I don't get attacked do you
have like a helicopter rescue team on
the day three yeah it's just like you
you can walk out you know where to go
you're done you're done where do you go
I don't know CU a fiction but do I get
brought to like Sanu you the the third
night the third night you go to bed and
wake up and you're just in your bedroom
oh easy 3 days though full 3 days i' I'd
be free imagine who that lady's walking
backwards Frozone if he was a bad guy
like when he was mad Nick where do you
come up with this [ __ ] froz Frozone
would never be a bad guy if if he's too
nice if if okay settle down [ __ ] um I
have like no opinion on that to be
honest I'm like yeah like in this
scenario I'd have to be like can't
picture him against me come on you know
okay a Boiling Pot of water [ __ ] no I'm
done what do I have to do put my hand in
dump it on
me I don't know CU you defeat it okay
yeah I just drain it in the sink Get
Wrecked yeah
same 15 really angry second graders and
all you have is a bowling ball as a
weapon absolutely but you can only use
the bowling ball like you can't like no
fist on like no it's just like two
bowling balls in your hands have to
smash honestly be easier second graders
15 second graders and they're pissed
have you seen the video of the guy bench
pressing or like squatting stop he's
squatting a ton of weight and then he
like kind of stutters and then he like
falls back and lets go and then he fell
to the ground and his head is on the
ground and like nine plates of like
weights land right here like if it land
on his head it would have squished it
like a watermelon and his brains would
went everywhere and he missed by like
this much of never
again it was the it was like during like
a lifting competition a night guarding a
castle in like those goofy tin outfits
and he's like absolutely [ __ ] yeah
absolutely I don't think so those those
look pretty impet I throw a CD slot like
a CD oh like a ninja star yes right
through his eyes ding
that's you thought that quick exactly
you've been thinking about it exactly no
I don't know from from dist I feel like
those don't even actually usually have
people in it no I feel like it' just be
the suit ah happy about it would you
take down I want one of those tattooed
on me a knight with Shining Armor an
elephant stamping at you a swarm of
elephants going boom boom boom punching
the ground as they walk up to anyone can
everyone's
dead yes everyone there not one person
yes you to I'd lay on my side go yeah
run right over me no they wouldn't Nick
You' be toast a what a baby elephant
steps on you you're [ __ ] Splat what's
the speed of which an elephant can run
why' you ask it like you were in
Jeopardy I don't know I need to know I'm
going to guess hold on if I can get
within 5 mph you guys owe me like a
something big okay the fastest speed an
elephant can run I'm going to go 26 mph
how fast how many you say 26 25 no way
actually oh
no they average 25 kilm on the daily
basis but it's about 40 mph they can run
easily 40 mph what isn't you say bolt
like see how fast 40 no a rabid dog and
you're in one of those dog suits but
he's like really angry like I want to do
this I want to do this you're sick in
the head no I want to do it no you don't
he was telling me this send me nine dogs
at me I'm taking all of them he was
telling me this I will gladly do that
like actually cuz it's nothing dude they
don't feel [ __ ] all you feel is a little
pinch no you feel it for sure I doubt it
attacked by rabbit dogs no but release
angry Mini chaas at me like a hundred of
them so I'm just
okay you have to eat a whole stick of
butter on a full [ __ ] no [ __ ] no [ __ ] no
[ __ ] no [ __ ] no [ __ ] no wrap it
up you don't like butter this much I'd
be disgusted if I had a stick of but no
on a full stomach and then you have to
chug a
soda a spray a spray buttery soda and
you have to close your eyes Nick and
shake it around like that why do you
have to close your eyes so no one can
see so you can't see anyone [ __ ] that
and then everyone the whole City's
watching you have to do it the whole
city what is going on I don't know my
God is it the 4th of July too all right
guys thank you so much for joining us
this Friday we will see you when we see
you thank you nice little shimmy thank
you before the video ends make sure you
go down and subscribe
[Music]