would I want to give Nick a present for
sharing the background oh my God
those were in the car
and all the things
[Music]
I saw them I was like no way I was like
I was just gonna become an annual thing
I'm sorry like I didn't it was so on a
spur of the moment so I didn't have time
to get you there I didn't say I kind of
want it I think it'll be good I'll take
something all right Jimmy's back in the
car yes okay
[Music]
last video with Jimbo we we put on our
Instagram story
questions to ask our dad but this time
dad doesn't have Instagram so he used
Google and it's questions that he has
written down for us instead that kind of
randoms random random random is good dad
you know what I wanted to say if anyone
asked you like what's your favorite food
I was thinking about this in length one
day if someone asked if someone asked
you what your favorite food was you
could say spaghetti and meatballs that
day and then if they get asked the same
question like a week later you could
have seen a burger commercial I love
that you're talking about this right now
it could be different every week
that's why there's videos of us like a
year and a half ago in like a year ago
where I'm like talking about like oh oh
I thought my matte like mashed potatoes
and not like but it's it depends on what
movies
I'm so happy Christmas because there's a
clip of Chris saying I'll never wear
Stripes again into my life he probably
wore strike Christmas
[Applause]
or one of the questions that someone
asked us like oh what's one of the
weirdest things that you keep like in
your nightstand and I had talked about
in a video how I had garlic salt in my
nightstand because it was in a phase of
I was like eating soup a lot and I do
keep that garlic salt to my nightstand
but I've moved past this right I have
more things in my nightstand so when we
asked the question on stage and Bob's
Beauty and the whole crowd was like
garlic salt garlic salt and I was like
what did they say I was like they're
like agreeing and they're all in unison
like I was like ever so they think it's
garlic salt forever and it's just Alex
will just show a period of time all on
the same page they all said it together
they all reminded me of that and I was
like oh my God it was just a crazy
moment so that that's what that's like
cool moments when with the viewers
remind me of [ __ ] that I totally forgot
happened I love like I love when that
happens oh oh each person it has to be
kind of spontaneous though so don't
think too much okay but describe
yourself in one hater
I'm the biggest hater ever oh that's
none I plot on 90 of people's downfall
wow Nick Nick that's so untrue you bring
joy to so many people that's good
that's one word to describe you then and
you know what the answer's Gonna Change
It's Gonna Change I know it's gonna
change
tomorrow no nervous is a good one but I
can't make that my whole thing one word
that pops what are you uh
all about
um one word delicious is mine
um delicious for me I'd say right now
delicious right now it's motivated I
feel like oh yes thank you motivative
Matt I was trying I was trying to think
of that my own question that I asked and
I I'm stumped
not yet okay we'll wait till next week
what about funny
inquisitive
what does that even mean
that's nice that's a good one next
question and it could change like in
tomorrow if I was asked myself the same
question is that change 100 it could
change
[Music]
before like oh before you go on to the
great beyond oh what activity what
activity do you want to do before like
if you like you have to do an activity
before you die what is it okay like
right before you die or is it like no
just you want to get this thing you
gotta scratch it off okay scratch it off
the list exactly I want to go on like a
big roller coaster that goes upside down
because I still haven't yet because I'm
scared that can be arranged I mean
something like I have something that
like the police could get called on me
say it so I don't know if I should say
it okay but like just like the
satisfaction like no victims obviously
but light an entire like house on fire
and watch it in golf influence
I know our house but our house like just
the satisfaction I think of like
throwing a match like you know like the
movies and like throw a match like a
whole place blows up like I want that
you want that moment you want that
feeling but no problem
you want to be uh sometimes no no I want
to burn a house down we actually want to
burn but nobody no no one in it no
personal building it's like just like a
really large wood structure it's just
not a bonfire yeah it's boring it's all
just like a pile of wood like a mock
house and then put on the beach and burn
it
okay but that costs money and it's like
see mine's really lame I just want to
play another five on five hockey game at
some point in my life I play hockey you
could do a club team you could get on a
club yeah but like I don't want to join
a team I just want to play a game and
call it a day I want to play one more
game yeah five on five yeah
you know what I'm gonna have that
arranged actually yeah I was just gonna
see we're gonna fly me out we're sorry
we're already three best summer memory
oh best summer memory my favorite summer
memories I guess you guys didn't have
any good summer memories I'm trying to
think I'm like I think going to Florida
with Nathan I agree one of my favorite
summer memories we're talking like all
summers right not just this year no your
favorite even your child no childhood
like all summer I found it really funny
when we went to the cape and Chris got
on a scooter that the handles weren't
matching up with the wheel and he went
to go straight and he kicked like really
really hard but the wheel was broken and
he slid like 30 feet it was raped up my
name
it was just so funny someone else's
painting it was so funny because he
connected he could clearly easily ride a
scooter it's just the wheel was broken
so it was just funny because it was like
such a simple task just went so wrong
you see here's where I'm at
I think just going to the cape a lot the
cape in Florida trips are really nice
Florida for our birthday is that one
vlog
really good yeah okay when you're in the
when you're in the hallway and I go Dad
what do you think about this [ __ ] even
I'm watching you walked right back you
know what I first I could hear in the
background there was a problem with the
room I wasn't mad I wasn't mad you know
what I was doing I was in there and I
was trying to like you guys because I
heard someone go this room smells like
smoke and I I heard it coming in so I'm
kind of like really and I was a little
instigated yeah yeah I was a little I
was a little aggravated because in my
head I'm like oh now we got a way to go
get the room changed and like yeah we
did need to do it you don't want the fun
and games you want to get to your room
yeah and I was just coming in like kind
of like what motivated yeah like I just
want to settle in we go out here and
it's like so you just wanted to see for
yourself what was up yeah I didn't mean
but it was funny the way you said
absolutely yeah that [ __ ] was on that's
like one of my favorite Clips ever that
was Winter
I would say lying down while the snow is
falling I'm just looking at it I think
[Music]
[Laughter]
what sport would you want to be like I'd
want to play hockey and I'd want to be a
center
yeah yeah Count Me In hockey defenseman
wow it's the only sport I played Matt
only when I kind of you just want to
hurt people right now I feel like the
two sports that I like the most were
hoggy and Lacrosse
I don't think you could pay me enough
money to step foot in like a lacrosse
goalie ever again oh no it was fun while
it lasted but once I was going home with
bloody shins yeah you need to be a
little crazy no yeah for sure very
suiting position for Matt but like now
it's like it'd be so weird if I had
animal inside of him was going a little
crazy oh yeah do you want to know what
mine is yes pickleball what no I wanted
to make you laugh that's okay
I was just thinking of what pickleball
was just show up at these beautiful
courses and like
there is stress involved obviously
because you need to cash but you need to
play golf
and like all the foreign animals and
[ __ ] like a kookaburra running around
you like open up in Hawaii and then oh
and then you go to Pebble Beach and it's
like oh my God how many Pebbles do you
think is that Pebble Beach right now
epidillian couple hundred you know what
it's all like big
hugees yeah
pebble rock Boulder Beach it sounds like
a Mario Kart or like a fortnight like
landing spot okay next question oh I
have to pee Chris what quality would you
want from each brother like what would
you want I would want Chris's creativity
oh that was actually really
complimentary I honestly agree what
quality would you want them I wouldn't
want Nick's drive and passion on things
he
doesn't like or likes he's very strong
opinionated person uh Matt
I'd want
I'd say Chris's creativity is good one I
agree um I also think like Chris is like
simple-mindedness well a lot of you do I
gotta take all of it or can I just say
something a lot from me Dad can I just
take a little bit well the question is
to take one does it got to be like a
whole thing oh just shut up I take a
little bit of Nick's just anger towards
people because sometimes I feel like I
could be a little bit too kind but it
kind of makes up for NYX a little bit
maybe if Nick's a little extra like that
and yeah more kind we just trade it a
little bit Yeah and then we neutral no I
kind of enjoy hating everyone and
everything okay like this is what I'm
talking about it's like a fun isn't that
you're in denial I don't want you to be
angry no no parent wants oh by the way
before I forget
if you're watching this give give your
care give her or your dad parenting
Guardians yeah a big hug oh that was
awesome I love you like I'm gonna be I'm
gonna advocate for the parent out there
go hug your mama dad or your grandma or
whoever you know yeah and tell them you
love them
or not with each other it's so important
it's so important sorry to interrupt you
really sentimental moment cardi B and
offset of a meal a meal together what is
it cardi B and offset the rappers oh
yeah
me and Matt never said anything from
each other I did I said I take a little
bit of your anger I would takes Matt
Matt's cool calm and collected just not
talkative I would what
we want you guys to think back when you
were little like I mean like in your
pajamas
did you watch on TV that you remember
the most LazyTown oh what I remember the
most I couldn't tell you one spongy
episode SpongeBob remember the most yeah
it really sticks in your head when you
were little SpongeBob Drake and Josh
iCarly SpongeBob
SpongeBob by far though if you didn't
answer this before I mean if you
answered it before like I said with my
games what was your favorite arcade like
old school Pac-Man old school oh I love
Darkness I love Donkey Kong Pac-Man I'm
so dog [ __ ] at Donkey Kong but it's so
fun
um Pac-Man I gotta say Pac-Man too I'm
really good at Pac-Man better Mick lugs
Dig Dug too
oh
[Laughter]
I'm kidding you all right
all right I feel like a grocery cart's
way too big but a basket's too small
I kind of agree like that that one's a
rare medium so yeah you're not gonna
wheel it around to get a few things in
the store yeah but you don't want to
carry a basket like if you get like a
gallon of milk and put it in the thing
you carrying it's already like kind of
too heavy to be walking around with
absolutely probably get that last
but then if you get it lasted you're
gonna Crush everything that yeah you
can't with the bread yeah it's just
nothing there's quite a dilemma with
that little basket yeah I agree I agree
it's a little basket yeah [ __ ] them I'm
never grabbing a basket I'm basking on
Wheels is money though oh it's so good I
love the basket on Wheels see if you you
know like you'll never catch me carrying
a basket if there's a car in the store
even if I'm grabbing like three things
I'd rather just push the whole card yeah
it's just always hard honestly yeah but
a cart's too big I feel like if I'm
grabbing something that's sometimes only
gonna fit in the basket I'll just use my
hands um
in the summer and some guy had
flip-flops on and he was sitting at the
front of the grocery store I remember
and I absolutely crushed his [ __ ] Toe
with about I gotta [ __ ] hair on my
[ __ ] candy we got 300 worth of
groceries I ran right over his [ __ ]
big toe and he had flip-flops on one day
I want to wear like the most bizarre fit
to a beach or like known to me do this
already what yeah no I wasn't looking at
oh no I thought something you guys are
talking to something different
guys
I was gonna say something what I want to
wear like the most bizarre outfit to a
beach like in my life yeah what is this
guy Matt shut up and just see the looks
I get
so you gotta go high black socks High
black socks Timberland boots no
flip-flops no to a beach what's weirder
at a beach yeah but oh yeah okay I'm
gonna do like like high black socks
no a speedo a dress shirt and then a
jacket like a winner winter coat with a
shirt and a puffer yeah
and then a propeller hat with ski
goggles
I say do it yeah I say do it too I say
live out your dreams like and then just
like try to see all the bizarre looks
you get I think shitley got so funny one
night I walked to CVS with uh um
with a cowboy hat on Timberland boots
and a dress shirt that's not bad and and
purple shorts thanks for having me of
course
it's my gift
thank you welcome
I have another one
how sweet I'll give I feel bad about the
gift
don't feel bad about the gift I'm not
worried I think I'm advocating for Matt
to say
something at the end because he it seems
to be quite important for a lot of
people no oh yeah like the yell or
something yeah he has to screaming
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
for my brothers