do it again do it again do it again wait
do it
again yes girl not really
[ __ ] and then what you saying how you
miss me yeah you miss me and all the
things that we did we said we going to
Trav from the island to Madrid we had a
lot of plans but they
all all because of someid but it's okay
cuz I'm moving different don't be saying
nothing when I'm p with
B what is up guys welcome back to our
Channel today we're going to have a fun
time and film an awesome special video
for you also we also all just got
haircuts so look at this new haircut
Vlog this going to be F
horrible Matt's not excited cuz of mine
and Chris's video idea but it's okay cuz
me and Chris are excited basically what
we're going to do is we're dude you need
a new shirt that know just screams dis
shuffled my sleep shirt it's my sleep
shirt basically what we're going to do
is we're going to go to the grocery
store and we're each going to pick 10
food items right and then we're going to
do a random generator thingy and then
we're going to like have to eat whatever
one you land on whatever and So when you
buy your 10 foods you have to be
strategic cuz you could be setting
somebody else up to eat it but it could
also be you that's going to eat it and
I'm not excited I I hate these videos
honestly I think they're [ __ ] really
annoying and I'm going to have to
[ __ ] throw up and I'm going to puke
everywhere so I'm really excited all
right I need to find my shoes all right
guys we've each picked our 10 we just
went to Ral or V wherever the [ __ ] we
were and we each picked 10 items um at
the store and now we're going to reveal
them and we shopped individually so we
don't know what the other one got first
thing I got is Full
Throttle what the [ __ ] is full I don't
know what this is but I got a full that
looks alcoholic I yeah what is that did
you have to scan your ID no what if it
has like alcohol in it energy drink okay
never mind coconut water e some raisins
I almost got raisins cream cheese oh I
want to eat the whole thing I want that
cream cheese frosting cream cheese yeah
but it's like cream cheese FR chees
frosting no that's that's like a gross
Nick that's like not the regular
frosting that's like frosting no it's
good going to taste six left Fanta
jell some pine nuts ah okay some bacon
bits yes oh my god let's real bacon
pieces bacon oh my God that makes me
feel like a little
dog
making here easy
cheese for me easy cheese dud easy chees
I can feel my stomach getting like
lighter dude like it just feels like
it's going to a dill pickle in
a oh my God a bag the bag still pickle
if I land that I don't think I'll make I
literally can't eat that sh oh my God I
hate pickles bro and then the last I
don't write the rules it's called
common what it
called [ __ ] man it's spelled coming
that's why I thought it was hilarious
not it's not I know it's not but it's
called com it's [ __ ] all right I
unfortunately got coconut water as well
wow look at that unfortunately it also
got raisins wow got raisins so those are
my I just I feel like we all hate
raisins and coconut water had to make a
classic love yes okay then we got lemon
juice I love lemon juice unpopular
opinion I could drink this all it might
sour I could drink that all okay this
one I got cuz it's like one of you
really like it and the other one hates
it black licorice jelly beans black
licorish and I know Nick likes it and
Matt hates it so I got it I don't know
if I like licorice I like the jelly be
90% cacao dark chocolate I love dark
chocolate I hate dark chocolate this
sh's probably disgusting this is why I
got a hassle at self checkout I got two
individual green beans weird joanni
Greek yogurt F I need a break
I oh my God hold on Nick get down here
give me a second a Haro
pepper fix your hair kid land on that I
don't know what I'm going to do I really
hope I don't land on that oh my God
that's actually scary Chris aren't those
like really hot what if someone like yes
Matt oh my god really good and then my
last
one Kobe
Jack there's no way you're you're so
weird you're frightening I had to get
Kobe Jack bro I'm sorry okay I had to I
feel like we haven't ever really I don't
think there's one of person that I like
I really would not want to eat other
than Chon yogurt I also unfortunately
got coconut water wow all right Super
Cash goldfish okay love it keep Super
Cash yeah Pringles okay Pizza Pizza
Pringles it looks like you got smack oh
Pizza Pringles no those are those are
gross sugar Combs oh that's a good one I
I knew you guys would go mostly bad so I
was trying to make it so that we had
like some joy in here as well just like
a gross thing I thought to have with
other stuff a York Peppermint Patty kind
of nasty I love those
done strawberry
applesauce how do you even find that did
you like go in there and look for that
or did you just find a raw egg you're
sick you are an absolute sick you're
sick in the head um cream soda I'm not
eating a raw hot sauce awesome hot sauce
that I'm trying to keep it
fun Matt the is
Nightmare that's it for me to pick who's
trying what I have this app called
Chooser on my phone never heard of it
before today for example I'm going to
put all I'm going to put these four
fingers on the screen at the same time
and it'll pick one of my fingers three
never felt like this under it picked my
middle finger this is just for practice
everyone put their finger everyone put
their finger 1 2 three one two and then
that will be the person oh gr gross I
don't want to open the yogurt yet CU
it's going to make r
s something smells like literally like
sin no is it the common dude it's got to
be the cuming I really hope I don't get
Chris got cuming all over the sink I
really hope I don't get that [ __ ] bro
okay does mom use [ __ ] and tacos I feel
like it smells
like Ready set
go two oh my God this
is two green beans I wish I got
that
no Vitamin Water that's not Vitamin
Water whatever Vitamin Water making [ __ ]
up more than that drink it drink it I
filled my mouth I filled my mouth I
swear to God it was not good drink drink
drink
it I'm going to take advantage of
having I'm going to take advantage of
having I'm going to use these as like
[ __ ] no you have to eat them all man
yes you
do take that fro and eat it
ew eatting It Go
yes all right move it move it next Matt
dark chocolate eat the whole Square no
you have to eat the portion that's
delivered it's too greeny can't you that
for I feel like I'm going to throw 30
more things left oh big jump is it good
he's like go Matt go go go all right
ready please be
chis yes Che easy cheese easy cheese is
nothing bro I feel like [ __ ] shake it
first Happ I got it tast like the Goofy
movie remember the kid that eats the the
cheese no just do it is it not coming
out oh my God look at that look at
[Applause]
that all right next next next hurry
hurry Chris oh my God that was the worst
thing I've ever had oh thank you
guys it go go go you got to eat the [ __ ]
go go go Nick the whole thing the whole
thing the whole thing yes good job man
go again go said go
again please don't
be yes
eat the yogurt the yummy yum go eat it
eat it Nick
eat eat
it sick Nick cream soda Matt please be
me the cream soda you got the cream
sod is he actually throwing up okay okay
okay Nick you got to drink the cream
soda Nick you have to drink the cream
soda just took fting off the
floor all right guys that [ __ ] easy
cheese was the most disgusting thing
I've ever had no one
ever no one ever in their life should be
come in and then yoga and then pudding
all right ready the combo of that was
terrif God give me
a you're so we're going to get a noise
complaint you have to be be quiet oh my
God I have to eat this [ __ ] dill
pickle [ __ ] pudding back to back was a
nightmare sniff it no do it no it's it
it's not my challenge you got it oh guys
I really I really po up to say hello I
really can't he's saying hi take a b oh
my God I'm going to throw up get the B
okay take a bite oh my God I can't do
this guys I hope I get like a lemon
juice that I need something else that's
not human can't do this hurry up you
have
to that's good that's a good bite just
eat it you're good you're good put it
away the trash Oh my God put it over
there get away from me whatever you do
it's please don't be me please don't be
me please be Matt yes mat this is all
you oh if I got that I would have died
oh my God is one of the worst things
I've ever had in my life oh no I feel so
bad I feel so bad man I just feel bad
for that doesn't deserve this oh that
was so gross are you okay I want the
next
one please oh Nick throttle is it good
go ahead try it try it try it go try it
it says
citrusy don't
oh tastes like laser cray what it tastes
like laser cray laser cres is laser tag
place used to [ __ ] laser tag at it
tastes like laser CR my throat is on
fire okay next it tastes like laser CR
where get it nice it's gross isn't it
you forgot how gross it was
right oh
no I tried to warn you it was bad Matt I
actually almost just threw up the
coconut water's awful oh my God oh my
God oh my God I can't get it again I
can't get it again want the coconut
water okay guys if I get the please give
him the please I'll take these I don't
want them I don't want them I don't want
them is he happy why is he happy he's
getting them he just doesn't want the
taste of the thing okay ready I can't do
this I'll die oh my God you're okay I'll
take it thank you God thank you God it's
been a while since I've eaten something
but I got three in a row so Friday okay
oh my God I going throw up I
can't Matt
okay I can't get the yogurt it I I feel
like everything I got is just like fire
and
spice so bad wash it down man fire and I
really hope that he get he get some
[ __ ] Aero pepper dude
no if I get the chani yogurt
I'm no what that the chani oh god dude
okay strawberry
applesauce I hope it's me so that I
don't have to have the yogurt okay oh
dude that means not oh look at how much
water just try it Nick Nick try it good
it's probably good it's probably
yummy oh he likes
it he likes it was it yummy no I just
wanted a lot to line my throat if I have
to
have line is go go go
go come on moving the let's go Nick get
on
here if this is me I'm diving over the
table oh
no
no we don't have have
y oh my
[Music]
God yes oh my
God I oh my God the jaani is I think
what I wanted least and I bought it
oh
oh my God I can't even sniff it I can't
even smell it you have to have to eat it
you have to eat it oh my God it's so
chunky okay sure not
expired is it huh either way you got to
take a
bite there you're
good let's go let's
move
come on CH come on oh my God it tastes
like Middle
School
pepper Matt come on eat the
pepper you have to do
it I want pepp it's screaming I don't
want the pepper I don't want the
pepper oh Matt chill be careful spit it
out spit it out spit it out spit it out
mat don't eat it all don't eat it all
don't eat it all you actually can't eat
the whole thing it's so spicy Matt spit
it out spit it out spit it out it's a
[ __ ] oh my
God I
need it's so hot it's so hot it's so hot
[Laughter]
Li said
come on me
jell he sounds like
Bigfoot oh my God P of jell
oh oh my
I on fire
mat Matt Matt eating that you
okay e taking me
out oh my
no coconut water next oh my God 1 2
3 thank you God thank you God we all got
one Chris it's fair you're
okay taking that big of a bite of the H
Arrow I have I have a proposition what I
didn't know it's was going to be that
hot that's so hot mat you took a bite of
a h almost ate the whole thing it's so
hot the lemon juice will help if you
ever get there lemon juice would make it
worse I don't know oh don't H me take a
SI it's so bad oh my God please God
don't be me than you BAC it [ __ ] come
on I'm so happy I don't have that that
look so bad you're okay lemon
juice oh my God oh my
God next oh my is it all gone uh decent
amount oh my God that was so
impressive licorice I love lemon juice I
do lemon juice all day I'm not eating
this whole thing are you okay yeah it's
really hot oh my God look at it oh it
was
[Music]
corroded good yeah next is it good
delicious oh so bad come on H like Willy
Wonka Willy Wonka yeah just like that I
don't know pine nuts what if I'm
allergic to pine nuts I don't know
you're finding out right now never mind
wa you missed dude
next me oh c got all
there Kobe
Jack sure give it to
me anything after that Al
Arrow took a bite out of several layers
of Jesus Christ raisins come
here it's not helping it's not
helping he sounds like a Caron I don't
know why he's
like you okay last one's an a raw
egg drink some milk you got [ __ ] on your
face all right let's
go raw
egg oh my God oh my God Nick oh my God
guys this is a Moment of Truth oh my
watch oh my God oh my God hold thing
hold
thing you have to have some of it for
the video ni thank you guys for watching
is pleasure Nick we're never doing this
again you have to I'm absolutely not you
have to I'm absolutely you have to you
made it already that's Lally cheat way
out this is gross Chris I don't care you
have to do it drink drink drink drink
drink swallow it oh Nick ew I'm not
swallowing that one's going to have a
lot of um that one's going to we're
going to need a lot to redo that one
this is going to have to get like 10
million views for me to redo that I'm
I'm yeah 10 million no that's mine okay
I'm not doing that yet unless it hits 10
million views easily Matt what was the
worst thing you
ate mine was easily the easy cheese like
they just how fake oh my God okay
goodbye
everybody he's going to bed okay good
night good night
man saying how you miss me yeah you miss
me and all the things that we did we
said we going to travel from the island
to Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
all why all because of someid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
saying nothing p with other [ __ ] for
my brothers