Matt stolo does laundry after versus
tour miss me and all the things that we
did we said we going to travel from the
island to Madrid we had a lot of plans
but they
alled I just farted what you know
laundry laundry laundry I was trying not
to pee my pants laughing when we were
filming a podcast earlier I could hear
the [ __ ] [ __ ] tumbling well like
we're in overtime right now sorry I just
wanted to get the whole outfit for a
second we're in overtime right now with
the we're in
overdrive we're going to risk
overloading the
motherboard stop touching me cool hat
Nick why did you wear it speaking of
things building up because of tour our
car I hate that what don't say that
nothing built up the laundry built up
there's a lot of sack and goop on our
car cuz it was parked under a tree for 4
days we both just over but we're going
to the car wash to get that [ __ ] clean
yeah scrub a dub [ __ ] Dub with
Nick put on his cool car wash hat I want
it to look as frat as I can all my
[ __ ] clothes are still in the
suitcase so I got the most questionable
fit on ever I don't like this hat either
and the shirt's too tight it's the I'm
not the shirt is way too tight fair I'm
not watching it it's the only shirt that
I have I'm not washing your
hats go get a
[Music]
hat the kids don't know about this one
no
all right I've never done this before so
first let's show them how dirty the car
is cuz of tour o that's like every
single window even the back and
look gross dirty and I'm not I'm not
even usually like a oh I'm not even
usually like a oh our car has to be
clean and cute and cool I just like cars
that move but this shit's gross like
sticky to the touch so we're fixing her
up today hold on is this free it says
free
oh no it's not free oh Spot Free Rin
like it will make it Spot Free oh
whatever I thought it was like a free
Rin I thought we were getting lucky no
trucks wo woah wo
wo um uh 12 minutes get to spraying wo
wo wo oh I think we get oh I think I
just did water I don't think I did soap
kid what I think I just did I don't even
know if we need that much soap now get
this scrubbing buddy
who oh this dial actively changes it low
pressure low
pressure away from me point that away
from they'll do the rinse for now no
we're high pressure rinsing or you got P
pull the Nick lower my pressure I
can't Nick I can't fly away should I go
in the car no okay hold on we're at
normal rates
oh I like the dial I like the dial it
was on soap this idiot wasn't doing it
there's soap everywhere there shouldn't
be water I did I am it's on
rinse it's like a gun look at this water
now it's so okay give it a minute I try
it you're pushing me down you IDI what
that's so I'm not ow my finger Chris
watch
it
yes girl you're
scrubbing yes can I have it can I have
it I want it get mad at turn where to go
spray Cris with
it we should all give our best frat guy
pickup lines while we wipe it with a rag
okay yeah I Like It Go Matt pause that
or go away from me Matt mat [ __ ]
you got me okay give it to us yeah I
like to car keep my car sticky clean
just kind of like me ew Matt Matt you
get one I got you yeah I need it to be
good Nick oh my god plain take off right
behind you wow that was
crazy all right let's see it Nick oh
this is a little dirty want me to wipe
it for you
yeah uhoh that's it it this looks a
little dirty you want me to wipe it for
you is the best you had hey need a scrub
call me a car wash the way I'm squeaky
clean rub against
it Matt can you get it wet so Chris can
rub against it what do you mean rub
against it like what like they do in the
show oh like guess yeah
yes I'm going to climb on the Roof oh my
god oh he's oh wow yes girl look that
scrub
oh it's like I love this feel it's
like Nick Nick Nick all right dude let
me move you idiot you're [ __ ]
blasting me what if I go up we all get R
Nick Nick Nick the whole camera's wet oh
my God look at this kid he's a menace
Matt oh I didn't even see this action
getting going wow Nick Nick hold hold on
the camera's
wet hold on okay oh hey I didn't see you
there you're you're got your rope
Tangled in
mineck Nick spray them spray them ni me
spray
after you're tangling I'm not dude dude
dude dude dude chill out there's people
everywhere dude Matt
what Matt I'm going to kill you it's not
my fault you're idiot kill you stop King
you're an idiot we are on a limited time
FR down yes that's why I'm trying to get
Nick I'm getting need to go back this
way [ __ ] oh oh wow you're insane what's
going on he's like soaping it up but he
won't let me rinse it off like are you
[ __ ] kidding best car pickup line
let's hear it um man oh my God I'm in
the strike zone holy Christ Nick watch
out Nick dude the camera is soaking wet
what did you say the only thing I have
is too dirty just say it no yeah my
pickup line is may be too dirty but my
car's super clean there a the outfit
just really does it for me Nick Nick can
I see
it Nick let me take a turn you that was
classic that was classic hold
on oh I'm scrubbing your car whether you
like it or not I'm going to [ __ ] so
him Nick stop F
left
[Laughter]
oh my God this looks
crazy what
happened oh my God I feel like a little
kid
again I'm so that's always a good thing
right
no you don't want to get me
wet oh my God I should take advantage of
being so where's
the all right rinse me offin no no no no
you just said spray the car spray the
car we're going to go back all right
take this Mt literally dying he needs to
take that look at me I can't grab it
Nick literally had it to why is there so
soap coming out Nick you have to get it
Nick rinse the car for 8 minutes no
[ __ ] soap why is soap coming out what
why is soap still coming out hit me in
the face where at the end of our turn
I'm soaking wet and I hate
you water water rinse it rinse it rinse
itse Nick rinse it I'm trying I'm trying
I'm
trying I'm just more accepting of the
fact that if I get wet it doesn't really
matter anymore I
agree D this kid is a
character
fire don't Nick don't you dare no you're
too
cute I just feel like I went through a
[ __ ]
Mar
away hey
girl let all get left like stop stop I
think we can head home I agree well as
you can tell that was semis successful
the car is clean and I feel like I don't
have to shower for another year but I
feel like we didn't do that right I
don't either no the instructions were
very unclear I feel no they were clear I
just don't think we read them I say we
definitely go to just a manual one next
time that's like a not
a I don't get it what dude it's [ __ ]
dirty still
what I'm telling you we just went to the
car wash and sprayed water on the car
car for no it's just the hood everything
else looks squeaky [ __ ] clean top and
the top everything else looks squeaky
clean look at this look at this door
y'all saw how pathetic and [ __ ] the car
was I'm telling you we just we just
sprayed that [ __ ] with water for 10 we
just I think we just did it wrong we
didn't put any soap on the car yeah we
dude did you see the amount of soap Nick
was laying on the [ __ ] car just on
the back go look at the back I bet the
back squeaky [ __ ] clean and the front
nothing Matt come on I think it was more
of what we wanted to have the experience
together I agreee I agree and we failed
but did I have fun absolutely was it
worth the money no still [ __ ] filthy
so this is like embarrassing but you
know sometimes if you swing and you miss
you have two more strikes to hit it out
the park yo Yoda is telling us to enter
the building where Yoda where do I go
[ __ ] are we Welcome to our car wash
please select an option oh I feel like
I'm ordering food please select a car
wash by pressing one of the service
buttons on no no no $23 no gorilla wax I
feel like I'm at Disney World right now
the we're at the Disney of car washes
all right we're through the lava wash
ooh that's what he needs to get come on
scrub that scrub that up come on now yes
oh my God oh my God I Chris open it yeah
open sorry are you a faking idiot oh
oh we're in the lava
watch I'm going to open the sunroof guys
do not do
not Okay lava
watch why would you do that I was going
to open the
rear yes spin spin spin
spin oh oh my God what is this called
called The Vortex 100% something Vortex
100%
reclaimed
water the gorilla W oh he's like big and
strong Mighty gorilla it's like a little
thunderstorm woo now it's like a nice
Pitter pattern wow why did we not just
do this look at that do the
Polish yes get it get it girl I like
this
one
oh oh bring it back here
what I want more gorilla wax can we go
back
what is this the fire clean protect is
this the dryer shets dryer oh but it's
getting us wet armor armor
L where do not stop it says donkey
K all right y'all oh my God the car
looks so you use as a mirror now if you
want so good you could see the shine on
this [ __ ] huh we're at Michael's craft
store I have no reason why let's go
explore
y it's so Christmasy theme though I love
when it smells good oh I got this
vest here I just buy the best I
think not
crackers Nick I'm going to get you a nut
cracker and crack your nuts with it we
should actually get like really cute
Christmas decor this year you know what
I mean like we should really decorate
our house come look at the little
neighborhood
Nick if you buy [ __ ] like this don't use
my money just use your you guys don't
want this in the house [ __ ]
no sorry I I get this hockey one it's
like a cute experience I don't want this
[ __ ] wow nice forehead thank you holy
[ __ ] got it from you Nick show them your
big purchase white paper where we
going I want paint holiday sleigh rides
right down Santa Claus Lane it's the
most most wonderful time of the year
although it's been said many times many
ways Merry Christmas to you Santa please
stop
here that was so loud it's Most
Wonderful Time of the Year lovely
WEA
together crazy bro they threw a tea in
front of the was they wanted us to say
TW TW the Night Before Christmas all
though all through the house not that's
like a whole story kiss the cook are you
cooking you yes kitchen conversations 4
gallon one gallon what the [ __ ] is that
just a recipe for what recipe for
disaster recipe for
disaster hold
on what did you say Nick hold on tough
guy
part I got the most the most valuable
thing Blow Pop bites hey [ __ ] it's
time to get wood we're headed to Home
Depot we're not even getting wood that
was just kind of like instinctual Home
Depot saying for me Matt we should get
one of these dogs for the house we
should get one for the house dead
puppies I'm down this
guy what does he do though he doesn't
have eyes yeah but he glows cool with
like the skeleton dude the puppies the
puppies dead puppies can you insert that
video uh yeah puppies dead puppies puppy
puppy those are dead
[Applause]
[Music]
puppies
oh oh that's the least scary Halloween
decoration I've ever seen in my
life [ __ ] bed this thing is just
running you your check huh bring me to
how do I don't break that Nick yeah but
it's the try me H what it's the try me
but try me kid if we ain't trying him at
the store how do we remove this what got
to be like that huh Nick you just broke
broke the [ __ ] like main system no I
think you got to be a button
now oh sh it hey he's twering you good
bro how often you
yell how
yelling oh it takes a 9vt battery are
you [ __ ] kidding what that moment
when it takes a 9
volter that was today's Wednesday Vlog
make sure you stay tuned for our really
popular car videos on Friday and our new
podcast Nick get away and our podcast
cut the camera podcast every single
Monday and make sure you have our
notifications on that if we forget to
tell you we posted a video you can find
out
yourself oh Bring Me to Life wake me up
wake me up I
sa dude what is going on I can't wake
up oh my God wait real man wear
black I didn't even know my shirt said
that that's
crazy yeah you miss me and all the
things that we did we said we going to
travel from the island of Madrid we had
a lot of plans but they
all because but it's okay cuz I'm moving
different don't be when I with other
[ __ ] my brothers