[Music]
hi my name's Dr Dave Cosgrave my name is
Dr Travis MCD and our company
distributes tog Gat scan we're here
today to align ourselves with a dragon
that can help take our company to the
next level we're offering 15% of our
company in return for a £75,000
investment Gat scan is an orthopedic
instrumentation to device that allows us
to measure foot function and ultimately
foot dysfunction there's a plethora of
research that supports that the foot
directly implicates and causes problems
in many satellite anatomical location
such as the ankle the knee the hip and
the lower back how this system works is
uh we sell the gate scan unit to top
Professionals in the country they have
their patients walk across this computer
chip 4,000 sensors in this mat send
information into the computer with a
touch of a button the information is
modem through cyberspace to our
laboratory where foot Specialists will
construct an orthopedic insert uh that
will help to alleviate problems in the
foot and in doing so will help to to
reduce toxin in the whole kinetic chain
including the knees the hips and in the
lower back we currently have 114 units
in action in the UK generating 4,000
annual orders of orthotics which
represent a turnover of £350,000 in the
short time that we've been a company
we've sold 11,000 Orthotics which
generate 1.3 million worth of Revenue we
feel that the company's at a Tipping
Point right now we feel privileged to be
in front of some of the great economic
Minds in the United Kingdom we invite
you to take the next step forward with
us in a synergistic fashion to make this
company as much of a success in the
United Kingdom as it is in other
jurisdiction such as Canada we invite
your
questions a slick sales pitch and a
pinch of flattery have got doctors Dave
Cosgrave and Travis McDonna off to a
flying start but foot Diagnostics are an
unfamiliar territory to the dragons and
for £75,000
investment theopus needs to know more
how does it work did you just walk over
it would you like to have a go I'd love
to have a go I got heel pains that's
that' be fantastic could I ask you to
take off your shoes just there would
that be okay oh no please just take them
off yes please and your socks and the
socks as well please leave your socks no
please if you don't mind that would be
good you want socks yes please we're
going to start you actually down on this
end yeah and we're actually going to get
you to walk across the pad just like
you'd be walking down the street placing
One Foot In The Box at a time Okay We're
Off to the Races
perfect we can see right away that there
are some problem areas um what do you
mean some problem areas he has dropped
what are called metatarsal heads which
are at the front of of the foot oh no he
also has a lot of heel pressure um in
both sides there's quite a bit of
asymmetry between the right and the left
side you fail you failed should I sit
down now are you finished with me you
can put your shoes so so what's the
diagnosis doctor but if I would you mind
taking a seat and if I could just touch
your foot there for one second and show
you some the problems are excuse me um
right now we have an angulation in your
toe from here to here and it's the early
signs of B of A bunion okay called halex
valgas old age i w got have a go but I'm
not going for I think this this toe is
starting to head towards Liverpool when
it should be straight okay and you can
see that if I pressed on the arch it
helps to straighten your toe out this is
a perfect example of someone who could
benefit from weing an
orthotic with the help of theop fetus's
nent bunion the gates scan Duo have
grabbed the dragon's attention now
Duncan bantine wants to drill down into
their sales
figures what price you see on the system
for the system is sold um into practices
at
£7,000 we've currently sold 114 of them
in the UK we're selling the system but
our our our revenue and our money comes
from the orthotic devices that are
prescribed off of it to the paying
public they're retailing the orthotic
device is retailing at about
225 up to 300 in London that would be
very very normal and there's 11,000 of
them been sold in a very short time how
much do they cost you they cost us we we
have a 100% uh markup so we're we're
we're selling them about about
4041 Dave and Travis haven't a foot
wrong so far but Richard Farley needs to
know more about their ownership rights
for the gate
scan are you a distributor for this
that's exactly it so you've got the
rights to operate this business in the
UK and Ireland exactly and Ireland and
and what are the details of of your own
of your ownership of the of the
distribution you've got we we started
two and a half years ago and they gave
us quotas to hit we hit those quotas
within the first 12 months actually the
first 11 months so that ex that gives us
a further extension of 5 years however I
go back next week uh to head office to
negotiate a 15 a further 15-year
contract extension with
then the gates scan Duo seemed to have
reassured the dragons with a watertight
distribution deal covering the UK and
Ireland Duncan bantine has more
questions about their company
finances yeah tell me what you you turn
over and and and and
PRX 1.3 million when uh in the last two
and a half years 1.3 million not two and
a half years year by year um a year one
um on start we had a turnover of um
£500,000
yep uh year two we had a turnover of um
£400,000 um and then we had um this year
we're gone for 500,000 again okay and
your profit over the last three years
this year we have we haven't taken any
profit whatsoever we've put all the
money straight back bus the company
makes a profit it stays in no we've made
zero pound we've spent every single
penny as a as a going concern to put
into seminars marketing launching the
products we haven't made a penny we
haven't we've only taken a very small
Sal account show zero zero zero
profit every year zero yeah so youve
spent all of your money generating new
business yes and you've got a business
that over three years is showing a
flatline well if you uh if I could if I
could if I could just um say when you
sell one of your Top Line your your
Revenue goes up very high so in the
first year I sold a great deal of Gat
scans and in the second year less Gat
scans concentrating more on customer
service to get the amount of orthotics
and the volume up and right now we're at
a stage where we concentrate purely on
our existing clients and trying to get
them prescribing more Orthotics and less
gate
scans under interrogation by the dragons
Dave and Travis are suddenly struggling
to explain why they haven't made any
profit at all for 3 years theopus is
determined to get to the bottom of
it I I'm now very suspicious about some
of these numbers I want you to break
down the £500,000
that you generated last year right I
want I want you break down where you
generated it from okay and I want you to
break down where you spent it okay 4,000
orthodics is that 180,000 y
180,000 um sales of the gate scans y
£210,000
y
and then we have we put hold two big
large seminars but we did we only made
£20,000 from them guys that makes four
410,000 where's the other 90,000 come
from and the accounting procedures
basically include Northern Ireland and
Northern Ireland is not the territory
that we're we're talking about today
we've fragmented Northern Ireland into
its separate company so I I have a
Northern Ireland company Irish company
with with shareholders and I have a
United Kingdom company at the time
recently we've just what are you
offering me investment in United Kingdom
excluding the northern Irish
territory unbelievably Dave and Travis
have left it until now to reveal that
although they've been boasting about a
watertight distribution deal covering UK
and Ireland they're not including the
Irish territories in the deal the
dragons are incred
ulous why have you hied the other
business off what's behind that
structure Ireland was where I started
and Ireland grew very very fast and it's
an example of where I I had the capacity
to infiltrate the marketplace easier
because it's smaller we do profitable
very yeah how much profit is that making
uh it is making about
117,000 last year did you somewhere get
an impression that we were
daed is that what you thought you know
these guys are d I know I know you're
smart shares in the dud company keep all
our shares in a profitable company if
you if you were to look at pure
potential if you looked at Ireland
there's 3 million people we do 600
orthodtic a month if you look at the
United Kingdom we're doing 300 a month
but there's 60 million people but why do
you not put that into the pot again I
like to keep a clear-cut dichotomy
between you want to own it all and make
profit and use my money to exploit and
make more profit for you no no it look
I'm not going to say that we're not
going to be thankful to get the money
cuz it's going to help us roll overow to
sales strategy but we need we clearly
need direction we're in front of two
guys very professional and all I've
heard is the fact that you're not
salespeople you're very very good
salespeople and Travis I thought your
presentation was fantastic you gave us
words like
satellite anatomical locations you then
went on to say taxing in the whole
kinetic chain your pitch was fantastic
but the bottom line is all you've got is
an individual ually made shoe
insert I don't know I don't know much
about marketing am I a good salesperson
you don't know marketing satellite
anatomical locations I've done it in
I've done the whole kinetic chain
together I've been there for years the
greatest mines in the whole of the
universe is in front of me I mean give
me a break if you're not a salesperson
what is I a salesperson I am a salesp
person but I'm not a mark honestly the
only Direction I can give you is to the
stairs because there's no way I'm going
to invest in this company I've I've
heard enough so I'm not investing so I'm
out the dragons are rra in arms furious
with the gates scan team's tactics in
the den Duncan vantine has made his
feelings perfectly clear Richard Farley
has also made his mind
up the puzzle that you're probably
trying to figure out and I've been
trying to figure out is why it works in
Ireland but you can't get it to work
here and I think that's why you want us
involved because that really is a puzzle
now you haven't been able to figure that
out I don't think I could figure that
out so I'm I'm dropping out as well but
good luck thank you I'm
out and to let you know where I am I've
lost confidence in you so I'm afraid if
I've lost confidence there is absolutely
no way I'm going to invest so I'm out
sorry to hear that thank you and I'll
just tell you at the end of the day all
you have is an individually made insert
company and that isn't good enough
you're a sales agent nothing else I
can't invest in a sales Agency for an
insert for a shoe so I'm
out Dave and Travis's pitch has
disintegrated with three more dragons
competing to declare themselves out it's
left to theopus to have the final word
on the turmoil that's ensued in the
den your
pitch resembles something out of delboy
Trotter's opportunities book you have
try to play the three card trick you've
been moving the the lady around from
left to right right to left you really
have not done your business any Justice
by the approach that you've taken here
today you're wasting my
time I will not be
investing so I'm out thanks for your
time okay
byebye after a polished start Dave and
Travis have felt the full wroth of the
dragons and they leave the den
empty-handed