Next up is a business that indulges in a
guilty
[Music]
pleasure. What's up, Sharks? I'm Kelsey,
founder and fearless leader at Dope
Cookie Dough. I'm seeking
$450,000 in exchange for 10% of my
company. I'm Dallas born, California
raised, and I'm loving life in the Bay
Area, running San Francisco's first ever
cookie dough bar.
Life is crazy and adulting is hard. But
what if just for a few moments, you
could be transported back to your
childhood, sneaking bites of cookie
dough in the kitchen? At Dope, we serve
nostalgia by the scoop. We're here for
the big kid inside of all of us.
However, we're anything but childish.
We're a millennial brand serving over
20,000 customers each month. I'm on a
mission to get dope in every city in
America through opening additional
hightraic storefronts, franchising, and
expanding onto grocery store shelves.
Sharks, this deal is too dope to pass
up. Who's in? We got samples. You want
to try it first? All right, I can get
some samples for you. Please. Do people
love cooking? Got the mouths watering.
Well, people that like sweets. Oh, I am
so stoked for you guys to try this.
We've got six different flavors. There's
one plate for you. There you go. Special
for you guys. We made a vegan avocado
brownie cookie dough. Cute. Cute names.
Thanks so much. Avocados.
People love the fun. I love the names.
Got to keep them laughing.
Wow. It's sweet. Thank you so much. You
bet. It's really sweet. Thank you so
much. Thank you.
So, we've got the OG. That's going to be
your classic chocolate chip. The vegan
OG is made with vegan butter so that
those on dietary restrictions can
indulge. Cinnamude is going to be like a
snicker doodle with white chocolate
chips. Raisin the roof is an oatmeal
raisin flavor. What? What? He's got it.
Choahholic is for the chocolate lovers.
And then this more is hella dope. So
that's going to be marshmallows, graham
crackers, and chocolate chips. Just like
love the names. Our three sizes,
self-control, legit, or fully commit.
Um, funny names. So we've got a
storefront on Pier 39. Um, it's one of
San Francisco's biggest tourist
attractions. I know it well. So is that
your only location? That's our only
physical brick and mortar. Is that the
actual store? Uh, it is. Yeah, we do
$1,100 per square foot. Oh, wow. That's
a lot. Wow. You have competitors? Yeah,
there are some competing companies. So,
there's one in New York City, uh, who's
sort of on par with me. It's definitely
coming in like the cupcake trend and all
of that stuff where it's going to take
off. Kelsey, when did you start the
business? So, I started, uh, in April of
2017. Um, I had spent 10 years in tech.
I Oh, I see the correlation now. Yeah.
Right. Processor chips to chocolate
chips. I had been working since I was 16
uh at Intel. And at Intel? Yeah. Since
you're 16. Yeah. Why is that? Uh I
started as a high school intern, but it
was really hard on me and I put a lot of
pressure on myself. So I developed a
really unhealthy relationship with
alcohol through the years. And Friday I
turned three years sober. Um got sober
and that changed my life entirely. Um
I've always had this entrepreneurial bug
and doing something on your own has just
been the most rewarding thing. So, in a
year and a half, we're over 850,000 in
sales. And what are you making on the
850? Yeah, we have a 35% net income
ratio. Okay. We've got 14. This
calendar, what will your income be
pre-tax? Our net income is $240,000 for
this year so far. And what's your plan
going forward? Where do you envision
your business going? World cookie dough
domination.
How are you going to get there? Um, my
main focus is on these hightraic
storefronts. I'm in lease negotiations
right now for a spot on the Las Vegas
strip and the mall sees 72,000 people
per day enter their doors. Wow. So,
you're here on Shark Tank today at a 4.5
million valuation. You're asking me to
pay 30 times your pre-tax profits. 30
multiple on something that is completely
not proprietary because it's cookie
dough. Yeah. Anybody can do it. The
difference is you're a good operator.
Yeah. But that one always makes a
difference. No, but it's not worth 37
times. It's just cookie dough. Here's
the problem. You're going to grow until
somebody says, "I want to compete with
you cuz it looks so good."
She has compet. Yeah, there's certainly
a lot of competition. And look at what
happened in cupcakes. I'd like to
compare myself to one of the major
cupcake brands that made it through this
with sprinkles. If you recall, kind of
this rise, every mom and pop opening one
on every corner. But there are a few
brands we all know and love still from
the cupcake trend. I'm going to be one
of those for cookie dough. We're also
expanding into wholesale. So looking at
grocery stores, you've got major chains
like Whole Foods. Do you have any
wholesale now? Um, yeah. So these jars
are just starting to hit the market and
we're in San Francisco's airport.
Kelsey, you're an amazing operator.
Like, thank you very much. Your story,
your numbers, everything. I don't like
cookie dough. So I know, I'm sorry, but
how many people like cookie dough? I
would say a significant amount. I call
it
like I I find it too sweet. You just
have to know that people love it. Even
if you don't like it, it's got money
behind it. We make a scoop for 68 and we
sell it for $6. So the the direct margin
on this product is incredible. I feel
like a shame to say that for customers
watching, but it's pretty awesome. We're
really cultivating an experience people
are willing to pay for it. And where
where's the value at 4 and a half
million? Talk to me a little bit about
that. So I did this valuation not even
including the Vegas operations, just
growth of our own pier store, growth of
local wholesale, and that's going to get
us to 2.25 million next year in revenue.
right in revenue. Correct. And what do
you think you'll make on that? I mean,
we've been moving uh with this 27 to 35%
net income ratio. I don't think I've
ever met a more sophisticated store
owner in my life. Yeah. Wow. 10 years at
Intel will do that to you, man. I've uh
watched some amazing leaders make really
difficult business decisions, and it's
undoubtedly the reason this has gotten
so far. That and my sobriety. Um I feel
so present and so focused, and I just
know exactly where this can go, and I'm
looking for one of you guys to help me
take it there.
I I wish it was something else. I can't
get there on the cookie though, though.
I'm out. I totally understand. Yeah,
probably pretty much like a Robert. I'm
going to go out simply because I just
don't like cookie dough.
Yeah, I understand that. It's cute. It's
fun. I know that there's a lot of people
that really love cookie dough and you've
proved it, but it's not something that
is a healthy enough option for me. Okay.
So, I'm sorry. I'm out. Okay. I totally
understand. Yeah, we are looking into um
some snack size packaging and something
more portion control where you can have
a little So, Kelsey, you've proven
yourself as a strong operator. Clearly,
sales justify what you're doing. I'm
going to give you the credit of making
2.25 million next year. So you're you're
basically going to end up with around
$350,000 to distribute to investors,
giving you about five to six times free
cash flow after tax puts a valuation of
you about 1.8 million bucks. The problem
with your deal was valuation. Nothing
wrong with you. Okay. No, I totally
respect that. I think a lot of uh
there's so many ways to do valuations in
this world and u I do the real way. He
says the sametick all the time. We're
used to I don't see you writing a check
mark. You forgot to write the check.
Look, I wasn't clear. Are you in or out?
Oh, did I not say? Okay, Kelsey, so that
we don't have to beat each other up. I'm
out. Yeah. Okay. But I wish you the
best. Well, you have Mark left. Yeah.
All my homie Texas. Texas. I know.
Dallas, I know. Look, Kelsey, what
you've done is amazing. Everything about
it says it's a good investment. Yeah.
And I need your help. The stadiums, the
arenas, I need literally the conflict I
have, and this is the honest guy truth
is the whole obesity thing, right? just
getting behind a product and saying,
"Eat more. Eat more. Eat more. Great
business. Congratulations. I have to go
out." Okay. I totally respect that. You
guys are amazing. I'm like so sad I'm
not hugging you right now, but I'm
really excited for the future and I
appreciate you guys taking the time.
Thank you guys so much. Thank you.
[Laughter]
Thank you.
The Sharks made a mistake today, but
they'll be back. I know they're going to
see us crushing it in Vegas. They're
going to see us doing amazing things
with e-commerce sales. And uh I'm
excited to hear from him one day.