[Music]
In the last four years, Dragon's Den has
attracted more than 22,000 applications
from all corners of the UK.
This summer, the Dragons are taking time
out of running their multi-million pound
empires, crisscrossing the country,
dishing out their infamous brand of
nononsense business advice. It's amazing
how many people get obsessed with an
idea and they keep throwing money at it
and they keep thinking it's the idea
it's going to make them a fortune and
actually it's pretty obvious it isn't.
And these are demanding times for
entrepreneurs. Banks are not lending at
the moment. It's one of the extra
challenges we've got with the recession.
Tonight, the Dragons embark upon the
first stage of their journey, traveling
throughout the South from the West
Country to Kent. So, we would make 10
times our money. 10 times your money.
Can I just tell you guys, that's the
kind of investment I like.
The Dragon's Den tour continues onto the
gentile Georgian spa town of Royal
Tundridge, Wales in Kent. The town is
thought of as representative of Middle
England with its infamously disgusted
inhabitants. Now the tour is coming to
town to visit the studio of entrepreneur
and artist Guy Portelli.
In 2008, Guy came into the den asking
for £70,000 for 25% of his latest work,
an exhibition of pop icon sculptures.
Hello dragons. My name is Guy Portelli
and I am a professional sculptor. I am
looking for an investment of £70,000 for
a 25% share in my pop icons collection.
I intend to use an investment to
complete a series of 18 sculptures which
I will then be showing at the
prestigious Mel Galleries in London in
June 2009.
What I am offering is a 25% share of 100
sculptures. I brought along some pieces
to show examples of my work.
This piece is my Grace Jones um that I
made some 20 years ago.
The John Lennon piece I made six years
ago and at the time it sold at £1,800.
The Bob Marley is fused with the idea of
the lion of Africa roaring and has
created a fairly spiritual strong
element to that work.
This is the new piece. This is the Amy
Winehouse, my goddess of excess. My work
is not about caricature.
It's about creating an identity that
relates to youth culture and fashion.
Any questions?
[Music]
The den has been transformed into a
gallery as 51-year-old sculptor Guy
Portelli pitches for £70,000 to fund an
exhibition of his pop icon sculptures.
Peter Jones is first to quiz the artist
[Music]
guy. Hello, I'm Peter. Hello, Peter.
What's the overall portfolio do you
think in what you're aiming to sell for?
Well, the whole 100 pieces would have a
today value in excess of a million
pounds.
Um, you would hope to sell them over a
course of three years
and the the price would go up at least
20% a year. So, what's the hundred
coming from? The 100 is the additions.
The the Grace Jones edition of 10. So,
we make one, we sell one, we make
another one. The John Lennon's edition
of 10. We make one, we sell one, we make
another one. Okay. I mean I have made
and sold more than a million pounds
worth of sculpture in the last 10 years.
[Music]
Guy has clarified the deal on offer. Now
James Khn wants to interrogate the
sculptor on his finances.
What's the latest piece you've done Amy?
The Amy is the most recent work. Okay.
And what are you selling Amy for? She
was in the gallery recently at 18,000.
What's the most expensive piece you've
sold? Um we sold one one recently for
28,000 a John Lee Hooker sculpture which
is addition of three. The first one went
to the Porsche family which I sold seven
eight years ago for £10,000. This one
went for 28 and the next one will sell
for 36. Are you saying that today if
somebody gave you £70,000? Yes. That
would get back 25% of a sale price of
every sculpture you sold for the next
100. Yes. Okay. Why? Why? Because I have
never put on a show of this magnitude.
Um, we would expect to sell 40 pieces in
the first year and then 30 pieces. What
would those 40 pieces fetch in the first
year? We would be looking to sell
£250,000
worth £250,000 worth in the first year.
So the investor would get 25% of that
£250,000 which is 625,000. Yeah. So he
practically get his money back in the
first year. That's the idea.
[Music]
Guy is showing that on top of his
undoubted artistic skills, he also has
an entrepreneurial brain. Theopetus
wants to drill down further into the
business plan.
[Music]
What are you going to do with the money?
The breakdown of the 70,000 is 25,000
for the exhibition
and 45,000 for the cost of materials and
and labor to complete the work. 25,000
for exhibition. What does that mean?
Well, I plan to rent the Mel Galleries
in London, which is a large prestigious
place. It can accommodate 3 to 400
people. Um, it would be a major show,
major. So, you're going to put your own
exhibition on. What commission would
they normally take? 50%. 50. Yeah. Ah.
By confessing that a gallery would
normally expect to receive half the
revenue generated by sales of his
collection, the dragons have worked out
Guy is offering them a much lesser deal.
And art lover Deborah Megan has other
concerns.
Guy. Hello. I'm Deborah. Deborah, what
you're doing here is quite simple.
You're saying, I'm going to take I'm not
going to spend the 50% on the gallery.
What I'm going to do is I'm going to
actually get an investor in at 25%. Mhm.
And think that I can actually do myself
a better deal. The bit that I worry
you're missing is the fact that when you
pay the gallery the commission, you're
paying them for their marketing.
Yeah. So, what's your marketing plan?
How are you going to get people through
the door? because that's the bit that
you're completely cutting out when you
cut out a gallery. Um, well, I'd hope to
generate quite a lot of media interest,
get a lot of editorial
thing, the great thing with this series
of work is it does attract a lot of
media interest and it also is
international. You could take the show
to Tokyo, you could take this show to
Paris, to Berlin and it would mean
something to people.
[Music]
Guy is clearly confident about his
project, but it's an unusual business
proposition and hard for the dragons to
evaluate their risk. Will Theopetus find
a solution?
If someone was to offer you the money,
would you allow ownership of those 18
pieces
to the person
that gave you the money, the investor?
Yeah. Till they got the investment back.
that wouldn't be a problem. Well, I'll
make you an offer then. I'll give you
the £70,000.
I think the way that Theo minimized the
risk by keeping hold of some of the
pieces, I think was a neat component to
the deal.
If it all went wrong, I've got all these
wonderful bits of art which I can
display around my house. Theo's off was
a very astute move. It gave them that
confidence that they couldn't lose. For
this to really work, you want maximum
impact out in the market. you want
people to know about it. So, I'd like to
recommend something that is that
you get £70,000
for 25%. Mhm.
But all of the dragons collectively have
a piece of the pie, but then you've got
five fairly powerful people supporting
this activity in 2009.
Wow. So, it's it's not just a question
to you. It's obviously a question to see
whether the dragons would be interested.
Um,
I would be quite interested uh guy to
um follow Peter's theme, which I think I
could probably add quite a bit of value
to that. Um, I think there's a return to
be made.
It's an astute proposal from Peter Jones
and James Khn is quick to sign up to it.
Will Deborah Megan help make it a clean
sweep?
I do back artists and I do commission
sculptures. So I I'm in this space, but
I have a very clear line between
investing
and buying something because I want to.
And for me, this hasn't triggered any
passion or any so whatever. Even if it
was a five dragon deal, I'm I'm not
going to be investing. So, I'm out.
It's a sudden setback. Now, what will
Duncan Banitine think of Peter Jones's
Dragon Consortium?
[Music]
I think Dylan before dragons would be
difficult. Yeah.
So, I wouldn't want to participate
before dragons. Yeah. Well, I'm very
happy if people are passionate about
what I do. Um, and if James, Theo, and
Peter wanted to all put some money in, I
would be thrilled with that team. Um,
Duncan,
if you feel passionately about it, then
I'm happy for you as well to be part of
that team. I feel passionate about your
work, guy, but I don't feel passionate
about investing with the team. No,
that's the problem. Yeah. So, what I've
been considering is making you a better
offer. Okay.
I'm going to make an offer. It's in the
same basis that I would own the 18
pieces until it was sold. But my offer
isn't for £70,000. It's for £90,000.
That's my offer. It's an offer by me on
my own.
In a bold move, Duncan Banitine is
trying to steal the deal and distance
himself from his rivals. Guy must now
choose between partnering up with three
dragons or go for the higher cash deal
with one.
It's very generous offer. I mean, I'm
um
astounded. Thank you very much. Um, I
think three people, three guest lists,
three lots of enthusiasm would be
beneficial to the project.
And if I could have an offer of 80,000
from the three, I would be keen to have
that
[Music]
Yeah, I'm I'm happy. I'm happy. I think
you've got yourself a deal, guy.
Thank
I think Guy won because not only did he
get the investment, he got the three
dragons. What this business really needs
is introductions of people who
potentially are going to want to buy
that art.
James Khan led the investment team on
behalf of the Three Dragons. So, he's
visiting Guy Studio in Kent to see the
creative process. firsthand. Welcome to
the studio. This is the studio. This is
where it all happens. Wow, that is
phenomenal. What is that? That's the
Jimmyi Hendris one, which um is
fantastic. Which we're just about
finished. What What would we sell this
for, guy? We're probably looking at the
round about £30,000 upwards. What works
for me? James seems to have a strong
sympathy for the arts. I think he sees
the way that he runs his business as a
creative process. There's something
about the concept of art and the
creativity and I suppose because I'm
married to an artist, you know, I I
probably find this really stimulating.
Yes. And I I can you just have to stop
me spending money here. I'm glad I'm an
investor.
I genuinely believe that guy stuff is
very very good. My instinct tells me we
are going to make a profit on this deal.
Before James' prediction can be
realized, there's still much work to be
done to complete the 18 pieces. So guy
is at the foundry casting part of his
sex pistols creation. It's a massive
project and actually a year is not a lot
for what we aim to achieve.
Since the investment, Guy's been working
full-time and flat out producing the
collection that he committed to in the
dead.
Molten bronze,
1240°.
[Music]
Yeah, that's worked. Well done. Well
done, mate.
[Music]
One year after Guy stood in the den
before the dragons, he's now preparing
for the allimportant opening night of
his exhibition. We've done the
invitations, we've done the mail out, we
work with him on his brochure. So, we've
been very proactive in ensuring that
Guy's exhibition goes off with a bang.
[Music]
And this is the last the final piece for
the show. And it's it's quite symbolic
really because the Amy was was really
the piece that opened the doors to me
getting their opportunity with Dragon's
Dead.
[Music]
Tonight is the Dragon's Night. They've
put the guest list together. They've got
the people out of the city. And of
course, these people are potentially
great collectors.
This is a very critical moment for Guy
Portelli. The exhibition is going to be
the make or break of Guy. Let's have a
tour by the artist himself.
What's the price? About 60,000. That's
including BAT. I'm worried about not
selling tonight. We need to get some
sales on the chart because that will
generate more sales. Is anybody
interested in buying this magnificent
piece? While two of the Dragon investors
are busy trying to drum up sales, James'
attention was elsewhere. That is
amazing. In fact, I think it's so good.
Let me just have a quick look.
You missed your mouth. I mean, clearly
it it's amazing. What can I say? Listen,
in these troubled times when your
interest in your money in the bank is
like two and six months, this is a great
investment. Is this going to work? Will
people buy the stuff? Well, that's what
we're going to see.
We invested £80,000.
What's the value of the art here today
that you're displaying? Well, if we sold
all 100 pieces, we would be over £3
million. you'd make 750,000 800,000. So
10 times our money. 10 times your money.
Can I just tell you guys that's the kind
of investment I like.
Art is a fantastic investment. I'm
breaking all the rules. Hopefully other
artists will follow my lead. Hopefully
other investors will invest in artists.
I shall be thrilled when I can give them
their check back. You know, it'll be a
great relief to me just to say here's
your investment. Thank you very much.
Now, let's move forward.
Since the exhibition, Guy has sold four
pieces for £65,000.
It's a promising start, and Guy is now
looking forward to touring his
exhibition around the world.
A day in the den is very different to a
day in the office for the
multi-millionaires. Good morning. I'm
here to invest some money. Behind the
scenes, the morning starts with a visit
to the glamour department. Well, come
in, get a bit of makeup on, have me
breakfast, then we all wait for Peter
George. I'm a little bit late, so um I
better go and get my makeup on and get
going. You need some makeup on, mate. I
need some makeup on. I don't have
makeup. So, we waiting for now. Oh,
waiting for Peter. No, we're not. We're
going to change the name of this show,
by the way. It's no longer be called
Dragon's Den. It'll be called Waiting
for Peter.
If you just focus across to him now,
he's just doing his hair look.
Mirror, mirror on the wall. Who's the
wisest dragon of all?
All right, I'm going to do my hair. You
might not see it on screen. He does
actually have hair. When they comb his
hair, they do it by strand. That's
actually for hairspray. It actually
sprays hair onto his head. The dragon's
multi-million pound business empires get
put on hold as they eagerly await the
next money-making opportunity. There is
a sense of anticipation because you have
absolutely no idea what's about to
happen. Is Peter Jones going to listen
for a whole half hour. Is Duncan going
to stay awake?
Is James going to stroke his beard more
than 32 times a minute?
These are all questions that we need to
know the answer of and we won't know
till we get in that day. After you,
madam. What was it?
Back on the road. The tour is heading to
West Sussex and Hosted Canes, home to a
small ethical packaging company with big
ambitions.
Rachel Watkin and Christian Richardson
were an unlikely business partnership,
and in 2008, they'd been working
together for 8 months in their fledgling
business. They came into the den asking
for £53,000 for 20% of their company.
Hi,
my name is Christian Richardson. This is
Rachel Watin. Uh together we run a
company called the Tiny Box Company. Uh
we've come to you today uh asking for
£53,000
for 20% investment in our company. Uh we
are currently the only company in the UK
that solely deals in recycled packaging.
We do all different kinds of boxes. We
do boxes for specifically the gift and
jewelry sectors. That's what we're
targeting at the moment. To date, we've
been trading for about 6 months. Um we
have taken £21,735.
Um we've sold about 66,000 units and the
reason that we're looking for investment
is because the packaging industry is
incredibly seasonal along with the gift
in the jewelry market. So most of our
competitors will take between 50 and 80%
of their annual turnover in the 3 months
run up to Christmas. So we need to make
sure that we've got enough money in the
kitty to buy the stock to make sure that
we've streamlined the operations and we
have the warehouse structure and also
the staff to fulfill the the coming
Christmas market. Um and that's the tiny
box company. Thank you very much.
Christian, can you hand me a couple of
the boxes? Just let me have a quick
look.
[Music]
Business partners Christian Richardson
and Rachel Watkin need £53,000 for Tiny
Box, their gift packaging company,
dealing only in recycled products. In
return, they're willing to give away 20%
equity.
Deborah Meden wants to grill the pair on
their green credentials.
Hello, Rachel. Hello, Christian. Hello.
Um, you started off by saying you're the
only company that does wholly recycled
boxes or packaging. Yeah. Um,
I that may well be correct. There's
quite a few that do it though, aren't
there? There are quite a few companies
that do recycle packaging. Yes. But not
solely. They're companies that if you go
on their their website, uh, they are a
packaging company. They do everything,
but they also do recycle. They have a
little small section for recycled. So,
this isn't a unique you haven't got a
unique product. your unique selling
point is the fact that you are set up as
a presumably you're you're you're um
focusing on the ethical side of things.
So we solely do it. That's all we do.
What what we discovered we did a lot of
market research on this and we phoned
probably about 30 packaging companies
and we said we're looking for recycled
bags. We're looking for recycled boxes
and the response was the same. Uh oh,
all our products are recyclable. No, we
want recycled. Um and the knowledge
within the companies just wasn't there.
So as a consumer, you know, if I want to
buy recycled packaging, they couldn't
give me the answers.
Rachel may have assuaged Deborah Megan's
concerns, but Duncan Banitine still
seems troubled.
[Music]
Rachel, hi. Why solely recycled? It
started off because I wanted recycled
packaging for another company I was
dealing with. Okay. Why did you want
recycled packaging? Because I had a
jewelry business. Uhhuh. Um, and it was
fair trade jewelry and I thought that I
wanted to put it in recycled packaging.
The jewelry business making money. The
the jewelry business, we were focusing
on both businesses. Is the jewelry
business making money? It's a very
simple question. No, the jewelry
business isn't making money and that
because two business is not making
money. No, because we focused on this
full-time. It It sounds to me, Rachel,
that you're on a crusade and crusades
cost money. Excuse me. I'm going to have
to stop you there because there's no way
that Rachel is is on a crusade. She
started a fair trade jewelry company.
What time in your relationship did you
decide that Rachel couldn't speak for
herself? Sorry.
Is it a crusade, Rachel?
I don't feel that it's a crusade. Yes,
ethics are important, but I see it as a
as a feasible business model. I think
it's absolutely ridiculous that you come
along with what you call a business that
you describe as ethical and recycle
materials and you produce a box which my
8-year-old daughter Emily could make
better at school. You know, the ends
don't match up. The lines aren't
straight. You know, it's pathetic. It
really, really is. So, I'm not
investing. So, I'm out.
It's a crushing blow. A furious Duncan
Banitine has derided the duo's business,
but James Khn is still interested to
find out more. Hi Rachel. Hi Christian.
I'm James. Who who your five biggest
customers that have bought this product?
Uh biggest names we've sold to Google.
We've sold to uh How many units did
Google buy? Uh they've bought 400 units
in the last week. Why would Google buy
these boxes? Corporate gift packaging.
Okay. This is where we're seeing the
market. How did you get to the customer?
They contacted us. Really? Yes. Give me
the others. Uh, Tate Galleries for all
the the shops at Tate Liverpool, Tate
Modern, Tate Britain. Okay.
It's an impressive client base for such
a young business. But Theopetus is
concerned the couple are ignoring
larger, more lucrative sectors of the
market.
I've got to tell you now I spend several
millions on packaging every year.
So I know a little bit about packaging.
Mhm. You come here saying I want to run
a business. I want investment to run a
business
and then you shackled yourself. Why not
have a recycled side and a non-recycled
side where you can then generate the
income to further your goals and achieve
what you want to achieve. Does that hurt
you? Is there a problem with that? We
recognized a market niche and projected
that okay it's a market niche now but
with with the economic climate climate
the political climate it could be
mainstream tomorrow. I went into it as a
business not as a crusade. I mean, it
does sound a little bit of a crusade.
Hearing such an influential dragon
pouring scorn on their business strategy
doesn't bode well for Christian and
Rachel. And unfortunately, there's more
trouble ahead. It's just not for me. I
understand that you guys are really
passionate and you believe in it, but
it's not a viable business opportunity.
For those reasons, I'm out. But good
luck. Thank you. I'll let you know where
I am. Um,
I like this space, but I'm not going to
make you an offer. And I'm not going to
make you an offer because at the moment
that market is quite small. That's why
packaging companies have a recycling
arm, but people's purchasing is still
driven by price. What does it look like
first and then recycling second? So, I'm
afraid I'm out. Thank you.
Christian and Rachel's bid for £53,000
is looking increasingly fragile. Now
Theopitis wants to pursue the background
of the entrepreneurs themselves.
What did you do before this? Uh before I
was in packaging. Uh I worked in radio.
Doing what? Uh I was doing radio shows.
You're doing radio shows? Yeah. I worked
for radio station in London called Kiss
100. I've worked for Virgin Radio and
didn't didn't pay well. Uh it paid
fantastically. It paid it played six
figure songs, but you decided to throw
it in. I um I went into rehab um about a
year ago. And when I came out, I wanted
to help people. So I met Rachel
literally 3 days after I got back. We
got talking and um we started working
sort of from the next day. And how long
ago was that? That was July last year.
Okay, Christian, I I guess some of your
story before I asked it, but I can't
guess your story. Okay.
Um, I went to university, studied
business studies, got a job doing um,
financial accounting as a graduate
trainee for the John Lewis Partnership,
and then ended up working for a large
software house that specialized in
financial software. worked my way up to
become the uh the technical UK sales
manager for that. Then I got sick
and um got sick. I got sick. I went in
for a routine appendix operation that
went horribly wrong. Picked up a killer
virus in the hospital and lost my job,
lost my house and everything else.
The couple's cander has transformed the
atmosphere in the den. Peter Jones has
been very quiet, but now he's ready to
have his say.
What's really interesting about this
situation is I think this is a very very
good example of actually why business is
as much about the people as it is about
an idea. And when you give your story,
it's resonates with me and it makes me
think actually how can we take these two
clear clearly been through a hell of a
lot individuals when you different
circumstances your life for whatever
reason you make it very very interesting
and you make yourselves very very
investable actually and it's interesting
now and I'm thinking sitting here how
can I help to make this a business I I
want to make you an offer Um, the reason
why I'm going to make you an offer is,
and I got to say this is the fact that
Theo and I have a very large investment
in a business and that business uses
these products. So for me, my offer
would be conditional on on Theo
partnering and my offer to you is for
40% of the business,
but it's for £60,000,
not 53.
Peter Jones is trying to tie his rival
dragon and business partner in on a deal
with the couple. It means that Christian
and Rachel's only hope of securing their
investment now depends on what Theopitis
says next.
If um I decide to gamble £30,000 of my
children's inheritance,
what do you think you can give back?
I think well Christian will vouch for me
on this. I am a complete workaholic. I'm
incredibly passionate about whatever I
do and
very determined as well. So I'm not a
flake that will be going home at 5:00.
I'll be there until the job is done.
Christian, you worry me.
Are you going to get stuck back into
that lifestyle that you, you know, I was
in that that lifestyle and I was stuck
in in a rat and it had me and for for
many years I thought I was in enjoying
it and I wasn't. My passion isn't with
with boxes. My passion is with
broadcasting and it always had it always
has been. But since I've met Rachel and
for what um for what Rachie stands for
and from what I can see in the business
and the passion and commitment that
Rachel put puts into it, I'm not going
to leave Rachel standing there.
You know, you got to diversify. You got
to probably compromise because if you
want to achieve and then sometimes
you've got to look at a wider picture.
Yeah. To achieve it. Mhm. Um,
so we need that commitment. I'd be happy
to commit to that.
I'm in for 30 on the basis of 20%.
Yes, please. We'll take it.
I was so shocked. I didn't know what to
say. I didn't need any time to think
about it. I think we should just bite
their hands off. Do it. Against the
odds, the pair walked away with two new
business partners. But I swear when
Peter said, "I'm making a love," I
looked up. I I kne I nearly my jaw
dropped.
Did I miss something there? Sometimes
it's not all about your idea. It's about
the heart that you have, the drive and
the determination and the focus. I was
touched by the individual,
but we're going to make money out of it.
And that's also exciting.
[Music]
12 months on. Is the company making any
money? Peter Jones is coming to check on
the progress of his and Theo's
investment. Hi Rachel.
This looks great. Yes, it's certainly a
bit bigger. It is a lot bigger, isn't
it? Yeah. These are all our stock
products which we sell largely on the
internet. So around here, the local
businesses donate their boxes to us and
we then use them to send out customers
orders. That's a great idea though. And
more import is good for our bottom line.
It certainly is. In the last year, there
have been big changes to the company and
Christian is no longer taking an active
role. My role in tiny box company now is
very small. I think I realized that my
passion wasn't in recycled or even just
normal boxes. Christian had ambitions to
relaunch his media career and he made
this his priority after his Dragon's Den
experience. After Dragon's Den, there
was a lot of media interest and a lot of
papers calling me up for for for my
story and and what happened. So, I did a
couple of interviews, you know, just
saying, "Well, here's me." Because he
chose to do the interviews, uh, it made
me question as to what his motivations
were, whether it was, uh, to help the
tiny box company or for his career or
I I was struggling to see the benefits
of it. So Rachel has managed the
expansion of the business and relocation
to their new premises with the support
of her Dragon Business partners.
Well, that was a nice tour. I'm glad you
enjoyed it. Let's get down to some
serious business. It's looking quite
nice, which is I'm not saying I'm
surprised because I know you worked hard
at it. I know you're competent. I know
you're good. What do you need from me?
If you ask me for another load of money,
the answer is going to be no. But
however, however, one of our competitors
in Holland has gone out of business and
in the shippers warehouse at the moment
is 40 pallets of stock. The shippers
have said to us, if we can recover their
costs of four or 5,000, we can have the
stock. So, there's a potential sales
value there about 90 to £100,000. Yeah,
let's buy that. I like it. I tell you
what, Theo's going to regret not coming
here now. That's a huge opportunity. I
think you're doing a really good job and
I'm going to say good luck over the next
week cuz you've got a busy week. I have.
Yes. I'm happy. And I'll speak to you on
Friday about that deal. So, what does
Peter now think about Rachel's business?
Tiny box company. She's got a tiny
business, but she's got big ambition. I
think she's tenacious. She's determined.
She's focused. And actually, I think
she's going to give it her all. I'm not
sure if we're really going to make it
into a really big business, but I'm
hoping that if anybody can do it, she
can do it.
Show business is big business at the
final stop for this leg of the Dragon's
Den tour. The West End is theaterland,
an ideal place to meet entrepreneurs
with performance at the heart of their
enterprise.
No one could have predicted that opinion
would polarize so rapidly amongst the
dragons when earlier this year Karen
O'Neal and Karen Kums entered the den.
They were offering 25% of their business
for a 100,000 investment.
Hi, I'm Karen. And I'm Karen. And we're
here today to pitch for £100,000
investment for 25% stake in our
business. Ice blading. Learn to ice
skate without the ice. Music, please.
[Music]
Heat.
Thank you, girls. Thank you, girls.
Ice blading is a new concept of learning
how to ice skate without the ice. We are
the first in the UK to produce an inline
skate that replicates an ice skating
blade. Unlike any other skate on the
market, ice blading has a progressive
learn to skate system. We see ice
blading as a big opportunity to create a
new craze based on the phenomenal
success of dancing on ice and also the
popularity of the Christmas outdoor ice
rinks. We've got three interlin but
complimentary branches to our business.
One retail, two the fitness industry and
three the education sector. For retail,
we plan to sell our skate and our learn
to skate system. For the fitness
industry, we want to be the first
aerobic fitness class that combines the
skills of ice skating mixed with
aerobics. As for the education sector,
we're currently delivering iceblading in
a number of schools right across London.
We now have an opportunity to go
nationwide as the National Ice Skating
Association has endorsed our product as
part of their national learn to ice
skate program. We hope we're not skating
on thin ice as we really need your
investment to help manufacture our
skate. Thank you for listening.
The two chirpy Karens were people that
you wouldn't want to wake you up every
morning. Having two such enthusiastic
individuals, I think would
make my head explode. We was really
chuffed with ourselves. The girls never
fell over. Everything went according to
plan. Yes. until they started asking
questions and then we just died.
Panicked. Ladies, hello. Hello. Hello. I
don't know what to say.
Is that good or bad? Well,
inline skating has been around for well
since I was a boy.
What's different between that and the
normal on inline skating?
And what has that got that replicates
that the angles basically it's your
angles. An inline skate is in line and
in a straight line and you can't do any
jumps or spins or any tricks with them.
But with these skates, it's at the same
angle as an ice skate and it's got a toe
stopper. An inline skate has another
wheel in the front there. So you can't
do anything else with an inline skate
apart from go forwards and backwards.
When you've seen people in the park, you
don't see anyone do jumps or stuff. Have
a look at one like that. Yeah. Um
Karen, I'm sorry, Ken. I don't know how
you can see you can't jump. Why? Why
can't you jump? We're all scared. Yeah,
they they do. What you're saying is they
can't jump in the same way that they can
jump in a nice They can jump off of They
can jump like this kind of jump, but you
couldn't jump off the top of your toe to
to throw it across into the air because
there's nothing to jump off of. Jump off
the top of your toe to throw in the air.
Show me that. What does that mean? to
jump, you have to jump through heel
through toe and you do it in that
position. Or you jump, if you go to
jump, you'd have to jump on your toe and
you couldn't do that on that. No inlines
you can do that on.
It's a promising start for the duo.
They're confident that theirs is the
superior skate and have managed to charm
the dragons. Now, Peter Jones wants to
drill down into their finances.
Girls, hi, I'm I'm Peter. um get down to
some I suppose key questions. What's the
manufacturing cost? What have you got
that down to now? To make if we buy say
10,000 skates is £25 and that's the
whole unit. We're selling them um for
£125.
And how many are you going to sell year
one? 5,000.
Okay. So, year one you're going to make
half a million pounds. Well, we No,
we've been um in talks with a
distributor which is actually the major
distributor in the whole of the UK. Um,
and they're very very interested in in
our product. We have a letter here as
well. We we hope in year in year two we
make a profit of um Can I stay on year
one? 5,000 units.
What profit are you going to make on
each skate? Um, us £25. You're going to
make £25 for every unit. Yeah. Profit.
Yes.
The initial glitz and glamour is
forgotten as business matters take over.
Duncan Baniti now wants to interrogate
the duo on the size of their market.
[Music]
How many people each year want to learn
to ice skate in Great Britain?
Well, there's 45,000 on the learn to ice
skate program at the moment. So, would
you say 45,000 people in Great Britain
want to learn to ice skate? Well,
there's probably more, but there's only
64 ice rinks in the country. Can you
give us a number? Um, well, Somerset
House this Christmas attracted over
100,000. I can't give you a number. No.
So, you have no idea how many people
there are out there who want to ice
skate who cannot access an ice ring. You
have no idea. No, not that can't access
an ice ring.
Um I I just can't understand this
actually
and I can't see this being a big seller.
Okay. So, for that reason. Okay. Thank
you. Thank you.
Duncan Banitine's assessment of their
business's potential comes as a blow to
Karen and Karen.
Will Deborah Megan see more promise?
Um, hello Deborah. Can you tell me about
this scheme that you've got going on
with schools? Well, we're we're teaching
them the ice blading syllabus. It's a
progressive learn to ice skate. So, you
go into a school Yes. And then you
invite pupils free of charge. No, some
schools, we've got private schools,
we're paying up to £120 per session. So
at the moment, you're all you are
retailing, you're not retailing the
goods, but you are retailing your time
and you are running these sessions. So
tell me about that model. That might
help me understand how much cash you're
actually generating. Okay. Well, we've
got 25 sessions a week at the moment in
schools. We charge from average price is
70 to1 £120. So, how much cash have you
generated so far? In five in um nearly
six months, we've generated uh 205,000.
This doesn't really sound like a very
attractive business proposition because
one of the key issues for me is I'm not
sure really there's a big enough market
for this. Well, there's quite a lot of
vice rings that are under repair at the
moment. There's about four that's
actually going down for Doesn't mean
anything to me. No, but they want the
show to go on. Okay. Let me ask you a
question. How many did you sell last
month? Like I said, we're only in
business six. How many did you sell last
month? I have another I have another
letter. How many did you sell last
month? I haven't sold any to date, but
we have letters from retailers here.
Okay. Now, I appreciate. So, you see
what I'm saying? When when somebody
sells tells me they've sold nothing and
they make up numbers of 5,000, 10,000,
20,000, it just sounds ridiculous.
There's no substance there.
When the two Karens were giving me their
cute little one lines, it didn't do
anything for me. I didn't get them. I
didn't get the product and I didn't get
the business opportunity. So,
regrettably, I'm out and therefore I
couldn't say I'm out quick enough. Peter
Jones was equally damning. This is
ridiculous and painful. I think you've
been very naive um to think that you've
got a business that's anything like
valued at £300,000. You have a business
that's valued at zero and I'd even
question that. Um it's nothing but a
little idea in your head. Um I can't
invest in ideas in heads and that's why
I'm out. Okay. Thank you. I never in my
head thought I'm going to give up.
You're still in. You still got to shout.
That's just my attitude, my mentality.
Just two dragons now remained. Deborah
Megan and the unusually subdued
Theopitis.
Only now was he ready to question them
on their key industry contacts.
You said it had been approved. Yes. Yes.
We can't believe it. We also But the
National Ice Skating Association and it
can be used as a training aid for ice
skating. Yes, it's an off ice training
aid and fundamental skating. You know,
we you can learn to skate anywhere in
the park. It works really well in
leisure centers who have got um ice
rinks because ice hockey takes up a lot
of time and it works really well if as
long as you've got space. It works
really well in leisure centers who've
got biz space and uh the sport England
survey for children ice skating came out
as the top three sports that they want
to do. So any is there any reason why
you shouldn't just buy yours and forget
buying inline skates? Yeah, because you
can do more you can do more on ours than
you can do on an inline skate. People go
around the park with their inline skates
and all their helmets and everything and
then they lose interest because it
doesn't go anywhere. Okay. So, before we
go any further, you did say you had a
letter from uh a distributor. Yes. And a
letter from the National Arc Skating
Association. Yes. Have you got those
with you? Yes. Can I have them? Yes, you
can. Thank you. I very rarely make
excuses for people in the den when they
don't know the numbers.
But I think the girls got such a pasting
from some of the other dragons unfairly.
I think a might have struggled with
those numbers as well. You know, we must
say, Theo, we've done all of this in 4
weeks.
Amazing.
Is he about to offer them the financial
lifeline they badly need?
Okay.
Right, ladies. I'm going to make you an
offer. Mhm.
For the full £100,000.
And I won't be wanting 25% of the
business. Mhm. Okay. I'll be wanting 45%
of the business because I don't believe
the business is worth anything near that
level at the moment. I could be burning
my money just like that.
And you're going to need a lot of help
to get this to market. Yes. Are we in?
When Theo made the offer, I was like,
"Oh, thank God for that. Someone's got
us out of this,
I felt really, really good. Really,
really happy." Really? But you wouldn't
have known we did cuz we were just so
Yeah. I really want Yeah. I was battered
and bruised.
Fantastic. Great. We're in.
You know, I'm going to love working with
these ladies, but unfortunately for
them, they've got a much larger task
ahead of them than they could have
possibly imagined when they accepted the
investment from me.
I'm very pleased with that. I'm ecstatic
with it. Somebody's put something in
Theo's water earlier today that has made
him turn into one of the Chuckle
Brothers. I was blown away when James
put his money into doggy treadmill. I
think Theo could have made the second
most ridiculous investment in the denim
on that one. You don't know.
I listened and um trying to find an edge
cuz that's what the den's all about is
getting that edge. Do you know you are
our chosen dragon? Peter, I was their
first choice. All right. Just thought
I'd tell you that.
Lovely. Well done again.
Thank you. Congratulations. Brilliant.
Thank you for saving us. I'm really
looking forward to it.
Just 5 and a half weeks after shaking
hands in the den, Theo's heading to
London's West End to catch up with the
Karens. But before the entrepreneurs
receive any money, there's due diligence
to consider. The allimportant patent
needs to stand up. And Theo has another
requirement for them to fulfill.
I made my offer conditional. conditional
on a world expert telling me it was just
like ice skating. Ice skating on wheels.
Let's just find out if it really works.
The retail magnate has many skills, but
ice skating isn't one of them. So, he's
called in a favor from a friend,
ex-Olympic figure skater and one-time
chairman of the ice skating association,
Hey Gunen.
Karen and Karen are still waiting for
the final components of their finished
product to be delivered. So Theo and
Hake have been watching the dancers
using a prototype skate. But will Hey be
impressed with their design. Hello.
Nice to see you again. Can I introduce
you this guy? Don't have to. Is he our
skating royalty? Is he
Oh my word. Wow. I mean this is where it
really changes from the inline blade,
doesn't it? Completely. What I love is
that you've taken a real blade. Exactly.
And maintained the toe pit and the
rocker allows you to move on just one
roller at a time or one and a half.
Right. Yeah. What I've seen mirrors
almost identical what we do on the ice.
It's an unusual form of due diligence.
Time to find out if they'd passed
Hunen's test. Well, ladies, of course, I
had a chat with Hagen.
Would you like to know what he told me?
Yes, of course.
This is a dragon's den face. Yeah, we've
seen this face before.
He loved it. Oh, that's brilliant.
That's brilliant. He absolutely loved
it. And now we got to deal with
condition number two. It's out of our
hands that one.
Okay. So, we won't know until they all
come back whether they stand or not.
Because what we're not going to do is
manufacture hundreds and hundreds of
thousands of skates and then find we're
infringing somebody's patent and have to
destroy them. In the meantime, we need
to get all the paperwork sorted out.
Yeah. Get the money ready to go. Mhm.
And then I think we might have a
business. Take over. And we're rolling.
We're rolling. I like that. I like that.
We're rolling. Let's get on the road,
ladies. The girls have proved to me that
this works. So, one of the biggest
hurdles we've now overcome. Yippee.
It's one more step down the line. That
That's good, isn't it? Much better at
the whole project and we will get there
and get ready to go.
[Music]