you look just like
this not a funny joke not at all it's
like sad honestly it is sad
oh oh Chris oh oh Chris oh
oh
random you're like a superhero I have a
serious question yeah if you were it
doesn't sound like I'm going to be too
serious if you were a superhero and like
what would your final stance be like
after you do the thing I really like the
Hulk goes
like that's that was good that was good
settle down I like that one I really
realized Captain America's like like
Shield being your brother is a lot like
having like a
5-year-old who's the tallest man you
ever seen
in what did you for breakfast all right
guys we're back and we're better than
ever random Wednesday video we were
feeling spontaneous we're here and we're
finally going to do dress to impress in
real life we have no judge we're just
going to judge each other on an honest
basis I feel like I can do it and I'm
capable and I think I'm going to be fair
what about you guys I'm going to win so
no you have to be fair now that doesn't
I'm going to be fair and I'm going to
win no but like if I did I'm going to be
fair and I'm probably still going to win
okay dude this doesn't sound very fair
no it's it's I'm just anticipating I'm
moving forward with confidence but I
also just anticipating a dog all right
these are our 10 categories we're
picking from first date 2,000 throwback
some sum vacation Zoom meeting superhero
in Disguise Rock concert fan emo gone
fishing mismatch Madness and hunting
trip only things we've had in our closet
prior of filming this video I don't
think any of us bought one thing to prep
for this video no we didn't I didn't we
didn't know what the topics were till 10
minutes ago so we're about to go hard
I'm just happy I have the best closet
for this yeah of course you spent
[ __ ] 14 years in there literally all
right I'm going to cut these up and put
them in my hat I'm going to cut these up
and put them in my hat all right we have
all 10 categories in this hat Nick's
going to do it and close your eyes my
eyes are shut idiot give me a kiss
summer vacation oh god let's see it all
right I'll see you guys in
summertime all right see you in
summertime it's over for you [ __ ]
it's over it's
over it's over for you this is so extra
extra yeah you got a toe bag extra extra
Read All About It put the towel in the
bag idiot no yes I have space cam lip
boms in here oh wow how awesome what's
with the Sass there's no sass is there
going to be alligators at the beach
there's going to be this there's going
to be a sun there's going to be a sun a
c brim would have done the
job and you're going to have a burnt
neck I'm wearing sunscreen are you I
dead ass put sunscreen on no you didn't
don't sniff me you did not I did where
on my face and my my my daily lotion has
sunscreen in it so it's not sunscreen
it's your daily lotion that's SPF okay
then I did the same thing get your
moisturizer drinks in here S V 30 30 SPF
idiot yeah I'm wearing more SPF than I
don't give it's on a bat I I and I get
the sun hat it doesn't matter what is
taking him so long I don't know [ __ ]
you look like a colorful zebra Got
Stripes everywhere you wish you could
clock this look bro I mean a little
bit take your earbuds out yeah earbuds
is minus star going to on vacation it
doesn't matter mine is earbuds are you
sick what is this bag it's a bag for my
summer goodies I have my sunscreen in
here that's not a very beachy what's
that bag this is a beachy bag cuz I'm
I'm summer vacation I'm going to
vacation I'm thinking airport like
walking to the beach like that's my what
airport walking to the beach who does
that you're to check to a hotel are you
ill you're and you have goggles on you
walk to the airport with those I made
sure I didn't want to forget them and
leave them behind they should be in this
your ass no it's not your fit is ass
ass Runway time
yeah oh
[Music]
wow he's not oh no countdown minus
points you don't need a countdown
[Music]
that'd be cooler to be throwing around
all like that this is taking a little
bit of time I don't care a little bit of
time lot walk is not good okay
okay
okay up the top wow subract point point
I'm going to do Chris's
move stole my move St to talk okay
wasn't a good runway for some watch that
much rul expecting one let's
get all right let's go
popsicle okay all right all
[Music]
right you have an apply
going sunscreen okay branding branding
you don't get a check from them kid you
have sunscreen on your lips there's
sunscreen in his mouth I don't know
what's going on all right who won this
round in your like
who won this round amongst our decision
and you guys are going to be able to
vote on every single look as well dude
all right
well I'm going to go first with my
ranking and I'm not going to be biased
and I'm going to be honest okay I put
Matt number one because I think it
is he is like if I was walking on the
beach I would think that I'd see someone
dressed like Matt first out of all three
of us I agree and that's why he's
getting my number one vote for this
round I agree thank you so much yep
who's your so you lost your mind so
number two vote Chris I give number two
to Nick and i' I'd take the third place
I have the I agree with the same
standards and you're and I'm being fair
as well thank you yes of course Matt is
clearly Matt is clearly like going to
the beach like it's a good second place
you look horrible okay so so so first
round I didn't say you iist you oh I'm
telling the truth though first round I
didn't dish you be quiet be quiet first
round I am first you are second you are
third that's the average yeah
unfortunately and what you guys and
contrary to popular belief they can
vote I'm not left I know that they're
going to vote that mine's the best okay
put on unless these girls want to sleep
with Matt vote for him cuz these get the
straight man's Advantage because you
guys are going to discriminate against
me cuz I'm gay and you I don't like you
back clock back that's so if I get third
it's cuz I know people are sympathy
voting for ma okay but you're gay
wouldn't that make them vote for you out
of
guilt poor little gay poor this is I'm
gay
but that was round one Matt do you want
to pick round number two it's round
number
two okay close your eyes I can't see
anything are you blind we
I can't see anything I can't see
sues Mitch M Mitch wow mismatched
Madness Mitch
Mitch Madness looks like a [ __ ]
orangutang wrote this is he talking
about my handwriting look at that look
at yourself I just shop space camp
wellness.com
all right thank you you you [ __ ]
about to eat my dust wait what is it
mismatch Madness it's over it's over I
do this [ __ ] every day according to Matt
so this [ __ ] about would be
easy nobody was ready for
this I know for certain they're not
going this hard and I might even ditch
the Hat yeah I'm ditching the Hat it
throws the vibe oh my God we kind of
ate we pull up What you going to do
where did you get this isn't this fire I
bought it in Japan yeah I got two
different shoes too clock that I got two
different he comes in if he comes in I
have two different sauce no yeah you ate
that if he comes in with the same pair
of shoes on immediately third place
immediately third place no we look we
look cool I had a hat on too that was
silly but it threw the vibe too much
these glasses match both this on that so
and this so you kind of [ __ ] up no cuz
it's a mix match like I still want it to
serve fashion like high fashion like no
the whole point is everything should
should be no not everything is
mismatching but the fashion is still
there black and white black and white
it's like it's like this is a CO that's
bad no it's a cohesive mix match fit cuz
I was giving us I I was giving up I was
giving up who who you looking at oh
you're crazy you crazy he's wrong I'm
doing fashion still no Nick yes I am
this if someone famous and richer than
me put this [ __ ] on a Runway there' be
[ __ ] out there eating it up and do
you want to know why
you're not supposed to match at all it's
mix match fashion I'm mixed matching but
it's fashion it's not supposed to be
this is you're supposed to get his crazy
it's dressed to impress you're not
dressed to look like a crazy lunatic hob
this one you are it's me no no it's
still like this is still giving fashion
to me if you took this hat off and then
Drew this on a [ __ ] Runway people
would eat this up watch out the mismatch
kin the a mix match
tank oh my God is that a Lobster Claw
where did you get a Lobster Claw don't
ask any questions you get a you have is
it still the worst Nick I'm I'm scared
it's first second third right now
what what first second third right now
come
on your outf thank you awesome thank you
it's literally that's the first time I
heard this is good mismatch it's
matching though these don't kind of
match though that's it's mixed matched
but I still made it work Madness it's
supposed to be crazy this is madness but
if I I could pop out like this and not
get questioned uh take it to the
runway
okay he keep it going o yeah yeah what
ooh watch out
I love I love that that that up give him
what you got yeah
yeah oh the ear
spa you look too good you look too
good wa moonwalk into the wall he came
in like a wrecking ball Pluto I hardly
know
her okay she said high five he said
which one
oh my
God where are
[Music]
we
sa laundry we need thr do laundry what a
show I feel like I I was really trying
to give fashion still I think my order
goes my unbias order goes in this round
first second third Chris your turn I'm
going to I hate to do this Matt cuz you
put me first yes first second third okay
that's okay I think
first what second
third like you were mixed match and you
were giving the madness but I wasn't
getting like fashion still where Matt
gives me mixed match but I'm still
feeling that element of fashion to a
point of which I'm shocked like me and
Matt I think could walk down some Kookie
[ __ ] fashion runway and look like
we're actually part of so what if that
averages out so you have a first I think
I'm in last TI yeah and I think you're
in first third second first first second
third
okay I don't know I don't know guys I
think if we're going from an actual
fashion perspective me or Matt win and
this is this is a fashion game so you
you win the buffoonery clown award
congratul and you've won that award
throughout our entire career
congratulations Matt one around I W
around Nix and laugh it's time for me to
go crazy going into round three Rock
concert it's over it's actually
over see you at the Rock
concert b i to say rock your
body
fatality hey you look cool oh wait let
me pause my ACDC so we don't get
copyrighted
oh are uncles oh you went crazy oh he's
oh I have a fake s oh my god oh yeah yep
oh you're a hacker hacker okay well this
round is mid yeah it's just like a
boring fit um I disagree you look swag
among though half of the [ __ ] half of
the [ __ ] in my closet was collecting
dust I haven't touched it in so long I
feel like that just look kind of cool uh
first no this belt no one would ever T
no rock star is ever going to have
you're not going like well I wanted to
show the belt it's to cash yeah too cash
really the beanie is also just like
aging you but I guess that's a good
thing cuz of like raw this is like I
think this is the most this is putting
me in third he holding a speaker are you
serious yeah throw these out you keep
this you're going to a concert you don't
need to bring the speaker I'm prepping
for the are you guys dumb people I am
not first second third in my in my
opinion I kind of like his fit more than
yours that's what I'm saying wearing
this in the no silver nothing just this
I I think except the Rand Nick's number
one okay n Matt's number one thank you
over you no no no I think I'm number one
I disagree the bandana the all I had a
black band I think I'm first you're
second you're
third me third is crazy in this one is
crazy crazy and I am rock me like
auran me being third is kind of nuts I
feel there's like SK there's like death
on my shirt you know what I mean like
first second third you should have
flipped your earrings upside down first
second third this this one we purely
need a fan vote but once again we're
just going to vote for Matt so it's like
it doesn't matter whatever wait we
didn't even do a Runway yeah we're about
I don't think we need a r ey for that
okay all right fan vote for this round
well for every round but this one in
particular we're not picking anything so
go to our Instagram stories it took me a
while to put my other [ __ ] back that's
what took me so long I'm not putting
[ __ ] back thre on the floor oh I'm
putting it my room's a mess right now
next category category number four bless
you emo I feel like no no we can't do
Emo after raw yeah you're right next one
Zoom
meeting all right all right see yall at
the zoom
no we've been a similar Vibe Mr Nicholas
and my fits better than
yours oh Matt someone cooked here wow
this is like this is like all
a first place we did the same thing all
the first
place yeah I am in the most iconic
version of this outfit in existence I
have a tie I think how hard he wants
first is like makes me want to vote him
I have a tie the the iconic version is
like white the tie and I got I got like
the you have yellow toe socks on that's
not iconic at all that's
stupid I
knew I take them old records off the
shelf ass [ __ ]
dance I just
started
what hit that one hit
that do it again that's so the only
do no give
it that was hard that was really good
all right final ranking I give you
number one no no no I don't like want it
cuz no I I give ni number one I no no I
I don't accept it I give you number one
I think you have the best I'm just happy
my schol L glasses again
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't like those stupid
jokes next or what number two number
three no cuz I don't want pity votes
like I no I that was what was my vote
was going to be number one number two
number three
swear no I don't know why I just did
three like I I swear swear I don't know
I think I won by Landslide like not no I
do think you won I have a basketball
short you guys have the under that
automatically puts me in third and then
I think yours is is more classic with
the tie than mats one two I'm my
underwar Schooler
and the [ __ ] it's stupid you're not
wearing the right outfit for this it's
fine all right
hey why was it looking right hey hey
thank you guys so much for watching this
spontaneous Wednesday video we hope to
do more of these but no promises and um
we hope you enjoyed it we enjoyed
filming it if you want a part two let us
know if you want a part two get this
video to 100 ,000 likes 100,000 120,000
120,000 likes for a part and make sure
you go to the stolo triplets Instagram
to vote on who you think dressed to impr
impress oh my God you just punched me in
the face so I don't feel bad for you no
I actually felt like my [ __ ] like
you're you pull the muscle like my my my
my hip Thruster like pop oh no Chris's
hip thrusting is about to be out of
business Chris does it way better than
you I don't know how to do that more
lean more lean in the knees in the
knees Perfect all right good goodbye
everyone hit one hit one
[Music]
[Applause]