there yes gumballs
where'd you get the gumballs
say how you miss me yeah you yeah
[Music]
what
I'm gonna dye my hair for fun again
she said she she wished there was two of
me
please don't record my countertops when
you Vlog Nick what what do you mean bro
I don't get this
it's getting in it
dirty gross bacteria everywhere what
color is it deep Purple Dream oh God
lather them up okay your own Deep Purple
Dream yeah we're going with a
semi-permanent hair dye because if I
look ugly I need it to go away quickly
it's always easier to add more than it
is to take it out
so true
oh Do you have a like a gross beach
towel or no not really and I need a
towel that I'm gonna like not
keep forever look at this
oh
how bad does it make me if I just put it
on the lens like that just
foreign
you should use this more often
maybe not to
what are you doing waiting this is
always like a really ugly fat wand just
stranded your forehead it was always
like a really ugly position to see
myself in yeah never want that I never
want this never
that was your fault unless are we
balding we yeah because like I feel you
have the same yeah I think it's just our
hairlines you think like I love how you
looked at my head and said we like well
it's like we have the same genetics like
it's gonna I don't think that's true
it's gonna happen at the same time you
really think so 100 I put a million
dollars on imagine like the sternian a
little trip let's put both
I could see it hey guys I'm gonna
embrace it that Embraces it and he looks
great I'm not doing embrace it I'm going
to get implants or something what
yeah I know but I'm gonna
look at you
[ __ ] it up
okay hold on I didn't think you'd
compliment me so soon
It's Gonna Hurt oh oh what are you
ripping it out yeah wow
I'm kidding I'm gonna do exactly what
we're doing how's the camera gonna die I
don't know because you're always not
charging it
oh what Nick my neck's a kraken this is
cute yeah yeah I feel like a little like
I was gonna say something crazy yeah I
don't do you know when no it's not crazy
like bad it's crazy it's crazy just like
super bizarre what you go first I was
gonna say something really weird God see
I was gonna say I feel like a little
lion cub like with the mom yeah that's
weird like when the mom like licks it a
lot to get it clean like I feel like I'm
just like being like cleaned by my mama
come okay
I think you're good it's a little messy
but whatever okay
Chris do you want to come help
okay
[Music]
camera died we're onto the phone now hey
phone
you just gotta kind of do it like piece
by piece Chris is good at this so I was
a little worried and it was just being
mad here okay like no hate Matt no
that's hate no it's not it's more
Chrissy's like just has more experience
like right now you're pulling on my hair
way harder than he is yeah
bro that's a Kelly Clarkson song right I
don't [ __ ] do you know that oh God I
put a lot I feel like it's not gonna
look pink I mean purple at all it's just
gonna look darker yeah but that's cool I
think it's not gonna really show at all
until it's like a little purple strips
you look like I've been on the floor I
really love that oh my God
it's not done yet but okay guys so I got
you're inspiring me Nick thank you yay
Chris put your gloves in this bag I'm
gonna sit for 30 minutes and shower and
then that's pretty much it we won't see
the reveal but I look really good right
now I kind of like a slickback hair like
if I was doing like a red carpet
like a award show or something this is
all right Nick's gonna shower I'm
definitely gonna put the camera away for
that and we'll be back really I feel
like I can charge
this is live yeah okay guys um as you
just welcome back iCarly Carly in Sam
yep as you guys just saw it yeah Matt
was trying to dye my hair and it didn't
actually happen but anyway it's so hard
to film Vlogs on the weeks we travel but
we're still here we just took a flight
into L.A we took a line to LA and we're
back this is our first week back in L.A
after tour so we've been like unpacking
cleaning all that nonsense so it's hard
to Vlog but here's a little podcast room
update we're in a [ __ ] Diner I guess
which is it's not gonna look
it's not this isn't the final product
but it's gonna be something similar to
this and we want to show you guys that
we're actually making prod pod pod
progress
progress on the podcast and that Nick
isn't a dirty Fibber so ever okay so
look booth for guests so this this um
what's it called this blue we didn't
like and also it's not going to show up
well on the camera and we didn't like
this pink either so these are the new
color samples they're very similar yeah
they look similar until I hold it up to
this but whatever but they're changing
these paints so that's why we're also
like not diving into the pocket they're
still a good like three weeks left to
work so yeah so we have to leave again
because they're gonna like build some
stuff so we have a little travel Vlog
for next Wednesday coming but yeah this
is like I want to give away all of our
secrets but we're gonna try to like
obviously give you guys a little update
so here's the room
progress we're getting rid of these
Checkers because I hate them um what
else am I gonna say I had something
important progress I have something
important
um
me and Matt have been setting up our
like PCS and [ __ ] for trying to game yes
or like twitch yet
um I'm gonna twist stream on my [ __ ]
soon but I got another podcast update
Matt yeah he's gonna switch your machine
and look out for it shut up I just gotta
get internet I gotta get why awesome
anyway turn the light on I meant to add
more can you hit that like all right
also would you like to give them a
tattoo update on what we do
on what we got today to um
to um wrap up this vlog
oh yeah go so you go first okay record
right okay so we got tattoos today
um and so I already had this deer for
curse and I had this really cool font
that I found so I got the C for Chris to
kind of like just put it all together
how do you feel um I feel very honored
and proud and I love my brother me too
I'm gonna get something from Matt here
I'm gonna you really can't get your arms
together wait is that like unhumanly
possible or am I just like you can do it
no but that's not no like I can do this
side and this obviously yeah no you
can't I just thought you were like doing
it on purpose okay but I'm gonna get it
I'm gonna get an m in the same font
match on the other side and then I need
to think of something to get from Matt
right here before
um and then me and Maddie got matching
Stars this is mine's right here my wrist
hers is in a more secret location
this is a seashell for my mom because
hold on it's blurry
okay so Matt oh way to just move and
ruin it okay this is just stop
it
it's a seashell for my mom because this
this dude is for my dad and I wanted
them to do them nice and close together
and then this is we're gonna explain why
the seashell for your mom
no it doesn't matter okay next matter
next to them it matters to me and it
matters to Mom amen
it's because mom always like looks to
see shells at the beach and she's like
oh my God she's such a seashell lady she
likes to collect them and me collected
them as kids walking on the beach all
fun and nice okay
my stomach is full I don't know anyway
you put a lot of attention
and then I got this
um fire ax hold on camera reset
and then I have this fire ax because we
had a house fire and it was stop moving
that was Nick I have this fight I didn't
see the hairs on your on your arms
sticking up y'all are bloody yeah I hope
whatever Chris just recorded is like
it's great it's awesome it's rad okay
I'm barely in this Vlog so can you take
the camera so I can Bust A Move yeah
sure
whoa whoa whoa hold on hold on hold on
you look so small
oh [ __ ]
oh
a little bit of tissue in my freaking
shirt back it's bloody like you just got
tattooed with that I don't want that
wait don't cut the camera yet I'm not
cutting it all in my pocket okay I will
put keys in there guys thank God I was
worried guys to wrap up the video Chris
is never gonna put keys in this box
especially now knowing there's a hole
because I wouldn't want to lose the keys
oh
he's vlogging on weeks that we fly so
sorry that wasn't my favorite Vlog but
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things