I love when we all have merch on
something about it just brings me so
much joy cuz it's really just us I know
like I just remember how little we were
wanting to make brand and merch and now
we got it bro napkin guys I'm not a huge
fan of inel fries I'm not a huge fan of
in out I hate in what is up guys it's
the St triplets we're here we're going
to eat a ton of in out food cuz we
haven't had dinner all day cuz we were
flying on a plane and we're all hungry
we're back here comes the plane
oh are you [ __ ] kidding me how you
miss my gums are about to like bleed I
tried to go down your throat but I
missed all right bro like you're nuts
anyway you want to know what my first
thing I want to say in the video is what
anybody TR that tries like one of those
impossible puzzles or like the all black
puzzles should actually just be put in
an allwhite room cuz your entire life is
puzzling wow see you wow you know what I
mean yeah I do CU like what's the fun in
that like you know how you know how many
other things you can do to be productive
instead of spending hour
doing a puzzle that's all the same thing
and you sit there and you go Peace by
piece peace peace by peace you collected
me I don't know this song Kelly Clarkson
come on girl Oh I thought it was a
Christian song that Mom played uh-uh
dude I don't know why I feel like weird
right now don't feel weird I don't feel
bad I don't feel good I don't feel like
outstanding I'm happy I'm chill alive
but I feel a little like awkward like I
don't know something seems off right now
I keep seeing people in public and
wanting to to cry I know Nick gets
really upset when he sees like really
nice people and we I just want nothing
bad to happen to them we just saw a nice
nice Lady In and Out World evil evil
Nick felt a connection evil who says
that Mermaid Man Evo everyone the in out
was so nice and I just think of like I
just think of a [ __ ] driving through
the Inn out and like just being a
[ __ ] douchebag you forgot my
mustard type beat then just like they're
there and they're like try I said no
onions and they're just trying to get
their check and no I said three double
doubles not two with extra spread oh
ordering spread is nasty ordering I feel
like wrong building I feel like I'm
going to be like a strip club or
something yeah like
order I don't know can I get the double
double and can I get some spread like n
that's crazy spread is crazy can I get
some spread a
style like that's insane
do me a favor flip over and spread it
animal style this is top this is crazy
flip over spread it animal
style give me 20
minutes to pull on up to the next
window you guys are nuts we're
nuts you're going further into the joke
oh my God it's a
seven actually that's the Grim Reaper's
curse look at that's a seven
yeah do any want to try a pepper God no
mm- I don't know I just I don't know why
you got those ew why is it so little
that's
huge that's the biggest pepper I've ever
seen in my life I don't know what you're
talking
about get the [ __ ] away from me now
because it's so small I can't even eat
it it's just like like it's just like
it's a big [ __ ] pepper it's just like
blasting the like [ __ ] you're going
need like milk or water um what's it
called spicy right I wish you would stop
anyways we don't have a topic for today
we're just eating our dinner but similar
to a video we filmed with our friend
Nate we were eating Wingstop we're just
going to answer some random questions
that you guys that
yep a little while ago I said that I
want our next car video to be telling
our icks about each other and we didn't
film the video but there is one that I
need to say out loud I'm ready all right
sit back down Chris Chris will always
say when you ask him if you want
something no or he will always say oh no
thanks or oh I don't actually need that
or don't get me anything and then you
get yourself something and he gets that
and he just eats it and I feel like you
know how like when people get into a
relationships and they're like oh like
what you want their girlfriend's like no
fries and you're like extra fries for
the girl like that Tye [ __ ] yeah
basically cuz girls always just [ __ ]
pecks away at my
food that's another one you you burp
like a [ __ ]
elephant start eating and you you're
chewing like a monster start eating my
bur bur almost gone you're the only
reason you think you're the only one
eating is cuz you can hear yourself from
a [ __ ] mile away that could be the
Weston Andes and hear your ass too
seriously it's
unbelievable go ahead say what you want
to say I was just going to say I'm so
happy right
now I love you guys oh my God you're so
annoying you cuz we're also trying to
joke around and every time we film and
we're trying to joke you're like man I
don't know like I just feel like like
you like I don't know like man I don't
know man uh I don't know man like you
just say that all the time do I say I
don't know man like a lot every [ __ ]
video we film you're like I don't know
how many oh my God I picture into my
head how many times has Chris I've seen
the clip you just goes I don't know man
and like that exact thing before saying
some stupid annoying [ __ ] for like 10
more minutes today then we give it you
in your life we got to La we just
experienced three fabulous weeks in
Boston and I just feel
so I don't know man it's just like I
don't know something about need
something
else what close I'm not going to say
that like I'm feeling like so much
potential is about on cage for me I
don't know what it is dude something
just feels really keep your potential in
your
[Laughter]
something just feels really like magical
right
now I don't know man I'm letting you
talk cuz you've almost said I don't know
man twice it could be this guy on my
shirt though that could be the magic I'm
just so B like I feel like blessed that
us three get to make decisions every day
on like what we want to do with our
decided to be annoying [ __ ] you can you
[ __ ] actually stop dude I'm trying to be
sentimental right now you know those red
but butt Apes that just like walk around
and go a baboon yeah baboon red butt ape
10 it's a
baboom why you that after you're like a
[ __ ] red ass baboon that's what you
are God you just monkey around all the
time I love monkeying around yeah I know
[ __ ] no can we actually be
sentimental and real with the viewers if
you got the [ __ ] point okay I'm just
really happy right now I'm happy to be
back in La I'm happy we just went to
Boston and like dude this whole debate
has been like a big big thing in our
whole career of like oh my God busted
versus LA how about you shut your
mouth like holy [ __ ] Boston oh I miss
when they were in Boston oh oh oh I miss
when your lips were sealed you obnoxious
[ __ ] oh oh oh oh oh I I don't
know I don't know I know I don't know
man whatever we're moving on no I just
want to
say that our three have been able to do
and go anywhere we genuinely want you
know if I want to be in La I'll be here
or I want to go to Boston guess where
I'll be Boston yeah I don't I think
people think that I think people think
we're like in jail I think that people
think once you hit 50k subscribers on
YouTube you lose your free will yeah
it's not the case at all my Free Will
has never been Freer Free
Will aren't you stunned that fries just
come from potatoes blows my mind every
day it's little crazy oh my God Matt you
cannot feed into it I can't I just spit
I can't do another potato conversation I
really can't I'll [ __ ] burn myself on
fire I'm going to go upstairs to my
bathtub and drown myself tonight if you
let Chris carry this no no no let your
thank you moving on how was that pepper
it was I feel like I'm sitting next to a
pre kindergartener a prek PR oh my God
that's what pre stands for don't touch
me I feel like I'm sitting next to a
child just one yeah you're fine yes
let's go last time I we filmed a video
and we were just eating food and it was
on the table and [ __ ] people are like no
plates straight up the table do you
think our table's a [ __ ] this isn't a
[ __ ] dirt pen clean the [ __ ] table
every time we film we clean the table I
would take that burger and wipe it from
the front door to the back door on the
ground and eat the rest of it people
love to pretend they're so clean oh they
didn't do this then they need to wash
this they need to clean their table
don't act like you're some prissy little
princess who's not eating a little bit
of dirt we're all human I literally
[ __ ] take these fries and hum them
behind my back onto the ground and then
sit on the floor and eat the rest I
agree so enough of the cleanliness talk
we're over that if you could swap lives
with one of your brothers who would who
would it be in
why Trevor he lays on his ass and does
nothing and eats don't count him yeah
we're counting him are you discounting
him yeah yeah okay uh that ain't my bro
that's my
dog I have to say Matt because I
disagree with Matt most so I just want
to live a life of his opinions for one
day I want to live a life as Nick cuz I
think that it would be so fun to see you
want to know how hard it is no I want to
see how
dramatic oh my God I want to see how
dramatic one could be about minuscule
things one thing I've noticed is Nick
does a lot more talking than doing
really you no that that's a good thing
or maybe I go in your head just to be
like just to see how many different
thoughts pop up from all oh my God you'd
be not like you'd be insane like you
just feel crazy yeah I do right now one
thing that I've noticed about myself
lately did you
ask see what I mean like what thought
just told him I think I have to get
tested for like terat not even kidding I
wouldn't doubt
it
I was thinking I saw this Tik Tok this
kid is making slime and he was using
glue and I'm like this could go south
really quick like I don't think we under
like we underestimate how self making
slime can go how could it go that bad
cuz it was just like Globs of glue and
like the noise was all chunky and it was
like pouring out that how could that go
so poorly it's all about ratio like what
if you made slime one day and you just
got stuck together that would never
happen like if you're like no and you
were stuck oh my you guys be making
gorilla using Gorilla as going to ask
stop dude what like do you think you
going to abbreviate Gorilla Glue just a
gorilla was he using Gorilla like no
using Gorilla Glue was your joke say the
full thing what was I going to say I'd
love to see you compete on are You
Smarter Than A Fifth Grader oh my god
get me some questions let's do it let's
do it no yes on the show no I couldn't
do it on the show why it's too insane
let me i' love to see it I want to see
those fifth graders your ass about that
[ __ ] you did you know they would no they
wouldn't they wouldn't touch me what
about the other day I was I was taking
Nick pictures and he fell and I took a
video of it tell them about it the other
day I was taking n stop no it was so
funny and he was like can you take a
video real quick so I have the video the
second I started recording he backpedal
into a tree stump and he fell and it was
the funniest thing in the world what was
the first day of the 20th century what
what was the first day of the 20th
century January 1st
2000 19 and
1901 no you cut a quarter into thirds
how many pieces would you have three
there you go there you
go this is just if I have five apples
and you have four apples how many more
apples do I have one
moreing good good you guys think I'm
going to get these wrong how many states
made up the United States before Alaska
and Hawaii joined
48 yep what makes a square
square um it has four sides and they're
all equivalent there you
go you're doing so good out of the
fractions below which is the greatest
three out of 20 three out of nine or
three out of five three out of five mhm
yeah what is the what is I think you're
the toughest cook is
38 I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry please
don't me please don't hit me please
don't hit me I'm sorry I didn't mean it
you just God grace me with
patience I'm sorry Nick I'm sorry this
is going to be a funny one I love when n
how many syllables are in the word
RH how many syllables are in the word
four Oh I thought you were going to
sounded out for sure I did in my hands
oh which one of these words is an
adjective cotton she jump or red wait
what which one of these words is an
adjective cotton ad adjective you're not
saying it correctly you know what he's
trying to say adjective cotton she jump
or
red do you know what an adjective is
that's what I'm trying either it's
either I think it's an action word so is
it cotton she jump or red that would be
jump you're wrong it's a describing word
so it would be red [ __ ]
Y which musical in instrument would you
want to play
most
I already see the edits if I play guitar
I play bass it's a photo of Matt and you
like the drunk have you guys seen the
photos of Matt photoshopped on a
motorcycle no what is
happening I'm officially as of today
deleting Tik Tok forever if you had to
live in a cage for the rest of your life
would you want the bars to be vertical
or
horizontal I feel like vertical bars so
I can grab them like this horizontal
bars you got to go like that I
horizontal cuz I would learn how to
climb around them oh you're
right no I want vertical so I can break
out like
this you're not breaking out of [ __ ]
yeah correct yes I could I want
horizontal so I could hang upside down
like put my feet through and just in the
funon or if I do vertical so I can
just so fast that's what I would do
that's a good question though really
creative we need more people like that
can you please give a shout out to my
friend your biggest fan that is not a
[ __ ]
question it actually
is no it's off topic what's the weirdest
rumor you have heard about yourself that
I'm not actually gay true I know
it when is Chris getting a tattoo never
I have one on my on my
ass it's like an aquatic fish scene
swimming into his
[ __ ] dude what the [ __ ] are you
saying LA or
Boston electric
chair did Matt get a chance to Fen to
have french
toast not yet biggest high school
tip biggest
what high school
tip
y'all are
insane I don't know biggest high school
tip
please what do you guys
laughing if your teacher says that you
can't get up and go to the bathroom you
actually can you definitely can anyways
guys that has been this week's Wednesday
video we hope you enjoyed yeah do we
know that Easter is already gone but you
can wear this school merch all year
round it's more you guys keep saying
Easter it's more spring like bunnies
well that one's definitely Easter spring
spring stuff is still available so if
you want to go get your spring stuff
drop I really enjoy this I love the
character tease a lot so if you want to
go shop the merch that Matt and Chris
have on the website is in the link in
the description and on the screen right
here it's only going to be available
until it sells out and then it'll
probably never be on our website again
so if you want to get these shirts and
claim your stake as a sternol triplet
fan at this time and place now it be
time to go shop link on the screen or
Link in description thank you guys for
watching today's Wednesday video sorry
if we were a little low energy we had a
big flight today yeah we literally it is
Tuesday or it is Wednesday at 1:00 a.m.
so I'm editing this and posting it the
same day so the day you're seeing this
we filmed less than 12 hours ago yeah we
had a [ __ ] that's crazy to think of
yeah we had a long week we're the
[ __ ] best we're here we're the
[ __ ] best momy nobody does what we do
and that's just a fact perod
Queen perod
Queen
[Music]
yeah