is it in Focus too Matt is it
good I always like forget he can't hear
he is it good can you not see my hand
when I point in which direction to go
did you set did you is it good is it in
no it's fine but all right so stop
talking
F and then what you saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
that we did we said we going to travel
from the island to Madrid we had a lot
of plans but they
all because of some but it's okay cuz
I'm moving different don't be saying
nothing
when yes young going to W to back
calling me
splur right off the curb yeah are you
feeling Str bully I am super I've never
felt strum bully in my life leave your
chair put it back leave it alone cuz I
checked and then it's going to be out of
focus and out of frame and then Nick
Nick's going to go to edit and it's
going to be like mat the type I got to
go like this mat the timee I got to go
like
this um
one of the editors [ __ ] somebody's
going to go back and get the clip of you
literally doing that when it's the same
video you literally looked at Nick and
went the same video
yeah that hurt me too you hit my
necklace you dumb [ __ ] would roast you
if you got an awesome let STP shirt on
all right today we're going to show each
other Foods then we're going to eat it
or delete it wait before speaking of
food before you even start do you want
to hear the craziest thing ever that
happened to me today this is actually
going to be my raw opinion cuz right now
Matt shut up oh yeah right now you're
tough go ahead what he said starving
Matt thinks he's tough though like today
he's extra tough if anyone was curious
Matt's super tough today Matt I love you
bro I feel like we haven't had a car
video where it's just passion of love
and I love you God remember when you
guys used to have like a love triangle
with one another forever ago first of
all there's two people here so it was
like it was like it was like so weird
like it was such a thing content like
you guys were in love and it was so are
you saying bro you guys are flirting
shut the [ __ ] up wonder what happened to
me today that was Insanity like
mind-blowing insanity like I was like I
literally like left the situation like
like like boom like boom like I was like
okay go ahead we get it I'm all four sh
I'm all for like service workers like I
feel bad for them you know what I mean
like if if something's out of the way
for a service worker and they're like oh
we don't have this we don't have this we
don't have that and they like work at a
drive or something I'm like oh it's all
right don't worry about it like it's
okay them next time whatever but when
they're wrong I'm like it takes me to
the Moon to say the least this morning I
went to a meeting before you guys were
awake and I went to a Dunkin Donuts
drivethru to get my morning coffee so
that I could have some energy right I'm
driving Nick the type of guy to have a
shirt don't talk to
me sh or a mug shck no the mug for sure
and it's like if it's not at this line
don't talk that's Nick no not true but
regardless Nick can you wait can you
shut up I want to have my caffeine first
I want have my coffee first regardless
laugh laugh I love when Matt laughs oh
don't do that trust laugh Matt um I I
will I will if something's funny go
ahead ni there's never a need to scream
like that if you're not getting shut up
Matt you're the best never need to
you're awesome you're so awesome I was
going through the [ __ ] drive-thru and
I was like hey can I get 10 pumpkin
munchkins it's festive time like it's
like autum I want 10 pumpkin munchkin if
someone ordered 10 pumpkin munchkins I
would totally expect Nick to be the guy
oh my God stop I go can I get 10 pumpkin
munchkins homie goes no you can only get
assorted munchkins through the drivethru
but and I was like oh I understand that
because like I can understand if like
you can only get assorted munchkins
because like that might be all they have
right so I was like oh I can't get the
10 pumpkin munchkins and he was like no
in order to specify the flavor you need
to either do a mobile order or come in
the store so I'm like you're telling me
you're not out of pumpkin munchkins and
I can't request 10 of them and he's like
no in order to get in order to pick the
munchkins you want you need to come in
the store or use the mobile app I don't
think that's true I said during the ice
spice collab dur I didn't say that but I
was like in my brain during the ice
spice collab crazy it's munchkins during
the ice spice collab the collab is out
right now during the ice spice collab so
I was sitting there what what's sense
does that make I I like I can't get Matt
come on no go ahead Matt I can't get I
can't get the 10 pumpkin munchkins I
want unless I go into the store or
through Via Mobile well I don't know
what's the I was I was in can the same
thing's going on listen what's happening
here's my thing go ahead let's hear it
Matt mobile Matt got a lay Mobile's more
likely for an assortment one of I'm
correct just here let me get there you
ready mobile I don't like the way you
act good go ahead Matt you don't have to
like it this the way I act o that was
tough that was real like that was cool
mobile orders I've seen multiple times
where somebody Moby order something and
then like mob orders sorry just like
when you put Moby order like when you
take mobile order to Moby order it's
something about it just makes you giggle
oh I bet go ahead anyway when you when
you Mo take a mobile order yeah and like
no say it again say mobile order when
you Moby order something the ventory is
sometimes off where it's like you could
do the 10 pumpkin spice munchkins then
they'll [ __ ] it up the thing that I'm
really confused about here is [ __ ] it up
whoa is the fact that if you walk in
there and say something at the register
you can't say the same thing into the
little box and the my exact confusion my
exact confusion who's beating around the
bush hiding the munchkins in there I
just think he wanted them all to himself
so he like I'm going to throw an
assortment at it the little [ __ ]
chocolate glaze munchkins make me ill
the little jelly two the [ __ ] worst
munchkins ever I was this close to
becoming a Karen like I almost was like
let me you you should just lay down wait
so did you get assorted no I didn't get
any zero didn't get any munchkins I
wanted that crazy who's calling me door
Dash give me a second
hello hi this is door Dash uh they don't
have that you can get any
color oh that's totally
okay
P
36 oh 36 36 is perfect oh the one that I
purchased was a 15
count 16 counts okay then let me get oh
it was 15 15 20 15 all right so we're
going to keep going with this video but
course see you soon thank you I
appreciate it it's crazy pumpkin spice M
munchkins eat or delete ooh delete
they're absolutely I love them contr
delete
for pumpkin munchkins blow
ass idiot you're an idiot pumpkin oh my
God it's fall season it's the fall Vibe
do they do do they do muffins that are
pumpkin like that uh yeah do they
something like it might have to take
apple cider donuts holy [ __ ] I just get
so like warm inside I just want to rub
the cinnamon sugar all over my body okay
oh my god did like go just go weird
about it all right guys eat it or delete
it that's so weird that's so St all
right I had to make that joke good job
I'm glad you made it now that you're
done with that let's proceed let's
proceed Nick this type of got to say
let's proceed go idiot you don't even
know what the [ __ ] you're saying half
the time you're just speaking oh that
looks nasty Matt I don't know what what
if it's almost like homemade favorite
meal you could tell it's homemade yeah I
can tell it's homade for sure I don't
even want to click on that one yeah I
know that was gross oh ice cream cake
made by our dad that's mat just talked
[ __ ] about what he he kind of went crazy
kind of awful what I don't like like the
middle it looks like it looks like a
fake it looks like a gummy Pizza you
look like a gummy Pizza huh I can't see
spaghetti with meat sauce AKA spaghetti
German asparagus with
sauce salt potatoes and guys we got to
we got to actually do the point oh my
God I oh my God I oh my God I'm actually
scared of that I'm actually scared of
that these scared of that that one looks
kind of good to me that one actually
looks terrifying pass it's cuz you just
don't like that stuff pass Chris it's
white asparagus that was frightening no
I love asparagus I love ham why did I
say ham like I was scared and I really I
hate ham oh I love potatoes let's figure
out a traditional food is he not getting
what I'm saying what you Googled it I
don't want to see Google I want to see
photos of food at home we're going to
show the the the food then we're going
to all say eat or pass do we have to say
it like a [ __ ] total goof
eat you can say it how it is however you
want going to say loser scent a lot
Matt what's that a pancake with
strawberries can't see eat can't see I
can't see [ __ ] look can't see I'm
eating that oh don't say it like that
I'm eating the can you eat say like a
little girl like a little goof okay eat
not eating that salad I'm definitely
eating these definitely eating the
potatoes for sure potatoes are so yummy
what is this is that like coconut on the
like fruit with powdered sugar on it
Nick that looks like your don't that
looks like your ideal Tuesday Nick I
only I can't get behind is this top left
plate but that's cuz I'm just a I like
omelets I'm not a fan of that salad
whatever's going on that's garlic bread
oh it looks like weat though I eat that
bread I eat that bre IAT that bread all
right all right all right you guys are
freaking me out o eat e that I need that
I need that I need that eat okay Chris
enough of that joke all right we're done
we're done we're done I'm going to quit
shut the [ __ ] I'm at oh I'm drinking
that too that little lime that's a lemon
that's a lemon that's a lemon whatever
you good I'm great Oh e actually I don't
like no get rid that one tomato chunk
right there and I'm good for a go green
is a light if you get if you get rid of
the Tomato chunks I'm in there I don't
[ __ ] with basil on top Basil's good A
lot of it do with the dish too and I
like that I like that like that plate
you like that scre I'm going to stupid
[ __ ] oh croissant croissant Matt almond
croissant go go go Matt has PSD cuz he
got a croissant that once and it looked
like it was filled with cream a mystery
cream we didn't know what it was and now
Matt gets nervous about croissant cuz I
don't like anything yeah he ate a
croissant and got surprised what the
[ __ ] is
this see someone Googled it like I don't
want to see Googled [ __ ] I want you to
get Crea they search like ugly meal or
something this one makes me four minutes
oh queasy great word great
word oh my God what the [ __ ] is
that what is
that Nick would eat it I can't even look
at it I
can't Nick would say Nick you remind me
a lot of packman especially since you
dyed your hair I don't [ __ ] with you at
all I hate you
actually
you you try to have such a cute laugh
but it ain't like that they laugh ugly
Nick I don't try to have a cute laugh
you do though O mint chocolate chip ice
cream that looks like good classic like
I feel like I'm at I'm at the fair I
feel like I'm
13 that's a class the scoop on top of
the scoop God you guys keep
talking I feel like I've had that mint
chocolate chip where the [ __ ] is he
going I feel like I've had mint
chocolate chip ice cream like that
before with those exact ch chocolate
chips oh my God oh my God oh my God okay
for those East Co East Coast kids around
our age to
1921 what did he just do he just went to
the freezer okay whatever um sorry I'm
thrown off remember those the fen if
you're from Boston remember those like
Fenway Hood ice creams oh classic Matt
Nick stop don't speak cuz I'm the [ __ ]
where'd you why Fork ice cream with a
fork didn't have any spoons and I have
to deal with the cards you're dealt and
that's exactly what I'm doing okay
listen go ahead oh my door dasher's here
sorry keep talking like come on this is
crazy kids a [ __ ] Busy Bee tonight
literally like just running around a
worker so if you're from b b like your
tattoo if you're from Boston or near
Boston and you got like the hood Fenway
ice cream the mench CH they oh don't you
don't got to tell me tell them I know
brother I know they put the the socks
were the chocolate the red so they put
the Red Sox logo in just nice coated
chocolate threw it in the ice cream that
[ __ ] was good oh my God I think it was
friendly it's not Hood there's no way
what oh my God what the most phenomenal
bacon cheese fries I've ever seen in my
life
really oh my God those look good so good
those look really good oh I'm eating
that like it's [ __ ] no none of my
business oh
yeah I don't know what the [ __ ] else is
that but I'm eating all that show Nick
show Nick show Nick show Nick Nick come
on look at how delicious that
looks bacon cheese waa bacon cheese
fries Nick would like look at
that that looks so good not look oh my
God that looks so
delicious Creme
Brule Nick's such the type of guy to
like Creme Brule Cru spoon okay but
listen but listen is this how you spell
it oh wow n they're being extra oh
French cuisine let's see Cuisine it's
quisine you're going to get sick no is
that I feel like you will I'm worried I
don't know it looks a little red to me
yeah no I send that back to the chef
yeah no
hate you're going to get sick
no go is the grill on i'
say usually usually I'd go up to I'd try
and be nice like usually when you're
cooking something you hear like a a
little Sizzle that one that was it a
plop they just plopped the meat on the
table all the chef did was skin the cow
Nick that's crazy
descriptive oh this girl sending videos
like let's all
the here we go for there you go we're
good we're good yeah we get it we get it
about what about this little sandwich
let me
see let me see I feel like Nick would
[ __ ] with it that's why I'm confused I
don't like that bread toss it on some
white and we're good okay exactly my
point M up got to get rimless rye bread
just cut the crust off or something
rimless bread is that not with the crust
does bread have a rim I feel like the
the crust is the rim you're ridiculous
bro calling crust a rim is insanity
really crazy waa what is that oh it's
dog food no why are we sending us dog
food kids just taking my phone every
time let's ask Trevor Matt get the [ __ ]
out of here dude
Trevor what was hey Trevor was crazy oh
my God Nick an octopus
leg I feel like I would try
it the you want to know what I heard I
would try what I heard about it I know
what you're going to say m it's like
chewing a piece of gum really yeah
that's like you were like on that thing
for like a while oh little P sucker That
Pie looked good it did look good just
really Berry full oh Berry full pie can
you see the camera can you see see when
it's real yeah yeah you're covering me
completely okay what were we going to
say nothing Matt don't cuz M will be mad
at me that's fine oh a s'more pie a
s'more pizza oh that looks so good they
definitely Google that like you a make
that yourself oh yeah for sure but that
[ __ ] looks delicious we should learn the
recipe to that awful to me awful to me G
cracker crust marshmallow topping
chocolate spread no I've fam no Nick
you're crazy that looks really good I
agree oh my god dude my wrist just get
so itchy sometimes I thought you got
electrocuted that was crazy I hope you
guys like it for your eat it or
pass no [ __ ] way that's not even eat
it or pass that's like I want to like
Matt would eat that oh my God that's
actually disgusting I really hope they
didn't eat that they okay out just take
the ketchup off and have the noodles bro
you're okay Matt it's not here it's not
going to hurt you you don't have to eat
it you're good oh someone just says
chicken alfredo like come on of course
we're eating that oh Nick berri a Tacos
yeah but those don't look as good as
berri tacos I've had in the past ooh
those look yummy Nick you're really
throwing me off by chomping in my ear
right now a little bit right yeah it's
just like a all right never do that [ __ ]
again you do that all the time bro
should we check what color balloons oh
homemade mac and cheese oh they snapped
I really am just a sucker for some good
old M really good really good that looks
really good I how old do we think the
soda is I don't know how I think it's
probably like a day
old regret wow look at
this let me see that's literally from
Papa John's sh is it really that's
literally from Papa John that's like a
mess waiting to happen like all the
little weenies and the bread I like that
sometimes my favorite part of the pizza
is the crust so you're just taking away
my favorite part how can you even eat
the Middle with the that type of crust
well I don't like that they're
portraying the dogs on the side let me
get this is it like a double meal what
Nick dogs on the side dogs off Andy no
no no
no it's two separate foods give me
pepperoni pizza and give me the in the
blanket right yeah the pigs in the
blanket all right I love that name pigs
in a blanket and they're just oh in the
blanket
I kind of want some of those did you see
that Nick what I'm afid holy [ __ ]
chocolate covered
pancakes oh uhoh it's like peanut butter
toast with pickles and ketchup I got to
get out of here I can't we're ending the
video oh my God clunk chunky CL clunky
clunky CH popsicle we're ending the
video these people have ending the video
n they were bored no that's just and
like the the thing is like they
definitely got that from Google but the
thing that's sick is somebody had to do
that to put it on Google I'm so foul bro
I think my favorite food that I saw was
that mac and cheese that looked good as
[ __ ] I really like mac and cheese the
creme brulee looked good
too Nick the type of gu to eat Creme
Brule and think he's fancy I'm really
disturbed by that the type of guy to say
eat it
eat well that has been this week's
Friday video we'll see you guys
Wednesday and then Friday and then
Wednesday and then Friday follow us
stolo do oh my God and our podcast on
Monday follow us at st. tries on
Instagram so that you never miss a thing
because we will always update you what
we're doing right there true and follow
us individually if you care to do that
as well one day and turn our post
notifications on because those are
always good so you never ever miss a
video anding what you saying how you
miss me yeah you miss me and all the
things that we did so to travel from the
islands to Madrid we had a lot of plans
but they
Alla why oh because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
when I with [ __ ] for my brothers