[Music]
Hey, I'm Mia. Let me introduce the
number one jumpsuit, Mono Suit. Ladies
love jumpsuits, but the nature's call
his drama half naked in a restroom. Such
a mental trauma. Behold, I get the fix.
No stress, no more lines at the ladies.
Sorry, Kevin. You might not get this,
but this little prick you want. Buy mono
suit for your lady with the zipper in
the right spots and hit a jackpot.
Robert, do you think my mono suits
ironic?
It's iconic. Let me explain. Fashion
causes pollution. It's an undeniable
fact and it's time to react. All ladies
want that. I turn ocean plastics into
minus suit.
It's my eco hack. It's my global impact.
Circular life, zero waste, eco-friendly,
and it feels divine. We cleaning up the
ocean. One man suit at a time. Mark, do
you think I'm cute and funny? Then show
me the money charts. Together we'll
purify oceans and make our planet
cleaner. And with your help, we'll make
this world a whole lot greener. So check
out the money suits that you have right
over here.
Outstanding performance.
Thank you. Good job.
Wow.
Good job.
Um, can I have that one on the end?
Oh, that is so me.
Yeah.
So honored to be here. Uh my ask is 150
uh uh thousands for 5% of equity.
Okay.
And here's your little secret zipper in
the back.
Exactly. We got a patent for the zippers
on the butt because you know that every
every women can understand that
the most problematic thing is sitting
half naked in the restroom
because you need to remove it all. I can
do a demonstration a little bit if you
want.
So
it works like this.
Yes, it does.
It's very important to to say that my
suit is not just one piece collection.
We have the whole sustainable line of
pieces including for example sneakers, I
mean accessories, I mean sleeves,
dresses.
So you sell everything we see out there
from the sleeves to the shoes to the
gloves to the belt.
How much is it? So the average cost uh
retail price $290 per piece and the cost
to produce it is approximately $60. We
produce it in north Italy and it's made
from the recycled ocean waste.
The whole technology that we developed
maybe you know that the most polluting
thing in the ocean is actually fishing
net.
This is my mission and I explain why
because I was born in a small village um
in USSR. My dream was to become a
fashion designer, but we don't have any
money for to buy new clothes. So, I
actually literally upcycle all the
clothes into something I could wear.
So, Mia, what are your sales in the last
12 months?
Uh sales for the the past year was uh
$245,000.
And very important to to say that we did
not use any paid advertising.
Mia, how should I think of you? Should I
think of you as a fashion line or should
I think of you as a jumpsuit company?
So we are the fashion brand building a
sustainable community and technology at
the same time. I would say the core of
the business is the whole technology.
You can produce of course uh
but are they made out of all the same
material these bodysuits made exactly
from the ocean waste
right? What percentage of your sales are
your mono suit?
Approximately uh 70%.
Have you raised any money for that?
Yeah. Uh several years ago we raised $2
million from angel investments.
Wow.
And uh to
What valuation did you do on that 2
million? What did you say your business
was worth?
Uh 12 million.
12 million. 12 million.
It was in 2018.
But what happened?
Where did the 2 million go?
I will explain. So develop the uh two
collections per year. So to develop this
technology and let me explain about
technology. So currently clothing has a
linear life. All the things we are
wearing right now it will spend hundreds
of years until it bros down polluting
the planet obviously. So my suggestion
in my technology works like this. You
buy monu for us. You wear it. You return
it to us and we recycle it into
something new. So basically zero waste.
We just need money for develop it
further to make it really circular. Let
me let let me clear things up. Look, I
think they're beautiful. The challenge
is you're in two businesses, actually
three. You're trying to be an
eco-friendly business, you're trying to
be a technology business, and you're
trying to be a fashion business. And to
me, that's hard because they're all
expensive and they all require a special
focus. So, I don't see the ability to
pull all these pieces together in a way
that's affordable. So, for those
reasons, I'm out.
So, um I think the business is all over
the place.
And personally, I think if you just
focused on this jumpsuit thing and rode
that wave, you might make a lot more
money. Great presentation, great
product. Not for me. I'm out.
Okay.
Mia, I thought you were coming out with
a beautiful workout product to take on
Lululemon. I have no idea what business
you're in.
I don't know if you're in a tech
business, fashion business, jumpsuit
business. I can't follow the uh the
bouncing ball. I'm out.
Let me explain uh also a little bit
further.
Can I mention one thing?
I thought this was the new Lululemon and
I was excited, but seeing all over the
place made me think that we wouldn't be
hyperfocused on making money through
this one outstanding product with the
great zipper in the back. Right. So, for
that reason, I'm out.
So, you're a very good designer. I love
what you've created. I would buy half at
least of what you have sitting here. But
my advice, I personally feel that
150,000 is nothing for you. Like
compared to what you're going to need, I
don't think this is the right investment
for me or for you. And for that reason,
I'm out.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you ladies.
Bye ladies.
Thank you.
I was a little bit disappointed that
people are continued focusing only on
making money but making money is good
but making money and making the planet
cleaner and making good for the planet
is much more important and big thing
that's why I was yeah I was I feel even
angry a little