belus is a totalitarian state I wanted
to be free the guy worked in it advised
me if you get that job you will be free
you can get out of belus you won't be
dependent on rules of the country where
your parents are where your relatives
are and and you were looking to get free
so that worked totally work everything
is working out I'm so happy in my life
but that changed dramatically with
Revolution B we had a raid in our office
government took four people hostage how
did I navigate that so you recently
crossed 100 million of AR how did that
feel when you notice that actually
happening there's a brand value of the
100 million brand value of becoming a
unicorn company yeah you feel good
but my name is Taye I'm a partner at
altto ventures we are very excited to
have Makita here with us today such a
pleasure to have you here and to hear
your story so thank you for being here
thank you Tay maybe just a quick
introduction of yourself and Pad do my
name is mik Mikado I'm the CEO and
co-founder of Pand benad do helps dozens
of thousands of companies to streamline
their work with contract quotes
proposals forms get those documents sent
to customers signed electronically
hundreds of thousands of people that use
our product Makita tell us the story of
starting padon it wasn't even called
pandadoc in the beginning when was it
what were your observations why did you
decide to start the company pandadoc is
a step function of web design business
I've run Landing in America some thing
like oh my God it's been such a long
time 22 years ago it started as very
simple tool to address an internal need
transformed into something bigger as we
learned along the way so let's just
start with the very early days actually
even before the 22-year Journey of panda
do you're from Eastern Europe where were
you born what was your upbringing like I
was born and raised in bellarus which is
a small country between Poland and
Russia I always wanted to have an
opportunity to using my passion energy
to try to build something Belarus is a
totalitarian state I want it to be free
I wanted to be able to unleash my energy
maybe my creativity at the age of 19 I
got an opportunity to enroll into a
student Exchange program and I came to
us to flip burgers at Han airport that
was the first place where I landed to do
variety of random jobs I also learned to
design and build website that was my
first small business in America that
small business helped to pay for college
here in the US it also funded with later
became our first software service
company and then kedu wow so much unpack
there you said you wanted to be free was
that something that was unique in your
yearning that even your friends or your
families notice where they were like H
Makita is a little different than most
people in bellarus or was that a common
sentiment in your community I think most
teenagers just want to be free so
therefore it's not unique maybe what was
unique and different is timeline of
circumstances that happen in my life the
people that I met along the way that
helped me to believe that sort of the
sky is the limit anything is possible so
I wouldn't say there's something way
different in my character there are
likely certain things that help me to
make the move give me that energy give
me that to leave at anything's possible
but there's also a lot of luck and a lot
of circumstances LED my path the way it
yeah were some of those examples let's
say when I was 15 years old for a long
time I've been I've been getting really
sick and my mom decided to send me to
Crimea so that I can get exposed to the
Sun and hopefully not be sick anymore a
guy who was her colleague he was an
intern at the place where she worked was
actually going to Crimea she asked
whether I can tag along the guy worked
in it it was his first job he was an
intern he over the course of the month
being there in Crimea became my role
model I loved computers my entire
childhood he pursued me to learn to
coach try to become software engineer
the pitch that worked with me at the
time was like if you get that job you
will be free you can go anywhere and
you'll be in demand and you can get a
job anywhere in the world you can get
out of bellus you won't be dependent on
rules of the country who your parents
are or who your relatives are and and
you were looking to get free I was
looking to get free so that worked that
totally worked how old was this person
he was 19 at that time maybe 20 at that
time something like that I was 15
turning 16 we went to Crimea did you
live together with them yes we were
roommates most importantly like I've
seen a role model who was just like a
few years ahead of me was already able
to pay his own bills and travel and be
free that's what I was looking for so
that was one Turning Point yeah why was
he going there oh just to have a good
time vacation vacation for it was was
total happen stance yeah then I think
the next Turning Point point when I got
a US Visa and was able to come here for
summer it was a mind-blowing experience
which is a wonderful program that
allowed a lot of Eastern European kids
to come to America work for summer and
see what America is all about maybe some
of the propaganda I've seen on like
belus and TV it just has shown a
different side of America not Hollywood
but hardworking and Earnest down to
earth the side of it that I really
really liked do you remember how you
heard of the program
yes it was a big deal in Belarus like
all friends of my friends who I thought
are really cool they all either wanted
to get into the program or have gone
through the program but yeah a lot of
kids participated a lot of people went
to us so yeah I've seen how big America
is compared to Belarus how much
opportunity is here the second pivotal
meeting at the time for me was meeting
my first landlord in America this
Japanese guy he rented his house to
exchange two three students per room we
were all cramped in that place but it
was wonderful time 14 16 hours a day but
somehow we also found time to see the US
the place where we work and have a good
time he was the first guy who said look
if you somehow stay in this country you
will be very successful you will become
a millionaire at the time it all felt
like a bit of a BS cuz I was flipping
burgers and cleaning toilets and I was
making
$725 an hour his whole rationale was
like as long as you work hard as hard as
you do you will be successful in this
country he just kept repeating and
repeating and repeating and at some
point I started believing it I think
that was the second the second kind of
big pivot and he was saying this to
everybody or just to you in a side
conversation to all the exchange
students that did work H 14 16 hours a
day got it so he saw something in some
of the folks there who are like working
really hard maybe he was able to relate
you grow up on a farm he worked really
hard growing up maybe there was
something else but yeah there were a few
folks whom he kept repeating this to who
he helped I remember there were many
many times when he had someone got sick
he took us to a pharmacy or he drove us
to work but he was helping here and
there and yeah that was the only support
system we had coming here so that was
for a full summer yeah that was the
first summer and then the second summer
I came with a goal to transition from an
exchange student to a student through
the summer I made me enough money to pay
for a community college it was $3,500
and I stayed I went to school onah in
Hawaii okay so this is back in Hawaii I
was back in Hawaii I studied for about a
year I learned to actually speak English
versus just read and then I started
building website I connected with a few
of my former classmates from Belarus we
built little software products we put
them online and people started buying
those little things at that point I
thought okay we buil five or 10 of them
what if we build hundreds of them I pack
my things move back to bellus so you go
back to belus you have this initial idea
that was kind of like a side project but
it was working do you remember like how
many sales you made or how many products
you had like what was the scale of that
quote unquote business that gave you the
light bubb of oh this could maybe work
it's a very small business the first
little Adon we built that was back in
Hawaii cost was 10 bucks $9.99 to be per
genius marketers we sold d thousands of
copies of this thing but the peculiar
thing for us at the time was that we
didn't have to do anything for this
thing to sell and generate Revenue prior
to that I built websites it was a
service I was paid on an hourly basis
therefore in order to earn money I had
to put in the time now we built
something and it just sold it crazy was
unbelievable yeah today we live in this
app economy software economy this is not
a novice type of thing but for a kid
from bellarus that doesn't really know
much about business that was a
mindblowing expl we sold thousands of
those copies of the software then we
built another thing and another thing
that was like okay I'm getting a passive
income of $5,000 a month maybe $10,000 a
month that was more than enough to fly
back to belus rante a studio sleep in
that studio and wake up make my bed and
then transform it into an office which
was frequented by my former thean
classmate who we partnered with to build
more of those little software pieces
little addons we were employing some
like 35 people and the business was
generating
$700,000 per year which again is not
much for the us but it was a lot of
money back Ben in Belarus why I decide
to go back to belus to do this rather
than stay in Oahu talent I would be able
to hire engineers in us to do this for
like $220,000 a year those is too
expensive so you rationally thought it
was better to go back to bellarus did
you have any like personal reasons that
you wanted to go back to your home
country at that time primary reason was
I didn't see a path towards building a
software business I had no idea how the
like this whole Adventure ecosystem
operates and works I didn't know Venture
funds exist so in order to build a
software company that sell
online which is amazing yeah I thought I
have to go back try to hire my friends
that's what I did wow what was the best
selling or the most used app in that
initial software like what was the
actual software supposed to do I can
tell you what the first thing did yeah
was the first one it was an extension
for webcon management system exported
data what I mean by webcon management
system imagine something that sits
behind a website and then updates
content y y they just didn't build
something that was needed by a lot of
other web designers or user we created a
little extension little adult it
exported data into CSV format the idea
was on the surface it was not something
incredibly smart kind of like Plumbing
with that CMS system then we created a
bunch of like designs for it so that you
can install a new design into your
website then we created a bunch of
little addons that integrate things like
Twitter that just came out or Facebook
that at the time just came out and yada
y yada we didn't really have an
overnight success or like brilliant idea
little software product that got us rich
fast everything was like a little step
function little stair so there's not
much to Brock about you know it's just
big boring business so you're back in
bellarus 700k Revenue per year 35 people
life is pretty good oh yeah life was
wonderful and what year was this we
started this business in 2007 we
operated it for 3 and A2 years so that's
through the financial crisis anything
that happened there we service very low
end of the market with very cheap
product although we did have Microsoft
as a client wow we got lucky with tell
us about that somebody within Microsoft
bought one of those little extensions
wanted a customization they came to us I
tried my best to present ourselves
something bigger that we really were we
were a 15 people two-bedroom apartment
turned into an office that's what it was
if they knew that they' never do any
business with us yeah we powered part of
microsoft.com did they also pay $9.99 a
month we build them maybe
$10,000 wow so 2010 you have Microsoft
as a client 700k 35 people and then what
happened whenever vendors of that con
management system that would built for
changed something without thinking
things through our software broke our
extensions broke clients thought it's
our fault so we were getting PS in the
middle of the night whenever that
happened that just started to become at
least once in a couple of months we had
that search we had to wake up try to fix
things at the time there was a Blog by
one of the pioneers of software as a
service company called 37 signals which
built software that was Standalone and
had a credit card swipe form and my
co-founder was like oh my God it would
be so wonderful not to be dependent on
anyone just be dependent on ourselves so
that whenever our stuff goes down it's
on US versus it's because of someone
else that never happened because you
know we're hosting AWS now and at the
time that was a good enough idea and we
wanted to build tool pool where user can
swipe their credit card use software
online and we get paid that sounded like
a dream again we had no idea that
software as a service is going to
explode we didn't think we're going to
be able to raise money at any point in
the future we had no idea we're going to
this little thing is going to progress
into padoc is today but we decided to
pursue that path of Independence we got
really really lucky so there's this
existing business though so how did did
you balance this new initiative with was
already generating oh poor we hired a
CEO who's a former client from a highly
profitable business within a year became
a highly unprofitable with a lot of
internal turmoil and conflict at some
point we were bleeding cast this first
business and then we were bleeding cash
in what later became pad do it was a
really stressful time the original team
in this first business which consisted
of our friends former classmates like
folks that we were in trenches with they
were Fed Up the new management our
decision to kind of step aside and start
this new thing they put an ultimatum in
front of us saying like look if you guys
are going to keep the new management
you're not going to fix this thing we're
out when a company is like 35 employees
and your core team like five seven
people exits then the company's done we
ask like okayy do you know how to fix it
they said yes we do we asked whether
they want to run it they said yes we do
we asked whether they want to buy it
they said we have money to buy it and we
asked what if you were to make that
money over the course of next however
many years we settled on a price of
$40,000 for that business wow which is
not much but it was bleeding cash and
those were our friends and they turned
it around and turned this company into
successful operation with at this point
more than 100 employees so it's still
going it's still going yeah it has a
different name but it is still going
this like founding team who we worked
with at the time has done really well
for themselves we're still friends yeah
the story had a happy ending so you
decide to start P roller effectively
sold or hand it off the original
business to your other colleague tell us
about origin of that idea like what did
you see in the market why that specific
problem we had a few ideas running
actually in parallel me and my
co-founder and I got to mention you
asked me what were the pivotal Moment In
the Journey I think pivotal moment was
actually starting to work with my
co-founder we are very different people
but I got really lucky meeting this guy
we met back in University in bellarus
played in the same band he was a drummer
I was base over the Journey of going to
us and coming down he was brightest of
all my friends not just one of those
very smart Engineers but also a very
empathetic person very down to earth and
very leveled very balanced the third
pivotal moment was actually meeting him
and persuading him to go into business
with me he had a great career at a large
company I was able to convince him to to
go into starting a company with me so he
wasn't involved in the first he was oh
he was he started the first company oh
okay so he was already involved he was
part of the 35 yeah the two of you took
the lead of hey we got to try this new
thing we were looking at a bunch of
different ideas some of the ideas were
my ideas some of the ideas were his
ideas there were a few things we were
trying to like tickle with quot troller
which later became Panda do was among
all probably the most feasible to
execute it just made them all sense I'm
on everything we we Tred to pursue we
tried to build Airbnb for Eastern Europe
Airbnb I want to say it was at the time
was launching here okay it was a really
tough business we tried to build a
scheduling system for small businesses
like brick and mortar businesses it was
a good business but Michaela didn't like
the code base there and he just trashed
it was trying to do a project management
system and I trashed that one because at
the time there were just too many other
options felt it's a red ocean type of
market and we shouldn't do that and then
there was a summer I had to go to the US
he had to stay in bellus and and hold a
fortress D got him into sales because he
needed to build sales proposals and he
hated how much time that process take
originally qu troller was his idea and
later I translated into pandadoc we
expanded it Beyond sales proposals into
all kinds of standard bureaucratic
document that we can automate that idea
kind of just kept at it what was the
existing process that he and most people
in this field took take a Boer plate
agreement copy paste back and forth
forever and then send it out never
knowing whether it gets open the
recipient really cares and really spends
time on that on that document that was
the process that preceded creation of
quad roller and some of the pains that
we experienced in that sales process we
Tred to Sol so it was really built for
his own use case and then there must
have been a moment where you and he were
like we should productize this or sell
this to others we were looking for
something to productize from the get
therefore we've been sort of looking
inwards at problems that existed in our
business at the time this was one of the
problems and we were building it as a
product and The Way We Were building it
is it's the wrong way to do things we
know everything we're going to build it
they're going to come and they'll pay us
a lot of money that was wrong we we
spend countless hours arguing about the
colors of the buttons or the where this
tab goes or whatever some nonsense I
remember spending all of our money
draining all of our savings to launch
this thing then see how people that come
to the appication end up paying that was
Soul wrecking but it helped us to learn
that we know nothing about like the the
market the problem the pain points have
to check our egos go talk to the market
go talk to customers tell them their
ideas and their pains and then their
thoughts I think that first failure was
in this particular product was very
impactful very helpful towards building
the the bigger Vision way it was set up
was similar to your prior version where
people could just come in sign up
download get access to it and just start
using with the credit cards it was first
just a free tool and we thought okay the
moment we're going to attach billing to
it people are going to pay us that was
not the case we had okay some like 3,000
premium users only six ended up paying
some like 9 or 18 bucks a month which
considering the money we spent to build
this thing was was nothing how are they
even finding out about this though like
the 3000 do you remember how they even
came myod of different techniques that
were the result of the natural anxiety I
had at the time
Su I was in a constant fear and I was
trying to run different experiments and
get the word out there was this uh
targeted to the Bellis Community or was
it Global from day one it was Global
from the day one in fact we were
building a tool for sales proposals it
wasn't applicable to belus Market in any
way we didn't build it in native
language it was English from the day w
got it and so no real funding yet right
you were self-funding it at that point I
didn't know that funding that it exists
I only later learned that it exists
weend kind of a Meetup that we randomly
read about online and we decided to show
up oh where was it it was in bellarus it
was in men I remember that a bunch of
people told us that what we're working
on is DS um but there were people called
investors at this thing and I was like
oh wow that's how things could work but
it's been at least a year between that
and our first financing when was that
our first financing happened 11 and 1/2
years ago do you remember the moment you
decided that you should raise I presume
there was some inklings of the idea from
meetups like that but then from a
business standpoint you probably wanted
to get to a certain point before tapping
that opportunity we needed the money we
on a Ramen diet for sure I've been
trying to fundraise for at least a year
we're talking like hundreds of
conversations hundreds of leads hundreds
of investors dozens of trips to here or
there because B doesn't have any Venture
scene it all kind of came together I had
a baby on the way I really wanted my
daughter to have a passport of a free
country so I really wanted to make a
move here I really wanted to be able to
start learning the Bay Area and growing
the business here the business was on a
CP to hit break even so all of this
happened sort of at the same time but
first I made a move I had to sell
everything in valo so that the baby can
be born here it was very stressful like
short period of time but there was a
happy ending eight investors chipped in
a little bit which amounted to
$650,000 which at the time I thought
they're crazy you can't even touch it
some piece of software a bunch of kids
in a third world country put together
it's somewhere out there in the cloud it
can break it can be hacked so many
things can go wrong why would they do
this I didn't misrepresent anything but
you tell some facts but then in the back
of your mind my mind was still not
really exposed to everything that's
possible the world of software in
Silicon Valley I was still a belarusan
kid that didn't know much so 650k do you
remember the pre-money post money I do
remember the post money what was it
valuation cap it was 3 and half million
do you remember how big the company was
at that time both from a p&l financial
standpoint as well as Personnel wise we
were making 20 grand a month we were
growing fast and we were a team of I
want to say 10 people at the time maybe
seven people at the time but definitely
less than 20 got it all in bellus still
somewhere outside of barus those were
remote contractor types that were with
the company so it seems like you already
knew that you wanted to build a global
company building business in bellus is
is I don't think it's feasible in the
software or Hightech sphere B is kind of
like Estonia or Israel internal Market
is Tiny there's so much bureaucracy and
so much corruption there was a lot of
talent but there's not much Market
therefore if you want to build a
software business you have to do
something globally so you had that and
then from a employee standpoint there
was some concentration in belus but you
already employing people from outside
how did you manage that because that's a
very intentional decision to have a
remote Workforce even at that stage of a
company well we didn't have money to
rent an office didn't have a know how to
run a payroll again didn't have money
and brand to recruit very tough Talent
so we had to be hacky and figure out how
do we find good people that for whatever
reason ended up being in place where
can't get a full-time job at a great
software company employing full-time and
we found them wow so you moved to San
Francisco where's your co-founder at
this time belus so he stayed yeah is he
still there he moved 2 years after me
okay so he followed suit so you both
come to San Francisco and then share
with us the journey from there so what
is the quote roller journey and then
when does the panda do name come into
play started our first office was
townhouse I rent it in s Francisco okay
pretty much the same as like the way we
started our affer business in bellaro
during the night that's where we flap
during the day that was where we worked
our first sales guy was trying to pursue
customers that that called in that it's
not the baby crying on the background
it's something oh cuz you had a baby
yeah it that was the case the baby was
crying in the background and then we
were sitting in the living room trying
to be the m h or write some code then
that progressed into a small office in
the middle of nowhere then it progressed
into a small office San Francisco one of
those live work Apartments townhouse
then that progressed to a tiny office on
cnie Street then AG Gro so you're
starting to have some center of gravity
in San Francisco was that intentional
you were hiring here and you have a
separate team in bellus and you wanted
this to be the center I read a lot of
dech crunch and um they said that's
where software companies in
retrospective I think that was another
good decision because it put me into
environment where I was able to learn so
much so quickly from so many people that
had experience that I didn't have or had
a Kno how that never exposed to it was
so much easier to surround myself with
people smarter than I am here in the Bay
Area compared to Belarus I stayed here
however we kept hiring people all around
the United States we had American living
in Europe who worked for us we try to
scramble and figure out all kinds of
like hacky Solutions towards Talent as
you're scaling you have a global team
and you've had some very interesting and
tricky situations to navigate Wars are
involved tell us about some of those big
struggles or challenges that you faced
over the years I think the first
struggle is what is I'm supposed to do
in my role it was rough trying to hire
people here in America it was rough
trying to lead people I made so many
mistakes if I was to go back I would do
a lot of things differently what is one
thing you would do differently the
biggest mistake you probably made I
micromanaged so many times yeah you know
what I'd leave you with this too um I
think lack of patience is a lot of
mistakes a lot of challenges came from
maybe at times some Bor headedness I
know like how to do better Clos mindness
there's a lot I got to learn and I have
to learn while doing while keeping an
open mind that helped quite a bit there
are some challenges outside of our
domain our control there was covid which
happened to to everyone but then during
Co there was a revolution in Belarus we
sided with the Democratic side of it a
video that I posted in response to
violence at the government induced on
people got way more Abus than I expected
we had a raid in our office a way to
retaliate the government took four
people hostage the last one was released
after 11 months in prison that was a
really really hard time we had to exit
bellus we survived and the team there
has shown so much resilience how many
people in Bel at the time at the time we
had 220 people in B wow what are you
actually doing to get them out we had to
employ lobbyist here in the US that was
hard that was a process it was really
tough so they leave where did they go
Ukraine we scale operations out of
Ukraine and then the war in Ukraine
breaks out and for another year and a
half we become a migration company which
enables people to migrate to Poland
Portugal then in belus and Ukraine
completely changed our pnl we had to do
a lot of catchup it's been a tough year
and a half but we migrated to over 300
people out of sight of dictators out of
sight of the war how do you balance like
perspectives on life you're running a
software company it's growing well
things are going well and you have all
these people hundreds of employees
contributing to that and you're like
very grateful for their contributions
and then you're also faced with this
situation where you're the leader of
hundreds of people who are going through
a war actually in this case two separate
types of Wars right how do you navigate
that it feels like a very tricky in the
summer of 2020 at the time I was here in
the US and I was for the first time
visiting Yellowstone and as I walk into
a lake into the lake with kids I'm
thinking oh my God life is so wonderful
I am so lucky everything is working out
I'm so happy in my life and that's
changed dramatically with Revolution B
about 2 weeks after that I started doing
therapy but it was a pretty rough time
yes one last question so you recently
crossed 100 million of AR how did that
feel when you noticed that actually
happening it did feel good it was not
something that kind of blew my mind pan
back is a very repeatable and
predictable business so we knew when
we're going to hit that Milestone
there's a brand value of this like 100
million AR there's a brand value of the
Unicorn company but it's a you know it's
a short dopamin head yeah you feel good
but for a much longer period of time is
having a positive impact on people that
surround me I be that customers or
customers try your product and you use
it and they love it and they say thank
you that has a more impact Milestones
Milestones are Milestones they feel good
what's your next big milestone that
you're looking forward to I millions of
people to use our product and I love it
that's what I really really want we've
been at it for like 14 years at this
point with this business and we've built
so much I want more people to use it to
like it there is a recent research we've
done on like how many trees we save
because but door paper list with pad do
and they get to sign electronically or
notorized documents electronically we
discover there like dozens of thousands
of Acres of forest that are saved uh
thanks to that that's cool you know
imagine 10 Xing that that's wonderful
but what it feels even better is
millions of people using the thing and
benefiting from the thing and enjoying
the product that's great thank you
Makita really appreciate it