The most uh profound experience that I
had in my career uh in healthcare and
one that I consider my most important
accomplishment was uh in in my previous
venture to to get more than 25,000 notes
from people saying thank you for saving
my life. I mean the the really like
amazing it was profound. I mean like
it's you know from somebody who's uh who
had dreams as a child as a you know a
computer geek to to build things that
that have some impact to to really get
you know tens of thousands of notes for
people saying thank you for saving my
life is something that uh you know
it's bringing me to tears right now just
to talk about this right I mean it's
it's it's really like I getting I'm
getting goosebumps and and I think that
like the the it's it's just it just it
really is special always do what you
love.
Always do what you love, right? Like,
start by doing what you love. I mean, a
lot of people choose to do things
because they're cool, uh, because
they're going to make a lot of money,
uh, because it's fashionable, uh,
because somebody told them to do that,
because other people are doing that,
right? Like a lot of reasons. Just don't
like go into where your heart is, right?
Like do things that you love. Why?
Because when you do thing that you love,
it doesn't feel like work and you're
going to become a lot more successful
and happier most importantly. It's not
just about success. You want to be happy
in your life. So follow your real
passion and then everything else will
follow like the the money, the fame, the
whatever you want to do when you do
things you love, they will come.
[Music]
Okay. Nice to meet you. Uh my name is
Ron Goodman. and uh co-founder and CEO
of uh Intrivo. We really like at the
beginning of Invo the the vision was to
to bring health and care to you where
you are. Now when the pandemic started
we tried to see where we can apply this
to actually help resolve the pandemic
and then we start solving the challenge
of how do we bring efficient testing to
use. So initially testing if you
remember was a terrible user experience.
We created this technology platform that
enable us to manage the entire supply
chain. And I really would like to be
part of creating a solution like that
that will change the way we manage our
health and well-being in ways that were
just not possible before. And I think AI
has a a great opportunity to be the
foundation for that. And I'm looking
forward to the next chapter of uh you
know how humanity managing not only
health and well-being but happiness as
well because I want more people to smile
a lot more often.
[Music]
The whole idea of helping other people
uh came from home. My mom uh raised me
with the the notion of tikun lam
which is an ancient uh part of Jewish
philosophy and tikunol lam means in
English very simply fixing the world.
What does fixing the world mean? My mom
used to explain that fixing the world is
something that is important for me to
engage in just because the world needs
fixing. It doesn't need to give me
anything. It doesn't need to have a
reason for it. But because things are
not the way they should be and I have
the ability to make a positive influence
with them, I should do it. And think
about it. If everybody thought this way
and pay it forward without even needing
to get anything, our world will look
such a better place. Every single day I
do things that help other people improve
their lives, improve their health and
well-being. Some of these uh really
important lessons that I've learned. Uh
first and foremost was traveling,
traveling around the world. So I I I
love travel. I love meeting people all
over the world. I made it a point to
meet people where they are and go and
stay where they stay, eat where they
eat, travel how they travel, volunteer
as much as I could. And when I did that,
I learned a lot from them and that
helped shape me as an entrepreneur
because when you build solutions that
are global solution, you need to
understand the world. And understanding
the world is not enough to just do
internet research. I believe you need to
meet the people and need to see them
where they are. Understand all people
are people and and all humans are very
much similar but they have nuances and
if you understand these nuances and you
understand different approach approaches
to solving problems it creates for you a
toolkit that is a lot richer when you
tackle some of these challenges to not
just look at it the way all of us look
at a certain thing but find different
angles that may be more applicable for
particular challenges than the tools
that you have in your regular toolkit.
So one uh was definitely travel and and
and I recommend uh people to do that and
particularly meet a lot of people doing
that
[Music]
being in the valley in a time that was
you know post the the dot crash actually
when most people left here and just a
handful of people uh remained that were
very very passionate about building
businesses. And and some of these people
that were very very early in their
career back then are some of the most
successful entrepreneurs of our time
today. But the people who really stayed
here stayed because they were passionate
about building things that actually make
a difference and change the world. and
having long conversations with them, you
know, early early in their career about
how they think about building companies,
how they think about building teams uh
very early uh in the TED community for
example uh the the TED conference before
there was even TED X before there were
like a million conferences before there
was even a website I used to go to to
Mterrey it was like we used to go a
bunch of people from Silicon Valley uh
to to Monterey every year and and it was
a small handful of people that got It
was all the people that started the most
successful companies that you know in
the world right now. It was back then.
And we, you know, we would go and hear
some talks and then at night we'd spend
until 2, three or 4:00 in the morning
just hanging out, chatting, talking
about our challenges, you know, figuring
out what to do. And I think that was
amazingly amazingly important in shaping
how all of us thought about doing
certain things. Just interacting with
one another, working with some of them
that were more accomplished and already
had, you know, some success. Some of
them it was their first time of doing
this but it doesn't matter. The the
sharing was very important. So we did
that at TED. We did it in the early days
of South by Southwest when it was mostly
a music festival that was a tiny little
interactive section to it. There was a
couple hundred people or whatever the
number was back then. And the same thing
we used to go there every year and and
just hang out with each other and and
chat about it.
[Music]
It's really really great to be here and
I I really want to say before I start
talking about that Silicon Valley I
really want to say that this is this is
not a community this is a movement I
mean seriously I want to give a huge
hand to Lara and Salomi like from
everyone like it's it's just
it's unbelievable it's so powerful We're
talking about collaboration. We're
talking about what we how can we
leverage the learning that everyone here
has achieved by putting together these
amazing events in universities, in
cities and everything and exchange this
information, share it together and
talking with Lara about trying to create
a platform that will make it very easy
to disseminate this information on an
ongoing basis. You know, you all put
together programs, you all put together
some software or something that helped
you make a better event. And I I felt
putting together TEDx Silicon Valley
that if we could tap into some of that
or if we can share what we've created
with everyone else, it would be
amazingly powerful. So this is something
that uh I'm very excited to help doing
going forward. Uh and and it's really
really uh important to get together in
these gatherings, right, that are
smaller gatherings with people who are
experiencing the same thing that you're
experiencing and share authentically
what you're going through in these long
midnight, you know, conversations, but
also absorb a lot of uh how they're
solving thing and get inspired by that.
So that was really awesome.
Entrepreneurship
is all about the people. It's all about
you are going to be only as successful
as the people around you. And it's very
important to choose the people that you
don't only think they're the best in
doing what they need to do. And that's
very important as a foundation. Choose
people who have the right skill and
right kind of level of experience to do
what they need to do. but also make sure
that they have the kind of energy right
and the stamina and the kind of
resilience that is required in order to
solve entrepreneurial challenges.
Sometimes uh you know I I chose people
who who actually were great and smart
and capable and had great resumes but
you know they did not have this kind of
dynamic and or this kind of character
that would take them through a lot of
ups and downs which entrepreneurship is
has inevitable huge amount of these
things. So think about how to bring
people, communicate to them. Don't
overcommunicate to them something that
like, oh yes, we're going to everything
is going to be great. We're going to
build a huge company. We're going to
change the world. That's great. Get them
inspired, but also be truthful to them.
Hey, this journey is going to have ups
and downs. There will be some tough
days. You need to think about that. And
here's what's coming up next. Make sure
that they are the right people. Also,
what's important is that they gel with
each other really well. Choose the right
kind of characters that get along with
each other well, that play well in a
team, right? Unless they're a personal
contributor that really wants to needs
to do one very particular thing and
they're excellent at it and doesn't
require collaboration. That's rare, but
that's sometimes important in things
that you're building. The majority of
people work with each other and teamwork
does make the dream work, right? So you
need to figure out how to choose people
that get not only are great people and
are social, but they get along with each
other really really well, right? And and
so that's that's a very very important
thing. And eventually people that really
resonate with the mission. I learned in
my life that it's important to have
missionaries and not mercenaries. Right?
There's some people who are really good
in what they're doing, but they're just
there for the paycheck and they do what
they need to do and they're done. Right?
I think the best way to identify if
somebody truly uh buys into a mission is
to have a deep conversation with them
that is situational. Don't just ask them
to talk in generalities about uh the
mission itself. Like it's everybody can
say, "Oh yeah, yeah, I really want to
help hundreds of millions or billions of
people live a healthier life." I mean
that's a very easy sentence to practice
at home in a job interview and and then
you know site it back. The best way to
tackle this is to ask them how they
practiced this uh this kind of mission,
this kind of uh world, this kind of
living, this kind of philosophy in their
own life in the past, right? So, so to
give you examples, right, of why they
actually resonate with that mission or
how they resonate with that mission, but
things that they did, not just things
that they're thinking about, right?
Right? And even if it's small things,
you know, some people want to help a
billion people and it's, you know, it's
it's daunting for them to even think
about it because they're early in their
career. So what how do you know because
they're early in their career? But
people who really care about these
things do things in their lives that
actually show that they are very very
interested in the mission. So look for
the doers, not just the thinkers.
So every everything that's worth doing
is challenging in my mind, right? I
think that there is a point in life in
which you just embrace challenge, right?
And and one thing that I learned over
the years and I practice right now is,
you know, I don't get too worked up when
things are uh challenging and I don't
get too excited when things are great,
right? I try to just accept the fact
that there's beauty in what we define as
good and pleasurable and nice and and
and you know fulfilling but there's also
beauty in things that are challenging
actually sometime make people sad. I
know that sounds a little bit
controversial but when you understand
that the life is the circular approach
and the whole approach of everything
that's happening to us good and bad and
and when you stop judging them when you
start stop trying to just go to only
figure out how to make things good and
try to avoid the bad because the bad
what we consider as bad or less
favorable will happen. Not strive to
make it happen but accept it. they say,
you know, it's going to be there. It's
fine. And it's it's it's something that
is part of life and we celebrate it. We
celebrate the good. We celebrate the not
so good. It makes us stronger. And I
think that the advice that I give
everybody is to try to get to that place
at least once a day. And then once you
figure out where it is to start applying
it here and there so you can go back to
this clean slate cuz you're going to
make better decisions, you're going to
feel better with yourself and you're
going to have a better, happier life.