we're relaxing today
oh I feel like this video should open
with like a cinematography moment
trust me
like honey what do you mean just trust
me
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
[ __ ]
Jesus Christ Nick your phone vibrating
ruined the whole thing I hate the
internet
try again
[Laughter]
[Music]
they really copyright [ __ ] just force
yeah that sounds insane like we looked
up a non-copyright one but like what you
know what is copyright
and make the same [ __ ]
no one owns that
hey guys
um about four days ago Nick went to
Urgent Care I went yesterday because I
didn't feel good Nick up prescribed
medication I had to do the whole thing
and Nick got an IV and water and all
that job I don't think it's water but
whatever the [ __ ] hydration I think you
just drink it if it was water
anyway go ahead not laughing Matt was
sick today so today we're relaxing
and we didn't really film this week
because obviously we're all ill I still
have a headache I took Tylenol this
morning but today is Tuesday we have to
post tomorrow and we're never ever gonna
miss a Wednesday
I could be on my [ __ ] I hope I die
one week
I really don't hope that oh hold on
oh it's uh hold on it's not recording
yeah you're lying I know no I'm not it's
not recording
okay basically as Chris just said we've
been really stressed out and sick so
we're the video is about relaxing for
General health and mental health
Nick you can't have candy we're trying
to thrive Better Health
defend here
I shouldn't pretend that I'm like
looking because I need her help
so I'm just gonna seem really like
interested need help finding anything
I'm in the car a minute ago yeah I know
I thought you waited in the car too no I
was following you guys in
my legs
it's obviously locked you're gonna have
to call an attendance
Police Department pain and sleep the two
things
[Laughter]
Department
yeah
I don't see it Nick here I don't
actually like wanna
there it is they definitely do
damn that's just expensive as [ __ ] right
like what am I gonna do like like that
little thing is 24. 23 better also end
world hunger
Nick come on dude what do you want
it looks so good like yeah it was not
gonna happen again what she guilted me
into a five dollar donation the other
day
you looked at me today I know that she
knew that it was me again and she asked
me for another thing because the other
day she goes oh can I get you to donate
and I'm all like I'm like uh sure like
like you know like hold on she's like oh
can I get you beeps to focus you [ __ ]
idiot you suck she asked me the other
day to donate and I was like you suck
[ __ ] you she asked me to donate the
other night and I'm like oh yeah sure
and I'm thinking she's gonna be like
round up or like a dollar or something
and she's like can I get you to donate
five dollars and like I'm not gonna be
the guy like no like three years I'm not
gonna demote the note donation like
that's embarrassing so I donated five
dollars the other day and then she saw
me and asked me again it's like what do
you want to [ __ ] run my bank account
down to zero after donating over and
over
ready
I don't know who you think I am I don't
know if I got
[Music]
literally nothing literally it's sensing
cars Casper or spazzing out for no
reason
okay time to open my [ __ ]
amulet price this cost I almost [ __ ]
I'm surprised they didn't make me fight
Captain Hook to get it
if you Google best ways to relax just
stepping away from something
stressful for a few minutes or taking
time away from your normal routine and
thoughts can give you enough space and
distance to feel calmer read a book or a
magazine hold on even if it's only for a
few minutes run yourself a bath watch a
film play with a pet and try out a new
recipe
all right I know exactly what we should
do take a bath together no I was pretty
sure we do
I don't know maybe we popcorn read a
book absolutely I feel like reading is
gonna stress me out more
try a new recipe that's also a little
stressful it's like a daunting task I
don't know daunting that was insane just
slip away from something stressful
I think Nick should just go downstairs
for a little bit
I just stepped away from him bold same
joke just different ways to do it yep
listen to soothing music dude soak in a
warm bath again another recommendation
dude
we're not like can we be realistic we're
not bathing together but if we just got
like big bro just a hot tub like type
[ __ ] okay reduce stress in 10 minutes
and improve your well-being number one
is Be Active or take a dance break let's
do it
I was building building a shelf so yes
sprinkler
well I think I
oh my God
it's terrible I think I want to learn
how to backflip one day let's do it
right now me and Crystal spot you wait I
need your hand no yeah no because it
makes it for momentum right okay go no
because y'all are gonna no we're not
trust or not
okay no no it's not gonna work it would
it was fun
I had a screwdriver in my pocket away
let's try again
see y'all didn't I was up but y'all
didn't get the rotation part down okay
well you're supposed to also work I'm
gonna wig in them
come on if y'all drop me again set
[ __ ] kill you
your legs are gonna hit the ceiling okay
try one more time
hooray uh we finally got to take a bath
together oh my God Nick looks scary no
one of the main relaxing things was like
calm yourself in some nice toasty water
so we decided to come to the hot tub it
was best or get naked in my bath
together and this was a much better
second option
you agree second option yeah
hold on they should have been the first
watch this
oh God don't break your neck please I do
feel very relaxed bad
okay okay swimmer look at him okay all
right I don't know what that was it's
like when you're [ __ ] like
three-year-old little cousin water in my
ear bro yeah like
ugh
you're all right this water in my ear
this is supposed to be relaxing oh yeah
I hope that this video relaxes like not
only us but the nation like Matt come on
what come join I will
I love swimming
what if a coconut came down from a palm
tree that'd be ultimate relax Matt come
play mermaids okay can I shut this off
ew
before I shut this off yeah
brand new gator light
I know but I keep going to add for it
okay bro chill out yeah there's a bunch
of like brainstorming like to do stuff
over here we show over there okay to do
is so funny to me
go this way this way
like you need to go over there dumb [ __ ]
okay put your shirt on Chris oh all
right guys that has been today's video
we are so thankful that you tuned in um
I know it's not like a super like
thrill-seeking entertaining Wednesday
video just because hey we filmed it all
today
we're all low energy and [ __ ] but but
it's just kind of a notice of like we're
sick we're human beings we'll get sick
you guys will get sick and it's just we
all need to relax so everyone should
just take a couple deep breaths this is
your notice to take care of yourself
take care of those around you and treat
yourself with kindness so for real
everybody's gotta take care of
themselves first so I was happy that
we're still able to make a video even
though we're all really feeling pretty
terribly but you know it happens and
we're gonna move forward regardless yep
I know I know we say it every week but
we actually have a lot of stuff we've
been working on so hopefully a lot of
new stuff coming soon
no there's actually so much coming soon
podcast I know I say all the time shut
the [ __ ] up you [ __ ] idiot say that
but it's actually soon don't say that
like why do you say that again
because it's actually soon okay
disregard anything the man to my right
says from here on to the Future
I think he's on your left he's on your
left according to the gun
and then it's Huron
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things