I think I'm gonna kill these two I feel
like they just do nothing but do me
dirty I don't think these actually
produced a lot I don't care just [ __ ]
do it
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
Matt shut the [ __ ] up negative I'm not
negative you're [ __ ] Nicholas Stromboli
new tattoo
Nicholas Stromboli is it insane
I wish that was her last name vote
Nicholas Stromboli ate spaghetti
when he comes around Matt I'm talking
did you hear Matt Nicholas Stromboli ate
pasta
what Nicholas all right guys welcome
back to the sterniola triplet Brothers
YouTube channel and today we're going to
be doing one of these other these car
videos again and today we're going to be
talking about Nick things that
weird habits that that you guys had
something that we had as like little
kids yeah in your ear
you're so cool holy [ __ ] thanks anyways
we're gonna be talking about weird
habits that people have as little kids
is that actually the topic no Nick made
it up you want to know what's a habit
Chris had as a little kid but he still
has now
look at the curse is the type of guy to
be like let's say he loses his phone his
keys his wallet or oh my God I can't
with the complying like just off the
start this isn't a complaint okay I'm
just saying it's something Chris used to
do I'm just waiting patiently to hear
this [ __ ] molasses about to come out
molasses
no Chris is just like the type of guy to
lose something let's say it's his phone
for example oh my God you're the type to
just bore the [ __ ] balls off me so
the topic is weird
habits you had as kids okay I'm getting
literally getting there we'll get there
go ahead dude we gotta lose his phone
and then go hmm if I wear my phone where
would I be
like that's not even funny that's
something Chris would do I've never in
my entire life like he'd be looking for
his shoes like leave those he'll be like
hmm if I wear my shoes where would I be
that's never happened ever they're a big
like retrace your steps guys
but like not just like the position like
the legit I used to just pray exactly
how you are I used to say dear God
please bring back what I've lost back
into my life please
did it work almost never I'd always find
[ __ ] that I oh my God remember when I
lost my air pods yes uncle got his
airpods for Christmas and I lost them
like literally like I think 30 days
after Christmas and my mom was like your
uncle's gonna be pissed to you that you
lost it was like you should you sh
should respectfully like you were out of
respect for getting them as a gift that
you need to re-buy yourself earpods
earbuds what I sound like yeah your
thoughts what are they called airpods I
don't like this I'm like so old air pods
whatever so I went and I bought myself
new ones and then a year later someone
found them in our couch which is crazy
because Mom cleans the couch like every
so I don't think it was our couch it was
our couch was it ours that's the crazy
part there was under me for so long ah
you don't know Nick's the type of guy to
do we're not filming this video Matt
this isn't the video we're filming not
filming thing like oh Matt's the type of
guy to be [ __ ] obnoxious and annoying
and then take eight years to say a
sentence like that's not what it doesn't
Nick just took
Winston I did the first the way you
it's like it's a equivalent to cradling
a baby that just peeled my skin off that
was insane it's the type of guy to when
we're taking a group photo be like now a
goofy one no I'm not and that's not
that's what we're filming I don't know I
don't like saying now a goofy one that's
you that's not true yes it is what are
weird habits as a kid I also another
thing before we get into your guys weird
habits because
um we posted a poll for you guys to
submit yours one of mine that I had was
when I was a kid I used to just like if
I was like feeling super emotional or
like I was upset like I had a nightmare
and I was scared I used to force myself
to get up out of bed go to the bathroom
turn on all the lights and look at
myself in the mirror
that's really weird I remember looking
in the mirror and just being so
Stacy because I just shut it off I
remember being so sad and frustrated and
scared for my dream and I was just
looking at myself in the mirror they're
trying to gather all my thoughts that's
like the weirdest [ __ ] I've ever heard
of myself
it's crazy how it works scary little
kids are
dude I know they could be like oh oh I
was talking to my friend and it's like
you're home alone it's like who are you
talking to this my friend was here like
30 minutes ago if my kid comes out on
weird [ __ ] like just talking like a
weirdo I'm gonna be so absurdly freaked
out like if my kid has like an imaginary
friend I'm literally gonna be terrified
I know or like if they have just like
fond memories of something that just
they should have never heard you know
what I mean like dude it's like the
Ghost Inside My Child everyone should
watch that show literally if you're
starting a triple fan you need to watch
a Ghost Inside My Child it's at least
it's literally insane chaos it's like
little kids that remember no we've
talked about this in a video yes but
it's crazy
kids are there like I was at war in
Arkansas and then they go to like
Arkansas and then they're like oh my God
I feel like I died right there and they
like get dizzy and [ __ ] and then they
look in the news and it's like there was
like legit a war field battle on the
court I can't even believe that [ __ ]
like that's not real crazy but yeah that
was a weird habit I have I remember one
time having a sleepover
we had a mirror that was out like once
you look into the bathroom mirror
there's a mirror on our wall in our
bedroom sorry and it was like how like
if you guys were the mirror I was
looking into there's like a mirror there
that like reflected into our bedroom on
the top bunk and we're having I'm
confused yeah you're having a sleepover
in one of our friends like in the top
bunk and I remember I was in the
bathroom with the door open the lights
on look at myself in the mirror and I
looked in the corner and they were
looking at me from like the top bunk we
were just like looking at each other
I can't tell you that's weird as [ __ ]
yeah really
11. I used to chew on [ __ ] a lot when I
was like grown as well like eight years
old like I shouldn't have actually been
now if Matt and Chris you have anything
to say that's actually fun or
entertaining about your own weird habits
before I get into our fans
um I'm trying to think I used to care I
used to chase Nick a lot
just run around I wouldn't consider that
who chased me into a doorknob one Matt
this girl looks like she just got out of
school and now she's like in the Amazon
truck where's her outfit oh this is the
Amazon lady yeah that's why I said look
at this Amazon like shouldn't she have
like a polo on or something with like
Amazon hair color like a hat a polo I
don't know like a little shirt that says
Amazon she has nothing signifying that
she's an Amazon worker on yeah I thought
she lived here I didn't know she was
chill like that I thought we were like I
was out of her house okay now we're
gonna get into your guys's fan fan what
Matt we're gonna do your guys
literally just yelling
and like tapped his mouth
we asked you guys this question here are
your responses and here's our reactions
and thoughts Nick stop talking like a
robot it's actually my least favorite
thing you've ever done I say it every
time when you talk like a [ __ ] like
it's like I've ever done yes I haven't
done anything worse never in my life
Nick
stop being annoying as [ __ ] you [ __ ]
[ __ ]
what are you gonna do right now like are
you stupid response Nick shut the [ __ ]
up I'll literally go home you're
annoying go home John said every single
time I had to use the bathroom I yelled
I pee now
no matter where I was so probably I'm
guessing is like a sibling or a parent
like imagine Christmas use the bathroom
I was like I need now you come now you
come like demanding their parents on
where to go
you would do yeah if you say it like too
many times fast it sounds kind of like a
a chant like a spell okay you know what
I mean no I don't think it sounds like a
rhythmic spelled chat Nick you just
looked at me like like what
it looked like you saw like something
crazy for a second like the way you
looked and you're like I was just
thinking
all right let's keep going sometimes I
don't think there's anything that like I
can there's a lot you did that was weird
as [ __ ] like what just being yourself
and you're okay
who's the [ __ ] you're just a strange
kid you were weird Matt was weird
really good apple flavored toothpaste
I feel like that's not a habit that's
like why'd your parents even buy you
that [ __ ] because I was like sick that's
not no that's not a habit though
Colgate press as a kid it doesn't matter
it doesn't matter that's not a habit
that's a one and done thing unless
you're eating like she literally said
it's not weird it's like a nasty I ate
the really good yeah but it could be a
habit like if she kept getting an apple
too that's what I'm trying to do but
also don't you doesn't isn't it like you
always eat the thought of eating
toothpaste in any form is really good
it's like I mean you're only supposed to
spit it out to the floor right and stuff
like that that's not true because not
every toothpaste has fluoride most of it
does just a small person okay I'm not
here for the dental records I don't care
sticks of water and hide them under my
pillow
wait I I like actually I don't get it
dude we'll match two separators
that makes no sense I'm gonna [ __ ]
knock your [ __ ] out one day when you
[ __ ] hit myself remember when I used
if you hit butter it's over it's over
it's over it's over it's over move on
yeah no [ __ ] yeah she's to hide it under
her pill it didn't matter she didn't say
what the consistency was the hidden
butter I'm just telling you where it was
at do you remember when I used to get
books and just wander yeah there was
just one night I was sleeping on like a
bunk bed had like um you know like the
bunk beds and they have like the end
no
no move down it's a funny story it had
Like These Bars like this I'd have to
reach my hand Between the Bars and I
would reach Between the Bars and like
steal books off the shelf and put them
under my pillow and my dad came in
because he heard me because making so
much noise he was like why aren't you
going to bed and I had I kid you not
like 80 bucks 80 children's books under
my pillow
wait till the morning it was like you're
in your own home like you can read these
at your own discrepancy at any moment in
surprise you that's like a [ __ ] up is it
not I don't know but it was like you
could read this you could read this at
any [ __ ] time ever and I was like
it's also you weren't reading them yeah
I was never reading books it literally
hurt my neck dude because I we all share
with oh my God we'd always share a bed
and Nick would just like make me hide
[ __ ] under my I remember you had yeah
it's getting so hidden are you still on
a puzzle you know that video the kid
where his mom opens the door and he
literally like pretends that he's not
eating Oreos and you see him like fold
it and tuck it under his pillow like
really fast it's a [ __ ] hilarious I
love I love that video reminds me of
some [ __ ] that you would do as a kid the
mom opens the door and the kid is
clearly has Oreos and he just like puts
it away under his pillow really quick
and like pretends to like fall actually
all in one moment like all in one moment
and they're like did you eat the
leftover like Cherry Slush or something
it could never be me I was like did you
eat like the chocolate ice cream their
shirts like brown like just covering it
and
like the thing of baby powder and he's
just like he looks like a little ghost
I couldn't I couldn't believe recreating
that like someone stupid like a 30 year
old man so gross um dude I saw one Nick
and it was I used to suck on coins like
like little coins
oh that really freaks me out I can taste
it you ever put a bunch of coins in your
pocket and like move them around your
fingers and like you sniff your fingers
they just have like that coiny smell
like metaly oh I don't like it yeah I
don't like it at all this is a little
strange I thought we were getting rid of
the pennies why is he still here I
kissed a worm for a quarter on a dare
pissed a worm no you didn't you like
you're reciting Junie B Jones
way too many children's books I thought
there was way too many children's books
about like worms and dirt and like
sludge and grosses
who just came in hi beautiful
like that wasn't Nick who just said
sludge someone just took over his body
you say it's slow
there's way too many like children's
stories that are like about like frogs
and swamps and dirt toads dude it's
crazy that like a toad is just like in
my eyes a toad is just a filthier frog
someone said I would sleep under my bed
instead of on it
oh my God psychopath that's [ __ ] those
kids are scared of under their bed and
you said you know what I am I'm under
the bed I am underneath it yeah like I
am the underneath of my bed that's the
Judy B Jones [ __ ] kill them well Junie B
Jones books we need a movie about you
Nick gun to your head how many
um how many children's book could you
list
easily ten really do y'all want to know
that why I always laugh at first dude
one of my favorite clips of our videos
ever is when Nick said um Cam Jansen no
um princess and the p
oh my God I love that [ __ ] it was just
so insane I loved Super Why and they
would refer back
frogs have long legs longer than their
head and body which is
not much shorter legs and prefer to
crawl around rather than hops see
they're just a dirtier frog frogs have
smooth songs
who's here
get away
we're not going anywhere buddy
keep it moving away
get away
should I leave no spare me the facts
about frogs because I don't [ __ ] care
at all should we please
I can watch US Film this whole video I
don't give up literally I don't give a
[ __ ] go away we're parked here goodbye
we're good next stop well it's true like
go find another one look they just drove
away good I went like this bite the side
of my cheek one time I do that all the
time still to this day no one time I had
like 30 warheads and like the inside of
my Jeep
goes the score goes I used to suck on
batteries and now I'm diabetic
I don't think
the batteries freaking me out go away
oh my God find somewhere else to be I
don't think it was the battery sucking
why you have diabetes now I fully yeah
I'm right there with you like who's
parent like if dude my kid isn't even
gonna be able to touch batteries no you
never know you can't say it suck it on
batteries though like I feel like I'd be
around my kid enough to know it's gonna
suck on some batteries it could take me
35 seconds to get better but also you're
a grown individually like no no I'm
talking like in a kid can't you just
curious like what's with this like
suckage on the little like weird [ __ ]
like coins and batteries little kids do
like eat and grab and touch I can't
believe parents like give their kids
like keys to fondle oh my God this girl
used to chew her toenails off oh
toenails that's insane you must have
chronic back pain my back hurts when I
[ __ ] let alone bite my toenails off are
you kidding I can't even touch my toes
with my hands and they're right here
yeah oh I could never bite my own let's
reset it I do feel a little bit bad for
the person who's part like driving by
because I don't like this and they drove
away like right away I mean they were
being all like a creeper like they were
being weird like coming back around is
this them we should do a vote of like
which one of us three was the strangest
that's children yeah I feel like we all
had our moments yeah I feel like I'm
definitely not even close to a
stranger's either of you as a kid okay I
used to cry and not go to school so did
I Matt was about 40 times worse than I
was no but I'm talking like preschool
like kids enjoy School in preschool you
get to like go color and make hand
puppets
nothing's going on in preschool what
other puppets would I make
you said a hand puppets you weirdo yeah
um I don't know which one nickel is such
a weird kid dude yeah what was I doing I
keep saying this but like what's the
evidence you were just strange like you
were weird I did stare at myself in the
mirror everything yeah that's like the
weirdest show every time Nick would like
it was almost like I'm settling it with
myself like I was like you can't sleep
let's go figure this out and I just go
and figure out why Nick you said dry off
like once he opened the door like I
remember that like come on I'm being for
real
yes it is
seven six years old Nick would shower
get out and then like open the door and
dry off like naked like I vividly
remember that like when we were like
seven six years old like just swing the
door open to start drying off after a
shower
I'm being honest and you still don't
shower yes I do actually at least you
know see terrible joke you guys always
make these stupid jokes that I like
don't try to shower just as frequently
as you guys it's like it's like not even
funny you're the like kids that would
roll around in the mud and [ __ ] no that
wasn't that Matt was the dirty one Nick
no Matt gave like really just like like
he was the kid that you were just like
oh he got germs
germs he was a German yes Matt was
covered in cooties for sure
oh my God imagine someone goes not
caring when I saw a ghost because of how
normal it became like what [ __ ] are you
and what is going on what are you
talking about not caring when I saw a
ghost because of how normal it became
like girl
I feel like we're being spied on there's
people
when I needed to pee I would just do a
dance
piece of Mario just seen you start
dancing like you just shaking like the
leg crosstalk flip people off all the
times they didn't know what it meant I
love that if a little kid ever went out
to me and flipped me off in a store I'd
be like happy about it yeah I agree I
flipping back off though yeah
sometimes I'll see you we're trying to
scare little kids while their parents
aren't looking in public no I've done
that once like a kid like a mom like I
was like I think I was in high school
and this this mom was like pushing her
kid in the stroller and she was like
shopping and like she turned her back
for a second and I was like like
a little kid I would cry if I was a
little kid literally be traumatized
hold my [ __ ]
they're like in your body with your
hands
what [ __ ] hit the toilet for me I was
never reaching my head I feel like Nick
would do that [ __ ] no I wouldn't oh
our main light source is that
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah