this camera on me for on the bed shut up
what is up guys it's your boy
Christopher it's not gonna work yeah I
told you
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
okay what's up guys it's uh not you it's
like the light like come on yeah back up
get out of my face echo through the
whole room
what's up guys shut up what's up guys
it's Chris ariello here and we're about
to film a YouTube video Vlog because
it's Tuesday and we have a show on no we
have a show Tuesday and we upload every
Wednesday and we literally forgot to
film a video this week so welcome to
charades in
Iowa Iowa
go Iowa I have my first charade what
like me and I have to guess that's why I
know I have my first charade watch out
Nick move I don't care if my dogs are
out I don't want my shoes on the bed I'm
sleeping inside and I don't got socks
off so that's fine two words
yeah
batter up
baseball bat home run Grand Slam out of
the park okay let's count two words
boom he crushed it up five balls
are my feet dirty I don't know
Pop Life
get around
strikeout infield fly there we go
oh my god let's go what a crazy word
choice two words
stripper
purple team
but it's not purple to you no what what
um waiter
um
yes I love the accessory thank you
necessary your turn I am a good one but
I can't go on the internet so I'm mad
don't do it two words okay
oh
bank robbery yeah good job
he hurt my legs so bad hey roll over
okay
I don't know why I immediately think to
do like aggressive things I know that
was crazy
um
y'all are weird
two words
who's y'all the camera I didn't know my
feet right now
two words
ceiling fan
explosion
um kaboom
plane crash fireworks fireworks
[Music]
sneak attack
alien
abduction aliens battle
alien is that the first word
is that the first word alien attack
Alien War alien battle the alien do the
second word we have the first one
I saw him win the fight and put the flag
in the thing claiming our territory
um alien landing alien fight battle
I don't know dude
the alien attack alien takeover
alien takeover
two words
oh oh bloody murder
homicide
stab
is the second word okay brutal stabbing
yeah that's a true Savage
brutal I don't know I guess
that's pretty brutal one word
Hi how are ya oh nice to meet you oh
this is my milk my orange oh waiter
a waiter cleaning out the fridge that's
one word
oh oh he's bartender yes yes
one word one word
hi
welcome oh
you're good
massage chiropractor
hi goofy [ __ ] how many words well sassy
girl
fake [ __ ]
oh fake people
fake pinch
oh
um oh
rude people
angry people L.A people
classic influencer
oh Skippy skip skip oh gross get out of
your fake friend yes there we go
there you go nice I feel like I said
that
goofy [ __ ]
whoa whoa whoa
boy oh oh getting [ __ ] up
he's playing two characters whoa hey
whoa superpowers
11 Crusader thanks yeah good job wow
um
um I'm trying to think about blinking
two words
okay
[Laughter]
whoa
what
eight words oh my God hi
love
team orange they're gonna win
four whoa oh oh it's an old lady whoa
she's opening the door oh no she's
pushing him out of the way oh heavy
heavy heavy heavy bag you're putting it
down you're an old person
you're a strong person you're a sassy
you oh you and
whoever sent the heavy bag
for the bag
two words you
you and me
friends
yeah
[Music]
the annoying English teacher the front
desk lady
oh through the back
what is that full Carry oh oh carrying
your stuff doordash delivery
[Music]
you're up next with priority delivery
we're gonna restart okay we're gonna go
one word at a time okay okay first word
out of eight feet
Smiles right Buck front teeth front two
wide Gap Gap wide hole big hole small
hole two fingers field goal square
SpongeBob SpongeBob is the first word
awesome what was the [ __ ] oh buck
teeth okay all right SpongeBob
and plus Sun Drop and Patrick no
SpongeBob and Squidward and Squidward
is Squidward
traveling
oh Krusty Krab pizza is the pizza for
you and me
SpongeBob and Squidward delivering the
pizza delivering the Krusty Krab Pizza
yes
oh oh dimming the lights interrogation
entire gator
interrogate therapist there you go it's
Unison great work that should be bonus
points
you know how they're always like mad
extra like the lights and all that [ __ ]
oh I was the only one that did that [ __ ]
four words
hiding hiding from your enemy
um
sneaking
quickly hiding
sneak attack brutal sneak attack
watching your prey from the corner speak
attack murderer
sneak attack serial killer
zero and killer sneak attack there it is
serial killer sneak attack
yes
three words
oh LeBron James oh
um three oh oh Gordon Hayward
breaking your leg
breaking your foot breaking your bone
breaking your tibia breaking your Libya
breaking your leg bones in basketball oh
my God
breaking your bones
oh he's a broken bone game time
crunch time what Nick
what's that bone breaking
bone
basketball first word [ __ ] a
first word snap snapping ripping
breaking ripping tearing tearing your
ACL yes
three words
Mama's fancy meat oh he got the whole
way Mama's fancy meatloaf why why would
it be Mama's fancy keep going I'm just
guessing
those spooky ghost stories Halloween
time well the Happy Ghost The Friendly
Casper the Friendly Ghost
let's go four words
whatever I didn't even see you get that
sheet prepared
chicken monkey ow
we're gonna wake up the neighbors
chimpanzee attack
monkey fight monkey attack
the first one
second word attack
gorilla monkey
angry monkey
ferocious monkeys
enraged monkey
vicious
monkey
sporadic
dangerous there it is
thank you everybody all right I liked it
that was my performance a dangerous
monkey with that being said I think
that's enough charades for now I enjoyed
filming that and I had fun so we could
do it again if you asked one I would
love to play some more okay we'll figure
it out but I think that's gonna be it
for today's video three words
see you Friday two words subscribe now
curious monkey
[Laughter]
five words five words go follow me on
Instagram that was crazy
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things