hey guys happy Friday welcome back to
this journey little triplet YouTube
channel today it's just me and Matt and
where are we we're in Chris's room which
barely ever gets
vlogged yeah and Chris doesn't know
we're in his room um for those of you
that don't know we are going on tour wo
starting at the end of March yeah Nick
I'm going to you in the face cuz you're
screaming right in my goddamn ear canal
Chris's took a week away to film tour
surprises but which is going to be so
fun and amazing and if you haven't
bought tickets to the tickets are in the
in the description you should go buy
tickets because we're going to put on an
amazing show and it's going to be so fun
to see what Chris was doing while we
were doing this so that's all happening
whatever and we decided Well I decided
that we have done the surprise Barn for
Nick we've done the surprise mariachi
band I said we got to surprise Chris
with something it was too last minute to
do anything super crazy but I bought a
thousand balloons on off Amazon and
we're going to fill them up and put them
all over his room yeah I already started
on the bathroom yesterday so let's put
let's get a clip of that in there whole
shower is full and the entire behind the
door is full but you can't really tell
Chris's room literally smells horribly
like it reeks of like latex balloons so
that's the only thing I feel bad for
that's going to be that's going to be
much more annoying than yeah he's just
going to have to light some candles and
whatnot yeah for Breeze it out but look
at this little alien mat got is it's
like a little cute little balloon blower
and this is where the air comes out this
is where the air goes in and it's like
it's loud and annoying but you just go
wait what are you
doing it's
amazing yeah we have so many to do and
I'm using this balloon tire because I've
didn't yesterday when I did the ones in
the bathroom and skin is falling off
with my finger
[Music]
if you guys did this to me I'd be so mad
really if you guys filled any of my
spaces with balloons I'd be so mad why
cuz I
just it seems really invasive
I'd be fine with
it got to take us three
Ms
literally your room would already be
full ofall oh I'm going to go grab the
mail real quick you are going to be
surprise your own
to wow guys how' you do that
PA
[Music]
all right Matt is picking up Chris from
the airport it's my job to stand in
Chris's room I'm
nervous it's my job to stand in Chris's
room record until he walks in and I
don't know if he's going to come in and
go right into his room I don't know if
he's going to go upstairs and linger for
a while so I'm literally just going to
stand in there recording the door for
maybe 20
minutes do we think I should shut the
light off I'm kind of scared to walk
over
there balloons in there oh my godell
like balloons are you dead
serious
yes no way I literally just said to mat
it smells like balloons in here I
literally I thought I was going to see a
clown in my room you did no th balloons
are you
guys it's a party watch out no no be
careful come
on oh my oh
oh Nick this is such a good surprise I
love
surprises Chris Chris Chris Chris our
neighbors wait this is
awesome yeah I hope you love it you guys
are crazy this took us a long time hi
memo it's only it's
1,300 oh my God open your bathroom door
no way are you
serious what's in here oh my God wa what
yeah shower yeah you're not showering
tonight are you kidding me guys
you're going to have to go to bed a
little
gross oh my God 1,000 balloons what a
good video to promote the surprise party
tour right wow dude I feel like you Nick
I is like really I was tell I was
telling Nick while we were doing this I
was like it's so funny cuz I'm the only
triplet that hasn't we have to get mad
no I know I'm thinking like a bunch of M
an elephant what elepant I'm down for
either both at the same time what did
you say Chris um I said male strippers
like firefighters oh fire fire yeah dude
it literally looks like a dream
like I literally thought like faded when
I hey what's up it's Chris and I just
got punked by the balloon Brothers
you're so weird uh balloon
montage or what sexy balloon Montage
want them to pop I'm going to jump in
that area ready come on guys yeah Matt
do
it Matt Matt you actually need to
stop my brother's dead Chris Chris Chris
guys our neighbors to see my our
neighbors are going to gen guys listen
to me the pops are very loud you need to
not pop balloons
Chris I'm so dead serious I'm so dead
guys chill please chill become Electro
all the static be careful the static
kept your light off and moved like your
PC and stuff we were afraid of like
causing Electric Shot just cut my
backw you quick Sam like B Vlog I yeah I
amly oh w oh my God no wait wait where
is he I'm going to go find him
st stop oh my God this is so fun I'm com
I'm
com that you got me this is so much fun
balloon killer this would be sick and
then he like has a knife and then he's
just
like it's so funny cuz you can see
where oh my God
[Music]
while I was standing behind Nick and he
was setting up the camera I think you
have slight scoliosis and I'm sorry that
I'm the one to break that news to you I
don't have scoliosis I literally saw a
part of your spine on the left side of
your neck it's cuz I'm like looking what
does that even mean like I felt spine
thing here that's not no cuz I'm trying
to set up the camera his spine was there
his I'm trying to set up
the camera I'm like dodging and ducking
like there's someone shooting at me I'm
like this trying to figure out where the
camera goes don't touch my neck well I
to feel you feel I don't have scoliosis
I know I don't watch can you
watch I'm
justr
looken that's like a he was like I look
like a grenade looking in the mirror I
look like a
grenade grenade is so funny to me like
cuz no one really uses the word grenade
like ever this made me laugh this made
me laugh it's so stupid but it's really
funny I'm
sure it's just like the burger has like
a really big piece of the sa Burger
thing s bger
ask me pound what the
[Music]
toming dude what
sh that's a good one up here what are
you going to do I feel it oh you're
sneaking on me what are you doing I'm
not sneaking on you yeah you are what
are you guys doing I'm getting a goddamn
piece of
cheesecake hurry up chees act I'm
sneaking around I live here
dude what are you
doing Nick you are so funny you're the
funniest person I've ever met in my
whole life oh I love that every day I
wake up I get to just laugh at Nick you
just like lighten up my day like I was
just gone for like a week and now I'm
back and I'm already laughing with you
and yeah it's a dream it's awesome it
really is you just you brighten up my
days Nick's been aggravating me every
single day I'm with him he's been going
up to me and he's every single time we
out to eat we go out to eat he just
records me and takes pictures of me yeah
I know every single
time ain't touching yes Matt grab
my nothing Matt grab my nipple let's see
another stupid video this one's actually
really funny cuz I Nick just likes those
like this one Nick just likes the like
crazy random videos
ready what's going on you're working
summer camp and it starts raining
hamburgers on a random Tuesday wow I've
had this exact dream
before look at everyone like running to
the hamburgers
[Laughter]
wow oh my God
wait I can actually see like the pieces
of after the Saturn Burger
talk what is going on with you tomato
natives are flying down on summer camp
it's just like what summer camp ever
requires a helicopter but it's just like
it's a dream tasteful patties it's so
funny
oh it's so funny it's so funny see what
this
does it
is um we're going to see what this does
we're
just I don't know if it's a firework
or scen is turning white
literally mildly what happened to us
that one time die I know that was
unbelievable is that is that my fault no
it was my fault I did it I put a lighter
in a fire pit once and a very similar
situation happened except luckily the
fire was surrounded by like stones so it
didn't it went up do you remember I was
standing right there and I was just in
the plan dude it was actually crazy you
I remember I was the only and I was like
you guys need to get down I was
literally I remember I
remember do you remember what I started
running to the water I no I listened and
I hear like like there was like the Tiss
of like the fire like like it really
about to like blow I was like I got to
get out of here so I turn around and I
start running toward the water and it
blew up and it like came around me like
an action movie and I saw it and I was
like
I swear to God I was standing on the
fire pit above the fire and I remember I
was standing there and it was just like
my eyes were open and I was just all I
could see was orange and I was just in
the fire yeah like I was in it yeah that
was so crazy amazing it was such
a good memory as I landed back in LA
today I was away filming a secret tour
surprise and speaking of tour surprises
our four tickets are available today
they go live right now wrong they were
Live 2 hours ago oh they're they're live
today so go if you haven't yet go get
tickets to CS we're going to put a list
right here of all of our dates and where
we're they're on the website go to the
go to the webite we should just put our
poster up okay yeah yeah yeah so you
guys know if we're coming to a city near
you we fully really think you should
come for our show it's going to be
amazing it's going to be it's going to
be like nothing you've ever seen the
stola triplets do ever before
it's incomparable to the vers tour it's
incomparable to the let's trip tour
completely different experience we are
so excited I'm so excited it be great to
see all you guys in person again I hope
I see some familiar faces I'm looking
forward to like seeing some people and
just being like I know youh yes we we're
doing seated venues this time around
it's going to be a lot more chill like I
know a lot of you guys like last two
tours were standing in a mosh pit of
people and we're like amount of people I
had to help that passed out in the crowd
great well I didn't help I didn't do
it's just like I had to we should
never have to have people passing out at
our show we want it to be a comfortable
environment we're going to be sitting
chill we should all be chill yeah it's
going to just be an exciting hour long
like a mosh pit is sick if I'm like
running out like rapping and but we
go out and tell jokes so it's like we
want people to be able to sit down and
enjoy the show I want you to sit down
and laugh with us you know what me that
would be the best thing hear some
stories it'll be fun oh yeah we don't
want to say too much cuz we don't
obviously we've been keeping secrets
from each other for literally half of a
year don't say that we I'm dead serious
the first surprise I filmed was in
November December January February March
April is when we're on tour like almost
half a year we've been hiding these
secret from each other we have so much
unreleased content that has never been
and guys that's why it's been a little
difficult lately that's why this video
might be a little bit shorter we've been
prepping for this it's a big moment it's
a big step in our career talk about like
not having you have no you have an
eyelash so maybe do that or say hey Nick
there's something said I'm
blowing in my face like a freak also
there's glasses on my face so your your
hair is not it's right on your nose okay
is it gone yeah okay I was going to say
are you actually like kidding me
no just like are you actually
like kidding me it hurt I don't know why
you do that remember the knife game I
love that game that was such an I'll do
it right now no no no no no nope Chris
what literally
[Applause]
ass you are so bad at this give me this
good you're doing it wrong hold on hold
[Applause]
on if I do that with a real knife
I'm to I'm
[Applause]
get on
get wow I'm
[Applause]
hey do you remember when that kid threw
a brick at me yeah and no no
repercussions at all brick to my face
yeah that was crazy no you didn't
actually hit me in the face with the bre
and the crazy thing is Matt do you want
know what's even crazier EX
exact same school year not a break K
with the coffee the kid with the coffee
kicks a coffee no some girl put her
coffee down and this kid is seriously a
dumb genuinely honest to God a
dumb I I saying I am saying it I'm
keeping it in don't care if they know
exactly who they are I'm talking with
them that girl is a dumb and she
told her friend if you can't I dare you
to kick that coffee
cup and what did the idiot boy do he
kicked the coffee
as I was walking by yep so I
turn covered in copy were blasted with
like what you say said how old are you
this is so lit first words out of my
mouth how old are you and he was like
uh I'm like why are you first of all at
a high school and second of all acting
like you're seven years old so
good so good I was this close to a
physical alteration I know this close
remember when our friend you know the
thing where you pop the water bottle cap
remember when he did it off the back of
my ear people are so stupid and
I fully one of my one of our friends
sent me a old high school memory of me
like jumping down six stairs and I like
look like I'm trying to be like cool and
it's like the worst video you'll ever
see let see I think I have
like you see me like load up and then I
run we need to put that we need to put
that in the video no it's your like
joggers going like into your boots can I
see it more look disproportion you look
really small not going in the
video it's actually like I have like I
look like a little grimy kid and all I
do is like jump down a flight of stairs
and I think it's like the coolest that
could be a full video as us reacting to
high school memories also sorry that
this video is pretty mid we were
planning on filming yesterday but
Chris's flight got delayed and he didn't
get here until today this is actually in
High scho We were supposed to film
yesterday but we ran out of time it's
literally this video comes out in less
than 12 hours from the point that we're
filming right now so we are aware that
this is not a good video no do you want
to know the worst photo of we ever look
no cuz listen to me right now do you
want to know the worst photo of me ever
in existence the worst photo of me ever
in existence I swear to you I swear to
you we we went to wa what we went to an
escape room mhm
with and the girl comes in after we're
done she said do you want to take a
photo like in the escape room and I was
like yeah sure and she took a photo of
us on our friends worst picture of me
ever do you have it yes see wait to we
cop just you maybe oh my God here it
is it's that bad just let me see if no
no show us oh my God I actually might
have to text you cuz I can't show you
Nick show us the phone no I I might
seriously they just text what do you
mean text like I can't turn my phone
around Nick let us see it texting it is
worse we have to keep it forever just
show us oh my God hold
on no Nick wow Nick wow Nick Nick Nick
it's it's 5x it's five Nick okay I hate
to agree when someone thinks they look
bad but you look terrible that's
the worst photo of me I've ever seen
that's really bad I don't think I ever
actually looked like
that never did keep going you never
looked never looked anything like that
it looks like you have like a
bulletproof
vest shirt your eye kind of looks like
wonky like can slow down the
oh my God easily the worst picture
and like you're leaning on the well like
in the background it's like terrible I
hate to do this easily the worst picture
of me ever guys I'm so happy to be back
it's good to it's good to all be back
wait a second Nick oh my God expect
someone to come stop D what are you
saying oh my God someone's here it's
that he's at the door it's LeBron James
hit the rolly St with the rol all right
guys thank you so much for watching this
Friday's
video see you guys on the internet next
Friday see you guys in person in April
and in March and and April yes so
exciting tickets tickets are live now
first link in the description will lead
you to all the shows go click and come
see us at a show near you you won't
regret it it's going to be our best show
ever guaranteed I will confir say that
most time put into it most effort most
money most Drive we're investing in
ourselves we're investing in this tour
and it's going to be one of the best
live shows that us three have ever put
on ever easily incomparable to the last
two that's it
[Music]