go Ahad Matt show the viewers what you
decided to do I've truly NE like I
didn't like him that much but I've truly
never been this hurt in my life I just
threw this gingerbread at Matt and it
hit him literally square square on the
Dick literally didn't throw and Matt
literally slit him open stabbed it and
drained it for everything it had correct
my heart is
broken I think this is what we should do
today
all right guys welcome back to the St
Yellow tripet YouTube channel the worst
YouTube the worst YouTubers ever stop
handing out like a freaking packet
yo that's that kid made such a good
point he really did today for our
YouTube channel I'm
hungry [ __ ] saw that are you okay
yeah rainstorm
Thunder we are literally 2y
olds I am hungry so for today's dinner I
want to cook dinner for today's video I
want to cook dinner sorry today's dinner
I want to cook dinner which basically
means are you guys okay with this which
basically means hello are you okay with
it Matt you're down to make can I make a
joke like I was going to make a joke go
ahead go ahead no now it's like insane
go ahead the joke make the joke I was
going to say okay so that basically
means I'm delaying a door Dash by an
hour and a half but sure we want to call
it Chris making dinner we can do that
too God you're so good me Matt and Nick
are about to start a new series called
is it cookbook what's the
what's yeah let Nick take care is it a
cook finally cooking dinner if you guys
don't know M Matt and Chris live in LA
and it's just us three in this house we
have no other roommates we don't live
with parents we don't live with anyone
else so our number one question whenever
we're talking to someone is literally
actually and I don't know why I say
number one question but it dead ass is
is like oh do you guys cook like what do
you guys cook how what do you guys eat
everyone asks us and we tell them we
live just the three of us and the answer
is always we order pretty much every
single [ __ ] yeah we eat like [ __ ]
literal slob Piggies like Monsters no I
feel stupid saying this now because
we're about we're about to cook
something like equally kind of unhealthy
no it doesn't matter as long as it's
like it's also not about health cuz we
don't really care it's more about so
this is what's happening new series
series called finally cooking dinner and
each time we are going to cook a
different meal and at the end we are
going to say whether or not that shit's
hit in the cookbook fire all right
[ __ ] my recipe today wait I
have a story I want to tell Matt I was
going to wait for a car video but should
we tell him right now remember yes I
vividly remember you tell them I'm
really scared Chris got in his ma his
first minor little scuffle with the car
oh my God and you weren't there um we
were at Target back home in Boston and
he home yeah he was driving mom's car it
wasn't your car and he was pulling up to
the Target and it was like Target
parking only on a sign and he was big
cement wall yeah he was like Nick should
I just park there and I'm like yeah like
along the building like it said Target
parking only and it was like an arrow of
like all these parking spots all against
like a cement wall Chris is driving and
he goes Nick should I park there I go
yeah he goes right here right I'm like
yep and he's driving in and he goes how
how close what did you say that close to
the wall after after he drives and he
drives into the [ __ ] wall like I both
of us go like this and he the front of
the car hits the wall and he goes am I
that close to the wall I go the wall you
just [ __ ] hit with the car yeah
you're that close to it you're actually
you're actually making contact with the
with the wall by the way God he
literally is looking both of us go like
this right he hits the gas and we both
go and then he goes am I no no you're
haming it up okay okay I am we both go
like Lally no no no one jolted anything
it was we both moved wrong I was driving
and I heard like the thump and I was
like he heard it he didn't I didn't no I
swear to God I was moving so slow it's
like if I go like this and touch that
Pepsi can I just touched it but no like
Major Impact happened it was and I
literally didn't even realize I hit it
cuz I didn't move or anything I go am I
really that close to the wall like I
couldn't yeah the wall you just hit yeah
put in Reverse reverse like 2 in and
look at the front of the car and was
totally fine today's meal for the first
ever finally cooking dinner episode I am
making pizza pockets which is like holy
[ __ ] yeah like are we de serious we're
eating little pepperoni calzones for
dinner czone or pizza pocket it's a
pizza it's like a Hot Pocket but
homemade it's like my pizza pocket it's
like how embarrassing that this is the
first thing we're trying it's not
embarrassing it's really embarrassing
it's a pocket pizza pizza pocket it's
pocket a pizza pizza pocket it's so fire
wait that is what we're calling it if it
gets cookbook status pocket pocket
pizza pizza pocket pocket Pizza it
basically is a little pepperoni pizza in
like a breaded like um croissant roll
that inflates and it's like a little
pizza
poet a pepperoni pizza pocket I'm lying
by saying we've never made it before I
have made we made it once before but
Nick didn't really try it no it's like I
swear to God takes me like my body wakes
up in different increments right first
is my physical body second is my eyes
third is my brain right and then like
12th on the list is my taste buds the if
I'm eating anything for the first hour
of my day it's not getting tasted it's
getting consumed literally just getting
dropped into my mouth there was no like
it's not an experience right like if I
like it takes a lot like the other day I
was telling Chris I literally woke woke
up with such bad allergies and so
delirious I literally the first time I
felt awake I was already in the shower
with my hair wet I'm like I'm I'm awake
but the wa the first feeling of
awakeness was halfway through my shower
recently trying to fall asleep I'm like
waking up at least three times in full
Panic before I'm fully out that means
you're stressed yeah probably cuz I live
with you honestly I don't cause any
stress to your life you cause stress
your own speak of those gray hairs you
know guys I truthfully wish that this
was like a more difficult to cook so
that way we could like you know I was
about to say you made these the other
day and I was impressed looking at the
ingredients on the table I'm not that
impressed anymore should you see how
high I could get my foot in the air you
did this last time no no no I got over
to the table I think I can get it to
like I'll I'll give you
increments oh wow this is
good get there get there yeah that's
impossible
ah what if I grabbed your leg flipped
you that would hurt I probably would do
a back just like pop my ham
spring all right Matt roll this out the
whole thing whole thing I want to roll
it out I love rolling it
out all right like what the [ __ ] this is
so boring okay Nick crack this egg into
a bowl crack the [ __ ] egg in the bowl
and shut your mouth yes sir bake the
oven to
425° okay can you beat this egg I'll
beat that
egg eat it the fork what the fork what
the
fork I also need the egg equal pieces
spreader one line straight down
horizontally to
start okay all right Nick dude I've
never seen an egg that color I hate it
it's kind of like yellowy that's kind of
impress kind like
Flemish I like how you beat that
thing all right Nick you're good good
you're good you're good Nick you're good
now you add a healthy amount of Italian
herb seasoning what's a healthy oh
[ __ ] [ __ ] now you have to rinse that
off okay Chris is that good yeah now two
more lines down that way so far there's
like a lot of what goo I hate the goo
all right goo goo this is actually a
really good recipe you can cook at home
can you [ __ ] off look at the camera no
I'm not doing that not [ __ ] psycho
now mix that INX right you said a
healthy amount that's barely [ __ ] holy
[ __ ] Nick you're Nick that noise is
going to but off slices ow it's going to
drive everyone off this video stop yeah
you're literally it's here how much
money did it suck this for
nickop tell me to suck things for
money that's not a reoccurring thing I
do I don't think I've ever told you to
suck things for money you freak freaky
freak can you IM me for you need to you
need a clean fork for the cooking yeah
look go get
it there we go good boy easiest task on
Earth okay get a spoon next and get a
plate giving fake instructions like
you're like get a fork and then a spoon
and then a plate like just like what's
serious Matt take one of those put on
this nice work [ __ ] work I did crazy
put like seven what no like at least
five the more the pep the the better all
well you guys don't understand what you
have to do though so then let's my best
friends 1 2 3 4 oh you're my best friend
get off of me I've never had somebody
put their armor on my shoulder like that
and then drag me to the floor like this
nobody nobody give me some leeway where
do you put the sauce on the pepperoni
I'll teach you guys how to make one and
then you all have to follow my lead you
oh get that spoon out of there why my
God why my God shake that off shake that
off shake it I was going to stir it I
was going to stir it that's good Nick
you're freaking everyone
out I'm probably turning some people
[Laughter]
on put the [ __ ] sauce down put down
the sauce but I never put down the
sauce okay much better you take a scoop
of the sauce I hate looking at sauce
like that one spoonful is enough y
you're really specific about this and
you bring it all the way across as far
as you can you take your fork and you
seal you Fork it you seal the deal yeah
you essentially Fork it you Fork the
[ __ ] out of that thing so then you push
down all the sides like this then dip
that a little brush that on there I hate
that you can get every little Edge you
want to Edge
it this lotion is nuts dude you have
done that jerking Motion in like three
different videos have I yes and then
then you're done and then you just put
it in the oven
yay and then you're done and then uh uh
yeah I think freak I think I by the time
you guys are done arguing over here I'll
have [ __ ] all the pizza pockets done
no save me a pocket these are so easy to
cook at
home Chris get out of here you're not
getting any like sponsorship right all
right time to cheese it up oh have you
seen oh I forgot to put cheese in
mine well now you're having a terrible
one try to peel it open dude I suck I
didn't give you anything Chris yeah you
did you cut the [ __ ] pastry [ __ ] no
wonder this you cut the [ __ ] pastry
[ __ ] did you just sneak a little
pepperoni yeah I didn't know where El to
put it so you ate it yep I have like so
many questions Nick I like a k of
questions you know that some
um do you think that pepperoni would
taste good if I [ __ ] what do you
think the hardest part of being a gay
person is not to get like deep and
emotional I'm just genuinely curious
like what do you think the hardest thing
about simply just coming to terms with
that oh wow so just like being okay that
you're a gay person is the hardest thing
a gay person can deal with I think it's
like the most challenging step and then
everything from there is just like you
it's barbecue chicken from
there it's barbecue chicken from there
yeah no the hardest part is definitely
coming to terms with and the rest of it
is just challenges that a normal
person's facing in their life I love
that answer that was really good all
right guys we are about to put these
pizza pockets in the oven and we're
going to talk and eat them and rate and
all the fun stuff when we're done yes
Matt you're doing a good job you did a
good little transition
there what is happening
[Music]
why is that making so much noise okay
which ones are whose these two which
which ones are whose who are you are you
[ __ ] stupid you're in my [ __ ] are
you a [ __ ]
stupid he is stupid yeah I can confirm
it holy [ __ ] just walked right into you
and
like you're like glasses do M yeah like
you lit [ __ ] me up pizza
pocket it's so
M so funny your guys tast is
automatically going pizza pocket oozing
with
sauce all right grab grab the pocket
you're most proud of and get ready to
take a bite they're all kind of
burnt little crispy but that's fine a
Chris what you burnt them [ __ ] are you
talking about oh Chris you burnt them we
did this we should make a rating of
light the oven of like five things right
presentation look ability like is it
disgusting Health flavor and taste
Health this is probably ease and ease at
cooking out of 10
yeah obviously poor health is really
easy to make not healthy for you I mean
looks all right looks okay if you didn't
burn it what is healthy nowadays nothing
celery that's about it like I'll eat
whatever the [ __ ] I want until I'm dead
take a bite oh wow is it hot on the
inside hot on the inside than the
outside it's
deep it has a really nice crunch M it is
good it it's definitely pretty good it's
good it is good like to
me so hot not to get crazy
but like oh God if I was at like a
restaurant on the 4th of July after a
baseball game and I go and I ordered
Caesar salad in Pepperoni Pockets and I
got this in a Caesar salad like and a
and a coke that's a good knif I feel
like this is like I always say Coke cuz
that's more pizza parlor Vibes that's
the only time I will take Coke over
Pepsi this is like this is like this
seems good like the addition to
something like this isn't a meal Caesar
salad in the 4th of July yeah like this
I could have like a like a
I don't think this is going on the menu
let me be the first to say because it's
a snack but we need you can have snacks
in the [ __ ] cookbook dumb ass okay
this can go as like an appetizer but
it's not going to be it can be a snack
it's not going to be the main core suure
salad Coke in a game of
baseball I I don't care about baseball
yes but how much more would you enjoy
this if you
watching did you just see that did it
squirt on you did it did it not it's not
on my face what burnt Nick legit reacted
like he ate it and [ __ ] bullets that
literally just like burnt my skin like
bad you literally reacted like it was
like a [ __ ] it literally lit me on
fire it literally lit me on
fire it bur so much Loose Hair on my
body I'm falling there's like hair
hanging off your
head are you dead [ __ ] no like two
there like two hairs so much Loose Hair
like as if I'm just like [ __ ] sh but
it happens all the time that's what I'm
saying yeah why aren we
wait mine's not hot mine
literally it feels like I put lava in a
[ __ ] you can see the pepperoni and
you can see the sauce in there like it's
good obviously imagine we put it in
there dude I I would order a six count
of pizza pockets at a restaurant I would
would you leave it on your lip or would
you wipe it off
make you kiss me and suck it
off wow um I think we can say confirmed
this that was code for get it off your
[ __ ] lip and not let it sit there you
go thanks I think we can say safely this
is a cookable thing in our home yeah but
not a
meal Matt understood ready guys we have
to do this every time a piece of History
all right does this get a cook this
really depends on what you're about to
do by the way okay yeah whether or not
becomes a part of History if you're
about to go boom oroom on them no does
this get a cookbook yes or a cookbook no
and you have to do the thumbs up or
thumbs down okay and everyone votes on
three are you ready cookbook yes or no
on three one cookbook yes or no on three
three two
one yes do the double thumbs up and stop
[ __ ] second guessing your answer okay
yeah so this gu in the cookbook page
number one pizza pocket snacks or
appetizers mhm good job
I'm not done I like how there's like
enough you know like that's a good snack
like lengthwise and like how much the
serving is that sound
crazy like that's a good kids raing the
length of no cuz it's good like it's
enough to like like eat dude you're
freaking me out each bitee gets more
tasty I think it's almost like I'm
unlocking more flavor as I one okay wrap
it up all right everyone thank you so
much for watching this Friday video we
will be back next Friday with another
one actually
and this Wednesday maybe
maybe
maybe we have some things to sort out
yes we have some business to handle yes
we appreciate all you guys sticking
around and having fun with us I know
[Music]
oh