A lot of these AI tools are getting
better, but that only means they can do
a certain set of instructions which are
seen in data. You still need to provide
AI what to do, right? You still need to
be able to describe it. And that ability
to describe what are the tasks AI should
do, what are the programs to be written
is still important. I think one job that
will not be replaced by AI is the
ability to be curious and go after hard
problems. So for young people, my advice
is not to be afraid of AI or worry what
skills to learn that AI may replace them
with, but really be in that path of
curiosity. I'm an animant Kumar. I'm
brand professor at Caltech. I've been a
professor at Caltech for about 8 years
now and during that time I also had
stints in industry. I was principal
scientist at Amazon Web Services. So at
Caltech, I lead the AI and science lab,
which means uh working on some of the
hardest challenges we see in science and
engineering and how we can not only use
existing AI methods to solve them, but
really develop new ones.
[Music]
I think one job that will not be
replaced by AI is the ability to be
curious and go after hard problems. For
a lot of students, there is a strong
motivation to just conform and go ahead.
Right? The number one thing I would ask
is to question everything. Think
critically. I always begin the classes
by asking questions, not writing down
math equations, right? Not going into
the details but just intuitively based
on everything that you've seen you've
done what do you think I asked them
simple cases for instance if you were to
design for a fire alarm when should it
say that there is fire or not that's
something you can change right you can
put a threshold you know what level of
smoke or when does it think it's smoky
and that's a very practical question so
if you just had fire alarms every day
we'd be just out and it would be useless
we would not have a functional office
space. But on the other hand, if we
never set fire, that would be bad, too.
So, how to balance this and how to model
how noisy this sensor could be. And
sometimes I see with students who may
not have the mathematical training, but
they're very intuitive and practical.
They may be like, oh, I would go and
measure how noisy it is, or I would show
different levels of smoke, have like
candles of different sizes and go and
test it. that and you know many times
people already maybe somewhat aware of
this so they have some intuitive ideas
so that already is a good starting point
and sometimes they are maybe really
wrong they have an intuition but that's
a wrong intuition which is still okay
because intuitions are not always the
only answer right so I think a lot of it
comes by asking questions and now you
can use these AI tools to get answers
very quickly and also verify them a lot
of it comes from being just like curious
or interested and that could be one
specific topic and if somebody's
interested in music they can delve
deeper into that if somebody is
interested in art so it just has to that
spark has to come from within and I
think giving students more the freedom
to pursue where they are passionate
where they have a spark I think is going
to be the future and that's the right
thing rather than forcing everybody to
learn
everything I'm always motivated by the
hardest challenge challenges. You know,
I want to know what is difficult, but
also why it's difficult, right? And even
though I may not be able to solve it
today, how do we build up the
foundations to get there? Growing up in
my sore as a kid, I loved just solving
math problems, you know, going to my
parents' factory. I was reading up their
program manuals. I was, you know,
learning how they could be programmed.
And unlike in other computer programs
here if something was wrong that would
lead to like physical failure parts
being like not manufactured correctly
and I'm like oh but how does it go into
the computer and how does the computer
tell the machine what to do so there
were always gaps because as a kid you
don't know everything but to me it was
like observing and then understanding
what the gap is and even if I didn't get
an immediate answer I would remember
that there is a gap and then later when
I was introduce use those topics. I was
in my mind I was like, "Oh, that's what
it relates to." So somehow I had built
up that mental map and I had put places
of where things I knew and things I
didn't know and I kept kind of growing
that in my mind as I progressed through
the years. So when I was growing up, AI
was considered science fiction.
Naturally, there were lots of science
fiction movies where I saw and was
fascinated. But that's not something
people thought were practical. Uh since
I was in middle and high school and now
it's almost 30 years, right? It is a
long time, but the amount of progress
that has happened is also so astounding
in so many ways. So since I joined
Caltech in 2017, the timing just felt
right to use AI as a tool and a
framework to solve some of the hardest
problems which until that point was not
considered practical. So after I joined
Caltech and wanted to explore problems
at the intersection of AI and science
and I was talking to everybody on
campus, I was like okay do you need
compute? What do you need it for? Let me
understand the problems that you're
tackling. And you know I can't possibly
go and solve each one of them problems
myself. Right? My question then was are
there general tools we can develop that
could impact so many different areas?
And that again put me back to
mathematical foundations. So because a
lot of these different real world
phenomena are modeled by partial
differential equations. So now can we
design AI that can solve this and do it
much faster do it much better than what
is currently being done with traditional
simulations. And to do that we developed
neural operators. We've invented an AI
technology called neural operators that
is trained to understand physical
behaviors not just highle reasoning with
text. So think of a hurricane. The
hurricane if you will just eyeball it,
can you tell where it's going to go? You
know, most humans cannot, right? It's a
superhuman skill to predict where
hurricanes are going to go. And for to
do that, we need finecale information
and finecale modeling. So this cannot be
just a core scale image like the image
of a cat where even if it's gets blurry,
you know it's a cat. The same techniques
don't work for phenomena like
hurricanes. Once we developed tools and
then the next natural question is what
were practical use cases that involved
and the weather models was a natural one
because it's widely used. It has huge
implications on our lives especially if
extreme weather events like hurricanes
if we get them right that has the
potential to save human lives and also
bring down economic costs. So I was
motivated by how it can be helpful to
people, but I was also motivated by that
being considered a very hard technical
challenge. In fact, just a few months
before we released our model, there were
a group of very wellrespected weather
scientists who published in the Royal
Society Journal thinking they're they
were under the impression that AI would
take more than a decade or even longer
to replace traditional ways to forecast
weather. and they felt AI was just not
ready. This problem is way too
difficult. And we released this and it
just took everybody by surprise. It was
not only accurate, it was tens of
thousands of times faster. So what would
take a big supercomput for traditional
weather models can now be run on a local
gaming PC with just a consumer GPU. So
that's the beauty of uh machine learning
as a field. We are not always stopped by
what others think as difficult. As long
as we can get the data and we can design
the methods, we can just go and try
it. So my mission is to constantly be
curious and learning and not assume that
any problem is easy. I can't imagine a
world where scientists will be out of
jobs because the definition of a
scientist is somebody who tackles open
problems, right? So there are harder and
harder problems to tackle. You know, if
you want to look at the deep secrets of
our universe, go down to the smallest
scale and understand at the atomic and
subatomic level how matter is
constructed to of course level of galaxy
and beyond and understand how the
universe is put together. There are
still lots of open challenges. Many
other teams such as Google Deepine focus
on what is known as an AI scientist.
Meaning AI that comes up with new ideas.
But so much of scientific progress is
not limited by the lack of new ideas,
right? Lots of people have lots of
ideas. But the bottleneck is going to
the lab or going to the real world and
testing them. That is slow. That is
expensive. So my focus is how we can
replace those lab experiments. Can we
come up with AI that inherently
understands the physics better? So we
can completely avoid the lab experiments
or maybe only do it to do the final
testing. And so with that focus and with
that physical knowledge, we can come up
with AI designed answers that we can go
directly to the real world and minimize
this need for testing. To me, human
agency is driving AI to do something
that you want it to be done. You have
the agency as a human to decide what
tasks AI does and then you're evaluating
and you're in charge, right? So, you go
and verify whether what AI is saying is
true or not and then over time provide
that feedback to AI and make it
better. AI is a tool. It can both help
curiosity but also kill it depending on
how it's used. Right? So for young
people, my advice is not to be afraid of
AI or worry what skills to learn that AI
may replace them with, but really be in
that path of curiosity, right? Use AI as
a tool to drive that curiosity, learn
new skills, new knowledge, and you can
do that in a much more interactive way.
Even when it comes to writing computer
programs, you know, a lot of these AI
tools are getting better, but that only
means they can do a certain set of
instructions which are seen in data. You
still need to provide AI what to do,
right? You still need to be able to
describe it. And that ability to
describe what are the tasks AI should
do. What are kind of highlevel
understanding of what AI is doing when
it writes these computer programs is
still important because a bad programmer
who is not better than AI will be
replaced. But a great programmer who can
assess what AI is doing, make fixes,
ensure those programs are written well
will be in more demand than ever.