so how do you want to start it off today
Chris I don't know how do you want to
start it off today I don't know Matt
beats the piss out of me
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah
I can't believe that you kept that shirt
what are you talking about why would I
ever get rid of it well it's like why
would you I don't know why you just like
are wearing it on a normal day all right
if you guys it's not a normal it's not a
normal day
it's today
and today is a gift
um
so if you guys are unaware and our last
Wednesday video that we just posted
um Matt and Christopher in Chicago I was
in LA for like five days without them
and then like when I came home it was
like the longest we had been apart and
with that I flew alone on a plane for
the first time and I have a couple
stories that I didn't tell Matt and
Chris yet of like things that happened
to me and honest to God I think that
[ __ ] this crazy happens to me and Matt
and Chris all the time but they felt so
much more surreal because I was alone
with my thoughts so I was like there's
no one for me to talk about you there's
no one for me to talk to and I'll never
like that so I'm like I was just really
like scoping out what was happening
around me because so next because I was
alone but no multiple stories
so you know when like you scan your
ticket for like the plane and it like
beeps bright red if you're in an exit
row yeah and they're like oh are you
willing and able to help in case of an
emergency due to like a [ __ ] plane
crashing and you're supposed to say yes
I'm willing and able and that's all they
need like they're never gonna get in a
plane crash but you just have to say
like oh I'm willing and able like you
have to say yes yeah well they're like
any handicapped Personnel can board the
plane first and this [ __ ] crutches up
there the slowest I've ever seen anyone
on crutches ever like I'm talking like
I've seen people on crutches and be kind
of mobile with it like moving at a
decent pace this [ __ ] crunched like if
she didn't have those crutches she was
getting nowhere I kid you not okay she
gets to the front scancer thing beeps
bright red of course and the lady's like
are you willing and able to help in case
of an emergency and I'm like why did you
even ask the goddamn question first of
all she may be willing but she is far
far the [ __ ] away from Abel like if she
says
there is concrete proof in front of my
eyes denying this like you are not able
girl at all
um but gladly she says no I said correct
it's like absolutely imagine though
she's like yeah I'm willing enable it's
like girl there's proof in front of my
eyes that you are not oh my God but she
was
dude I was just a little in shock
because I'm like of course why are you
so high up I'm like looking fixing my
posture recently but I was just like in
shots I'm like if this girl says like oh
yeah I'm really enable you are far from
the truth okay and of course they put
the girl in crunch it like obviously
they don't know but it's like how ironic
for the girl would crutches well she
booked her own ticket yeah but she
probably broke her leg after
what are the odds of that um but also
I've never seen someone when they're
like oh are you willing and able to not
say yes and the funny thing too oh my
God I forgot the guy before her was like
absolutely like he was like acting like
a soldier like getting ready for War I
was like buddy this is a [ __ ]
in case scenario you're probably gonna
sit there lounging eating peanuts
speaking of I just perfectly
transitioned into my next thought and I
didn't even mean to do it
we're we're on the plane
I can't we're on this plane right okay
I didn't forget and I have as a bullet
point served peanuts question mark
question mark question mark because we
get on the plane and they do all the
normal procedure and like right before
we take off the intercom starts and I'm
like oh God they're gonna tell us the
engines are busted like we're done but
because it's like a random time Tuesday
okay but the lady goes oh I was just
informed that someone on this plane has
is a severe peanut allergies if you
brought any snacks on board that
contained peanuts tree nuts any kind of
nuts please refrain from eating any of
them and if you want a replacement for
your snack well absolutely like we have
a bunch but just please don't open any
peanuts and I was in first class
of course no I'm kidding we don't fly
first class often but I was alone and
scared so I was but I was in first class
and the guy comes up to me like 40
minutes into the flight and he's like
warm peanuts and hands me like a little
dish of peanuts I'm like
the line
like is someone under a life-threatening
circumstance in the background because
they said don't eat peanuts and they
bust they pull they they gave them out
that's crazy yeah anyways let's see if I
have another that is insane so they just
serve peanuts and everyone oh another
one I have written down two
[ __ ] with guitars okay they
have they're like oh we're extremely
limited on space like we cannot have
anyone put like anything other than one
carry on the overhead bin if you want to
check your bag out of a courtesy like we
can two [ __ ] with guitars as
their carry-on item
it let it happen like I know it's 2023
but guitars cannot bend and folds like
that [ __ ] was big yeah and they're like
trying to fit the guitars in the whole
time and this poor woman like they got
the guitars in and this poor woman had
to like check her suitcase because there
wasn't room I'm like have AC DC check
that because that's ridiculous like no
one should be bringing on a carry-on
item a guitar well I get it they're more
fragile but that's ridiculous when
you're pushing for space like that's
ridic
and then I got [ __ ] confusing
me by not by moving weird as [ __ ]
yeah we're good like I triple checked my
boarding pass I checked the app I'm like
I checked my flight number you know I'm
there and I'm like okay like these
people like they're probably going to
Boston you know that's where I'm going
so I'm looking at this one guy and then
this one family of five and they're like
my two staple people like because I I
saw them around I got to the gate I'm
like if they're here at the gate
I'm good you know why because you
thought because I was like oh like if
they're here at the gate like I'm in the
right place because like they're getting
on this plane you know what I mean like
I won't end up in the right if I'm I'll
be in the wrong spot if both these
[ __ ] aren't here when I'm
getting on a plane okay yeah you know
what I mean
getting off the plane when I see someone
go to like a baggage claim that I'm like
oh they were like they were on my flight
I'll go down regardless it worked for me
but the family is eating at a table at
the gate
gets up and walks away after like the
intercom and I was like
oh I was really afraid so I look at the
guy and he got up and walked away too
and I'm like oh my God I'm in the wrong
spot so I went over the screen triple
checked got on the plane [ __ ]
sitting next to me I'm like where'd you
go dude was boarding like they called my
boarding number he walked away and I was
like oh no I hope I'm in the right place
and I see on the plane sitting next to
me that's crazy like why are you moving
weird as [ __ ] like that's bizarre I
wonder where he went I don't know this
lady she got a first class ticket and
like the plane was supposed to like like
her seat was supposed to fully flatten
out and she was like oh I just had back
surgery like given the flight attendant
her whole sob story and she's like my my
seat isn't like going all the way down
and I'm like you know
this is the one time I wish I was one of
those [ __ ] that could say no or
like was a bad person because the flight
attendant comes up to me gives me the
girl sob story and is like do you mind
like if you switch seats with her and
I'm like you know what I'm probably
gonna pull in all night you have to you
have to say that she was also first
class but her chair yeah she was also
first class her seat just wouldn't lay
down mine would lay down but the reason
he asked me is because I wasn't laying
down yet because my seatbelt sign was on
so I'm like there's no way like like I
didn't know I could go into laying
positions
yeah obviously so
he asks me and while he's asking me the
girl's looking at me like Matt right now
like looking over her seat like
with her [ __ ] holding her back and
her [ __ ]
stupid face mask like not the mask the
mask the eye mask like okay oh
all right
what's that it's the book with the girl
she's got like 100 mattresses it was a
really good reference for this story
Google princess and the P the book
Princess and the p i remember reading
holy [ __ ] you just
I don't know how you have like that book
I haven't seen that book since fourth
grade what is it if it says
bothering her on the first one goofy
[ __ ] you don't haven't seen the book
Princess and the Pete look it up Google
it that was a good it was a really good
really good
Y episode with it when I was a kid and I
loved it but okay anyways Princess and
the P so she's looking at me I'm like of
course yeah fine and it's like dude it's
like it just shows
oh no [ __ ] the [ __ ] who had back
surgery I'm going to bed like if I say
no I'm the bad guy yeah you know what I
mean they're stuck she had back surgery
it's like on America's Got Talent when
they get the golden buzzer because like
their grandma died but
anyways she's looking at me
with their sleep masks yeah and I was
watching RuPaul's Drag Race I'm 30
minutes into an episode my wife my
fly-fi's going great I'm like okay I got
Wi-Fi this is awesome I'm like oh yeah
of course like let me grab all my
[ __ ] [ __ ] I unplug my charger I get
all my [ __ ] together and then I switch
seats with her she's like oh thank you
I'm like yes of course just take my seat
and then I get into my seat
and bro the problem was not that it did
not lie all the way flat the problem was
it was positioned if I was a [ __ ]
contortionist like the back was arched
the feet were up I felt like a kangaroo
on the Frogger you know what I'm talking
about the ride that goes up and down I
feel like I was at Star blast at Canobie
Lake it was Unreal I was like what
coaster did I just get on I felt like
they put me up like like I've never had
this happen to me because I'm I don't
have female genitalia but when you're
giving birth like your feet are up on
things that they can get a good look for
the delivery I felt like I was just up
in the air like
weirdest position I've ever been in in
my life for five [ __ ] hours
and then I tried to like lay it down and
the problem was that the things didn't
go flat it was just like stuck in that
position and then I'm like okay like
whatever RuPaul will get me through this
so I go I go to my TV show and it's like
oh not loading and then my Wi-Fi did not
work for the rest of the flights I'm
like what songs do I have downloaded
I'll just listen to my downloaded music
and try and sleep as if I'm [ __ ]
delivering a child and I hit Shuffle on
my music
silence the whole point silence silence
so I spent the whole flight
sitting there
in despair no music no TV stuck with my
legs in the air
that's hilarious and that was my night
it was terrible all around like it was
just a bad [ __ ]
that's so funny I feel like you
shouldn't have gave her this do we have
any sort yeah but like imagine Chris
said [ __ ] you in your back surgery go
take it up with JetBlue well I wasn't on
JetBlue Delta United no but I agree it's
like you you get it get what you get and
you don't get upset like no I play with
the cards you're dealt with and those
were not my [ __ ] cars I'm sorry
go
fishing you should have at least gotten
a refund it was just an unreal
experience like it was like also like
how are you gonna sell first class
tickets and not have your first class
seats work all right I feel like do we
have anything when did we get a
SpongeBob air freshener yeah I don't
know I love it it smells like Jellyfish
Fields
give jellyfish feel to change pineapple
anyway get in my car driver do we have
any stories that we can tell Nick about
our trip if you want to know what I'm
about
what did we do on the on the trip that
like it could be funny I thought we
vlogged our trip yeah I saw your Vlog I
left my duffel bag in the Uber and I
felt like an idiot oh my God and then
the dude was like begging for an extra
tip he deserved it he did deserve it but
like I felt so bad yeah oh my [ __ ]
word that scared the [ __ ] out of me what
else me Chris and um our new friend
Mason that was there he orders us a lift
and there's three of us and then the
dude pulls up in a Chevy Silverado truck
yeah I hate Uber and Lyft catfishes it's
like bro there's three of us and you're
coming over here with a pickup truck
like let's at least have the right
supplies this happened to me too many
times we're like we've ordered a car for
like six people and like a four and then
they get mad at you it's like no you're
the one that accepted the ride not
having
I'm on the way and it's like
all right it sounded like someone just
spawned in bro the Teenage Mutant Ninja
Turtles better come dude I was thinking
it's like very Teenage Mutant Ninja
Turtles I saw Master Splinter a little
while ago no for real oh there he is
whoa I've Just Seen Masters look at him
oh my God are they actually perfect
timing people are gonna think we're
lying no for real that was a rat no
they're not gonna think we're lying are
you [ __ ] boxes there's rats
everywhere
shout out to all the fans that took
photos with me and Chris at summerslash
and waited to the end of the festival
days to post them to keep it a surprise
from everyone that we were in Chicago
because isn't it crazy that people had
no clue we were there at all maybe like
a couple maybe like 15 people until I
was on the stage ever no one knew you
were there until you got on the stage
yeah except for like we took except for
the people like at summer smash already
that song yeah besides and then nobody
had any service so people saw that Chris
was there live but couldn't post
anything it was so fun it was how did
you how do you feel like I feel pretty
good
onenote's crazy also I just remember
from the airport
say it what the only Waters they sold
were in glass bottles at the stores I'm
like that could be turned into a weapon
very quickly it could
it was only option like why are we
having like let's like when you're on a
plane usually you want like minimal [ __ ]
that can fit all in your bag yeah
plastic water bottle it was like glass
Evian I'm like I don't know what you
think you're doing but it ain't that
better have a bank account if you want
to see what I'm about
I think I slept for a total of like six
hours the entire time I was in Chicago I
slept three and 48. I slept three hours
and 48 hours and then you're walking
around three hours in 40 years
sounds like a rap bar mmm it's only
Taylor Swift
red
bro I got a BLT and they threw a
jalapeno in the middle
[Laughter]
your eyes dude a BLT is one sandwich you
cannot [ __ ] up
the [ __ ] name BLT
J
it's your problem
like if you're adding she'll surprise
[ __ ] to a BLT at least add it to like
[ __ ] if you're gonna add surprise
ingredients to a meal it has to be like
Nachos Supreme mess disaster that's how
to be the title of the thing you order
because then you could throw [ __ ] cow
[ __ ] on it and I would expect that
that's part of it because the name is
like [ __ ] disaster tornado nachos but
BLT
but it was a blta with avocado as well
um no Jay yeah correct okay so that
changes nothing it makes it more clear
on what should not [ __ ] mean if
anything they should have just put the J
also what where's my respect for Mayo at
because he's on almost every BLT and I
don't see a
um thing about him for real it should be
bltm should be bltm red B can't have a b
b l TM I think we should have started
abbreviating [ __ ] more I know we've had
this horse
better have a bank account if you want
to see what I'm about I'm a good girl
work power
I'm just a freaky what's your favorite
road sign
road sign mine's U-turn like
going the other way I like a good yield
because it's like the balls in your
court like it's proceed with caution but
do your thing
that's a good stop you wanna know I
don't know what signs I hate I hate when
it's like no parking and then it's like
a full paragraph about when and where
and he's not gonna have a fun answer
because he can drive you know what I
mean yeah
that's true that's true
yeah I like road signs that are easy I
feel like signs are like dude what would
we do without signs what would you do
without traffic lights
Drive yeah and then you're just hitting
everything no yeah I feel like it'd be I
feel like there'd be a memory pattern if
it wasn't the color pattern
like it would be like instead of
following red blue green I mean red red
yellow green it would be it would be
like a pattern in memory of people it
was like for five seconds or five cars
five cars like it would be a whole Road
not because then people are gonna have
to start DR dude stop driving it away
people are think of older people's self
better like when they're driving old
people that are little they're like
colorblind like glasses to see the well
no because red green and yellow are the
probably but red green and yellow and
like the lights are never changing from
the right spot so colorblind people
probably just think like oh green likes
the top one yeah but how do they know
it's glowing
um because that's not color blindness
that's blindness then you definitely at
all like if you don't know it's glowing
that's a whole nother [ __ ] case that
you need to do that they have a bank
account if you want to see what I'm
about let's all think of things to add
the other one should start doing
like not like a rude way like not don't
oh I was gonna say shower
that's like so like I think you're clean
no Matt makes these jokes and then
people look we went to we went to a
three I think you should work hard we
went to a three-day festival and Chris
walks into the room on the third day
with everyone in there and he goes bro
he walked into the room after showering
from the other hotel room and he goes
and he goes that was the first good
shower I had in two days I said that was
the first really good shower I had in
like a couple days because the other
nights I got home so late because it was
a [ __ ] festival and then so I like
cleaned like in like like three four
minutes like soap all everywhere and
then just washed it off and then dried
my body off valid and then then the
other day I like you went to bed and
then I didn't have any requirements that
night and I actually was gonna stay up
until my flight so I was like you know
I'm gonna take a nice long shower love
it so then I took showers every day
which is a normal [ __ ] thing I do and
I just said to everyone soap ad on Tick
Tock and the guy goes out to people with
the mic he's like how many showers you
take yeah
and some guy was like oh look how old is
your shower on the beach yeah but yeah
that's not what I'm getting at okay shut
up don't interrupt me okay he goes
oh my God
okay no violence he goes how often do
you shower and some guy was strapped
like every three days
that's crazy I was like that's I know if
I don't shower for like I know your ass
stinks if I don't shower in like every
15 hours I feel like sometimes I feel
like I gotta shower every 10 minutes bro
I'd be changing my underwear just to
change it oh the second my uh they're
not even dirty I'm like I got it the
second I step Outdoors I'm like I need
to once I get back indoors I have to
well it's just almost like there's like
like toxic masculinity so crazy we're to
the point where like some straight men
thinks it's like straight men are like
it's gay as [ __ ] to like clean like
straight men straight up only shower
once a day even if they go to the gym
and smell like [ __ ] because it's getting
clean and taking care of your own body
is gay so I mean if it's gay then
[ __ ] get me another pride flag
because I love it I love taking my
showers what's that Gonna Shine I can't
believe that that's like a thing okay
the one thing you wash their face I
think Nick I think it'd be really good
at rock climbing oh my gosh yeah I can
just see you just I feel like I wouldn't
be good at rock climbing I think I'd be
good at life or death rock climbing I'm
gonna like no harness plummet to my
death then I feel like like [ __ ] my
toilet was like clogged or needed like
assistance you'd be the guy like I feel
like you'd be like watch out I can
handle this well I'm the bug killer of
the group
that's true don't look at me did I have
anything to do with what I said though
because you're talking well did rock
climbing have to do with [ __ ] fixing
your toilet that's very true no but I'm
saying what I think we'd be good at
correct that's what he did but if I had
like a big like like problem in the
bathroom I'd be like like and my toilet
wasn't flushing I'd be like Matt
and he just like put some gloves on
crack his knuckles and Mario
I feel like Nick would like really make
good caramelized onions
you know what I mean I wouldn't even
know where to begin you just sauteed
them on the pan till they're golden
brown I feel like I could cook a lot
better if I had the time to come no like
I feel like yeah I'm hungry like I could
see Nick cooking something up nice like
like I feel like no I can't I can't cook
while I'm hungry because I'll eat it raw
no like whatever I'm cooking I'll just
check I'll just eat this now I don't
want to wait
I had no patience when it comes to a
meal like if I'm here we know if I'm
boiling water I'm like looking at it
like please
everyone clapping a rhythmic pattern on
three and if we if two of us Clap the
same rhythmic pattern we have to just
end the video right away okay ready
ready
okay okay Ready Set Go
but it's okay
for my brothers