wow that was the first ever Stern buly
moment where for Matt where he threw no
more
St and then what you saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
that we did we said we going to travel
from the island to Madrid we had a lot
of plans but they
all why because of some but it's okay
cuz I'm moving different don't be saying
when I'm post with other
[ __ ] the other day I heard I
overheard someone call someone muddy and
I was like that sounds kind of czy oh
she's muddy dirty washed
up no but they said why are you acting
muddy like why are you acting mud I
don't know I think this might have a
bigger meaning that we don't know it may
be like a thing do you guys know what
muddy means I don't I don't I usually
relate it to Three Little Pigs rolling
around in mud if it's not that I don't
know follow your
nose I'm [ __ ] out of
lock muddy meaning slang to make a
situation more confusing or
oh wow true I love that so why you
acting muddy bro you're making this
situation more I love I know lots of
[ __ ] acting muddy way too many I can
point them out hey guys welcome back to
Ser tripet car video it is your favorite
day of the week it is Friday and we're
going to really really reach back with
our fishing LS and reel in an OG Stern
YOLO triplet content Vibe we're going
straight we got a topic today and we
have all your answers we're not going to
weigh our own opinion at all we're going
to see how this [ __ ] goes and we're
going to get after it happy Friday
follow your nose my nose is telling me
to go far away from Nick for $1 million
would you blank is the central idea
today every single thing I read is
submitted by a fan walk through a car
wash I do that for the experience of a
lifetime sorry I'm just waiting for
these people to pass by leave us
alone I'd walk through it just for the
sheer joy and experience if if it was
being recorded I'd do it for free I do
it last three naked
all soap beat through the car wash that'
be so lit if I had to streak I'm running
through a car wash for sure it's crazy
we used to do that as babies low key we
were like eight or nine we used to just
like get naked and run around sprinklers
together remember that uh I would not
say eight or n cuz I like don't there's
photos of it that's crazy BR stop
talking you guys remember that no I
don't it was a fun time like we were
just kids and we like probably five I
think five okay maybe I have no get away
from us you want to know what I oh what
ises this little kid doing on a bike you
know what I would do get away from us
where are they you want to know what I
would do the car wash thing for what the
experience in movie nachos movie nachos
yep what is the at the car wash yeah I
do it for the experience not connecting
these but I also want like some movie
nachos after for what where where are
you getting the nachos I just want them
after I'm confused where these two
things tie together I was going to say
you're saying that like like movie
nachos is like a classic after a car
wash no I just like that's what I'm the
type of vibe I haven't had movie nachos
a day in my life what dude car watching
movie nachos I'm still kind of confused
someone
said you need to be studied in a
lab Matt you got to come back here yeah
like he used the excuse to go play
Pokemon like I bet for sure hey Ash
catch him you [ __ ] loser get in the
car what are you do on your phone out
there there's just a couple things I
won't tolerate and that's why of them
for sure I don't get why people run with
baby strollers like that's got to be so
rude to the baby like they're like like
they're in there like it's like a roller
coaster okay someone said f you doing
the central to you want to kiss me or
something for $1 million would you and
then someone said kiss you all so I'm
guessing they're asking if we'd kiss
each other for a million dollars that's
not what they're asking go to the next
one it's like we didn't ask what you
would do we know You' do that for 30
cents in a sweet tea you little bastard
get out of here God go see the Titanic
in a tiny submarine too soon bro too
soon and targeted you seem upset about
someone who's on that someone paid that
much to go do
that you ate them up low key that's
crazy rest in peace
literally lick Nick lick Nick's toes a
million dollars to lick your toes yeah
I'd lick all of them a million times for
a million only cuz I know my boy Nicki
showering twice a
day he's he's he's keeping if I had to
lick someone's feet for money it would
be Nick cuz I'm clean and I would I
would lick Nick's feet and I give him
money for dealing with that and then i'
take oh I don't need any money for okay
then i' just take it's your bet yeah i'
just take the million and and relax and
get I have to eat literal horeshit eat
literal horseshit I feel like I'd get
sick and have to pay a million dollars
in medical bills to get my body here's
thing it depends how if there's million
cash there's not a lot I won't do I
agree
would you eat horeshit it depends how
much it depends how much how much if I
have to take a bite and just swallow it
and get it down I agree like if I just
have to like if it was like just eat
like a speck of hesit said get a buzz
cut I'd get a buzz cut for the i' get a
buzz cut for like $5,000 I have 5K mhm
I'd get a buzz cut for let's be
reasonable I'd get a buzz cut for yeah
5K you even less I have the UR to shave
my head every single day I wake up so
I'd get it for free
tomorrow I'd do that one for some movie
movie nachos kid what's with the movie
nachos lose it like what the [ __ ]
going on what there's so many better
options at the movie theater that was
never like a negotiable thing for this
[ __ ] Butterfingers dude Reese's
Pieces might as well be a movie theater
exclusive at this point I don't get it
cuz they're always just hidden at movie
theaters I've never had Reese's PCS not
at the theater they're really good
though they're all right a top tier
candy in my opin they're
mid what I can't say it why people are
naughty why why naughty so weird which
one what is that the one you're talking
about
obviously God
obvious [ __ ] hit me with the bottle
there you go give up your favorite tooda
would you give up Pepsi for a million
dollars like I'd be stupid not to what
of course I would Nick million dollars
like Absolutely I'll just have Dr Pepper
or root beer root beer no root beer root
beer no root beer you do so perfectly
you know that audio from Tik
Tok beer root beer no root beer so it be
homeless for a month Nick come on crazy
like I just feel bad spit everywhere I
feel bad saying all these things yeah to
it's not me it's not me go to the next
one Nick like and I hate idiots I hate
them we asked a question oh tell us your
type mainly for Chris mind your [ __ ]
business not the video idea correct I'll
tell you for a million dollars date your
brother's girlfriend like I can't find
normal people suck toes lick your
brother's toes kiss my brother jump off
the tallest tower in the world oh yeah
like can we get can we can we stop lick
peanut butter off someone's toes I do it
just to eat some peanut butter you're
insane crazy Nick sell Chris ch is worth
more than a million do wow thank you
Nick of course leave the country or go
to space very different things here
we're talking money involved do you
think the moon landing was faked 100%
dude the lighting was just too
phenomenal the moment they live streamed
it what way back went on TV I got what I
got to find out how do they live stream
like I don't know I don't know if this
is like can you get cancelled for saying
that the moon landing is fake I hope not
cuz I think it's fake as [ __ ] I just
don't I I really can't get behind how
haven't we gotten back back to the moon
have we not gone back to the Moon
apparently we just don't want to
1 bro said zero that's crazy where's
Neil Armstrong on the Moon is he here
he's back right what he's back let's
talk to him let's get him where's Neil
Armstrong if he's back I need to talk to
is Neil
strong Neil Armstrong is Neil Armstrong
alive and well and on
Earth he died in 2012 oh my goodness at
least I got to walk who went to the moon
Buzz Aldren as well Google that that's
what Buzz Light yours Bas off of is Buzz
Aldren is
balls is Buzz Aldren alive
[Laughter]
balls but Aldren oh he's alive
uh-uh there's no there's only a date of
birth there isn't a date of death I'm
just happy I got
to
[Music]
what' you do I spilled water all over my
feet and legs by accident that was
[Laughter]
freezing oh my God I totally got excited
that me and me and Neil Armstrong were
alive at the same time and just poured
water out on my God that was crazy it's
wet back here just the FYI the wet
sandals is crazy yeah why you put him up
here like
my my feet are so dirty okay so are you
buzz that's such a hard first name I
know I was thinking that that's so hard
better than Neil like that's an action
Neil's an ugly name no hate bro got an
action yeah yeah yeah it looks like
gravity's really well there as well like
I feel like gravity on the moon got to
be way crazier than
that I don't get it dude I just don't
understand how the [ __ ] did we get all
the way up there like I look at the Moon
and it just seems so like distant like
it seems like a whole another like I
agree I was about to say it seems like a
whole another like place but it
obviously is that's the whole point of
the Moon never talk to each other again
no way more than a
million 25 cents in a foot rug become
gay for the rest of your life I'm good
being gay is not a
choice get do M Dr that's crazy
weirdo it's like it's really difficult
to hold conversation about what you do
for a million dollars when every single
one is kiss your
brother yeah not kidding I'm like
Scavenging prowling for better ones I
can't believe the penny is still
around eat a cooked
placenta live underwater for 10 years is
that plausible no no I feel like I'd get
sick you'd probably get sick by the
[ __ ] first day literally like I feel
like being under waterer that long is so
scary in like a suit eating like like
tube
food run through your high school naked
no no I wouldn't either naked is there's
not much I do naked for a million
dollars I'd step outside my house and
dance around for like 2 minutes the
thing is okay next not be a chis girl
couldn't do
it I need a million dollars but not that
bad Nick get out of here you're so eat a
Yankee Candle ew dude if it's yeah if I
wouldn't get sick or hospitalized you
would get sick no in rations in RA in
ratios like if I just mix it with water
like ate it with soup like if I figured
it out I could get after it you're so
weird Nick eat it with soup is crazy eat
a whole bottle of ketchup
Matt for a million dollars you suck
ketchup down dry enter a twinky eating
beer no root beer Twinkies are so gross
dude I like Twinkies as a kid I feel
like I'd enter the contest just
lose
whoa that took a year for me to process
that that was crazy very evident you
didn't even know what that word meant
what a crazy way what a crazy thing do
school all over again oh oh how much
money would you realistically am I going
back into time or am I just doing
another 12 years of school I think it
would be another 12 years
another yeah I don't think that's worth
any amount of money I think I need a
million every extra year I did School
eat 10 big old bowls of potato salad I'd
do that yeah yeah for sure I wouldn't
enjoy it I just don't like like I love
potatoes I'm I'm surprised I don't like
how much a big H yeah like what's a big
old give me a measur a big old Bowl
what's a big like probably like a what
are yall saying big big old Bowl much is
a big old Bowl probably like a salad B
stop touching me and [ __ ] it's an
accident I don't care if it's an
accident
ooh you're
tough but I answer the tough guy
competition and' be all
tough that's good that's really good I
can't believe I dumped water on myself
I'm water I dumped water all over myself
forget all your memories flashbang oh no
no no I would never do that but the
thing is you I need to try potatoes out
like I can't I need to think about it
I've never even had it I don't even know
what I'm working with it's potatoes and
like Mayo I think
like 90% sure that's what it
is swallow 10 coins yep he's oh that's
so gross I just thought of the coin I I
could get 10 dimes down like Advil well
you'd have to [ __ ] them out they
wouldn't like that's fine I'd be scared
to choke isn't it crazy that there's
something things you could eat that like
won't digest that you just [ __ ] out Matt
[ __ ] out of marble
once true story true story root bear no
root bear
no root bear root be root beer tickle a
wizard man's feet okay find me the
wizard man and then I'll think about it
yeah do wizards even exist definitely I
feel we got everything on this Earth I
feel like there's fairies there's like
Bigfoot I feel there's everything I
always think if if Bigfoot was here we'd
get him we' we'd catch him yeah he has a
big foot like he's big he's not small
foot slap your mom I feel like mom would
want me to slap her for a million bucks
yeah I don't know do it just do it mom
like split it yeah give actually i' give
her give her like 80% of itre true like
Mom for 80% of it I just want 20% can I
slap you and then whatever she say I
just do it and give her the whole Mill I
agree sorry for the troubles swim in
chocolate
pudding dude I feel like there the
consistency isn't there my God it's like
jello from um cloud with the chance of
meall I drown I drown dead that's
actually a really big fear of mine what
jell no imagine being like just enclosed
and like Jello-O and you can't get out
so yes Jell-O not Jello-O itself being
trapped in it I don't think you got to
worry about for YouTube video we should
make as much Jello-O as we can and fill
up like a kitty pool even bigger than
that I'm thinking big we should make
like a we should get a pool like an
above ground pool sorry I need it it you
don't need it there's nothing around me
that I can touch I feel so like whatever
you don't need it there's not much room
for me back here I don't care I
scratching
my I don't even have shoes on or
anything that's fine that's your fault
we should get an above ground pool and
buy tons of Jello-O mix and then just
make Jello but at like a way bigger
scale like huge Jello that would take
forever I don't have that time
commitment to make big jello decorate
the
house no no that's where I draw the line
no I can't decorate the house for a
million bucks no way what does like what
does that even mean I don't [ __ ] know
dude sick for a whole year ew no I think
being sick is my least favorite feeling
in the world it's so gross last time I
got Co I literally thought I was going
to die I know I remember you know what
Scooby-Doo's mom's name
is Ruby dooo that's a good one it sounds
like EMB barking Ruby dooo and it's her
name like scoobydoo rub Doo he can't
pronounce his S as well anyways let a
lion chase you for a million dollars no
I die dead do we not understand this
anything that ends my life I wouldn't do
for a million dollar cuz a million
dollars would vanish Into Thin Air and
become nothing I
agree think about it I thought about it
guys we're going to eat
Barnacles Barnacles Barnacles lowkey
like good scratched your throat no not
like Barnacles but like there's actually
like Barnacle Bills They don't serve
barnacle no I feel like it's got to be
good like it's just Seafood it's got if
you could cook up a barnacle I feel like
like the inside's a worm is it not I
don't know for a million dollars they
wouldn't be able to put fire on all
their books they wouldn't be able to
light their books on fire just can I
tell you what books are paper words
literal the definition of Fire Starter
if I'm in the woods and I have a book
I'm lighting that [ __ ] on fire you me
papers fire starter not words you said
words it's words it's just words words
on paper I had to light a book on fire
in 35 seconds hold and burn it hold on
the way that I think about it is you
don't have a million dollar worth of
books so like them all and on fire buy
the books again and then you have some
profit left I trying to say m but you
just said it with no energy like a baby
like Matt talks like this and then
expects people to be entertained he'll
make a joke that I make loudly like this
and it's like what do you want them to
hear they can barely hear you is not
[Music]
funny not be able to shower or bathe for
a year I wouldn't be able to do it I
need to shower I need to shower right
now actually actually really need to
shower like the thought of not being
able to stay a year is some things like
in real life that just seem so cartoon
that would happen Nick manorisms like
something like you didn't even say
mannerisms right I fully manorisms
correct doesn't exist whatever you said
aneurisms but with an M okay you meant
manism you wi for tour I'm throwing
shoes in the crowd at numerous location
I'm not trying to I don't have room here
I'm sitting on the edge of my seat
literally sit like this goodbye everyone
we'll see you guys next Wednesday and
then next Friday we're on tour so
prepare to go follow yeah whatever go
follow us on like Instagram stuff so you
can be updated with the tour that we're
on right this very very moment also
follow us on Instagram at stern. triplet
Nicholas stolo and I don't care about
either of them but their links are in
the description down below Nick [ __ ] you
don't touch me yeah but do what you got
to do love you love you guys
kissing and then what you saying how you
miss me yeah you miss me and all the
things that we did we we going to Trel
from the is my we had a lot of plans but
they
allad why because of someid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
saying nothing when I with [ __ ] for
my brothers