So the first day that I joined Figma, I
remember I was sitting in a presentation
and Dylan was kind of walking me through
stuff, showing the product and the name
of the tool at the time was actually
called Summit. And I remember I thought
to myself like this just isn't going to
work. Metrics are so important, but I
feel like when you're doing something
really early and you're like, I have to
10x this, I have to 100x this, I have
to,000x this, you kind of have to go
more on intuition and more on feeling, I
think, and really believe that because
metrics just aren't going to get you the
answers that you're looking for. If you
joined Figma, you had to start spending
time answering support questions. And so
it sounds like pretty un unscalable,
right? Oh, you have your engineers
sitting there answering support tickets,
fixing bugs, like you can't do that
forever. That doesn't scale. But
actually, it does scale. You think about
people as companies. And I think the
biggest advice that I would give is like
people are people, right? And I think
you see that it can conf like you'll see
people and you'll talk to them and
you'll be chatting. It sounds so basic,
right? But like I think so often in
marketing we we split people into like
you as a person at your desk and you as
a person outside of that. Whereas we try
to think of people as one person. It
wasn't like let's have a communitydriven
strategy. It was just we need to listen
to our users and we need to build a
product that's going to be really useful
for them and they know what their
problems are more than we do and we need
to spend time with them and and fix
their problems.
[Applause]
Hi, I'm Claire. Uh, I'm the director of
brand marketing here at Figma. I was
also the first marketer and yeah, I've
been here since the beginning. So,
coming up on 9 years of Figma. So, it's
been it's really fun for me to see
everything come together today.
My name is Cory. I'm designer advocate
here at Figma. Um, I'm based in Tokyo
and I've been here at Figma for about 2
years and been a longtime Figma user in
community. As a designer advocate, I'm
part of our community team. My role is a
mixture of helping build community but
while also helping enable um designers.
So um could you give us an overview of
your career um before joining Figma?
Sure. Uh it's kind of funny. It's hard
to remember a time before Figma because
I've been here for uh 9 years. I was at
another startup before that called
Climate Corporation and Index Ventures
was one of the investors in uh Climate
Corp. and we got acquired and you know I
kind of knew a big company wasn't for me
and I I really wanted to roll up my
sleeves and and do something early
stage. So Danny Rhyr who is was the lead
investor over at the last company I was
at uh also invested was the first seed
investor for Dylan. So um I was meeting
a bunch of different startups and
different companies and uh Danny
introduced me to Dylan and I met Dylan
and kind of just decided that that was
it and that's that's you know went from
there. When I started at Figma, we were
pretty launched. So, there was there
wasn't even a product. There wasn't a
company, you know, there wasn't even a
name, honestly. We were going to name it
something else at the beginning. So, I I
think back to just how much we've grown
and evolved over the past 9 years and
where we are today. And it really blows
my mind. It's just so amazing to see the
excitement. I just got emotional
watching all the people come in and just
how many people how many how much Figma
means to so many people and how many
people love it and use it every day.
It's just a surreal moment for me to see
everything come together. What was the
first thing that you did after you
joined Figma? Literal first thing I did.
So the first day that I joined Figma, I
remember I was sitting in a presentation
and Dylan was kind of walking me through
stuff, showing the product, also showing
me where to like the bathroom was like
all of the basics that you get on your
first day. And uh I saw one presentation
where they were going through some of
the branding for Figma and some of the
different naming and how they were
thinking about launching it. And the
name of the tool at the time was
actually called Summit. And so um Figma
was always the name of the company, but
we had the strategy at the time where
the tool would be called Summit and like
the Figma editor. And then the company
would be called Figma. And I remember I
thought to myself like this just isn't
going to work. Like uh nobody knows who
we are. Summit is just like a really
basic name. There's PCs named Summit.
There's apps named Summit. This isn't
anything we can own. And so I remember
saying just kind of off the cuff like,
"Hey, like how locked is this? Is this
something we can change?" And Dylan was
like, "Yeah, what do you think?" And and
I was like, "Well, I I really think we
should probably only have one name. We
can't really have two." Um, and he's
like, "Well, well, how about you think
about that more and make a presentation
and and maybe can show everybody it and
then we can talk about it." And I said,
"Okay, cool. Like what does what does
the timeline look like for that?" And he
said, "How about tomorrow?" And I was
like, "Okay." And so uh I remember the
literal first thing I did on my first
day was um make a presentation about how
the product should be called Figma and
not Summit. And that was the first thing
I did. When Figma first launched people
saying especially among designers like
there are a lot of people liking the
product but also saying oh if this is
the future of design then I would quit
design or like this is not the future I
want as a designer. So, as a first
marketer at uh Figma, like what were
your like go to market strategy or like
how did you deal with these market
response? You know, I think it's really
interesting because as a marketer
working online and collaboratively, it's
it's just intuitive to me, right? Like
was used to using Google Docs, was used
to just having Google Slides, a sauna,
these things where you just have things
constantly updated and working really
collaboratively. But it didn't really
click for me until I saw the response.
Honestly, that, you know, before design
didn't really work that way. People were
used to working in these offline tools
and sharing when they're done and doing
these like beautiful presentations and
showing kind of more of a finished
product. Um, and so yeah, there was a
lot of questioning uh of that in the
early days. I think that there's a
couple things that I keep in mind when I
think of like how to approach something
like that. The first is, you know, you
have to have a level of confidence that
you're going to keep going anyway,
right? Like there's some people who
don't like it. There's different
adoption curves and it's okay. Not
everyone likes your product right away.
So this just having a general confidence
in that and a belief that that's the way
to go and that's the vision and we're
going to stick with it is very
important. And then I think the other
thing that we did that was really really
helpful was we really looked at design
is an interesting space where uh you
know people really learn from each other
and so people are always looking to
other influencers or other people to
help understand you know what's the
latest in design how do you work how
should we work so we really built a lot
of relationships and focused on building
relationships with people who had a lot
of thought in the space a lot of thought
leadership and um talked to them about
things. So even if they had a negative
reaction at first or weren't sure about
something we were doing, we just engaged
in conversation and talked about it and
uh you know over time heard their
opinions, we shared our opinions, got
feedback from them and that was a a
really important thing where maybe
initially people had concerns but as we
built trust with them, built
credibility, uh people started using the
tool that was really important and they
changed their minds. I'm also curious
like Corey your response when you first
got to know Figma but as a designer
didn't didn't you have any like mixed
feelings towards the product or as a
designer like what were your thoughts on
the product as a designer at the time I
was using Figma this was probably like
2016 2017 like a lot of different design
tools were coming out like when every
week seemed like there was different
design tool like and I was you know
using one tool as my main tool but like
I would be using another tool beta
testing it like on the side and like
recreating the design like every week
and testing you know, these AB testing,
these design choices to see like which
one is the is going to be the best one,
which one I just I switched to and like
through that whole process, like one of
them I found like Figma and I was using
Figma and I I picked it up for a bit and
I was like, "Okay, this is web- based.
This is kind of interesting, but like it
doesn't make much difference compared to
like what I'm using now, right?" And
then um I went back to it for some
reason again to use it and I started
thinking about the collaboration
features, right? I was just like, "Wait,
wait, you can just Oh, it's web- based.
You can just share a link. I don't have
to like export this and every single
time it's my final final final final
version. Send that again and then I you
know I could just share that and it's
always up to date and thinking about
like the repercussions of that of like
how that would change the way interact
uh and just reduce the friction I think
was just a big thing I think about a lot
of time uh in the process. So I was like
oh well to realize the value that I
actually have to do use this tool with
somebody else. So that the first thing I
did was okay let me find some other
people on my team that I can get to get
in the tool and let's use it together.
And then once I did that, they
understood it. I understood it. I was
like, "Okay, this is a game changer."
You know, once you start using it
together, you just realize it's like
it's completely different experience.
And I think that was when it was
clicked. And then I realized that and
then I was like, "Oh, I need to get my
whole team on this. I need to get
everyone in this and get everyone in the
file." Before I was like going to
introduce my team to it. There was
actually an issue with like Japanese
input. Um, and you know, back in the
day, like I you still have it today in
the bottom like right corner of Figma,
there's a little question mark right
there. And if you push that you can have
like you can send a message right to the
help desk and get support on that.
Right? So I was using Figma and when you
input the Japanese characters it
wouldn't show up correctly. Japanese was
basically broken in Pigma at the time. I
was like oh this is great but like I'm
in Japan and like I'm I'm designing in
Japanese so I can't use this on my team
until this is fixed, right? I was like
uh maybe I'll just try to send some
support and see what happens, you know?
So I I told him I I sent some
screenshots. I sent a detailed request
and I said, "Hey, you know, this thing
is broken here. and if you could fix
this, this would really be helpful for
your Japanese users, right? And then
couple weeks go by and I pick it up
again and it's fixed. And I was like,
wow, this is pretty nice. I was I was
like, the tool is pretty cool, but I was
like, what was really really cool was
it's like, oh, I gave this feedback and
then they fix that. But also, I know
that like they're accepting feedback
from the community and the speed of that
iteration is is something that it gives
me confidence that um so I think like
changing tools is like an investment for
the whole team. That was kind of me
weighing the option. I was just like,
"Okay, I'm really kind of investing in
this team and I'm going to tell my team
we should use this this product." So,
you joined Figma before the product
launch. How did you approach marketing
marketing a product that was still in
self mode? So, I was the first marketing
hire, but I was also the first just go
to market person. In the beginning, when
we didn't have a product, I would go
around and drive around PaloAlto, San
Francisco with Dylan, and we would just
pitch Figma to differenti. We made a
bunch of connections in different design
teams and we would just go there and we
we'd show them the product. And so a lot
of what I did in the early days was meet
these people, gather their feedback,
kind of like what Corey was saying and
in that more of a one-on-one setting and
hear what they thought about the tool.
And then uh we were really trying to
understand okay when are we ready to go
at it stealth then launch la la la la la
la la la la la la la la la la la la la
la la launch the product and so a lot of
what I was doing was trying to
understand you know our teams ready to
adopt this and is the the tool good
enough to launch. I think it's such a
balance that you have to think about
where it's like, okay, we want to get
out of self and want to get in this this
people's hands, but if it's not good
enough, then it's also like, well, we're
going to lose our chance. You only get
one shot to launch. And like, what were
some of the factors that made that
decision? Yeah, it's hard, right? It's
such a a hard question for people
because you really do only get one
chance to launch the product and you
want to do it right and so you want it
to be good when people are all going in
and looking at the tool. You want them
to have a good experience. So that's on
one hand, but then on the other hand,
you don't want to wait too long, right?
Because the tool, the team had already
been building the tool for years before
I got there. You want to keep things
going. You want to start building with
people and getting their feedback. And
so it is a really hard balance. It's
definitely more of an art than a science
in terms of, you know, when to launch.
And I remember I was sitting in this
meeting and someone literally took the
laptop out of Dylan's hands because they
wanted to play with it. I don't think
that they didn't mean to like didn't
take a laptop, but they were just like,
"That's so cool. I have to try it." And
I think once they saw people starting to
do that, that was like, "Okay, this is
this feels like it's kind of ready." One
of the biggest challenges that we had in
terms of deciding when to launch was
multiplayer wasn't actually done when we
launched Figma. It just was going to
take like another year for for
multiplayer to be done. And so that was
a really hard decision at the time where
it was like this is our most important
feature arguably and we know it's going
to take another year before it's done.
And the decision that we had to make
was, you know, do we launch without
multiplayer or do we wait another year?
And we decided just to go for it and to
launch and to start getting feedback,
start getting in people's hands, keep it
in beta even though we knew it wasn't
finished. But that is such a hard
challenge, right? Like I think there'd
be a lot of good arguments on why you
should wait uh for the the core feature
to be done, but it definitely becomes
kind of more of an art than a science at
that point in terms of making that
decision cuz you also just got to keep
the momentum up too. Metrics are so
important, but I feel like you can't
really look at them that closely when
you're in a micro setting like that. You
kind of have to go on anecdotes, right?
Like we didn't have enough people to
like have these metrics dashboards and
be like look at the usage over time,
right? Like honestly, we were meeting
these teams and what we looked at was
like at at the beginning, can we get one
team to transfer full-time? And it
sounds so funny because it's like our
metric was like zero or one, right? It's
not like you're looking at these
dashboards. And that's why I feel like
sometimes when you're doing something
really early and you're like, I have to
10x this, I have to 100x this. I have to
thousandx this. you kind of have to go
more on intuition and more on feeling I
think and really believe that because
metrics just aren't going to get you the
answers that you're looking for. What
were your um team or your um plan or
strategy on building this community and
um how important was that at the time? I
wouldn't say in the beginnings we ever
set out to like have a communitydriven
strategy. Kind of to just take to
parallel Corey's story with what was
happening at Figma at the time. In the
early days of Figma, that little
question mark button that Cory was
talking about, uh we didn't really have
a full-time support team or it took a
while for us to do that. And so our
engineers would rotate and answer those
questions. And so it makes a lot of
sense that somebody reported a bug and
that Corey reported a bug and then one
of our engineers saw that and just fixed
it, right? Like that's just kind of what
happened. It was really all hands on
deck. And Dylan, our CEO, really
believed that we need to be as close to
the users of our product as possible.
And so even even now that like up until
a long time ago or until recently if you
joined Figma you had to start spending
time answering support questions because
he wanted people to know and understand
what the problems were and be really
close to what that looked like. So
that's been integrated and woven into
who we are since the beginning. And
along with that it's really building the
product alongside of the users of the
product. It wasn't like we thought to
ourselves like let's have a
communitydriven strategy. It was just we
need to listen to our users and we need
to build a product that's going to be
really useful for them and they know
what their problems are more than we do
and we need to spend time with them and
and fix their problems. And there's
people like Corey, like Corey was one of
those people that put it went into the
chat, but there were thousands of other
Corey's. That idea of listening to
people and then having a personal
relationship, really becoming close with
them and then having them go spread
Figma to their company, to their
communities, to where they live. That's
just what we did at scale. And so it
sounds like pretty un unscalable, right?
Oh, you have your engineers sitting
there answering support tickets, fixing
bugs, like you can't do that forever.
That doesn't scale. But actually, it
does scale because once we empowered
him, he can burn it his team. He grew a
community in Tokyo, right? Like that has
a huge amount of ramifications down the
line. Um, and so that's what that
strategy looks like when it when it does
scale, right? It's it's how those people
these people who you really build these
strong relationships with then spread
Figma for you. That's the whole crux of
a community tribute strategy. The advice
I would give is focus on a niche because
it's so hard to be too broad, especially
when you're new and you're early and you
don't have a brand yet and find out who
your users are and have somebody who
really understands them be the face of
face of what you're doing. We definitely
started with designers. you were very
focused. It had very specific niche of
designers. They wanted someone who
really understood their pain points,
what they were going through, what it
was like to design. And that's when for
me, I realized that immediately and I
was like, I don't know this. I can study
it. I can I could try and and learn my
best. I I have over the years, but at
the end of the day, I'm not a
classically trained designer. It's not
my my core expertise. And so that's when
I you know I decided I was like we have
to hire somebody who knows this really
really really well and have them be the
face of this and having them be the
people who are talking with users who
are creating content who are checking
all of our marketing um who are helping
us do things and that's that's when we
decided to have a user from the
community come join the team and that
that function has scaled. How did you um
come up with this idea of having like an
offline um community and how did that um
scale also? Totally. So in the early
days uh we did meetups and so that's
what it looked like at the beginning.
Some people were skeptics in the
beginning, right? And maybe they'd want
to go to meet other designers or they'd
show up, but we realized how valuable it
was to bring people together and to
talk. And we just saw how amazing it was
when people just learn best practices
from each other um and just learn from
being together. and we were able to
build these one relationships, we could
kind of overcome some of their concerns
or talk them out or just kind of hear
people out on why they were skeptics or
why they weren't sure and how we'd have
these conversations and it might be I
remember one u Tom was in in Seattle,
Tom, our first designer advocate was in
Seattle and he was talking to somebody
who at the time was a very big skeptic,
right? Uh and then he kept talking to
them, had these relationships, built
this relationship with them. Turns out
they were at Uber. Um, and that person
then brought Figma to Uber, right? And
we saw the power of how that process
worked and we started growing just these
people and and having these
relationships. And then we had this
thought of like, well, wait a minute,
you know, we've been going to these
different cities, these different
places. What if we brought everyone
together, right? And what what would
that look like? And it was really funny.
I remember when we first had the idea,
we're like, okay, how big should it be?
And it sounds so funny and I laugh at it
now. It was actually we thought we were
going to be at 200 people and that was
going to be the conference and we even
booked a venue for 200 people that was
the size and we launched the conference
and in the first day we had so many
registrations and people who wants to
join that we're like okay we have to
change the size of this thing because
there's no way 200 people is going to
work. Um and so expanded it and so the
first config was a thousand people. We
have all these relationships. People
have these connections online and
because of just the distributed nature
and the global nature of design, people
have been talking to each other on
Twitter for so long. But then they all
came together in person and it was just
pure magic to see these people. I
remember so many that the line the
conversation was like, "Oh, that's not
what your avatar looks like on Twitter."
Because this there's a strong community
that existed and that people were
already meeting each other and talking
that we've been doing from these
meetups, but also just from the nature
of design. designers have been talking
and learning to each other regardless of
BIGMA for so long and so bringing
everybody together in person and having
these relationships that were just
online happen in real life was just so
magical that we just knew we had to
continue like so do you have any like
advice on like building communities for
early startups? Totally. I think the
biggest thing is that sometimes in in
you know especially for us in you know
enterprise marketing or B2B marketing
you think about people as companies and
I think the biggest advice that I would
give is like people are people right and
I think you see that it can fit like
you'll see people and you'll talk to
them and you'll be chatting and then you
look at their badge and you're like oh
you work at a really big company oh that
was a company that in theory you might
want to like target for sales but that's
not how we think of it we're just like
you're just a person and you have
interest like it sounds so basic right
but like I think So often in marketing,
we we split people into like you as a
person at your desk and you as a person
outside of that, whereas we try to think
of people as one person and you can just
you're yourself all the time. And sure,
you happen to work at a company, but uh
I think it's doing these things that
don't scale and building these
relationships one-on-one like like Gory
and Gory's example and then those people
bring other people and those then that's
how word of mouth really spreads. So
Figma is beyond just a product. It seems
like it's a brand, it's a community. So,
um, what are your advice on yeah, making
a brand, you know, I think that the most
important thing is to actually start
with a product for us and that's like
what productled growth looks like,
right? And I I think that what we have
as a brand really starts with a brave
product by starting from the bottom up
and saying like, okay, first we have a
really strong product that's awesome.
We're improving it as we go. We're
listening to feedback um as we're
building it and building it with the
community. And then second, we have you
know these relationships with people and
if those people love the product,
they're spreading it to other people and
that's that's growing over time of
community of people. Then we can do it,
right? And then we can say, okay, now we
want to layer on top all these other
things like a 10,000 person conference
or like um you know all these beautiful
visuals that we have. The story of Figma
is not about ending at Figma. The story
about Figma is where does Figma get in
that person too. And in most cases, you
know, people using Figma, their story is
something like, you know, I just want to
create great products. I want to enjoy
the process and create that product
together. So, the narrative that we're
creating on the community side is often
like, how do we just enable those people
to get to where they want to go? Do you
know where the name Pigma comes from?
It's It would be great if you can
explain it to us. Yeah, it's actually it
comes from the idea of a figment of your
imagination. And the initial vision of
Fikba was uh to eliminate the gap
between imagination and reality. Like
that was that was the vision. And so
they it kind of shifted for a while
there cuz uh some people told him it was
too ambitious. And so it was make design
accessible is kind of where it went to.
But as we grow and as we continue to
evolve it, it always comes back to that
like how do you how can we get better at
as a tool helping to make eliminate that
gap um and make it so anybody can have
what they're they have ideas in their
head turn it into a product or turn it
into something that a's world