There were maybe six or seven things in
my life where I was in a very difficult
situation and I was having a very tough
time and what I did then uh led me to
being here today. I think as human
beings whenever there's a setback
whenever there is tough time there's
almost like two things we can do either
we can accept the setback we can say
okay this is terrible but then what we
do after really matters right and so I
think the most important thing is like
to suspend this belief and I think it's
really important because one of the
things that I tell people is that I am
really sitting here almost in every
critical part of my life people tried to
put me in a box and that was not the box
I wanted right like they're like oh like
you're going to stay in Turkey, you're
never going to get out of it. Then I
come to the US and like, oh, like,
you're only in this university and not
the best university. Then I go there and
they're like, you're not engineer and
you won't work at a tech company. Then I
come to a tech company, it's like, well,
you haven't been trained for this.
You'll never do it. And I do it and it's
like, well, you were not a VP and you
won't do this. And then I come to
venture capital, it's like, you can
never do venture capital because you've
never done venture capital. So I think
this is just one example of like a
setback and disappointment. Like as
founders, like they're going to tell you
it's never going to work. This idea is
horrible. it's not going to happen. And
I think at that point what you need to
do is like set everything aside and burn
the bridges and say the only way is just
basically like do whatever it takes.
Come up with a different idea like go
back. Is there some other way it could
be done? And that literally is the
difference between being successful and
making it or essentially you let other
people put you in a box, right? And like
the nice thing about it is a much harder
and it's big effort but it means that
you control your destiny, right? Like
yes, it might be horrible. It might be
even more difficult and nobody's
believing you or depressed, but just
remember that that doesn't mean that
somebody is taking charge of your
destiny. You still have control of your
destiny. And what you do with that
matters and that's why I like to say all
that setback, all that difficulty, I see
it as jet fuel. So put that jet fuel
back in the jet and like get into the
rocket and try to uh try to get to where
you're trying to go.
[Music]
Hi, thank you for having me. My name is
Iden Senkut. I'm the founder and
managing partner of Felicis, early stage
venture firm with a global mandate. We
are also very proud that so far from the
companies that we've invested early,
more than 45 of them have already
crossed and exceeded a billion dollars
in valuation, 100 exits. especially
proud that in a little less than 14
years. Our portfolio, we already have 17
IPOs, some notable portfolio companies
include companies that have gone public
and achieved a very high valuation like
Shopify and then some of the largest
private companies including Canva in
Australia, Notion uh in the US. I
believe notion was also already on the
EO channel. And then some other really
exciting companies uh some especially
focus on AI like Runway and then also
some other interesting companies like
one of our labs which is in defense and
AI. So before I started Felicia's
Ventures I was Google's first product
manager. When I started at Google, one
of the most interesting and brilliant
things we did is to launch Gmail. I
think Gmail was extremely important to
us and it really helped Google scale.
Google was just beginning to monetize.
Believe it or not, we did not have ads
yet and Larry and Sergey were vehemently
against ads because they did not think
yet how we could incorporate ads in a
very quality way into our search
results. that came while I was at Google
and a huge breakthrough where we decided
that the way to make ads as relevant was
to basically measure and rank them by
click-through rate because then we could
have confidence that as users indicate
which ads are most helpful to them the
ads could be as interesting and useful
as the search results. I I would say
there are three main lessons. One is and
this is something that I especially
learned from Larry but he was very
adamant and he always really cared about
focusing on a very few things. I used to
joke that his favorite word was no. Uh I
think 90% of the time he just said no
and then very few times he said yes. But
when he said yes, you knew that that was
something that mattered and everybody
rallied around and try to make that
possible whatever it was he was asking.
The other thing that Larry did that I
think was very interesting is he always
asked for very uncomfortable, very
difficult goals. I think that the other
message from that was you cannot build a
truly great company if you're only
striving for a 10% or 20% improvement.
We did something interesting at Google
where we essentially had a very healthy
disrespect of status quo and what we did
is often times we tried to find the
world's smartest people gave them
challenges whether they had an
experience or knowledge in this area or
not and just told them to do it. So a
good example of that I used to bike with
the lead engineer in the ads serving
team and interestingly that engineer was
not specialized in ad serving at all.
One day Sergey went to him and said,
"Oh, we decided that we're going to
build an ad server. Chad," his name was
Chad, "you're very smart. Pick five more
engineers. You have about 6 months. And
in 6 months, I want to make sure that we
have a functioning ad server." And they
did it. And I joke, they did it because
they had no idea what they were getting
into. And so they just made it happen.
And if this wasn't in any other large
company, they would have asked for
hundreds of engineers and probably said
it would take them a couple years to
build something like that.
So, one of the rules or principles that
stuck with me from my days at Google is
the 10X principle. Meaning that if you
want to be really great at something
like if you have a startup, even in an
investment firm, whatever it is that
you're doing, if you're working at a
company, starting a company, scaling a
company, it is very important that
whatever is you do has to be 10 times
better, 10 times cheaper or 10 times
faster, maybe ideally all three than the
competition, than the existing
solutions. this uh give me a sense of
the philosophy of your own mind. I mean
you have this idea of 10x I mean you you
don't simply want uh to go in some small
measurable arena of
progress. Yeah. I think you know many of
the things we just talked about are like
that where they're really non you I
almost use the economic concept of
additionality. Yeah. Which means that
you're doing something that wouldn't
happen unless you're actually doing it.
And um I think the more you can do
things like that, the bigger impact you
have.
And you know that's about doing things
that are you know people might not think
are possible. And I've been amazed the
more I learn about technology the more I
realize I don't know. And that's because
this technological
horizon the thing that you can see to do
next. The more you learn about
technology the more you learn what's
possible. you learn that the balloons
are possible because there's some
material that will work for them. So the
10x principle can also apply to the
markets that you decide to go after. I
think one of the things that we really
care when we're making investment
decisions, the number one thing is that
we try to find markets that are poised
for great growth. The markets can be
either very large or can potentially
become very large, especially if there
is great growth, if there is a critical
product. And one of the things that we
like to think most of our most
successful companies have a very broad
customer base. For instance, if you look
at Shopify powering commerce, I mean
commerce basically applies to almost
every business in the world. Adan with
payments. Any business if they want to
create revenues, they have to have
payments or some of our other companies
like recursion or cancer. I mean at the
end of the day there are certain
illnesses and diseases in the world that
unfortunately at some point might affect
either ourselves or our family members
or our friends. So, we love companies
that are doing something not just
important, but something that's
potentially applicable to almost
anywhere in the world. We can see this
as the extension of the 10X principle
because the larger the market, the
higher the potential for a company to be
successful. But one of the other things
that we really pay great attention to is
that the companies are doing something
that is so revolutionary, so incredible
that the impact coincides with the 10x
principle. It's that 10x better, 10x
faster, 10x cheaper. We tell our team
over and over again is look for that
either that the company can do it or the
company has an idea and the potential to
do
it. We really start with the market and
one of the reasons for that is I call it
is almost like a Newtonian law in
startups is that when anything else goes
against markets the markets win. So you
have to be in the right market and you
also roughly have to get the timing
right. So I think one of the ways that
we try to make our decisions better and
use mental you know conserve mental
power we are very selective in the
markets that we go after and once we
choose that I feel it's one of the most
important parts of the decision then the
secret is can you identify the founders
that can really scale I obviously am not
going to lie to you founders are
extremely important and the next most
important thing in our decision process
is essentially understanding founders
understanding people and this is an
important point because not only do we
have and this is the reason why the
teams Diversity is really important, but
one of the things that I don't think
people appreciate it in my background is
the fact that I spend a lot of time in
sales. Spend a lot of time trying to
understand people. And everybody thinks
venture capital is finance. It's all
about the numbers, but everybody's good
at numbers in venture capital. What is
more difficult and more rare is being
able to understand people and being able
to relate to people. So, I feel like
that was my superpower that really
helped me be a great investor. And we
actually went even beyond that. And one
of our operating part amazing operating
partner we brought on uh Michelle Delra
who joined us from stripe and she also
worked at stripe octa data bricks each
one of these companies were 10 billion
plus in value and she specializes in you
know people and like recruiting and
interviewing people. So, we actually
like have her often join our investment
meetings when we're evaluating founding
teams because we want her to also look
at the founding team and say what she
thinks of the team and if she thinks
that their culture or their ideas or
something about them gives us confidence
that they're going to build a truly
great and enduring company. And it's
again something that we do that's very
different and unique where people that
have these different strengths and not
necessarily part of the investment team
are leveraged before we actually make an
investment decision.
I mean, I can pick some some examples.
Look, I think one of the most impressive
ones is Shopify. Shopify was another
incredible concept. You know, Toby,
who's the founder of Shopify with his
two co-founders, actually he wanted to
do a snowboard store and realized that
there were no no great tools available
to do that. And then he basically
decided that actually a better idea was
to start a software company. He was
clearly very good at that. But he had
some really unique insights. One,
Shopify underpriced the product to make
it available. Shopify I think always
undercharged for the product because
they thought hey if people are getting
value and those businesses are scaling
they can grow with those businesses. I
think Toby also made some really great
decisions. I will mention couple for
instance from very early on even though
Shopify was very easy to use. People
were still finding Shopify and using it
through agencies and other channels. So
they went to the channel and agencies
said look we're not going to give you a
one-time fee. If somebody is using
Shopify through you and they continue
using it through you, you're going to
get lifetime commissions. So,
underpricing the product, fantastic
product, treating the channel really
well and being very creative of giving
them lifetime commissions. I think the
other aspect of it, similar to what I
experienced at Google, Toby realized
what were the most important product
aspects. So, for instance, when Shopify
launched payments, it was at a perfect
time and it really contributed the
company's stratospheric growth. So
again, the idea that hey, listen, if you
want to scale a business, there's going
to be a few really important decisions
and it's important to get it right. The
last nuance, this by the way happened
both at Google and Shopify, but both
Google and Shopify had very good
internal uh data, real-time data on how
the business ran. And for instance, like
early on Google when we were even like
50 people, we had internal dashboards
that I could see anything from which
servers are up to how many cues are
being served around the world and how
our customers doing. Every aspect of the
business is available. the information
on it was available in real time. I
think Shopify built something like that
internally as well. I always like to use
the example of F1 is one of my favorite
sports and one of the things that's
special about it is it's a sport where
everything is measured in 1/1,000 of a
second and the success is often
determined by very very tiny like minute
differences and they can do that because
they measure every aspect of everything
that's happening. One of the biggest
things that I learned for startups is
that yes, you might want to be
successful, but the only way to do that
if you know what to measure and you're
measuring it in a very comprehensive way
because that then allows you to realize
that
performance. I think there are many
factors. We will talk about personal
elements of founders but I will
reiterate I think being in the right
market is very important. So if you
choose the wrong market is very
difficult to be successful if not
impossible. So no matter what happens I
think finding the right market and
ideally getting the timing mostly right
is very important. After that I think
there are certain elements. Number one
whoever is the founder you need to be
very focused. I think early on because
you have very few people the tendency is
well the only way I can feel successful
and great as a CEO is if I'm doing like
50 things. But the reality is there are
very few things that truly is going to
make a difference in the company. and
doing 50 things or 20 things, it means
that you're not going to do each one of
them extremely well. But success in the
beginning means you have to be focused.
You have very limited resources.
Understand one or two things that matter
and absolutely do the best job in those
things. The only way you can do that is
if you're able to focus on them and do a
great job. One important thing is uh
just consistency and you know staying at
it like I'll give you an example like
one of the tough things as a startup
speed is your biggest friend. You can do
many things with a small team but
because the team is really small in the
beginning probably the progress will not
be super big. There will be like small
things but what we forget is small
things can compound to something very
big. And then the other thing that I
will say I think everybody thinks that
great companies succeed in a straight
line and they never succeed in a
straight line. So I think one of the
hardest things to do as a founder is
essentially like take setback, take
disappointment, take no, take skeptics
and then keep going, right? like you
have to like be at it. And to me like
what I always like to say is um people
that underestimate me or my team any
type of rejection any type of setback or
disappointment I call it jet fuel like
it makes you angry you know it makes you
upset creates this feeling it's like no
like we deserve better honestly how you
feel doesn't matter but what does matter
is to take that mental energy and then
say okay you know what I'm going to take
that and make things better I'm going to
do try one more time I'm going to try a
different way and that's what it takes
and sometimes it might be 10 times 20
times 30 times until you get to the
first time where it's a yes or it works
or your first customer. But it's very
important that you stay at it and you
don't give up. I think the second thing
we kind of touched on it but how
important it is to find a way to measure
success. Let's say that we have a
vision. We you know we want to be very
successful. Well like for instance if
you want to be a great successful
investment firm you need to have you
know density of success from a 100
investments you make. How many of them
are exited? how many of them become
successful companies. These are very
black and white numbers. If we say we
have a global strategy, one of the
things that I'm very proud of any stage
that we worked at, any sector we looked
at, any country we invested in, pretty
much every single area of our strategy,
we have a success. We have an IPO or an
exit. And so that basically makes it
very black and white. And when you can
measure things that specifically, it
really does help like optimize and you
know like make the business successful.
Um that's I think like super important
as well. I think the last aspect of it
is combination storytelling, combination
charm. Let me explain. I think one of
the most important jobs of a founder,
especially a CEO, is you have to be able
to get customers. You have to be able to
hire people. You have to be able to keep
scaling the company even when times are
hard. A lot of times that means that you
have to be a great storyteller because
let's be honest, if you're buying
something today, you're not buying
something just because of the product
and some future, but there is something
about that brand that appeals to you.
It's the same thing when we're joining
companies is that yes, you know, maybe
at the end it's a job, but the company's
culture and the company's vibe really
matters. How charismatic the leader is
matters. And so that's very important.
And I think something that I found in
founders and it is unfortunately not
negotiable. Like you either have to have
yourself or like maybe a co-founder
who's very good at storytelling, who's
very charismatic so that it allows you
to hire amazing people. And part of it
is also the mission. The more ambitious
the mission of the company, obviously
the more people will get excited about
it. And that comes again back to the 10X
principle is that a lot of times ideas
are ideas but some ideas are more
powerful and more scary than others. So
the bigger the idea and the bigger the
impact I think then even though it might
be difficult it's going to inspire
people and it's going to motivate them
to do something that's really hard
because at the end of the day we want
our lives to have purpose and the best
way to do that is if you're pursuing a
very challenging problem. I think I was
a horrible storyteller and how do I know
that? When I first tried to start
Felicis, I had, I think, at least 40
nos. It was very disappointing because I
thought I was telling a great story and
I was very proud of my idea and I was
very excited about what we're going to
build. And honestly, the main strategy
has always been the same. But what I
realized is that what I was trying to
talk about and what people were hearing
were not always the same. What I also
started appreciating is that it wasn't
just important what I was telling but I
needed to understand what people cared
about on the other side. And so for me a
lot of it came down to just practice. I
think I shared with my team but when we
got our first check I think the version
of our deck was like 107 which means
that we had 107 revisions to the deck
that the message was the same. The
strategy was the same but we like
iterated 107 times to tell the story 107
ways until the first person said yes. I
think the second thing is you have to be
a great student of people. I think a lot
of times we get so excited about the
ideas as founders. All we can think
about is what we love and what we are
going to do and why we think this is
going to be successful. We don't think
as much about the other people. And so
part of being a great storyteller is
know your audience. And in order to know
your audience, you need to really
understand them. Who are they? Where did
they come from? What do they like? Where
did they go to school? How how were they
brought up? And I think that matters
because it feels like the last 10% of
the details are maybe the 90% of the
value. But most people do the first 90%
but then they don't want to put the
effort into the last 10%. And the last
small details can make a very big
difference. One of the things that I'm
really proud of investment is a tough
business because what we do is
essentially like we're writing checks
but the thing that we're doing is not
something you can touch. like you can't
touch this table and say look we are
carpenters and we make great tables. The
thing that really means the world to us
is twofold. One, we feel that as our
portfolio globally becomes larger, it's
becoming more and more clear to us that
every minute, every hour of the day,
somebody in the world is interfacing,
interacting with the Felic's portfolio
company and hopefully in a good way,
right? Whether it's one of our, you
know, biotech companies like curing a
rare disease or cancer, diagnosing a
disease, it's one of our other companies
like Shopify helping somebody uh become
an entrepreneur or at the end, you know,
help process payments. uh or one of our
you know creativity company like Canva
maybe it's a kid at school and you know
they want to create something and the
first tool they use is Canva and that's
a very fantastic feeling that the way
that the world is today the way it's
going to be in the future and as the
future gets created it's Felissa's
companies that are taking the lead to
create that future and that's an
incredible feeling and then I think the
same is true uh about our limited
partners so the people that invest in
our funds basically they're all like
endowments they are health systems uh
their organizations that have kind of a
charitable cause or mission. Uh and some
of our other foundations or families
that we work with are working on freedom
of speech or you know they have like
great charitable causes like saving the
oceans and all of that. So what we feel
great is that we are not just about
financial returns but the impact of that
is going to be making the world a better
place. Partly true with our companies
but also partly through our limited
partners and our
investors. I really would like to see
technology play a bigger role in peace
whatever that may be. I mean, look, I I
think I also want technology to make us
happier because one of the things that
I'm seeing that stresses me out. I have
two kids, teenagers, and I see how much
technology is pervasive in their life.
But I am also seeing maybe compared to
my generation. This generation has a lot
more in terms of technology and wealth,
but they're more stressed and they have
more mental issues than I've ever seen.
I think it's very important that we have
to take ownership and responsibility.
the world is not just about the impact
that technology can have and the wealth
that it can create, but if it's making
us more depressed and less happy, I feel
like then we we lost the point. We
missed the point. So to me, my dream and
my hope would be that not only does
technology keep advancing, which it
will, will create more value, which it
will, but it also has a positive impact
on humanity. I'm not just saying like
cleaning up the oceans or whatever, but
we as people hopefully like my kids
generation can say, "Oh, like we are a
little bit happier and we're little bit
less stressed uh than my generation."
Uh, and that would be a great dream. If
technology can achieve that, I feel like
we're going to be in a much better
place.