every startup's biggest Advantage is
you're obviously able to move quicker a
VC might ask you it's like okay what
what do you do when Google starts doing
this honestly a lot of our advisers or
investors were telling us hey support is
going to be too crowded it's like such
an obvious idea my name is Jesse I'm one
of the co-founders here at deagon deagon
builds AI agents primarily for large
corporations on the customer support
customer experience side as a team we're
able to hit seven figures ARR in about 6
months and uh have been growing quickly
since then we're always just looking for
more customers more folks to work with
and we're growing the team as
[Music]
well I was born and raised in Boulder
Colorado I grew up doing a lot of things
like math contests science research
stuff like that and I ended up studying
computer science at Harvard I would say
I was very focused on trying to build
something and so most of the time I
spent outside of classes was towards
like learning how to build things
talking to my friends about building
things I finished College fast for a
bunch of different reasons I thought
that I had already gained what I needed
to from from college and I was excited
to just start building things and so at
Harvard there's a program that allows
you to graduate a year early pretty
easily after Harvard I started my first
company it was a very different startup
we eventually got acquired by Niantic
then decided to start this company so
specifically the problem we're solving
is a lot of these companies have very
large not that efficient operations in
terms of answering customer questions
looking up data dealing with tickets and
many of them will Outsource to large you
know bpos and things like that to have a
lot of human agents answering and so if
you're able to use some of the new
generative AI technology you're able to
automate and just improve the customer
experience by answering all of these
questions automatically looking up data
automatically doing all the sort of
things that a human agent would do every
startup's biggest Advantage is you're
obviously able to move quicker you can
kind of cater towards the customers a
lot more and make sure that you really
capture their needs a VC might ask you
it's like okay what what do you do when
Google starts doing this honestly a lot
of our advisors or investors were
telling us hey support is going to be
too crowded it's like such an obvious
idea but on the flip side that's also a
great a good thing because it allows you
to get to adoption very quickly because
our customers also see the value when
they start using it they immediately get
Roi this is what our customers are
telling us our customers are telling us
that there's need here that they're
willing to pay for a solution if it
works and so that's kind of what led us
there that's also what's made us
successful in terms of competing against
the older generation of chat Bots
because if our customers were happy with
those then they wouldn't have told us in
the first place they wouldn't have even
mentioned that hey we're willing to try
you out and so we're able to basically
capture a lot of the newer needs and a
lot of what was not possible before by
building from the ground up using
generative models a lot of older players
they will have a huge product built
already and they probably have hundreds
of customers and so when they're
shipping new features they have to build
things that kind of satisfy the average
customer they're just slower to adapt
because they have to carry along all
this product they've already built out
so I think when you're a startup like us
we've done a good job at executing and
so we we move really fast there's been a
new technology introduced right large
language models if you just think about
the more traditional chat Bots where
there's some intelligence built in but
it's it's not AI it's not generative and
if you're able to adapt faster then you
have a big Advantage when you're
competing against them I think we've
just built a better product hi I'm T
from if you are enjoying this video
you're going to like one of share before
founding EO I founded three startups one
small sof test and two failures this
experience that me to my current Vision
empowering more Founders to access their
are content and opportunity in growing a
startup I wanted to share a free
research that I would have loved to have
when I was starting out a comprehensive
guide to Startup fundraising kit
provided by hotspot one of the biggest
challenges as a Founder is when you hit
that first wall of fundraising you're
good at building what you do but
convincing investors is an entirely
different task this resource is packed
with practical strategies on finding
investors and building an investor
Outreach strategy managing the due
diligence process like a pro and my
favorite part was the financial planning
worksheet simple actionable resource to
get me started right away so be sure to
check it out download for free and take
your startup to the next round and
thanks to Hotpot for sponsoring this
video now back to the
[Music]
story when we first started we were very
open-minded uh we were not super
opinionated about like this is exactly
what we need to build we kind of just
let our customers tell us what the need
is when you're early it's it's hard to
have a very coherent strategy you're
just trying to get as many customers as
possible and so in the early days it was
just us trying everything we could to
get new customers get new introductions
things like that and with each customer
we would have the same process of going
in and really trying to understand what
they needed and what they wanted instead
of trying to push like our product
Vision on them for a lot of our early
customers vanto would be a great example
vanto was one of our first customers we
just kind of came in with the mindset of
hey you may have some issues that uh
you're dealing with and we just want to
see if we can solve them in a good way
and I think if that's your mindset then
it makes it easier because you're again
putting the customer first and like
really being customer-driven fortunately
at the time they actually did have a
very concrete situation which is around
you know having automation to answer
customer problems it's a complicated
product and so when people come in they
have a lot of questions and if you're
able to answer them well then customers
are happy and they're happy so that's
how we got started we were able to ship
a initial version very quickly they
liked it and then we tested out on on
real customers and they liked that as
well and so we just went from there for
the first 6 months we didn't build
anything that wasn't a direct request
from one of our customers and now
obviously we're slightly farther along
so we we have our own views on what
makes a good product but we still are
extremely customer first we really love
talking to our customers they give us a
lot of Direction and that's how we
approach product
building my first company low key was
very different from what we're currently
building first of all it was a consumer
company and so we didn't have pain
customers off the bat we were much more
concerned about getting users and
getting a lot of them very quickly uh
what we did was we were building
software for people that played video
games to capture their Clips edit them
share them and just you know explore
Clips in general by far it was just
being a new grad and not knowing much
about stuff I was a solar founder for
most of it I didn't really know like
what things were important to work on
what things weren't I didn't really know
how to evaluate of a good idea if an
idea was good or not every day you're
working hard but maybe you're not
working on the right thing and just you
know after few months go by it just
feels like a lot of the time was wasted
so I think that's very natural for
firsttime Founders because especially
younger ones because you don't really
have that perspective what kept me going
was more just yeah being young and
having a lot of energy and being a
little bit naive is also helpful because
you don't really have that much
perspective on how hard things are or
how hard things can be so that that was
by far the hardest part for me I think
being a consumer um exaggerated that a
bit because there is not really like
customers paying a lot of money that you
can talk to and like all right what do
you need I'll build it so that was by
far the hardest um once you start
scaling of course you know what you're
building but there's still that element
of okay you know you're at 10,000 users
how do you get to 100,000 and once
you're at 100,000 users how do you get
to a million and the answer for those
might not be the same and you have to
keep figuring out new things to try and
and things like that and then for that
company you eventually have to figure
out how do you make money so that's a
whole another phase yeah for me the
first part is definitely the hardest as
a Founder you can always overthink
things and you can always rationalize
different things but at the end of the
day it doesn't really matter you just
have to get to a point where you have
customers that really appreciate and
value what you're doing and that speaks
for itself in terms of the growth of the
business so this time around when we
were in the very early stages of
building decagon my co-founder Ashwin is
very similar background also
successfully sold the company before we
just decided hey let's not overthink it
we just want to go out there and see
what people actually want and what
they're willing to spend money on and
that just made the initial ideation
phase much easier uh and we really did
not want to spend too many cycles you
know going back and forth in that in
that stage so I think number one you
need to line up a lot of customer calls
and so you can get those from asking
your friends to introduce you asking
your investors to introduce you reaching
out cold and once you have them set up
you want to make sure the calls are very
structured and after you leave the call
you feel like you like learn something
concrete and so part of that is you know
you have an exploratory phase where
you're kind of just listening to their
problems and seeing like what could
possibly be solved and then the next
phase of the call is you're generally
talking about hypothe IAL Solutions and
then the last part of the call is super
important to get a sense of like how
much people would pay for it because
many times you could get in a
conversation where people are telling
you oh this would be super useful but at
the end you know there's no budget or
they would only be willing to pay a
decent a little amount and how much
they're willing to pay for it is the
only real metric for how useful it is to
them really and so if you're able to
have a call like that then after the
call you're like okay well we talked
about these things and I feel like this
would be really useful to them or it'll
only be kind of useful to them and once
you you've had enough of those calls um
that's like the real signal and as I
mentioned before people were telling us
at the time that customer support agents
customer experience is super crowded
it's like too obvious of an idea but
when we had a lot of these calls that's
what people were saying so it just it
means that there's a need and people
feel like there's Roi there for them to
adopt something uh I think when you're
young the biggest disadvantage is you
just don't know how things work really
um you might feel like you're very smart
or you can work really hard but you
don't really know like how you make
revenue or you don't really make know
how like companies in general so I think
the biggest thing is just uh staying
patient with that and trying to talk to
as many people as possible to get that
intuition the biggest Advantage you have
when you're younger is you just you can
put a lot of hours in and work really
hard I think for me I would just
describe the difference between you know
a lot of successful entrepreneurs that I
know and you know not so successful ones
is mainly just like intensity so I think
a lot of our friends who have built huge
companies or a lot of our advisers or
investors uh they all have intensity I
think it's impossible to build a big
company without intensity and intens
just kind of means like you know you're
always going you're always pushing you
have a very like no excuses attitude
where you just get things done and
that's what we admire about a lot of the
folks who you know help us and that's
what we want to have in our DNA as well
I don't know if we have the best
perspective to give advice on like a
global sort of AI Space level I think
for us the way we think about it is
there's like the core fundamental
players who are building new language
models and building new infrastructure
we of course sit on top of them we we
are an application we interface with our
end customers if you're building in a
space that is deep enough and it's
complex enough to have like a bunch of
features a bunch of product decisions
and a pretty just like a pretty big and
deep product no one really is going to
be able to replace your application
because you know the big players are are
building models right they're they're
not in the business of building like
customer support agents so I think
that's one piece which is what you're
building has to be deep enough and
complex enough for it to like be its own
product and be its own company and I
think there's a big Advantage when you
are the one interfacing with end
customers cuz when you're interfacing
with end customers you're the actual one
that understands their needs and this
goes back to what I've said many times
which is you have to have a good
relationship and a deep relationship
with your customers like really
understand what they need and everything
they say and everything they do gets
baked into your product you're the only
one that has that right because all the
big players and the like Googles of the
world the cloud providers like you're
building on top of them but they're
never going to have that access to the
exact customers I think if you're
building an application that that's
important uh if you're trying to make
sure that you know a big a big player
doesn't come around and just replicate
your product