So ultimately, fundamentally, I am a
hardware person. There's like screws
flowing through my blood or something in
there somewhere. My parents would
occasionally complain when I would take
stuff apart in the house, but usually I
was able to successfully put it back
together, so it ended up being okay. I
want to build the best laptop. I want to
build a laptop company. framework is a
company that builds longerlasting
consumer electronics products so that if
anything ever happens to the product,
something breaks or you just need more
out of it, more performance or more
capability, you can actually just open
it up very easily using the screwdriver
that we include in the
box, swap out a part and keep using it
for longer. growing more than double
revenue year-over-year for the last
couple of years, which is pretty unusual
for a consumer electronics startup,
especially in a pretty tough
environment. Fundamentally, the mission
is about empowering the enduser of the
product, making it clear that this is
their product, not our product. One of
the problems that I thought was most
important to solve was just how hard it
was for consumer electronics startups to
be successful. But looking across
consumer electronics across the entire
startup space, it was clear that there
were a number of companies that had
really interesting and really excellent
products but failed. Anyway, the thing I
needed to do is prove that there's a
better business model for consumer
electronics. One of the secrets to
building a successful startup is that
the CEO needs to
be in school and actually I graduated
from university in 2009. That was a
period of great economic uncertainty. it
was uh the start of a pretty heavy
recession and so actually there weren't
a lot of jobs available and there was
not a single hardware company hiring. Um
but it turned out that Apple in one of
their software organizations did have
this role open that I was able to jump
into right out of school. And so I ended
up at Apple for a little over 3 years
working on software of all things. Apple
had just released the iPhone 3GS. This
was like right still at the dawn of
smartphones becoming the default mode of
interaction and actually kind of the
default mode of computing. So I was
working on FaceTime and uh Game Kit and
Game Center which was this kind of
multiplayer games framework that Apple
was developing from a software
perspective. And mostly what that
experience taught me was that I didn't
really want to work in a company like
Apple. Um one of the challenges at Apple
is that it is a very very siloed
company. as an engineer there, it was
actually quite frustrating that I would
see all this cool hardware or see all
this cool software but have no real
ability to either influence or even
understand or speak to the people who
were building it. So I was working a
relatively normal number of hours a
week. So like say like 40 to 50 hours a
week, a normal number of hours. And I
would spend another 40 to 50 hours a
week actually tinkering on mostly VR
stuff. And this was before VR was like
actually really a thing. building these
little gadgets and tools and toys to
basically just see what was even
possible and doing it within a community
of other people who were like-minded.
And so one of the other people in that
community was probably the farthest
along in that community was someone
named Palmer Lucky who of course ended
up founding Oculus. My name is Palmer
Lucky and I'm a virtual reality
enthusiast and the designer of the Rift.
Where this all started was in my
parents' garage in Long Beach,
California. And I was interested in
stereoscopic displays. I was interested
in headmounts. And the problem was there
was nothing that gave me the experience
that I wanted, the Matrix, where I can
plug in and actually be in the game. And
I was sure that somewhere out there
there was something that I could buy.
And the reality is there's nothing. I
set out to change that with the Oculus
Rift.
And at the time that he founded Oculus
back in 2012, there was just one piece
of the headset that was missing, which
was motion tracking. And motion tracking
happened to be the one gadget that I was
personally the furthest along on. And I
had sent one of two prototypes of motion
track that I'd built to Palmer a few
months earlier just to get his thoughts
on it and see see if it would be useful
to him. And so in mid 2012, Palmer
reached out to me and asked if I wanted
a demo of this VR headset that he'd been
building up and said, "Of course, of
course I want a demo of it." And I ended
up meeting with him and the rest of the
early team, the rest of the founding
team there. And what I thought was going
to be a demo turned into a job offer.
And they said, "Uh, you have to leave
Apple and join us within a week cuz we
really need your motion tracker." And
that was just an very obvious choice for
me of like, yeah, I don't want to be at
Apple. I want to be working on this cool
stuff here. VR, let's do it. But
actually, the move from Apple to Oculus
was a bit more a bit more of a jump
because at that point, of course, Apple
was on its very rapid growth trajectory
and to leave that very rapidly growing
company and join this scrappy startup of
people trying to build VR on on its
surface seemed crazy. And I think my
parents at first were like, "Oh, are you
sure? This doesn't seem like a good
idea." Um, but I was convinced. I I knew
that that it was the right team of
people. I knew it was the right
technology space to explore at that time
and of course ended up being a good bet
to have
taken. This episode is sponsored by
ATIO, the AI native CRM for the next era
of companies. Connect your email and
ATIO instantly builds your CRM right
before your eyes with every company
contact and interaction you've ever had
enriched and organized. That's atio. And
here's what makes it even more
game-changing. You can build AI powered
automations and use its research agents
to tackle some of your most complex
business processes, freeing you to focus
on what matters most, building your
company. Join thousands of companies who
are already using Atio to power their
businesses. Visit the link in the
description to begin your 2e free trial
with Atio.
The first two years of Oculus. So from
2012 until we got acquired in 2014,
literally every month was some new
insane occurrence and insane change,
insane learning. Like the pace of
iteration that we had across those two
years, I look back on and think like how
did we even do that? A normal hardware
product, a consumer hardware product, it
takes somewhere between 12 to 24 months
to go from initial idea of like, oh,
this is a product I think I want to
build to being able to do development
cycles on it, ramp up production, and
getting it into a customer's hands. the
Oculus Rift dev kit, the first dev kit,
we went from the company forming to
getting it into customers hands I think
in six months, which is not not normal.
That's not how you build build hardware
normally. Working with devs to get all
this going. There's some really
incredible and interesting stories
around that. But that's not what this
talk is about. This talk is only about
the hardware side of the story. We
decided to take a different optimization
and optimize for getting the virtual
reality ecosystem seated as quickly as
possible for the sake of figuring out
what is VR, what works and what doesn't
work in VR. And for that we needed help
from all of you which required us to
take the risk and build a product really
really
quickly. And one of the challenging
things here, one of the the biggest like
mistakes maybe that we made is that
obviously we were a startup. We're on a
shoestring budget. We were being
incredibly efficient. We're going as
fast as we can because we knew we needed
to make progress before running out of
money basically. And as soon as we got
acquired by Facebook 2 years in, we had
effectively unlimited money and
unlimited resource and we could hire
literally as many people as we wanted
to. There were actually no limits aside
from how quickly we could physically
onboard people to how quickly we could
hire. It actually slowed us down. It
slowed us to a total halt. basically
went from iterating on a new version of
VR headsets essentially every few months
to not being able to ship another
product for about 3 years. And so we
lost the massive iteration velocity that
we had. And it meant that that
three-year bet instead of the six-month
bet had to be so perfectly right
otherwise the opportunity cost of
missing those three years would end up
destroying us. And we kind of got it a
little bit right, maybe not as right as
we needed to, but looking back on it
now, those early years in Facebook, what
we really needed to be focused on was
iteration speed, not trying to build a
big team and build a big consumer
polished product. And so that's what
brought me to then start up framework
and then build an even more incredible
team, but a very small focused team
where we have this clear mission, clear
vision, clear roadmap that we're able to
execute on.
One of the things that works really well
for us is that the market that we're
entering, the categories that we're
entering in each of our products,
they're just colossal. So for us, we
look at $200 billion notebook market and
we see massive, massive headroom to
continue to grow and succeed in this
business model that's focused on
longevity. It actually means that the
more we grow as a company, the more
market share we capture, we're actually
shrinking the size of the notebook
industry because we're going from a mode
where consumers and businesses are
defaulting to replacing a product, let's
say, every 3 to 5 years to a mode where
they're using the products for longer.
And so that's actually a win condition
for us that we're converting an industry
from one that is shorter lived to one
that's more efficient and longer lived.
And as a startup, of course, we have an
immense amount of headroom and a ceiling
that's very very far away that we can
continue to grow within. But even as we
capture more and more of that pie, that
doesn't mean that we would need to then
change our business model to go back
into that transactional model that other
companies are taking today. It means
that we've grown in an install base
that's large enough that this network
effects based re-engagementbased
business is a massive business in
itself. And of course, as a company,
we're not only limiting ourselves to
notebooks. It's that we're taking the
success that we've had with notebooks
and bringing that category by category
across this just huge consumer
electronics
industry. You're really thinking about
the audiences that you're going after.
We actually have this concept that we
call terminal audiences. this idea that
we enter a new product category and we
lock in an industrial design and a form
factor and set of features that we're
defining both the initial set of
audiences that we can win with most
efficiently but then also the terminal
audience basically the broadest furthest
away audience we think we could still
win with this product and we make sure
that we know what those bounds are when
we reach and build new products for
example a framework laptop 12 that gives
us a moment of reset of this is is a new
category. We're renting a new segment.
We have to figure out now who are our
initial audiences for this product which
actually start from the same core
audiences as our other products. But
then who are the terminal audiences? And
one thing we were deliberate on with
this new product is we made it simpler.
We made it much much lower cost and we
made it more generally appealing to
people who are not necessarily tech
enthusiasts. And so as we think about
this product, the core tech enthusiast
is still there as an initial audience,
but our terminal audience is a lot
bigger and a lot further
away. Audience expansion is definitely
the key to success in consumer startups
in general. We have a set of core
audiences that we kind of layer outwards
on top of one by one as we go. And of
course like it's easy to come up with
personas like define these discrete
personas of like DIYer and we have Linux
user and we have like IT manager and we
have environmentally conscious consumer.
We have these very clear personas. But
obviously in real life people are more
complex than that. Like everyone is some
combination of a million different
things. And so it's not that we
necessarily have this like clear set of
like layers where it's like a discrete
layer, discreet layer, discreet layer.
It's that we're slowly growing the reach
and awareness and credibility of what
we're doing as we go and then pulling in
those people whose personas match to the
things that we're delivering value or
interest around. So we took that tech
enthusiast gamer persona and the various
subpersonas within it and thought like,
okay, how do we win that audience? And
we thought they want latest and greatest
graphics. Like graphics upgradability is
huge for the audience and they just
can't get it out of a laptop. And so we
thought, okay, when we build our next
laptop form factor, the thing we should
prioritize is graphics upgradability so
we can go win that audience. And so this
goes back to fulfilling our mission. We
have this long lasting repairable
upgradeable product but doing it in a
way that also expands our audience reach
by being not just a new version of our
laptop in a different form factor but
enables this functionality that is
actually the key thing that was holding
back a specific set of consumers out
there in the world.
One of the biggest things that I've
learned actually and I've actually tried
to share with other people starting
consumer hardware startups is that
critical fundraising roadmap. And of
course, if you're building hardware,
there's typically a 2-year ramp from
coming up with the product you want to
build to being able to ship the first
version of it and collect revenue for
the first time. If you can't fund your
way to escape velocity, you're going to
fail anyway. So, what you need to do is
think through what is that path? What's
the high assurance path that you have as
a company with the product and business
model you're building and the audiences
that you're going after to reach escape
velocity? Meaning the point in time
where you're able to self-fund your own
product roadmap and your own growth. And
so one of the most important things for
consumer hardware especially because
those development timelines are so long
is to make sure that you have funding in
the loop almost this idea that you're
talking to investors very early and very
regularly to make sure that at the right
points in time when you're going to need
funding that you're going to be able to
show the right kinds of traction and the
right kinds of metrics for those
investors to see the signals that
they'll need to see to be able to put
funding into you. that even though we
have a product time horizon that's two
years away, we have a vision time
horizon that's 20 years away, that we we
look out 20 years and we see a world and
a consumer electronics industry that's
fundamentally different. That this
business model that we've adopted at
scale is just so fundamentally more
efficient than the traditional business
model and so much better as a model for
both us as a company and for the
customers buying the product that we
know it's a winning model. And so we see
that as this north star for us that we
continuously move ourselves towards as
we go down this road
map. The key lesson is don't give up.
That resiliency is the single most
important trait and you're going to have
to pull rabbits out of hats over and
over again in a startup. And as long as
you are still willing to reach your hand
into the hat and find another rabbit,
you should keep going.
[Music]