well if it isn't that time of
year and all the things that we did we
going to from the island to Madrid we
had a lot of plans but they all what's
up guys welcome back to sternol little
Christmas today we got a gingerbread
house kit and we're going to do a little
no baking needed a no baking need it put
the [ __ ] cone
away put it down
how' you fail to break it I don't know
it was a moment of weakness damn okay
anyway welcome back to 30 Christmas
today we have gingerbread house kits and
we're going to do something we've never
seen before I'm a little terrified
giving us a moment of flashback from the
last time we had a gingerbread house on
this table not good what was it not good
let's all look back at
it table it's in the air so what does he
want me to draw it frosting in the air I
can't it's in the air put it on the
table put the [ __ ] frosting in my
hand and say put the frosting here cuz
I'll be able to act on it I'm going to
bed see like the the past 10 minutes
I've been trying to tell him about this
don't [ __ ] hit me in the face man the
see the last 10 minutes I've been trying
to tell him about this little get away I
can't see I can't what is he
doing yeah did not happen not good not
good at all anyways well today I don't
know I know why we have two of these on
why they
burn oh my God why they send us burnt
ones can't catch me as fast as you can
the ginger kind of like he kind of ate
he said you can't catch me I don't know
I don't know what it
is we only need
one slime is good thank you guys we only
need one gingerbread house basically
what we're doing today is not it's not a
blind deaf mute baking video overdone
we've seen it ow mother freak
are you in sixth grade [ __ ] Square
anyways both you stop we're going toz a
minute anyways what we are going to do
instead is work together to try and make
a presentable gingerbread house for the
gingerbread man to live in yes he has he
has to live in it he has to look nice he
has to impress all the neighbors he has
to live in a nice beautiful Town correct
so we're going to work together to build
a gingerbread house but the catches
every 30 seconds we have to swap yep so
we're going to be hyping each other up
we're going to be really working
together to build the gingerbread house
a presentable home so that he doesn't
get kicked out of his
neighborhood what are you
doing all right y' hold up who's your
daddy reveal I'm first M second Chris
you're third we can use this frosting
too no we can't cheat it's not cheating
this is like the Y 30 second timer going
ew put that [ __ ] away don't put it in
the microwave I no no no no put in the
trash we have this one yes that one's
awful this is it's what it came with
it's the gooey good stuff doesn't mean
you can't buy come on man we need as
much gooey good stuff as we can
get on your mark get set go go better
get that icing yeah oh my good gracious
Nick relax Nick if you actually ruin it
in the first go I'm going to be so I'm
not and he does
what are you you just ruin it in the
first 30 seconds of the fu thing you
ruin how I'm trying to make it that we
can decorate the front door nick you
literally just ruined it in 30 seconds
how you ruined it please make that's the
back of the house that's the back of the
house why 30 seconds put it you never
you're not you're not supposed to like
blast the thing with frosting off the
first go why I'm decorating it cuz it
looks ridiculous
oh he's adding a cute door though you
see what I mean he's adding an adorable
front door [ __ ] adorable back door
that's not the front that's the front of
the house you're the front of the house
your mother's the front of the house
come on Matt move I just like I wasn't I
was going to do like the decorating last
and the putting together first but Nick
just totally threw me off with the we
can change the vibe okay there we go oh
get out of my [ __ ] 30 second over
yeah in the
crack 30 seconds 30 seconds Chris to R
the damn house Nick I had to put my
hands up yeah but he has to live happy
Nick what do I do you have to put it in
there do it okay my best I'll tell you
what it's I feel like Mr Ginger couldn't
be more pissed you [ __ ] suck oh Nick
you're you're [ __ ] that's why you
don't do the [ __ ] house first just
don't decorate we'll decorate after oh
my God he broke the door I didn't break
the door oh my God he broke it he broke
it I didn't break you Dr E it wor oh
yeah of course you have to act like this
is your house 30
seconds when you want your house to be
nice you're awesome ni you're a [ __ ]
idiot no high five no I don't high five
morons high five you're an idiot okay
Love is an Open
Door Guys how do we do this 30 seconds I
just wasted my 30 seconds touch I think
that this one this one might bet the
glue we need really that's what I oh
never mind throw it out oh my God it
smells like clay yeah that's cuz it's a
mold that's actually cuz it's the good
sticky stuff that that it's expired I
can't smell thing I'm spending it smells
good that smells delicious we have to
use that one yes we have to use that I'm
spending my 30 seconds and hearing this
together come on guys what is going on
we have to get it together what's
happening right now well why is it not
sticking together
clearly I feel like the adhesive I feel
like that's the number one problem of
gingerbread house makers is that it
doesn't stick together like it's
supposed to for get out get out 30
seconds get
out we keep ending up back at the same
spot that's it don't don't don't Chris
oh wow I like it I like it wait you're
thinking you're using your head this is
really gross I like it oh no wait hurry
up you have 20 seconds how you have 25
seconds you grab that immediately 27 28
29 30 got it good good idea good idea
let's just [ __ ] stop [ __ ] around get
this house on the ground I
agree yes it's like a big buttery spread
oh just butter at all just spread it
everywhere if we get the sticky stuff
all over the bottom it'll be really easy
to get everything attached yes correct 8
I like the way you did that I like the
way you did that I like the way you did
that hold on no he has to live in this
neighborhood for the rest of his life
wrong way wrong way wrong way
Windows oh my wrong way you have
to what that oh my God that tooking way
too long what are you doing what are you
doing shut up h i Frost it all over
myself yeah me too I'm going to murder
you I love this shirt so much Chris stop
Nick hey oh my god get it off screw you
you can [ __ ] yourself can May [ __ ] this
is crazy Chris stop yeah now look at
yourself white handed and now the front
door is falling cuz you're a [ __ ]
dumb [ __ ] get off of me you weirdo get
off of me you freaking Beast wait what
if we do a drop top house that's kind of
hard no roof no roof in this [ __ ] we
need a roof on the gingerbread house he
4 seconds he doesn't live in California
he Liv in the North Pole or you [ __ ]
dumb I can't believe you've been at this
for how long you've been at this and you
don't have for gingerbread house
together yet 30 seconds 30 seconds 30
seconds CHR stop do
it stop doing that show them your
back yummy okay watch out back get off
get away you just got all over me yeah
but why is it on me yeah frosting all
over your face stop
Chris you know what Chris I think I hate
you what I'm covered and
frosted if you don't keep the [ __ ]
pattern I'm going to kill youell green
yellow
green orange part of the fall off oh
yeah let's individually wrap all these
too let's make it a big hassle [ __ ]
stupid thing wasting my
turn 30 seconds is up CH not too hard I
hate gum
drops get that we're not allowed to you
have 30 seconds you idiot ooh ooh I like
that I'm going to [ __ ] blow my face
off at this thing I'm going [ __ ] blow
my face off at this
thing are you making a door knob yes
you're ridiculous how ridiculous is that
huh comes out as [ __ ] slow as syrup
on a breakfast morning on a breakfast
morning are you dumb get out Nick ow
what the [ __ ] was that get up big blonde
Beast you hit me first yeah I didn't hit
you as hard as that nearly wo big snit
oh my
god wow oh I likeed that idea just cut
more
off no what no method of organization oh
my god oh I'm freaking out freaking out
what is that what is that what is that
what is that are you sick what else
should we do let's add some of these no
stop stop stop stop please don't Chris
please don't please don't oh no don't
tell me he throws on he's just going to
throw one oh gentle gentle nice actually
it's really cool okay time's out Nick
you got Nick you got 8 seconds my is way
too high as well yeah what is he [ __ ]
710 man plays for the Rockets I
love oh you got to do the big ball thing
the balls the balls what Big Balls those
are not big balls yeah yeah Chu him on
there woo oh my God oh my God he just
broke the whole thing I can't look take
a photo before he ruins it take a pH
before he ruins it I can't all right
guys I think we're done I can't believe
snap it into place I can't believe this
Matt come on can move I can't believe
this oh I got it I got it I got it got
it t some fillers
Nick the big reveal everyone hold on
let's let's show you guys come on over
God I thought he was going to throw
it I don't
know welcome to the
breakdown so the sides of the house are
snowy with Jingle Bells on the side
that's the other side we just took it
off so that you could see it yeah we
didn't it didn't fall off didn't fall
off it or anything we just took it off
so you could see
it back of the house here can you hold
this just a
little the back of the house you just
got a little a little button on the back
of the house I don't know what it's Ro
on the roof we got the lights we got the
lights in the snow all right Chris on
the roof we got the lights in the snow
and then the chimney gum drops and the
front how many chimneys you need and in
the front we got Santa doesn't know
which one to go
down got it and in the front we got the
front door the two sides the little
green thing on the top back why can't do
anything oh no well I'm definitely not
going to help clean that he missed me
hold on it would have been way funnier
if I got hit with it stay over
[Laughter]
there
what are you serious you ni I'm going to
take a shower cuz of how
much [ __ ] [ __ ] are you guys for
real oh let's do how he added the
[ __ ]
sprinkles are you stupid get away from
me
stop
yeah I'll wipe your
ass I think I'm going to start to take a
more violent approach turn around M show
them your
back do I have anything on me
no dude thank you guys for watching
thank you so much and Merry Christmas
get ready for the next video on our hope
you're enjoying the December Christmas
content
bye miss me and all the things that we
did we said we going to travel from the
islands to Madrid we had a lot of plans
but the all this why because of some but
it's okay cuz I'm moving different don't
be saying nothing when I'm post with
other [ __ ] for my brothers