Hi Sharks. My name's Kimmy and I'm from
Oceanside, California. I'm the intuitive
baker extraordinaire behind Doughnut.
I'm seeking 100,000 for 10% equity in my
company. Sharks. We all know Americans
struggle with salt, fat, and sugar
addiction. But eating a sugar-free,
gluten-free, and or dairyfree diet can
often feel like you're eating dry
cardboard with high calories and an
unappealing aftertaste. That's why I
took on the challenge to create a
healthy version from a guilty pleasure.
Say hello to doughnut.
This might look like it's full of sugar
or ingredients that we can't pronounce.
But what if I told you that this
contains no dairy, no gluten, less than
one gram of sugar found naturally in
sweet potatoes, and you can count the
ingredients with one hand. Let me
sweeten the deal for you. It's only 90
calories. The magic behind doughnut is
in organic gats, which are oats in its
original purest form. Once the farmers
harvest the oats, they are tested for
gluten, packed, and shipped to my little
pink store where I mill it into fresh
oat flour. It's a farm to finger
experience.
Sharks, who's ready to partner with me
and bite into the best decision of your
life? Me me me me me me me me me me me
me me me me me me me me me me me. Little
pink store. Is it really? I think it is.
So each of you have a couple of my
donuts in front of you representing my
most popular flavors. Churro, which is
That's what I just ate. I think it is
sugarree by the way. This frosting is
all sugarree, dairy free. It smells so
good. It can't. And what do you use? Do
you use any sugar alcohols? Are you
using alulose or stevia? We use monk
fruit as the sweetener. This is great.
That chur one. Very good. This is just
90. That's right. And it has 2 g of
fiber in it. 2 g of fiber. So ingredient
wise, it's your oats, your special gats.
Mhm. Oats, sweet potatoes, egg whites.
Egg whites, monk fruit. Mhm. What's
number five? Baking powder. Baking
powder.
I've never heard of the term gross. You
like it. So like, did you come up with
that term or is that a term that's used
in Yeah, that's a term. So when when the
farmers harvest the oats, when they pull
it off the husk, that's a gat. So it has
not been touched at all. So you're
grinding the whole fiber seed. I am. The
benefit of milling it yourself is one,
you're retaining the natural oils that
are found in whole grains versus it's
sitting on a shelf. And then it also has
almost like a brown butter almost taste
to it. And I mill it fresh every
morning. Well, Kimmy, I will say
something. We get a lot of products like
this here in Shark Tank cuz people are
concerned about sugar, salt, all of
that. These actually don't taste like
I'm amazed. No, they taste really good.
How are you distributing them? Yes. So,
I have a little pink store. I actually
Of course you have a pink store. Look at
how cute that is. Super cute. That's the
little pink
store. Yes. So, I I sell at my little
pink store and I actually just turned 2
years old. So, how much does it cost you
to make these doughnuts? And what do you
sell them for? It cost me between.70 and
80ent to make it. Okay. And we retail it
at the store for $3.50. Too cheap. You
know, for a solution like this, I think
$4.99 works. I could eat half one of
these for dessert. That's 45 calories
without any spiking. That's fantastic.
The question is, how to scale this
business? How many can you make if this
thing blows up online? So, right now, I
do all the baking. I do all the
marketing. I do all the selling. I do
all everything
how you going to scale it. But that's
why I'm here, Mr. Wonderful. So that I
can scale it hopefully. Do you ship them
frozen? So I don't. I ship them fresh
and then I put a little note card to
refrigerator freeze right away. And are
you shipping to other bakeries or other
businesses? So when I first started, I
went from gym to gym uh selling my
doughnuts. And as a matter of fact, this
is a full circle moment for me because
my very first popup event, I sat at my
table next to this most beautiful table
that had some gorgeous jewelry on it.
And I walked over to introduce myself to
the gal and she said, "This is Kendra
Scott jewelry. I love it." And she went
on to tell the story about how you
started in your spare bedroom with $500
and that you went from boutique to
boutique. And at that moment, I dared to
dream. Oh, I dared to dream that it was
possible to have big dreams. Now here I
am, and I just feel like things happen
for a reason. They absolutely do. I
mean, what an amazing story. And you
should dream big. You were destined to
be next to our little table that day. I
love that. But you're a single operator,
Kimmy. You're coming in here for 100
grand and investors want to see returns
and you're not worth a million bucks
yet. The pro listen the product you know
you don't even know our number we don't
know it's just wonderful. Let me tell
you my total sales have been 350,000
since the beginning of time from 2021.
What about this year lifetime? Yeah. For
sales this year are $50,000.
Okay. That's not a lot of of sales,
Kimmy, to be honest with you. From my
point of view, the product's
spectacular. I will become a customer,
but you're not worth a million bucks
right now. I don't see doing this deal
cuz there's no plan for me to get a
return. But I'll be be a customer. Oh,
Mr. Wonderful. But we could do wonderful
things for you. I know, but I don't need
a job as a chef. I'm already a chef. I'm
the chef, Mr. Wonderful. I just need
your money. No, listen. It's It's a
great product without a business plan.
That's what it is. You just have a great
product. That's a great place to start
because this is actually a good product
and and I never say that unless it's
true. It's a very good product. I'm
sorry, but I'm out. Kimmy, I um I like I
like it, but this is not my type of
business. I think there's some more
qualified sharks up here with better
experience in that area. So, uh I wish
you luck. Uh I'm out. Thank you, Damon.
Do you see like part of your plan is to
open more Little Pink stores? Like, is
that part of the dream? Oh, absolutely.
Well, listen, Kimmy. I had one store in
Austin, Texas, and I could have never
dreamt that today I would have 138. So,
I love your dare to dream because it is
possible. It is possible with a great
product and dedication to it. You're
doing all those things. I'm sitting here
and I'm I'm struggling. One, I love you
and I I look at you and I see so much uh
similarity going into a market that is,
you know, a very big market. You have
that tenacity. You have that passion. I
can see it. I can feel it from sitting
here with you. And the product is
really, really good. I'm just This is
not something that I'm as familiar with.
I don't sell into grocery stores, right?
I don't think that I'm the right
investor to help you expand the way you
need to expand. And for that reason, I'm
out. Kimmy, do you have any debt or any
like other crazy stuff we should know
about? I have 70,000 in debt. Okay. 70K.
Anything else? No. No. I actually have
invested every last penny. I mortgaged
my house and the rest I I just So you're
still living in the same house says
before Mark says more to you, I just
want to say something. Okay, this is
completely my cup of tea. Like I am your
customer. I haven't eaten a donut from a
normal store in 20 years. Like I don't
eat donuts. Um no offense doughnut
community, but I just don't eat I don't
eat donuts. This is not a donut. And
this is not a donut. This is delicious.
I love that it's all healthy
ingredients. Like you check check check
to the moon. All the boxes that I love
and Mark loves those boxes, too. So, we
are both your perfect customer. I'll
blow these up. Blow these up for sure.
Yes. Like, we would love to make you an
offer and to blow this up a variety of
ways. So the offer is So the offer is
boom 150,000 for 30%.
So we each get 15. We give you a little
bit more cash and we'll be your biggest
advocates and your biggest salespeople
and we will make this big. Like this
needs to be everywhere.
Thank you so much. I really appreciate
that. Would you be willing to do it for
20%.
I mean, it's going to take a lot of
work, right? I'd be willing to go to
$200,000 to help you pay off your debt
to so we get the 30%.
$200,000 for 30.
I love it. I'm so happy for you. Let's
go, Kimmy. Let's go. Happy for you. Oh,
so good. Oh my gosh. Thank you so much.
I love it. It's a great
product. Love them, Mr. Wonderful. I
expect an order from you. You'll get
one. Very exciting. Congratulations.
Thank you so much. Wow. So boom. Love
it.