hey guys what's going on the first thing
you're going to notice about this video
is Nick is in a different seat and
that's because you're about to have a
Monumental crash out if you had to sit
back there to today it wasn't going to
be a Monumental crash out I just get so
annoyed because we used to film in a
minivan that had a row of three back
there y or no the original original
original van OG OG was two seats but it
was far enough back and cushioned nice
and I was like I was comfortable I was
comfortable and I always feel like in in
our original when I look back I'm like
how the [ __ ] am I stationary in a car
but moving so much like I like I feel
like I had so much room to like to
gather around and like to just [ __ ]
really Frolic and let loose and now when
I sit in the back of this car I'm like
literally on the edge of my seat the
entire time I'm like my my tailbone and
like I feel it go half halfway up my
spine I feel numb no yeah numb
num dud I seriously been back here for
literally 3 minutes and like it's ins
turn those lights on my taint like
lights on in the back don't talk about
your burning taint never say that to me
ever no ever ever my taint is burning
sounds like a sick like emo band like
taint
burners we're not like I hate that
that's a conversation that we ever I
hate it I hate it every single time we
speak and release a video I regret my
digital the only thing that I regret my
digital only time I ever regret my
digital footprint the only time I ever
that was actually really rude to say oh
my God oh my God stop talking the only
time you want to know what I've realized
I'm listening to you no you want to know
what I've realiz my ears are on I'm I'm
just going to start beeping the horn
when you guys don't listen to me that's
like that's something that I've just
realized that's a good idea that's a
really good that's something I've just
realized I've had the power for our
whole it's good and I can just start
using it now I love it it's great anyway
we went to a dinner tonight and Nick I
had the pleasure of sitting with Nick to
the right of me right can you [ __ ] off
he went through so much I no no that's
not what I was going to say oh my God I
was going to say that's not what I was
going to say like they were serving
things a for the table Vibe like it was
like no one order food like just get it
for the table and you let him speak Nick
ate that ice cream for the whole table
that's I did I did I did yeah no we were
sitting there and I was like so is what
I was going to say cancel he's still
talking cool I'm going to finish I want
you to I want you to fin they gave two
giant
bows they gave two giant bowls of french
fries and one was here one was there
stupid really you think yes like gave
him like a a full basket I feel like I
was just reaching over so Nick Nick was
one of the only people at the table that
wanted to use ketchup and they got and
it was like the glass bottle that you
really got to just and you know you know
they ask you a bunch of this is it's
it's not even real people there's this
there's this philosophy I have of
function versus aesthetic yeah and those
glass godamn hindes ketchup bottles are
purely for Aesthetics cuz people think
they're coming out with this nice fancy
little glass [ __ ] ketchup bottle
thinking they're doing something that no
one's ever [ __ ] done before but how
do you know how convenient it is to
squeeze ketchup and have it squirt out
so basically the plate the plate is on
Earth I have a glass Coke bottle I'm
trying to get the plate is on Earth and
in order to get ketchup on the plate you
got to put the the ketchup to the moon
and then go
down and Nick's doing this and for those
of you that don't know on on this
channel or and that are new uh cuz I
think the last time I talked about it
was like a year and a half ago I have a
burning passion that I hate ketchup so
much and Nick's doing it and I'm seeing
the ketchup fall from the glass hit the
table and
disperse and this this lands on my shirt
ew This lands on my shirt you can barely
even see it I was about to have the
biggest crash out of my career in that
restaurant I grabbed the napkin and I
held it there like a shield in between
me and you held it together you didn't
yell at me did you were this close to
getting a smack across the face I was
like going like this like I was beating
the [ __ ] out of the stupid glass hind
when I get those do you know what I want
to do I want to take it just smash off
my head and then just pour the ketchup
out the thought of ketchup [ __ ]
stupid
oh my God
gross what the [ __ ] was that my hair's
[ __ ] up all right Willow relax
definitely is not going to Willow smithz
I'm whipping my hair back and forth you
are smart thanks just like you Matt
always has those jokes where it's like
you just got to pause the video and
think for a second and be like ah yeah
that's good maybe only for you every
other people like that watch people
every other person that watches the
video gets it and do you want to know
what Chris was talking [ __ ] about my
eating habits and I talking sheit [ __ ]
you just said sheet didn't say that yeah
you did definitely said talk watch it
back it's on the video even even no I'm
talking even if it sounds like talking
sheet can you use your context clues
like any like for a fber of a second he
he can't no but Chris is talking [ __ ]
about my eating habits I'm sitting there
they're talking about we're bringing ice
cream to the table yes the [ __ ] you did
yes the [ __ ] you did it's not your
eating habits I said you ate a lot
tonight it's not like you're eating
habits it's a habit of which I was
eating yeah at dinner just go Chris shut
your mouth if anyone said that's an
eating habit no it's not you ate one
meal and you ate like a bowl of ice
cream tonight an eting habit is like
don't open your mouth again ni it's like
if you always ate Lefty for some eating
habit is how you're going to get your
toes cut off one by one cuz you're
drinking a bunch of fake sugar from your
Pepsi cans and you've been doing it for
six years wrong and eating habit is a a
like a habit you have every time you go
to eat like if you were like oh I have
to have like a TP tucked in napkin and
like my Coke halfway empty to start
eating that's like an eating habit
both are correct I disagree your eating
habit can be what you eat and the
environment which you put yourself to
eat in I think you're think of the word
have aat thinking like I'm a tiger in a
Lily Pond eating [ __ ] meat wrong
eating you're like eating circumstances
Tigers would never in a Lily Pond you
have no [ __ ] clue where tigers would
be not in a how many times have you seen
a tiger in the wild and how many times
have you been in a Lily Pond never but
every single time I have never to both
I've seen more tigers in my life than I
have Lily ponds and guess what the
Tigers were not even close to him they
were a zoomat correct Zoo doesn't
[ __ ] count why don't they have
lilypop if they oh you don't even know
what a Lily Pond would look like a pond
full of [ __ ] LLY dumb ass it's a lily
pad no it's not you stop talking back
there while we were at this dinner too I
was we were with a bunch of I still have
something to say by the way when we get
back there all you talking about is
tigers and lily pads and you're like I
was saying my eating habits but then you
started to interrupt me cuz you're a
[ __ ] idiot and I was saying don't
call me a [ __ ] idiot idot you're a
[ __ ] idiot oh trust me I don't
[ __ ] I don't I don't think for a
second me idiot go stop squeezing your
hand so tight it's freaking me out looks
like you're like trying to choke
somebody that's not how you choke
seriously I been see if it go they come
over talking all this talk about ice
cream that they're bringing for dessert
like and it says on the menu what ice
cream they're bringing they come over
with three I see your ugly face they
bring over three big scoops of ice cream
in three separate dishes a table of like
eight people I look at everyone side to
side no action not seeing action I said
let's to somebody else let's try this
tried it yeah wasn't loving it I said
man let me see that one I ate I the ice
cream I didn't like because it was in
front of me I ate probably half of and
then I I was like swap them out didn't
like swap them out I didn't really like
it is crazy no I didn't really like I
just ate it anyway can you stop can you
stop I'll eat [ __ ] H [ __ ] if I'm
hungry doesn't matter if I like it I ate
half of it I didn't love it it was all
right I didn't dislike it okay that's
where you're I didn't order this I
didn't order all this I I ordered a cob
salad that's Nick's Vibe okay well
anyways moving the [ __ ] on
I I I asked Matt to swap out the ice
creams I ate the whole thing in a matter
of like [ __ ] like I'm looking none of
the ice creams on the tables are touched
everyone's sitting prim and proper my
ice cream scoop and a half gone tanked
melting falling out of the tin I'm like
that was [ __ ] amazing I literally
took one bite of it I ate it and then I
went to get another bite that's not how
fast and I look over at Nick and it was
like all over his face this is all lies
obviously you wish a piece of that and
then a unicorn bursted through the room
and [ __ ]
you you're stup wouldn't you love that
you wish huh that's your dream that's
your dream your dream what I was going
to say is Matt always thinks I'm [ __ ]
around when I'm I'm talking about like
the matte girls are going to love this
Matt put these earrings in the other day
and he's wearing them right now and I
complimented Matt like 10 times and I
think we finally found Matt's best pair
of earrings in my opinion these like
thin cuz these are usually the earrings
I wear but Matt had these hoops and they
were really big so he's like Nick I'm
not going to wear those you can wear
them then I put these in and I like
these for me and these are like kind of
like similar to my old ones and I love
them for you thank you so much cuz I
really ging me up the day these the most
ever gotten in my life these are a good
vibe for you I think Matt girls do you
like the earring shift we were at the
that dinner right and um stop I had a
weird yeah
Chris like stop I had a weird moment
where I looked around and everybody was
like joking around and laughing and had
like cups of
alcohol no I looked around the I looked
around the whole room and I went I'm
really not a kid anymore wow I just
looked at everybody and I was like this
is what I do now yeah I was like I go to
these dinners and talk to people I don't
I don't go to the playground and mess
around anymore and I don't go to and I
don't go to the baseball park night you
know play Let's Play just a moment I I
almost got hit by a kite the other day
walking down the street a little kid
flying a kite through the wind poorly
yeah yeah it was a [ __ ] I mean for
you to get hit by it air missile coming
down I'm like I'm literally walking and
I see the kite soaring through the sky
through the not windy enough to fly a
[ __ ] kite just it's like almost it
gave me the energy it was in the I'm
going to talk right so it gave me the
the it gave me the vibe likeone like go
fly a kite and he actually went it was
not not the time or place I'm walking
down a sidewalk when I see if I look up
and I see a k a kite in the sky first
thought is I'm at a beach yeah so I look
I see kind I look down I'm like oh I am
on the sidewalk on a normal [ __ ]
Street and it is a normal day I'm not at
the [ __ ] beach and you're flying a
kite in the neighborhood for a second
when your eyes were just up you felt the
I saw the I'm like oh I have to hear
waves crashing nearby or no nothing
nothing and then I look down how how
like fast was the wind mil he didn't
like like how many like like yeah like
how how many miles per hour I wouldn't
even know where to guess I wouldn't even
know what starts a tornado or what's a
casual Breeze I don't know the
difference yeah but like did you feel
the wind on your body Chris Chris like
was it a successful you know that the
wind is stronger up in the air too it's
not like than surface level natur are
you serious there's more space it's like
that freaks me out you do some Googling
tell me the average win mile per hour
and then I'll let you know what I feel
like I thought I thought it was got but
the kid was flying a kite and I'm like
I'm walking and I check my phone and I
pause my music cuz deep down there's an
in it's like a spidey sense I'm like I
got to be more alert for a second let me
shut this music off when you're reverse
the AAR yeah I'm like I I'm seeing
strangers about flying kites and such
let let me pause my music for a split
SEC just in case something dangerous
happens 6 to S mil per hour year round
is the average prob giv a 12 oh wow
maybe a 15 double it was windy it was a
windy okay got it can't can't speak
can't the you think he waited for that
day to fly the kite cuz it was like the
windiest day you know what I was walking
around I can bring you and ask I'll I'll
find him and I'll say hey my brother has
so many questions about the [ __ ]
miles per hour of wind like he was also
doing this for casual he's not a [ __ ]
parasal you I mean I don't think they're
really waiting for a good mile hour wind
day to bring out the [ __ ] if I was a
kid and I bought a kite I would wait for
the next good windy day to fly it okay
Chris it was a good windy day mile per
hour go ahead leave it there but the kid
flying the Kite pause my music I'm like
a little bit more alert and I pick my
head up and it's like like it's like I
literally was like if I I almost ducked
like the that I'm like chilling and I
almost had to duck like did it go from
like super high to like Missle downward
that's so C like Grand Slam like if it
was like like it was it was getting Thum
from Mario where it's like just like
shooting at you yeah literally I was
just like I color was it I don't recall
the color of the kite Chris I don't know
classic rainbow don't know yeah don't
know it was coming fast at me I thought
it was going to it was a blur was his
mom like taking like was she letting him
freely fly
it or was she I can actually answer that
yeah like I'm curious
so since it wasn't that windy but it was
relatively windy M they had some slack
built up and she was holding the kite
and he ran and then she threw the kite
and the wind took it up what was that a
trip it was kind of starting in like a
paper airplane fashion like she kind of
so they must have left a lot of slack
uhhuh promise you if we went forehead
for forehead yours is bigger promise
that a weird tiny baby head I'm not
doing I'm not doing forehead for
forehead cuz they're going to make me
bald on to which if I ever see that
again fair warning I'm blocking you
there's so many things I hate seeing on
Tik Tok me AI Dancing Yeah what is going
on enough of that freak [ __ ] for real
you're ruining my digital footb freaking
me out hate it oh my God can we talk
about the the new the new photo of me
from the Prada event yikes like this
shit's circulating like blood in a body
and I look godone awful what are we
moving this around quick for I look
terrible y'all are pumping through this
worst photo of me
ever y'all are sending this off sending
off Kites and flyers I've seen like 10
accounts tag me like unreleased photo of
Nick I'm like put that back in the vault
I look crooked now yeah [ __ ] awful
I'm like I feel disgraced to see this so
funny got to unrelease that [ __ ] holy
[ __ ] the wind was the wind speaking of
the wind not on your side that day the
wind in Italy was like holy [ __ ] another
fun story that I have to share um the
other day I had to build up the courage
to ask an Uber driver to pull over for
me to pee that's a
nightmare that's like an actual Batman
for those of you that don't know the LA
fires burnt the Pacific Coast Highway
and you need to be a resident along the
highway to take the highway currently
because they're like working on it so
like they're minimizing the amount of
cars on it I am not a resident
in that direction so I was visiting a
friend I'm ubering and my ETA is like 30
minutes and then we can't get onto the
highway so my car ride doubles and I
already had to pee when we were a half
hour away so then I'm like [ __ ] what am
I going to do and I asked the driver and
he pulled over to A Whole Foods parking
lot we go to the back of the Whole Foods
together in the produce take an elevator
up both pee take an elevator back down
back to his car and then he drives me to
where I'm going that's insane then
doesn't end there I'm like what azy day
I inconvenienced the [ __ ] out of this
guy never seeing you again cuz I'm
probably your worst
nightmare calling Uber to go into the
space camp office today same guy picks
me up and goes oh I drove you to Malibu
the other day I was expecting to hear
like he's like I'm coming back to
[ __ ] kill you cuz you inconvenienced
the [ __ ] out of me the other day wow he
was chill never gotten a double backtack
Uber in my life I felt so unsettled the
whole car ride I'm like oh he's going to
get revenge guy now that's your boy yeah
no it was terrifying that's insane it
was crazy I bought these
sunglasses I hate when you do this okay
so um my heart just stopped or skipped a
beat cuz you [ __ ] pile drobe into me
stop doing that are you [ __ ] stupid
no I'm not you're annoying every time I
try to tell you a story you what is this
called I need a new one bro my sternum
no that's your ball not scrotum wrong
thing my sternums broke
[ __ ] freak slap it on my
sternum if I was choking that would have
knocked the [ __ ] right back out of my
throat I would have been saved thank you
get your [ __ ] foot away from me every
time I talk every time okay
ah every time I talk to Nick he makes
these wacky ugly faces which is just so
gross to look at and it makes me laugh
Chris what do you think you do I don't
want to hear anything you have to say
Matt the one time you speak up and it's
against Chris okay um I bought these
sunglasses and I put them in a bag and I
left the whole bag in an Uber once gone
stolen forever $3,000 sunglasses yeah we
remember when Chris lost the bag yeah
yeah I re-bought the
sunglasses same exact pair and left
those in an Uber the other day so I
would have lost the same sunglasses
twice I feel like that's fate it's like
oh I probably look hideous in these if
no I look great no how many times so
then no I'm not saying you look bad if I
lost an article oh I don't know where
this is and then like 10 minutes later
stupid voice and you walk
CH so then I called to Uber such a kind
lady and she came back to her house and
dropped them off for me and I gave her
$150 sweet angel sometimes when I'm
asleep and my alarm goes off I think to
myself thank God for that alarm because
if that alarm didn't go off I would have
never woken up ever I would have been
dead straight coma correct yeah they
would have to put that thing from do you
ever
oh I'm so dead serious for this I'm so
beyond dead serious with this do you
ever wake up and you're like you have to
check in for SPL second like who the
[ __ ] am I like never in my life I wake
up and I have to like reset to realizing
I'm a alive being I woke me like I'm I
feel like the man every day I wake up
like that song by what's his name Alo
black you can tell everybody I'm the man
I'm the man I'm the man this is what I
do I I I play a song yeah walk into my
room start brushing my teeth as fast as
I can cuz I I I hate I hate how long of
an activity brushing my teeth is going
faster does oh not doing that iy I try
to that doesn't make your your teeth
like corre I know that that's why I
don't go fast I brush my teeth as fast
as I can like getting to the sink I you
want get but do you like speed up the
brushing process no that's the same
that's the same what just shut off
this no it's on it's on is it
yeah then his light no there's no light
what the [ __ ] did oh
these oh my
God Chris shut them off [ __ ] I'm going
to kill myself did our car just die [ __ ]
I'm going to kill myself try to start
the car try to start the car shut those
lights off get the off off yeah they are
off make sure they are off off guys I
think our car battery just died no
that's the first time our car battery
has ever died in a video makes
sense let's take her on the block or
something yeah I was literally about to
say that om great heavens of God wait
let's film an outro no no no no wait let
me finish my story let me finish my
story let me hurry I brush my teeth I
brush my teeth I brush my teeth I brush
my teeth and then I do everything that I
can to prep for bed while brushing my
teeth play my play a video on my TV
while brushing still get undressed while
brushing still and then get in like
pajamas and stuff and then right when
I'm done brushing my teeth and putting
my retainer in everything I wanted to do
to set up my bed is ready so that I can
just hop right in and go to bed like a
little caterpillar and an apple all
right guys we have to [ __ ] film an
outro right now we didn't really want to
but the car battery is going to die and
we need our car tomorrow so we cannot
deal with that um so we got to go I
can't believe it even just started no
I'm really scared we're going to make
sure that this is working but happy
Friday we are coming to a city near you
especially if you live in Montana yes we
did not sell a lot of Montana tickets
yet I think it's one of our only shows
for this tour that didn't sell out yet
so if you want to visit Montana if
you're from Montana and you love the
stola triplets and you want to come see
us live we are going to put on a good
show and now I'm going to be so super
extra grateful to be in Montana with the
fans that are there so make sure you get
tickets to that show cuz now that it's
not fully sold out yet I feel like I got
to go to Montana to [ __ ] prove some
[ __ ] I agree I got all my mother [ __ ]
jewelry oh that's your feeling yeah it's
a song called earned it you said
something about earnings like your stri
but we my [ __ ] jewry on we are
coming to a city near you I know we sold
out of a lot of our shows pretty quickly
but check the link in the description
down below see what city we're coming to
closest to you and try and shop for
tickets if there's tickets available I
know a lot of our shows are sold out
slight flex but if you can manage get
ready for us to unload with the YouTube
content coming my God that's
that's it
[Music]