I'm going to kick it. Don't kick it.
What the [ __ ] do you think it is? Matt.
Matt.
This other one like flying in. Oh my
god. Are they everywhere? I don't know.
What the What is your hat? A fan made
this for Matt and I stole it. Do you
think it actually has Look above me.
At the best place basically on the
entire planet here, guys. If you
couldn't see the big ass sign above us,
we're at the home of the beaver. We're
in Bucky Lane. We're going to Beaver
Ham. We're going to the Beaver Ham.
We're going to the Beaver Ham. Bies.
Bies. All right. Beaver. I hardly know
her.
All right. Basically, if you don't know
what Bies is, there's it's a local chain
to like It's a gas station where they
have a bunch of stuff and it's the best
place on [ __ ] And we're going to go
[ __ ] ham. We're going to go Buckw
Bies. It's like seeing another one of
those [ __ ] ass. It's literally like
seeing an old friend. It is like seeing
Bucky. I like to hold this. Do you think
we've been to this Bucky before? Guys,
let's thumbnail. Let's thumbnail. You
ready?
Where? Nick. Nick, what are you doing?
We lost Nick already. What are you
doing? What are you getting? A [ __ ]
Buckyy's coloring book. Oh my god. Oh my
god. It's a good one, too. That's
stupid. That's stupid. Can you please
When me and Bucky can only be the same
color.
When music are coloring in this and
you're not allowed to take a page and
you're upset about it, you're going to
be jealous.
Guys, we got to try. We got to get a
bunch of crazy things to try. Banana.
That Buffy's Buff Buffy's Buffy's duffel
bag is the coolest thing ever. Wait,
should we try to spend like a minimum
amount of money? $100,000.
Lemon cookies.
Wa. Going to need two of these. Let's
keep going. Wait, hold on. Are we
getting any of this [ __ ]
Oh my god, the pose is nasty. My leg
hurts from standing up during the show.
So, I have to stand like this. You want
to know what a hot takeake of mine is?
All gummy [ __ ] Unless it's like very
out of the section. Unless it's like
very branded to be a different flavor
gummy all taste the same. It's all
[ __ ] awful. That's what it is. Any
nuts? Any dark chocolate banana? I
really like banana taffy. That's dark
chocolate espresso beans. I think we
should fill one of these with the [ __ ]
is this? I think we should fill this
with Cheetos.
That's really good. No, it smells good.
It just hit me hard. Love is in the air.
[Music]
Smells like Bucky. Smells like Bucky.
Banana pudding.
Okay. Okay. It can't be that bad.
It's good, Chris. That is awful.
Smells like fermented Fruity Pebbles.
Smells like good. Smells like Fruity
Pebbles and ass. Smells like [ __ ]
legit funeral. That's awful. Wait.
Signature scent.
[Music]
Dude, what's Buckyy's signature scent?
Turn me into a horse.
Dude. Okay, done. Enough. Done. Put this
back. Put this back. That actually
smells like Do you remember when we used
to drink the soda at Granny's house?
This one? Yeah. Vince, you know exactly.
You're going to smell it and know
exactly.
Dude, you know exactly what I'm talking
about.
God, that's like smelling salt. Matt, do
you know Do you know? No. Mac. Matt.
Matt. Matt. Snip this [ __ ] Mac. Nick.
Just Dude. Oh my god.
Smells good.
Do you know the soda at Grammyy's house?
Yeah. That's the vibe it gave me. It's
really good. Nick, open that [ __ ] like
it was O'Hare Air. Literally got blasted
in the face.
What are you doing, dude? Chris, to make
Tik Toks, a Buckyy's phone holder.
Stupid. No, you don't need it. We don't
need it. We don't need everything, guys.
I I kind of want a slush. I really want
a pinina colada
slush. Oh my
god. Dude, last time we were here, they
had a flavor called Bomb Diggity and
Coke. So, they have downgraded on the
slushy flavors. I'll tell you that.
There's no Bomb Diggity. I can't do T.
What the [ __ ] is that? It's called Bomb
Diggity. It's got to be good.
Oh, that was fun. All right, let's go.
Matt. Matt, my [ __ ] slurpee is in
there. Finish rattling my slurpee. You
You don't want me to rattle your
slurpee?
Yeah. Do you want to say hi to our vlog?
Hey, vlog. Oh my god. Is this going to
Is this going to be on? Yeah, it's on.
But I don't know. It was going in the
video. No, y'all just gave me nervous.
Why? I like I noticed y'all, but like I
was like, we saw you and we walked in.
We said, "Oh, there's boys." And I said,
"Do I look cute?" And I said, "Do I look
cute?" And I was like, "Oh, this boy
with a good style." Cuz you know, I like
the baggie fit. Yes. Thank you. And then
I got a crochet hat. Yeah, that's that's
a fan gift. That's a That's a dope hat.
Thank you.
Oh, he's getting all the angles. Wait,
hold up. Hold up. Wait. I wasn't on
camera. Wait. Sorry. On the camera.
Sorry, y'all. Sorry, y'all. Sorry. Okay.
Ready? Ready?
Nick didn't even see the cup holder.
Dude, look at that. Right here, M. Back
here. Back here. Look at back. That is
getting some That is some serious like
like perfect usage. Guys, I really think
I want that Bucky. What are you waving
at now? What do you think came first?
The Target cart or the red B cart?
Target. Who robbed who? I really wanted
Buckyy's duffel bag. If Bucky were to
walk in here and say, "Shoot and kill
someone for me." I'd do it. I'd say
whatever Bucky wants, Bucky gets.
Whatever Bucky wants, Bucky gets Bucky
gets. What if Bucky
[Laughter]
Bucky comes up to me with those buck
teeth. Whatever your wish is, I grant
it. Dude, you are actually Okay, let's
go. What do you guys want? Oh my god.
Let's start getting [ __ ]
Let's go. And let's go. Come on. Let's
stop just throwing [ __ ] in there. We'll
make decisions. I don't want to. I love
that freaking dude. You look like Peter
Pan. I am Peter Pan. I'm literally
shopping with a
Fortnite. Y'all are mad funny.
Thank you. Let's go. All right.
Go this way. Go. Yo, Matt, there is
nothing left that way. Matt, what are
you getting? He's like convinced he's
going to buy something, but he won't
pick [ __ ] off the shelf. I'm getting
peach strings are probably not Matt. Yo,
it's [ __ ] 3:00 a.m. Can we do like
Can we move? I honestly don't want
these. Matt, Bucky demands you to be
here. What Bucky wants, Bucky gets.
Have to get Bucky flavored things for
the video. Dude, the whole video is
going down. Chili lime peanuts. Hey
guys, I'm so sorry to come back. Okay,
you're good. But can y'all say hi to her
twin sister? Hi.
How are you? She's 6 weeks pregnant. Oh
my god.
That's amazing. Good luck. Over there.
Just one. Now, how much fudge do you
think would kill me?
That's what I need. You can get fudge
over 5 lbs. And this we're only on the
first stop. I could get a lot of fudge.
It could last me a good while. All
right. Let's go get What's the Are you
going to get an assortment or are you
going to just go peanut butter all the
way? Peanut butter is the go from top to
bottom. Here. Here.
Well, let me What?
Now that I'm here. Really?
Hi. We're good. Hi. Can I help you?
We're going to get a lot of fudge. The
fudge isn't going to attack you, dude.
Four peanut butter. Four peanut butter.
Are you going to ask them? Yeah. Six.
Yeah. Eight.
No, cuz look. Eight. It's a lot. Six is
enough. Okay. Just don't give me the
rest. Oh my god. Peanut butter
chocolate. No. That's nasty [ __ ] Okay.
That's No, that's not my favorite. There
you go. Okay. Six. I think we're going
to get I'm gonna go check on the pull
pork sandwiches. Yeah. Yeah. I think
we're going to get like six squares of
the peanut butter fudge.
Yes. All the same.
Making this ridiculous hat is like
seven. I don't know what sandwich I need
to get, but I'm going to go make some
decisions shortly. We'll all go.
Buckyy's overbite. Chris has an
overbite. Excuse me. Can I please get a
picture of How's your night? Good. Oh,
guys, I watch.
[Music]
What? I don't know.
Oh, you got the sandwiches.
You ate the sandwiches. What do you
want?
One, two.
Feel good about that. I love it here.
You look sick, dude. You're freaking me
out. This [ __ ] looks so fire. Can you
help me? Yeah.
Nick, I thought you grabbed it. Wait,
why would I grab it? I said help. Hey,
Bucky. Smile with those big punch teeth.
Good boy. Oh, photo and photo. Yes. Good
boy to Buckyy's like crazy right there.
Let's see photo. Say Bucky.
Oh my god. Full split. You got this.
[Music]
Yes. Look at this. I almost just pulled
a hamstring.
Only thing I'm not buying Baky's lip
balm. No, not getting my money,
Nick. All right. Oh, I just Why? I tried
to flip off public. They don't know what
I'm doing. Okay. Okay, Matt. Dude, we
don't need this [ __ ] I'm going to buy
I'm going to buy a bunch of Bies baby
clothes, and when I have a kid, they're
going to only be wearing That's the
weirdest [ __ ] I've ever heard in my
life. Did you just hear that? Missed it.
Unfortunately,
he's only exclusively letting his kid
wear Buckyy's merch when he has a baby
and I'm going to buy it all right now.
That dude, that baby would probably
smell like pull pork forever. All right.
Best thing ever. Are you not getting
anything over here? No. What do you want
to try? A B waffle maker. There's a B
pillow pet. I'm good. There's something
This isn't going to entertain some
people. No. Let's go, bro. Come on. Oh
my god. What are we [ __ ] doing?
Victory. I feel great. I'm so excited to
get into this pull pork sandwich. Like,
it's nobody's business. This pull pork
sandwich is about to Thank you, Bucky.
I'll see you next time, Bucky. I love
you, Bucky. Dude, what? I'll miss you,
Bucky. Thank you so much for everything,
Bucky. I'll see you again sometime in
some ice on the ground, Bucky.
Guys, this Bucky onesie has pockets. We
didn't really get much else other than
uh what you saw.
Are the sandwiches as good as you
remember? Making love to this thing over
here. Look at that. Oh my go the B visor
over this hat. Is it like regular
standard pull pork or is it like got
some flavor to it?
It's probably good.
I'm just so tired. What? Mine's upside
down. You open it upside down, you
[ __ ] dick. Look at how easy that was.
Wait, dude.
Oh my god.
Can you stop smacking people with pull
pork sandwiches? Dude, I just want them
to see the hood. Does he have a one? Oh,
they're two. I was about to freak out.
Dude, pull pork sandwiches have like
like crawled. They've prowled their way
into the top one of my foods. Like I was
going to say like man oh man. How about
that one in Hawaii?
That one was That's unbeatable actually.
It's the best sandwich I've ever had in
my life. So good. We got so much.
Rank this one one through 10. This is in
the two slot, I think.
What? Hawaii number one. Hawaii number
one. Bies number three. What's two? Bies
number two on a good day. Yeah. This is
like a Bies. Really? What?
I don't know. The way you were looking
at that a second ago. Lowkey a B miss.
What? Are you serious? Not as good as it
could be. Nick, you were just literally
falling in love with this thing 30
seconds ago. I'm so [ __ ] tired right
now. Also. Mhm.
It is hot in this [ __ ] onesie. Wait,
I need to be in the onesie. I put the
ones on. It's like my realest fantasy
come to life. Dude, you're sick. Freaked
me out. Can you put the hood back on?
Why? I don't like looking at you without
the hood. Put it all together for me. I
wish it was a full zip so I could like
Do you have a tail? You have brown legs.
Oh my god. Hey, shake your ass. No. Come
on. You can have to do a little shake.
Oh, okay. Just sit down. Yeah. Like
boring. I'm not shaking my ass in a
Bucky onesie. So, is this technically
Bucky in a hoodie in a
shirt? Deep breath. Is this Bucky in a
hoodie? And then this is Bucky in a
Bucky
shirt on Matt. It's Bucky on Bucky in
Bucky. Hold on. What is this thing?
Fudge. The other fudge. Did she give you
a bonus? No. Mac O chocolate with peanut
butter
mixed. Need
that. Got to try this. I got to see if
this is as good as I remember it was. I
can feel my temples squeezing right now.
What? Oh, when you chew. I can't feel my
left. Oh my god. Sniff it. Sniff
it. Sniff it, Matt. Why?
No, it's really good. Doesn't matter.
It's good. Like glazed little It smells
like an amusement park, but like in a
good way. Glazed little what? Glazed
little almonds. Yep, that'll do it.
Glazed
nuts. Next type of vibe. Glazing nuts.
Dude, that's the craziest thing ever
said on her channel. I can't even
believe that.
I don't even know what to say. I feel a
little violated. I don't even know what
that would mean. I'm not trying to think
about it too
much. on fudge or no. It's like the
magic f
word. That is not the magic f word. I
can't say the magic f word.
Fudger what? Sorry.
Fudger what? Yeah. Hold on.
What was the other one you just said?
I think we should eat all the other
stuff tomorrow. Really? Yeah. Okay.
Bucky loves you guys and I love you too.
We're tired cuz we had a show today. See
you guys tomorrow. Tired.
[Music]