[Music]
I love what is up guys welcome back to
our YouTube channel um today we have a
blast from the past a big old blast from
the past I changed to gray cuz you were
wearing white and then you changed into
gray we got we took we took a walk in
the rain so I got all wet so I put a
gray shirt on guys I love you too Nick
love you so much my big friend my big
brother when I say big I mean like
you're my big brother not like in size
you're actually my big brother you know
that and it just happens to conveniently
work in multiple ways basically we went
down a rabbit hole of watching some of
our older videos mhm and just
reminiscing you know feeling the
Nostalgia really no I just like I was I
love watching the old like videos of me
Matt and Nick like doing our challenges
and whatnot but cuz it's like actually
mindboggling like we were just watching
it like literally on our TV minutes ago
and I was like I cannot believe that I
sound the way I sound I look the way I
look cuz I remember being in that
situation but I don't remember talking
and or looking all it's crazy to look at
all that type of stuff cuz us blurring
out the word [ __ ]
yeah like we censored the word [ __ ] in
our video no it's just crazy to me cuz
it's like it's crazy cuz you see how
much you are different but in so many
different ways the same little but in so
many different ways how similar enough
of the [ __ ] Sab story today we're
moving back with that Blast from the
Past yeah we got a big old blast from
the past and we're going to um we're
going to refil guess that triplet from
the zoomed in picture challenge part
three the first two being like some of
the first two being some of the earli
videos of our YouTube career yeah we
used to do punishments in our challenge
which I think is so creative and we
stopped doing for yeah we're going to do
punishments again for this one loser
gets an embarrassing photo of them
posted on top of all the embarrassing
photos of them gets shown throughout the
video awesome deal deal set
go that's a lot of money oh my God is it
a lot of money I think it's you yep
that's the photo oh you're cash at bro
makes sense one point wait Matt you
didn't get that nicked
who just got that I got it 100% of that
question on camera hold on I said Chris
but Matt hit the button before me and
never took a gas so I hit the button and
gas no I think it was Nick okay Matt hit
the button
[Music]
went I just gave I just gave Nick the
point Matt Chris that's Chris 100%
that's Chris ready for the answer Matt
yes I knew it you're the only fool who
covered your face fully like that like
who are you hiding from I have no idea I
got
very I got it that actually y set go
that's me that's maybe me that's baby me
that's baby me those beautiful pearly
teeth okay dude oh I was the cutest cute
what a little critter I was cutest Nick
I'm three right now crazy that's me
that's me that's you yeah doing what
what looks like you're playing the
clarinet I played the clarinet that's
why oh party streamer best day of my
life yeah that was one of my favorite
days oh my goodness Chris so who got
that Nick I missed me yeah yeah
yes that was at our 19th birthday in
Palm Springs what a time one of the best
days in my life go that's that's you
that's 100% you that is Chris yeah oh
it's me and Matt physics God yep fetus
first point let's go literal baby
fetuses me 100% that's neck
yeah you were getting your hair
die damn I won both of our OG ones
that's Nick that's
Matt don't tell me that's me yeah I knew
KN knew like
Dobby elf all right I look like a
[ __ ] folk a Family Folk tail that's
Chris you that's you I said it first OG
musically profile photo yeah I I busted
out that one wow who got that Nick me
sadly Ready Set that's me that's Nick
that's Nick that's Nick that's Nick
that's Nick Nick I don't know if you're
going to want want this one the
[Laughter]
internet I look like the Tomato from
[ __ ] V T Veggie Tales that
[ __ ] is going to tell you a
veggie tail straight to your
face oh my God a v tail holy [ __ ] okay
my last one are you guys ready that's
you that's Nick that's Nick that's Nick
that's Nick I said it first I I said it
first I said it first I said it first I
said me before he said said I think that
I said me before he said Nick I said it
we'll have to instant replay it but
there it is I said that
first said that first absolutely I who
who got that first I definitely got that
first I think I did we're going to have
to instant replay that
one all right Nick do you want to go or
should I go I'll go okay we're doing
business with
you Matt that's me that's Chris Nick
yes wow Nick you're not like a tank top
guy no he's not though y Get Wrecked
this is the next one's really flat
flattering that's Chris mad that's Chris
that's you that's you oh it's me what
the [ __ ] sound asleep like a little baby
I hate when I don't know myself it
reallys it's it's a hard thing to I hate
that we like look this much alike you
know I me well like I mean it zoomed in
it's like
yeah that's you that's OG Nick for sure
Pez head of the PE fact that was your
first like Premiere ever yeah
that's Matt that's Chris that's Matt you
can tell it's like gorgeous like is that
me yeah that's you Matt not on the
zoomed out photo yeah like that's just
such like a magnificent matte
photo magnificent matte oh this one's
not as hard as I thought it was now that
I'm looking at it it's so obvious
whatever that's me all day
yeah it was way too
obvious I'm killing you kid I know I won
the first two
Matt's shoulder that's your shoulder
your kneecap you it's Nick's shoulder in
color yeah oh I hated though I did ex
I'm never shirtless so it's like I have
to throw like my shoulder in there you
know what I mean see but you are the
only one that would take a selfie like
that in the beach yeah that high
up that's that's a me foot right there
that is Matt I should have known about
[ __ ] sock wow your bed that's crazy
your room was empty kid Matt you got
that point yeah damn you you wear weird
socks that's like a weird sock those
socks ready really weird
sock those are my hands oh yeah that's a
nervous mat Moment Like This notice how
you haven't said someone oh Nick what
Chris Chris it's
Chris
Grandma yes yes I love grandma me too I
miss you Grandma that's a nervous mad
hand is like the craziest it like this
like you were scared yeah it did look
like a ner nervous M hand that's why I
did it so like throw you guys off you
guys literally were standing there not
guessing me for like 10 minutes to be
fair I did say that's a me hand
immediately okay this one is
crazy I don't even is I'm going to go
with me I'm going to go with me I'm
going to go with
Nick oh my God that's the that's the
monster from a Chet place he like runs
in like that oh my God if that was in
like black and white that'd be like one
of those like unsettling moments on Tik
Tok that you see [ __ ] God you got
that right Chris yeah yeah that one was
crazy that's my thumb that's my thumb
that's my thumb I don't know who said
that first but you're right I did I
did nice okay that was my last
one you obviously you y I need to move
faster get out of here every time
there's a hat you guys just want to put
me so bad
me you it's Mt it's me I see a nose ring
[ __ ] yeah than God thank God I
thought I wasn't sure [ __ ]
idiot dude while I'm waiting for him to
show the next time I'm going to rip this
table wow only one way to find out you
me Nick it's Nick 100% me that's no it's
you it's you it's Matt the ring the
silver nails it's Matt that's I think
it's me it's Matt
yes
RI my skin off I guess you first and
then I guess Nick cuz he guessed
himself me
Matt it is
Matt
yes you're just guessing to guess you
need to actually I thought that that was
me didn't am I going too fast okay Nick
just sucks he's guessing too
quick me Matt mat mat Matt 100% me it is
me it is me it is me no it's 100% me I
have the same stain on my Shir sure it's
me right Nick you can't just keep
hitting it like you're doing the same
[ __ ] you did two years ago where you
click the button and you go Nick Matt
Chris like obviously no I don't I knew
that was me I have that you literally
went me no Matt like right away and I
was right with the first one no I think
if you guess it and then guess another
person you should be like voided out
till I guess cuz that's just ridic once
you take one guess you have to count to
like one two and then hit it again well
you're just ridiculous but go ahead you
me that's me and Peter that's me and
Peter it's me and Peter it's me and
Peter it's Nick and Peter [ __ ]
idiot you're going too quick you're just
wrong how about that you're you're just
stupid you me me it's me of course it's
Chris with that little crab ass finger
you look like a little lobster with
holding that gummy bear like a baby
let's see yeah it's me okay that's an
iconic photo in the St iconic shut
up all right no there's some sto moment
that are just classic you know you
ready Chris me [ __ ] and you lost and
you're losing fck it's so obvious when
it's
me yeah it's easy to find ugly oh got
him Nick good job yes Nick Chris Nick
it's Chris Nick it's Chris and I think
Nick said that first no I did no didn't
he said no you didn't no you didn't I
should have known cuz the [ __ ] damn
stupid your legs are always skinnier the
Nike Bigg legs the Nike socks I always
wear Nike socks your legs are like Twigs
in there the converse is such a throw
off I never wear my Converse
[Music]
ready Matt I said it first Matt Matt
Matt mat Chris
Matt
[ __ ] I so it's me that was my frat bro
ever and you're
wrong [ __ ] I suck at this [ __ ] would you
guys like to play two more just for fun
yeah sure little bonus
rounds me e me I know that's my toe I
only have this is
the this is the other picture and it has
like the white border and everything I
don't know how or why I took it oh my
God is that my foot yeah Nick my toes
are like curling or like I'm a falcon
going to eat its prey literally I look
like a bird escaping a nest that's
bad M you OG you that's you yes I love
MTH photo that's my favorite MTH photo
of all time y oh classic A Memory Lane
we took a stroll down and you fell face
first
[ __ ] you're insane you're insane that's
it oh that was so fun so now you guys
did you guys feel the oess I felt the
Bost just insus Theus Jus C oh my God I
hope I didn't feel
Theus that was a lot to feel the oenus
like
that oh overbearing oenus that's why I'm
going to clickbait this video do not
click if you can't handle overbearing
amounts of
oenus okay me over all right no I just
felt like the Boston inside of me I felt
it don't say that I hate people like I
miss the Boston triplets it's like what
a terrible like way to say you missed
the past we still go all the time that's
where I'm still from all right miss the
Boston tripet what you want me to go
[ __ ] remake the Tea Party dump tea
into the harbor for you next vog St TR
is going back to Boston dumping key in
the harbor no yeah I feel like every
time we do go back to Boston now it's
like we we're not we're just not posting
as much cuz I'm like enjoying being with
my family my friends I never get to see
I agree but yeah it's still classic you
know I'll start posting more there if
you guys want me too I agree but yeah
we're also like if we do implement the
new schedule soon which we keep yapping
about and yapping and yapping and
yapping hopefully that means that we're
going to get um more time to go to
Boston and more Vlogs back in Boston and
more videos back home as well I want you
guys to know as our
viewers that nothing ever forces us to
come to La we always just want to be
here we have our own house here and
we've become independent here we really
don't have to be here um but besides our
podcast cuz the studio is in our house
but for like merch and all this other
stuff we really don't have to be here
yeah we just like like anywhere I just
want you guys to know wherever we are we
choose to be there whether that's on
tour whether that's on vacation whether
that's in Boston whether that's in La
it's like no one's choice but M Matt and
Chris is to go and I'm just excited cuz
I feel like 2024 is going to be a year
of travel where every time you guys
click on the Vlog we're going to
obviously mostly be in LA but I want you
to like click on it be like oh my God
where are they like I want to just
travel more so that we have more more
more under our belt mhm cheers to doing
new things in
2024 and cheers to still having fun
filming videos as us three that was so
much fun that was I love this video
concept it's just all right guys thank
you guys so much for watching this
week's Wednesday video we will see you
next week on Friday Wednesday Monday
Friday Wednesday Monday Friday Wednesday
Monday until that changes yeah until
that changes which who knows when
that'll be but we're super grateful that
you guys stick here and watch our videos
go make sure you go check out my
Instagram that you can see the
embarrassing photo I post of either one
of them depending on how the score rolls
out and make sure that you are
subscribed because you never want to
miss a video and like this video if you
liked it we're on the road to 6 million
subscribers so come join be a part of
the family oh my God
family Nick get out
of um but yeah I'm leaving the
family if you joined the family it's
just Nick
yeah
[Music]