are you
ready what's up guys so loud okay what's
up
guys hey guys what's up welcome back to
our YouTube channel today bringing it
back to OG YouTube we're doing like
gummy food versus real food this was a
this was a YouTube video like this is
the YouTube that raised us this is what
YouTube this is one of YouTube's
foundations really what it's all about
honestly this is what I this is what we
would watch when we were like eight and
You' be like what G be food versus Real
Food what
first up first up and this is Gummy mac
and
[Music]
cheese they look like those cheese puffs
they look like cheese curbs you know
what I'm talking about Chris you have
forks no can you get Fork salt is it a
do you guys spoon or Fork your Mac and
Cheese I fork cuz you can put the I fork
it I [ __ ] I
fork okay wow I did L see this is why I
like the fork it's your fork I mean yeah
I've been eating this since I was 12
you're not going to get much of a
reaction out of me hold on it's not
going anywh it's so good wow
[Applause]
neon
ooh wait I hope it's not like cheesy oh
wow it's it smells like the crabby
patties craby patties I don't think I'm
going to sniff that actually sniff it
okay such a baby wait hold on can we all
do it at the same time our warm cheesy
macaroni fills your belly and feeds your
soul all right ready set go that's smell
good Ready Set Go
it tastes nothing like macaroni which is
great that's a good decision it tastes
like it tastes like the crabby the
crabby patty bun mhm like when you take
the or like the gummy food where you
take the bun out of the hot dog and then
you eat the you know eat the dog this my
favorite meal yeah like I'd eat the rest
of these me too um you can't really
compare the two I'd say they're both 10
out of 10 that's a 10 out of 10 gummy
this is a 10 out of 10 meal I agree
shout out moving on but if if we're
ranking the gummy to taste the closest
to real food this is at the bottom cuz
this tastes nothing like mac and cheese
I agree guess how much this was 16 bucks
I just saw
16 that's wrong did I spend all that
were you guys you guys weren't sitting
like this last night were you yeah we
were anyway it's time for breakfast this
doesn't feel right today we're starting
off with breakfast so we have the gummy
breakfast we're starting off with
scrambled eggs scrambled Sizzlers look
it it has weird instructions it says
Place sizzling candy powder into the Pan
place your gummy egg in the pan squirt
candy gel on top and enjoy I'm not
putting candy gel on top yes come on we
have to enjoy it exactly how prompted to
oh my God it's candy ketchup
Matt fine so Pop Rocks okay Pop Rocks I
can get down with that place egg in pan
how do I get this egg out just hit it
like a smack
oh the Yol is separate oh my God you
hear it sizzling wait can I get kind
that's kind of creative e maybe not
touch the whole thing I hate that it's
like
detached this whole thing looks a little
gnarly wait I almost just fell should we
do real egg first
yes no I can't get any egg on my Fork
dude you're in such a race to eat I know
it's like sick it looks like you're
starving like it looks you don't eat
it's cuz I'm actually
hungry I like eggs I cooked those like
beautifully yeah you did all right mid I
know what an egg tastes
[Music]
like okay this is my goal we're going to
go we're going to go as you would put it
in there into the mouth like I'm going
to
go egg okay yeah yeah
ah
oh it's not gummy that egg that gummy
egg is too wet yes that's the problem
that is the exact problem it's not gummy
the sizzling candy powder was delicious
I would have IE this [ __ ] tastes just
like something I don't like I didn't
have that that was awful the egg was
like just very like gar
like very like wet it's like it tastes
like you're eating a slug yes exactly
like it it feels like you're eating like
nothing I didn't even I couldn't even
swallow it all right all right next up
for Gummy breakfast we have bacon bacon
and I'm I'm excited for this cuz on the
bottom it says fruit flavored gummies so
it's not so it's not bacon it's not
going to taste like meaty gummies you
know look at how perfect I cooked all
three pieces of this bacon feed could we
like really admire this yeah that's
really good bacon
oh that crunch is even
satisfying that's some really good bacon
crust
really oh it's like a little party of
fairies dancing on my
tongue mat do you have the fairy party
in your mouth yeah you do it scares me
like what
it sorry way to go oh wait I kind of
like it's like um yeah stop don't say
that and do that motion please stop
liling it around Nick he oh I kind of
like it I do it's like very like do we
each get a stick or do we or do we
separate one three times I think we're
can to each bite one okay h no let's do
that I'm not doing that you do the turn
with him do that with him Matt no you
don't don't waste don't
waste it's pretty good it's like a
standard gummy yeah it just tastes like
a it tastes like an it tastes like an
elongated gummy bear ow yeah like you
guys are my gummy buddies for for this
video don't call me your gummy buddy
that egg was mid the bacon is great the
egg wasn't even mid the egg was I never
need that in my mouth again correct I
agree all right moving on to the next I
just dropped all of these it's okay you
dropped all the what the little balls
the little balls that I got the gumballs
my little balls are okay we're back um
we have a gummy burger and a gummy and a
real burger and we're going to a gummy
burger and a real Burger not eating this
burger Nick claims he's not eating the
burger but he's going to have a bite for
the video no I am not yes you are I'm
not eating that Nick claims he hates
burgers all of a sudden this burger is
going to look ridiculous with a bite
taken out in four different
directions so um I think it's going to
look not taking a bite Nick I'm not
eating it yeah you are I'm not eating
this disgusting Burger I'm not I'm
really take bite right now you actually
have to by a nibble I'm so scared you
actually like have to or I'm quitting
the channel a nibble
right where I a nibble good boy swallow
chew swallow is
yummy keep going he's freaking me out
chew and swallow big boy that was worse
now the gummy Burger wait everyone rate
their burger was it good great burger I
love the
bite it's a monster there you go oh wow
oh wait so this is the bottom
bun wait and then you can't eat the
bottom bun it instantly exposes the
pickles oh so you have to eat them in
greeding at a time yeah pickle what is
this the Patty no that's pepperoni no
this is the Patty is that Patty is this
no this is like mustard and ketchup
gummy bear give me give me pickle I'll
take pickle give me a pickle
okay always take n pickle okay and
you're ripping it apart huge butt you
ready that's actually kind of
good oh Massa eating it like a burger
this makes feel sick oh look at it it's
like ripping apart there's like gummy
bear um residue on this I'm going choke
this is awful that's actually disgusting
you guys don't like it no no I like all
the ingredients you would well that
tasted like Terror no it didn't that's
awful that's like bad gummy oh no
something think the burger part is gross
it's like bad gummy food I've had good
gummy food that's bad gummy food like
hard to eat like I feel like none of
these compared to like that pack that I
always eat that like that are good are
the crabby patty ones I agree bro you
would have love the mac and cheese ones
last night dude if I like actually fully
consume I don't have trash that would
have taken like fully
a all that yeah no that was
terrible okay moving on all right guys
welcome to dinner part two tonight's
dinner is
burritos gummy burrito first okay gummy
first they already [ __ ] hate this
because the tortilla is like not an an
actual part of the gummy it's like all
the ingredients of what would be in the
taco which is [ __ ] stupid there's no
point of even doing it like this soft
gummy mix it should come with like a
fruit roll up that you roll into a
burrito maybe what bro that's kind of on
the table on the table like it's clean
it's clean it's kind of like the gr like
the lamest one then this is like lime
yeah this is not even a burrito this is
lame the beans are really good what's
the white cream in the in the cylinder
sour cream
so I think it's I think it's
tortilla all right real burritos does it
not tell
you y very
good [ __ ] this thing yeah this is
[ __ ] stupid I'll eat the beans though
you can put the beans those aren't
beans I just spit everywhere they are
[Music]
beans we're trying a gummy popsicle
that's been in our house for almost a
year it expires in like a month yeah we
were going to filmed this video last
year and we didn't Matt why don't you
get in the frame of the video I I
thought that I why get away from
me maybe chill get it out oh wait turn
around and drop your
pants thank you ready Nick stay still oh
my
God oh my God it's wait get it out get
your
bite ew bite why is it so like tough
stop wait dude I'm I like I have to take
a bite out of this too stop like you're
can you Nick stop I did it to you once
and I didn't do it on your clothes you
can wash off your skin I have to [ __ ]
wash the shirt when I'm chewing gummy
shirt I feel like I'm chewing cement no
this was actually bad gummy gummy g u m
m y there was no Y in there like it
smells like the school you need to go
away oh delici the big idea oh my God I
love these things so much don't be
licking at like that why it's a
popsicle I don't like that these are
classic I'm thinking like we really
haven't done a like a like this video
has like no
purpose can't believe I'm about to eat a
hot dog I know this whole video Nick
hasn't invented this is such a looks
like a carrot it looks like a carrot I
kind of want to smack it on you what
Nick stop eating so fast can you get out
of here I kind of rather have a plastic
fork with a hot dog you know what I mean
I'm already on the paper plate I'm like
a bun of Firework and mustard away love
hot dogs I really like that hot
dogjoy all right are we split here Nick
you can have your on I hate how much
like I hate when gummy [ __ ] is like hard
to pull apart I don't need it I don't
need it I don't need my own
yeah I think it's just the
gummy I have a cavity
awful it doesn't taste like awful awful
bad Donuts not bad oh it actually smells
really fruity bad this might be the best
one smells kind of
fruity your face is gross okay it was
like a little no it was like a little
kid face you made that's what I meant is
everyone
ready yes got it go I hate how hard it
is to eat gummy
stuff this might be one of the better
gummies from today I agree good still
tastes ravenously horrible I agree I
don't know guys are we not gumming
people eat probably a
90 oh my God Nick you just broke a
childhood Relic and it was mine and it
was mine no I think that these just
aren't the particular gummies we like
and I think because you're not buying it
fresh like when I go into CVS and I buy
a pack of gummies I know that they're
like kind of a couple days old see when
I'm who how many people are buying a
gummy dut like this had to be sitting on
the shelf for like a
month shoy and then you there's nothing
worse than chew Meck remember I said
this last time Nick just reminds me of a
donut like a n like you are a donut like
visually as a person you just are a
donut I feel oh was good I love donuts
yeah see I don't like strawberry
cream what like the strawberry cream on
top oh yeah I love the cre this guy's
oldfashioned can you stop elbowing me in
the rib cage like I get a nudge of like
Joy but like this is like an actual MMA
move a nudge of joy we appreciate it we
will see you Friday peace out peace
[Music]