welcome to the Halloween festivities
we're about to do a bunch of Halloween
[ __ ] tricks treats whatever the [ __ ]
you want to call it when we used to go
trick-or-treating as kids me and Nick
would sit in that red raag Red Wagon
Chris would sit in that one and the
candy would sit in the fourth and mom
and dad used to pull us around in Little
Red
[Music]
Wagons come
here guys we're back at the McDonald's
where it all started yeah this will
probably be the last time we ever come
here cuz Nick shut up we at the
McDonald's that me man Chris used to
film our videos at but we don't film
them here anymore cuz our privacy was
infiltrated infiltrated that's all right
all right guys for the Halloween season
I was Googling what can we do for the
festive times anyway we're getting
[ __ ] boo buckets go boys what did I
just say goys ghouls inside yes Nick up
oh no they don't have them wait no where
they don't have them cuz it's where they
don't have them on the menu idiot I
don't know what you want me to say say
do you have boo buckets ask take the
camera hello were you using them today
no can I take your order um do you guys
still have the the Halloween bucket oh
I'm devastated what do you got that's
very spooky like the what's the most
Halloweeny item Halloweeny can you
repeat that
again can we get three pumpkin spice
lattes or pumpkin spice iced coffees can
we get three of them and then can we get
one of the pumpkin like pumpkin P
yeah awful Matt did you get give me
chicken nuggets please um can I get a 20
piece chicken nugget and some sweet and
sour sauce score we saw at another
McDonald's in La that there was pumpkin
buckets for like Halloween seas are back
come get yours on yours now on the
godamn thing but it's [ __ ] whatever
there's no [ __ ] godamn boo buckets
I'm going to [ __ ] h no boo buckets is
crazy on Halloween day I'm so mad it's
October 31st change it tomorrow
fair oh wait I have a gift card to hear
Matt let me grab it he already has my C
hold on get back he already has my C
[ __ ] [ __ ] Matt I [ __ ] should have
used my my damn dude I was going to use
my gift card but Nick kept talking so I
just what what all right guys pumpkin
spice McDonald's coffee secured we got
our pumpkin pie secured we're going to
park it and try it or park the car and
try it the guy in there said happy
Halloween like when he gave us the stuff
and I almost shed it here I just
something about people doing the bare
minimum will always get to me no it's
not the bare minimum it's just no it is
the bare minimum just say happy
Halloween on Halloween but it's still
it's not the bare minimum cuz people
don't even do that [ __ ] nowaday not even
saying if you guys look at that scenery
right there hold on that bench the light
well let's try these stupid McDonald's
pumpkin catastrophes don't say don't
call it stupid McDonald catastroph I
just don't like pumpkin [ __ ] like what I
love pumpkin I was just praying on a boo
bucket and I get this [ __ ] this [ __ ]
actually looks pretty good I can't lie
it's just coffee I don't like when it's
like not mixed up mix it up a little you
know I love it yeah it tastes like
sin you going to have mine sin is crazy
really listen it's not bad I just don't
like coffee I hate coffee like why
didn't I just get a Pepsi I was shocked
you didn't ask me to get you a soda yeah
whatever I I'll get one soon tonight for
Halloween while there's a bunch of
hooligans out I want
to what you like a chunk of what's at
the bottom yeah yeah I knew that was
going to happen that's why I never put
no that was just shocking cuz it tasted
nothing like anything in here woo okay
I'm good we have this little pumpkin pie
oh it smells delicious and it's kind of
warm still I feel like it makes sense
for you to be the first one to try this
I I feel like it makes sense if I don't
try it yeah I agree what it smells like
Trevor hold on sniff it it kind of does
no no get a bigger right you're just EA
cross you need to get the cream and [ __ ]
in
there it's a good bite maybe a little
more though like take a good sh
definitely not bad okay but I don't want
try it yes Matt eat what he ate o oh big
bite you ate
girl it's not bad it's just the texture
of the pumpkin wasn't what I was
expecting but it's not bad it's
definitely not good either it's not holy
[ __ ] remember that one time that her no
dad went to Dunkey donuts and that guy
got like 12 Splenda yeah leave him alone
the guy has a sweet tooth no that's some
that's some [ __ ] I would do this's like
12 Splenda it's like why get a sugar
sugar substitute if you're getting 12 of
them like let's just put sugar in there
[Music]
what
hey you're funny break dancing yeah
you're funny all right guys welcome to
part two of the St yellow tripet
Halloween extrap again we've been to
McDonald's and now we are going to carve
pumpkins isn't it crazy pumpkins just a
vegetable come on y'all we were about to
carve these but it took us forever to
find pumpkins so instead of carving a
pumpkin I had a backup watermelon but
since I bought the watermelon I kind of
want to do that instead so I'm going to
carve watermelon wow this watermelon is
not ripe what a good watermelon to
carve gross why is
this that was disgusting okay why is
this this an annual thing for us to just
carve pumpkins it's annual the world are
you dumb it's not an annual thing for us
it's an annual thing for Halloween guys
can we just break them all
noay I'm going stab myself don't stab
yourself please I can't handle that you
were to be bleeding I think I'd be the
least helpful person ever and you'd be
annoying as [ __ ] guys this is literally
disturbing wow Mt you are doing
phenomenal how are you gutting it
already how would it's say phenomenal
are you guys not gutting it no you both
didn't take the cap off I'm gutting mine
still all right I'm done there we go
guys that's my pumpkin happy Halloween
you need to do more that's what I did I
wanted to do that okay that's fine but
you have to wait for me in that oh
that's cute Nick you said [ __ ] out the
way oh my God I kind of love it you
actually did really
good guys I look it Hollow it out too
wow you did actually phenomenal man I
carved a watermelon I've never been
happier in my entire life like why don't
we do this with watermelons more often
like why is pumpkin the fruit this was
so easy pumpkin veg
okay
whatever you're a [ __ ] weirdo
freak all right guys we're done carving
our pumpkins and watermelon we're going
to hold them up and then I'm going to
post this exact moment on our Instagram
story and you guys can vote for which
all right guys sorry the camera just
died but what I was saying is we're
going to post this exact moment on our
Instagram story after we posed the
pumpkin so go vote who's is the best
Chris [ __ ] ID cheese stop it stop
Chris like he's like
Chris [ __ ] out the way Nick decided to
put sweet and sour in the [ __ ] Target
bag we got today and covered it in a
mask was him you're the goofball thrat
St sour sauce everywhere I got a mask to
make a good video on Chris just thinks
everything that's not his is the trash
and throws the [ __ ] everywhere shut up
[ __ ] you're ugly and annoying and
Relentless ugly annoying and Relentless
wow what are we doing three words I used
to describe you now say three nice
things remember oh my God oh my God
that's the camera bad idea what are you
doing bad idea uhoh Chris is going to
be not a good play at
all not a good
move it was a trick it was a
trick this is not focusing at all would
you pee yourself two-year-old you're
funny
kid just wait till I get a trick for you
Nick I'm going to get a [ __ ] rubber
boot and hang it from your door
[Music]
down welcome to part three all right I
went to Target to get some Halloween
costumes and whatnot but all they had
was Halloween mini mask cookie my shirt
ain't got no Stripes but I'll be so
official that's me I'm the referee oh
it's a cat or a witch hat the [ __ ] is
that [ __ ] I want some real [ __ ] you
guys going to do I'm going to make
that's not a witch hat it is it's like a
witch eyes nose and a hat I'm doing a
cat we can all do a cat I'm doing a
kitten yeah let's all do a cat [ __ ] the
wi Kitty I can't believe people ask like
trick or treat like no one's going to
say I can't believe I I hated going to
the houses say trick I hated going to
the houses where they made you say Trick
or Treat like I I just want to pull up
be like yo hey give me candy [ __ ] and
they'd always like I don't think give me
candy [ __ ] is going to work I wish did
more fun like Halloween Tricks and
Treats as kids than like just trick-or
treating like just trick-or-treating
isn't enough for me well I'm trying to
go to a Halloween party this year and
get hammer and smoke some weav I want to
get Absolut have you seen that photo of
CHR niolo smoking I think believe that's
real I see it like a video it's like a
person that's not you like are we
dumb oh my God I don't even want to
say where did he get
into he broke into the [ __ ] Dairy
Department of the store not good oh my
God I forgot cats actually drink
milk cute he's drinking milk drinking
milk
look so bad he drinks some milk he has a
white
smile you're you've created a monster
holy [ __ ] Yik yeah Matt when you're done
we're ready I'm actually really really
proud of myself I think I did a really
good job I don't want to ruin them so I
I I think we
should no SU on it I need that you
[ __ ] freak what are you doing want
some frosting all right guys the one
that's popping up on the screen right
now is mine and I guess I'm done no you
can keep going stupid idiot [ __ ] no
one's rushing you I feel very rushed so
it's okay no don't feel Rush why rush
you can wait forever yeah we could wait
in Eternity for you Matt I will wait
what's that song I don't know wa Chris
what's your favorite Halloween movie you
want what I've never seen before trick
or treat okay what answer treat here get
out that's a trick [ __ ] that
[ __ ] is
ugly that's a trick that hoe is ugly oh
yeah is Trick or- tree like a you're
asking which one they're about to do
like if someone says goes up to the door
and they say Trick or trick they say
Trick and like a boot Falls do you have
to announce that it's a trick or can you
just trick I feel like you have to tell
them it's a trick like right before well
they don't say treat before they hand
out the candy oh true that's a really
good point so the trick C be sneaky no
well you say trick-or treat they give
you some treats no no I think you say I
I think you saying trick-or treat is
initiates one or the other it initiates
that you're okay with either outcome yes
I you can trick or treat me right now
see what Happ I think what we should do
is get like aund tricks together and
then I love it I'm going to put each of
the cookies above our head like the ones
that we made so mine's right here matth
is right there Chris's is right there
and you guys can go over to our
Instagram and vote for those as well as
the pumpkins that we just previously
carved so we can see who's the winner
it's not really a challenge because he's
the winner of the extravagan on
Halloween I really love mine he's really
like I wanted to get that really orange
cat you know me and I had a similar Vibe
yours is so good all right talk thank
you huh show yours I already did you
didn't share the inspiration or anything
I just said that I wanted to go for an
orange cat I went the Picasso abstract
route and I wanted to have those dark
Halloween green eyes that you see and
like Scooby-Doo and stuff you know like
the
night you really spooked me with yours
yeah and I wanted to have white ears
just because like I feel like having
white ears it just means you like you
listen like they're just ears like pked
up like I got ears like I wanted to make
sure that you can really see the ears
like make sure they're listening like
they're like yeah they got the ears that
are propped up yes the black is actually
a hat like a top hat oh but the cat is
in motion so it kind of looks blurry
like that okay what's the black [ __ ]
across his whole face the the like that
is it's an actually an upside down Nike
Swoosh oh so it's like Travis Scott yeah
like he has he has Travis Scott on okay
yes and then the sprinkles is cuz he
went to like the big sprinkles like
these ones uhhuh or cuz yes those ones
is because he went to the door and got
tricked like I'm eating a [ __ ]
rock yeah here go oh my god look he's a
mummy
[Music]
now mummy cat what noises the
mmy that was good thank
you Mama mmy they definitely grunt they
definitely
grunt that's good yeah they're very
similar to zombies just wrapped up oh my
God that's what it is essentially TR why
do you get treats all year long and not
just on Halloween f f bom another one
fist bomb another one fist bomb good boy
[Music]
Chris is making us throw [ __ ] giant
bottles I'm not throwing like I'm really
afraid you want to just go to a
different parking lot we went to the
world's most open wide open parking lot
ever guys there's a mad GE [ __ ] too like
this ain't right we need to lay low guys
we're I'm I'm just afraid I hate [ __ ]
like this I don't like causing Mayhem
but it is Halloween and we have to do
some tricks we it's a Halloween we have
to make a Halloween I do the first one
right now yeah let's do one liter should
we do a little one give me give me a no
we'll do a full liter right here A whole
liter right now yeah yeah but fair fair
to say dude it's it's soda you want to
know what the equivalent is me doing
this that's the I think I've spilled my
drink in public before all right let me
do it no yeah I have a plan I hate this
close it Matt what are you doing close
it close it Matt and wow you're not
supposed to do it like that you like
angled it right
at right wow I feel it tensing up really
oh my god get away get L throw it don't
throw it don't throw it Nathan dude it
might sound like a
gun Matt you have to go get it no
littering just drop it just drop it just
drop it the only thing I'm scared of is
this guy in the truck behind yeah we
should go to a smaller parking lot just
drop it on its cap right in front of you
no no no cuz what if it what if it's the
car thr it over there it's not going to
like explode like that just drop it on
its cap Matt
you guys are awful this isn't even
fun okay put this one in the car you
guys are awful how do we do this wrong
okay go somewhere else dude get in a
[ __ ] car put that in the
trunk yeah did I even show y'all how
many Mentos I got too many like it's
unbelievable we can always have we can
buy more Diet Coke that's all I eat the
men and this a it looks gun dude it's
not going to be that loud it's loud
we're across the street from the police
station too do I do it I feel like
Tuesday you need to get away from the
car this what you have ready listen you
have to it shake shake it throw it you
got
it shake it shake it shake it shake it
shake it shake it shake it
shake
turn no what guys guys I get away don't
throw it away from the car you're going
to get me
soaked
dude like a n that was a terrible
decision I'm going to need to get a car
wash
what this is a terrible decision you
need to get away from the car Chris did
it way too close if it blows up it's
going to be so loud it's not Matt throw
it a little bit away from the car I
don't want to get wet oh he's doing it
he sucks oh and he couldn't get the lid
on mat you [ __ ] wasted it again oh
dud my do that
wasted it oh my embarrassing dump it out
and put it in the trunk it's not going
to do anything it's not going to do [ __ ]
there's no C you keep ruining it man
shaking it throw a football thr that
[ __ ] oh my it's not going to do
anything oh that was actually really
loud that's what I'm saying it's going
to be super loud okay get in the car you
[Music]
suck kissing and then what you saying
how you miss me yeah you miss me and all
the things that we did we said we going
to travel from the island to Madrid we
had a lot of plans but they
alled why because of but it's okay cuz
I'm moving don't be saying when I post
with other [ __ ] for my brothers