[Applause]
Next up is a business that's making
custom fit products more
[Music]
accessible. Hi Sharks, my name is
Matthew from Ventura, California and I'm
the founder of True Fit Customs. Now we
know it's important for sharks to keep
their teeth in their mouth. Well, it's
also important for athletes. It's why
they wear sports mouthguards. But
traditional mouthpieces are big, bulky,
and uncomfortable. They're the first
thing left behind on your way to
practice, and they almost completely
eliminate in-game communication. How do
we expect these boil and bust appliances
to fit everyone's unique dental profile?
And getting a custom fit guard from the
dentist is expensive and such a hassle.
That's why True Fit created a mouthpiece
athletes actually want to wear. Each
guard is made with the latest 3D print
and scan technology. They feature
shockwave dampering compression pads, a
sleek, slim profile, and are cut so you
can breathe and speak as clearly as I'm
talking to you now. In
fact, I'm currently wearing one. Nice.
It's no coincidence that over 1,000
professional athletes across the NFL,
NHL, PLL, NCA, and UFC choose to wear
True Fit in our game. But we don't just
make the best mouthpiece in sports.
We're on a mission to bring custom fit
to the people. And that's why we're
asking for
$750,000 for 5% of our
his mouthpiece. Where's my mouthpiece?
So Sharks, we have some samples for you.
Now Matt, when I get my grinder for
sleep, they laser my mouth to get a
perfect fit. Is that how you're doing
these? Cuz how are you going to get
custom unless you're getting the exact
fit for each mouth? It's a great
question. So that's why I asked it
actually.
So that impression kit right there is
what we use for our direct to consumer
model. So this is the gooey stuff you
stick in your mouth. So what you're
going to get at the dentist is an
algaynet impression putty. What we use
is silicone putty. It's easier to work
with, but there's a lot of these. You
have a ton of competition. It seems like
a solution to a non-existent problem
since there's so many already in place.
Like is there a reason why you think
there was a lane that wasn't being taken
by others? We have a great hold on
digital manufacturing. We specifically
know how to scale custom fit
fabrication. So when you say digital
manufacturing robot, are you talking
about 3D printers or actual robots? The
whole thing 3D printers to the uh 3D
scanning to CNC machining. We can
manufacture at such a high level because
we're almost like an assembly line. When
we're fabricating these, we're able to
do it at such high volumes cuz it's
machine to machine to machine to
machine. All this is great, but you have
a hefty valuation. And so we want to
hear about those hefty sales. Yes, sir.
We started in 2022, we did 115,000. In
2023, we did 750,000.
Wow. And then now this year, we're
expected to do 1.4 million. That ain't
worth $15 million. Now you have my
attention. And how much will you lose?
We will make money. Okay. Matt, you
understand you're asking for close to
15x sales. This is not realistic at all.
You know, Mr. Wonderful, I know that you
did your dissertation on the dental
industry. Yes, of course. And you know,
there's those three big guys in the room
that are that own the entire market, but
the legal landscape has changed over the
past years and it allowed direct to
consumer to enter this market, which is
taking market share from traditional
medical practitioners. How much does it
cost you to make and tell us how much
you're selling it for? Our direct to
consumer first-time customer is $95. It
costs us 31 including shipping. Our CAC
is $23. We do about a four times return
on ad spend. And so even with that CAC,
we have about a 40% margin on our
first-time customer. Matt, the valuation
is
insane. And it's not even like almost
reasonable. So let's negotiate it. I
just don't see it working to the
valuation. So for those reasons, I'm
out. Okay. Listen, when a guy who just
put another 3.5 billion in his pocket
said the valuation's too high, it's
really too high for me. Meaning Mark. So
with that being said, I'm out. Yeah.
Look, I'm I'm super torn on this because
on one hand, I mentor and I work with
over 100 athletes who are not only
athletes, but they're investors and they
like to get into product now. It's this
new generation of athletes and I'm a
limited partner in the Atlanta Falcons.
So, I'm into the product. Let me ask a
question. How much have you raised? Uh,
we've raised a million total. What
valuation did they put it in as 7.5
million? How many units are you going to
be able to make and ship this year? You
know, we'd probably look to do 20,000.
It's not a lot for world domination of
mouthguards.
How are you going to get millions of
customers outside of the athletes? So,
let me explain and win. So, this year we
have a team sales model that's really
budding. What we do is we provide guards
to all these teams. They seed the
players. The players love them. Then we
approach the players for an affiliate
deal. That's smart program, right? Are
you paying commission? Yeah. Yeah. We
give them percent of sale. Okay. I love
your deal. I like you. I'm having a huge
problem like everybody else about your
valuation. makes no sense at all. So,
here's an offer for you. I'll do the
$750,000. I'll drop my my equity ass
down to 3%. But you're going to pay me
two bucks a unit until I get back
$2,250,000.
I think that's a bad offer. It's going
to take me 4 years at your current rate,
but you get Mr. Wonderful. We do one
thing for you and only one. Get your CAC
way down. I got millions of followers. I
got a massive social media network. say
yes and we fall in love in the denture
business. Wow. Kevin, I will just tell
you my thought. You're doing things the
right way, but I think that your
valuation is too high. I would want to
see a lot more proof and it would take
forever to get my money back. I'm sorry.
I'm out.
Listen, I'm a venture capitalist and
there are two types of investments.
They're motorcycles and rocket ships.
So, motorcycles are common and they take
regular fuel. Rocket ships are rare.
Very few of them are made and they take
rocket fuel. VCs sell rocket fuel. So,
I'm looking for rockets. You don't have
the growth rate and the amount of
revenue as a rocket, but you have the
potential. So, you're trying to take
advantage of that. And I know why your
valuation is 15 million because someone
told you that you had to double the post
money valuation of your previous round
like every other ventureback company.
So, I get all of that. So, I want to
make you an offer.
Three sharks are out. Matthew has one
offer on the table from Kevin for his
custom mouthguard company, True Fit. But
Rashan is also interested. Just to give
you one more summary of it, 750,000 cash
areno. That's a lot of money. Yeah.
Yeah. 3% equity and two bucks a unit
till I get back
2,250,000. That's my deal. First, don't
do the royalty deal. That's a bad deal.
I would rather you take There's never a
bad deal for Mr. Wonderful. less
impossible. I'd rather you take that
money and reinvest it into growth. I
don't want you to be profitable at all.
I don't want you increasing your
expenses. I don't want anything coming
off top cuz I want you to grow that
revenue and crush all your competitors.
That's the venture way, right? So, the
first thing I want to do is I want to
offer you the
750. I want to bring in 10 to 20
athletes as brand ambassadors andor
investors. But for that, I want 10% of
the business.
The greed. The greed. I have never seen
you say no to that. I thought I was
being generous.
That sounds smart to me. Uh, would you
be interested in doing a million for 8%.
Oh, you're going the wrong direction
here, man. No, you're going the wrong
way. I just offered you things that are
worth more than a million dollars
because of my track record. I was an
early investor in Coinbase, Robin Hood,
Ring, Casper, Pill Pack, Dropbox. I'm
literally on a winning streak. So, if I
invest in this, this thing is gonna
catch fire and you're gonna raise money
and you won't have to do anything but
kick ass.
Yeah, I'm sticking to my offer, so I
need an answer. Okay, so you got two
offers.
Well, we already provide to the Falcons.
So, Rashan, I'd love to do a deal with
you. Let's go. All right. All right. All
right. Excellent.
Oh, thank you. Welcome to the family.
Congrats, Matt. Good job. Congrats.
Thank you, guys. All right. Appreciate
it.
[Music]