can you open this for me po
pop is this like cemented shot Nick
don't spill it on
yourself it's should have seal when I
get it open oh my God are you pranking
me I wish I was you can't get that open
neither could you I can do it first try
promise to God give me
it in the dead of winter you're not
allowed to have this lemonade this I
weakened it the edits are about to go
crazy that was
say I'm
in we're trying way too hard to be Nick
bro with the Chris the F get suck it off
suck it off I was going to say I was
going to say the fuzz but then I
realized it's not fun that's crazy I'm
happy you did this it's like creating a
nice little fun environment for yourself
I feel just in
case another one yeah just in case how
about a guarantee how about a 100%
certainty hold I was watching inter
practical joker clip and they had to go
up to people and start vlogging them and
recording them and then they're like
what what's this what is this for the
the other Jokers like gave them like a
title of the Vlog I was like vlogging
this lady and and then he was like oh
you'd be perfect for the Vlog she goes
what is it and Q makes him say the [ __ ]
what oh hell no
okay the there has been a viral Tik Tok
Trend boring basic we don't like posting
on Tik Tok we rather post a long for
format content YouTube video we are
taking our the hear me out cake videos
and and we're making a long form and
we're making a long form in-depth
version of that other than a one minute
stupid little TI I need that gone anyway
we don't have a cake and me and mat Matt
came up with a good idea I came up with
a good idea cuz it's all we really can
do we're all hiding a bag look we need
we needed something to stick it in and
we didn't have a cake so we're doing a
hear me out case of waters and we're
going to just stick it in the plastic
wait that's actually perfect right
there's nothing else that that's all we
can okay let's do it let's go I feel
let's go I literally was going to say I
feel the bosson or I know and I know and
I know and I know and I know that people
are going to say I I growing up growing
up being a public figure on the
internet my least favorite thing to do
if you haven't noticed in watching our
career is acknowledge my popularity or
fame I hate it I hate it my mom works in
a school my dad Works in a school I got
a big brother I got a dog like there's
no difference between me and you my best
friends work normal jobs so I hate
talking about being a YouTuber cuz it's
glamorized and I feel normal but with
all that being said I in the past in the
p in the in recent times I feel like M
Matt and Chris have always
tried to maintain and this is a random
deep yeah this is we've always tried to
maintain our roots and our Aura of
Boston bonian triplets and I feel like
I'll be the first to admit it I feel
like I've been corrupted a little bit by
like the life we live you know and I
feel like that's okay I feel like in the
past I've always been like I need to
steer away and like pretend that
nothing's changed because change is good
and this this and that but I do think
things have changed a little bit but me
and Mt Chris have learned so much about
oursel in the process and I think we're
back I feel and I'm okay with saying
that I think things have been it's I'm
not ashamed of it cuz I'm a
person oh my God cuz everyone's going to
beat her around the bush like oh your
video you're not as funny doing this
you're not as funny doing that we're
trying new things [ __ ] you seriously so
it's like I'm going back and forth I
don't give a [ __ ] if I get clocked oh
this isn't funny this you shouldn't be
doing this you shouldn't be doing that
this person is not funny I'm still
growing up I'm still becoming who I am
shut your [ __ ] there's nothing I can do
I can't I can't regain past aurura I
have to move on need to you need to take
your aura and you need to evaluate your
aura and move thank you you know what I
want he's giving me [ __ ] trash give me
these but you have to you can't move
forward with netive aura you have to
evaluate the aura you have and move
forward and I have good or this is a
classic mixer real little fit I know we
all have a lot and I want this video to
be short Snappy and fun let's get all
the obvious [ __ ] that I'm not going to
have a reaction to out of the way all
right are we ready are we ready could
leave Bey hops
of that photo is cool what is what's the
photo oh wait my bad wrong
photo J my God y'all didn't see the
first photo oh
you like it's obvious a little
Shrine this you got to show the camera
that one yeah oh they see it a lot of
mine are obvious mine's like a obvious
hear me out okay I have middle part mat
of course like come on like that's
obvious middle part mat is okay then I
can I add to this collection then I have
comfy Nick in a
h ni Matt took this photo a h Matt took
this photo of me in a hammock and I've
wanted it the entire time it's existed
and I've asked Matt for this photo and
it's his Spotify playlist cover it's his
[ __ ] like he just uses it for
everything he won't text it it's my
favorite picture of Nick now all I have
is a printed copy because we've already
started in zootopia Ni wild I feel like
I have to continue okay I didn't do Nick
wild cuz I out we know how I feel do we
have any like guesses before I reveal
the lamb little mouse mouse the New
Yorker Mouse are you serious guys that a
good one that's a good one Mrs otterton
oh like lowy she kind of bad but she got
him in bro yeah but he's
gone he went wild on him
he what did he go he went he went
Predator I think he went Predator no he
went oh we can't say that
Rogue I don't know where did he go where
did they go in that movie they go nuts
bananas I think speaking of rabbit
rabbit rabbit speaking of bananas I just
put a banana like their Aura like a
banana like a
banana no you got to hear me out that's
the whole thing is like a banana to me
wait hold on it's like a curated Vibe we
should have started in I I feel like a
person who like starts their day with a
banana an to me is like you have Aura
we'll do one for Judy and then are we
not going to regard the banana anymore
we don't like the banana Vanessa from F
and firm
obviously you just got to see beyond
that big ass forehead that Dr D look at
that Cranium on that [ __ ] like she's
thinking hard we got the
Riddler Nick that version of The Riddler
yes I'd love for him to tell me jokes
and riddles and I'll figure it all out
you know I put the
before he turns into a person of course
we can't have so the Beast is the Beast
yes okay what's the beast's name Beast
it's Beauty and the Beast Beauty and the
Beast him and The Riddler okay um him
Ridler at the same
time roxan
from A Goofy Movie hello she can go
Goofy on these
balls my guys are going to have to hear
me out on all of these these next two
are the only like semi-normal ones I got
okay I got the tasan devil okay cuz he's
always going
crazy you know you You' seen what he can
do it's going to be Nick in the
Tasmanian devil and he's going to be
like and then that's like that cartoon
smoke and then it's going to end with
the Tasmanian devil yeah yeah he's going
to stop he's going to stop like this
like and then next's going to be like
naked and you're going to have to hear
me out
are you going to say this every time yes
cuz it's I have Crazy Ones Matt so I
have to warn you
go campfire wood yes yes why just like a
good stack of campfire that's honestly
like the least hear me out I can hear
you this is the vibe I can hear you out
more on that than I can on the banana uh
Kitty Katswell from tough puppy
wa I have not seen this and you're happy
you have now right boots yeah wait who
where's tough puppy kitty kitty cats
spell tough puppy T I don't know who you
don't know tough puppy I know tough
puppy you I know tough puppy well if
this was tough puppy you'd hear I'd be
barking yeah on all fours in the back
seat uh Melody from Gravity Falls who
the [ __ ] is that Zeus's girlfriend why
is she backwards wait she's got yes she
is mad her she's got her whole head
backwards yeah like she's like literally
that's like the wa she double jointed
for sure in that shoulder yeah no
[ __ ] she throw a ball quick yeah
that's definitely something wrong with
her for sure yeah want to know who else
is bad in the Gravity Falls who when um
Dipper goes to the man cave whatever and
all those like oh manitar manitar oh my
God I'd have love to go to that cave for
a
day okay oh my God Jesse from Team
Rocket okay okay I can get behind it you
don't need to be heard out bro
yeah I got Sophia the First's mom that's
a good pick bro like come on bro she was
a girl in the village doing all right
then I became a princess overnight they
oh Matt you need to put that down it's
funny for no specific other reason other
than she's a [ __ ] she's a [ __ ] she's
hold on hold on no no no no no no no I
have a good one I have a good one I have
a no I have a good one I have a better
one I a [ __ ] better one I promise
mine's better let's go one let's go
let's go ban for ban all right let's do
it you go first we went to IHOP the
other day oh my God it's going to be
like a pancake monster yes yeah come on
it's the [ __ ] October Pancake Man on
the [ __ ] IHOP
menu you wouldn't even eat that though
no well it's really concerning you are a
sick you are a sick y'all a't Hur me out
of a nothing nothing let me try again
let me try again let me try again no
you're okay okay no no this one's good
an Edible
Arrangement okay that's like an edible
arrang now you heard me like this is
good [ __ ] chocolate cover shs we got
pineapple we got cute Shades no The
Grapes the grapes are this is like ideal
now we're in business I'll hear you all
the way out with that one thank you Nick
do to the side dude I have the bear
jelly cat oh with a robe and bunny ears
oh yeah right he's com like fresh out
the shower took a nice little bath I got
the lady from the AT&T ads all right
like obviously bro obviously hit her up
she's the baddest for real other mother
from Coraline bow poow pow all right I
like a little villainous moment yeah I
do too you know like take me to your
little dungeon and let's see what you
can do for
real okay I brought
um Plankton from SpongeBob and it's the
vibe it's like his determination his
level of like I want this I'm going to
get it and he's like and another one if
you want to talk about good
communication good communication skills
are a really big green flag for me yeah
which is ironic because I am about to
pull the biggest red flag of all time
okay and hear me out a stop sign the
name cuz it's just like the aura a stop
sign has is like first of all stop
everybody listening okay perfect
communication style stop you stop you
know what I mean it's saying exactly
what it needs you to do it's not oh I
think this I think that straight to the
[ __ ] point stop yeah Chill Vibes yeah
yeah and I feel a little bit of
dominance coming from the stop sign you
know he's like stop and I'm like okay
and then what you know what I'm saying
you guys are catching that Vibe right
yeah I'm catching that like he's just
like it's a strong communicator
and a dominant figure stop
sign okay I'm feeling it uh how do you
feel about the Elder one is this is that
crazy of me sorry the Elder one oh my
God if I can if I can wield its magic
I'm totally it's the most you are the
most magical wand in all Hogwarts oh
Matt why do you want to play with the
most magical wand in Hogwarts I do I do
I'm just saying hear me out no I
whoever's got whoever whoever's got this
it's going to be a little bit harder for
me to agree with this one Chris it's not
about the wand's shape it's about the
wand's
power my God we need to delete that
can't go out I'm holding the Elder Wand
you're fine oh my God the Elder W you
were holding the wand it'll it's context
it's not about it's not about that like
fully went over my head it's about
whoever has the eler who's wielding the
the most is the most magical wizard in
all of Harry Potter yeah so okay we'll
say I hear you on the Elder wands um
whoever's magico give me head I'm going
to go with one from my most favorite
movie of all time Back to theut Future
second favorite movie of all time what
the animated One cars yep my girl Flo o
i loved FL Flo you both have Flo we both
have Flo Shout Out Flo she's an
underrated character she must feels so
good right now in this moment she's a
bad great like a boss like she like
great pick she's a boss an independent
woman she got her business going she's
running radiator spring she has Aura
exactly great pick you got to hear me
out on this one and I'm prepared to do
so yep Aunt Fanny from
robots are we hearing me out I can't
hear you out why you're alone Matt
that's that is insane that's diabolical
is it though that's a diabolical hear me
out is it though it is I feel like
Nick's going to hear me out better on
this one than you are always let's see
just like the idea of being a pirate
absolutely right dude absolutely like
the squash squash bucking this is what
I'm talking about this is the nness we
need that you are SI the concept of
being a pirate and we got pirate Aura on
paper dud you're you're swashbuckling
swash
buckling walking planks yep you got the
Hat you're with the crew you're a teamw
worker you know how to tie a good knot
correct you got maybe a little hook on
you yeah Peg Leg hello peg leg Yeah dude
sailing the de Canon balls yeah boom
Kaboom I just don't think they're
showering and all that you know yeah but
it's the lifestyle didn't they have some
sort of disease yo ho yo ho Li is like
for what they what they what did they
lack they lack like vitamin C or
something no dead ass this isn't
a [ __ ] that sounded stupid I said no but
dead ass they lack St at the game wait
is that the joke that I'm missing yeah
oh my God oh my no they I swear to God
they need it I swear to God why did all
the Pirates get sick why did all the
Pirates get sick I swear to God I swear
to God juste a
vitam by accident wait no no no I'm dead
ass why did all the Pirates get sick I
got to Google it lack of fresh fruits
and vegetables in their diet it's dead
ass like the vitamin C jokes comes from
reality swear to God I swear to God
scurvy scurvy
scurvy okay fire scy it was SC what does
that mean it was the disease thatx they
didn't have vitamin C oh my God that's
the disease name no scurvy yes scy I
thought that was like a greeting and
widespread disease called scurvy which
is caused by a deficiency in vitamin C
as citrus fruits and primary source of
vitamin quickly spoil that sea Pirates
were lacked adequate sources of
essential nutrients obvious I just feel
like we needed like one fortnite girl up
there course I
knews like come on bro of course i ns is
the baddest every breed of Jonesy
everyon ER Jonesy preferably Matt I got
Helen Henny from
Chuck-E-Cheese oh my God I don't know if
I can hear you out she kind of bad like
she kind of creepy like she got that
mysterious like oo she's hideous she's
rocking Fair too much Noggin um my last
one and hear me out okay the pair of
pants that I have tattooed on my body no
yes no yes that has to be like the worst
thing I've ever
seen the worst thing you've ever seen do
you know how many things you've been
alive for and this is the worst thing
you've ever seen Chris correct no no
waste up but I can imagine it like I got
no no no not in that not in that sense
you dirty little [ __ ] you said it no
you know you know Sam Sparks cloudy with
K come on she got that she got that
goofball aura yes goofball AA I'm so
silly it's raining meatball catch me
that's type her I don't know I don't
know know about all that I have wendle
from Lemonade's mouth but his
stepmom oh my god wow remember her I do
she brought the folder to school exactly
and he got she got Wendell in trouble
because all the kids are like damn like
that's your mom he goes it's not my mom
clearly what are you stupid and that's
how he got sent to detention to start
the band to start the band she has AA
you know while we're on Lemonade Mouth
you guys know I had to do this one Mo no
mo money no all right go go go Graham
who the [ __ ] is that it's Richard man's
grandmother Graham in the movie oh
that's dad CH she's not dead she's dead
that's the whole point of the movie her
she dies no she doesn't does
die cuz then she has a cat and it's like
a whole thing oh I forgot
that's ridiculous we got we got New
Year's Eve we got Christmas
Eve well Hallow's Eve where's Halloween
it's a
thing is all Hallow's Eve not a thing
all Hallow's Eve are you hearing me out
on all hallow Hees a
thing I've heard it yes but it's not
it's not talked about enough well cuz
it's being corrupted by October 12th
it's the sleeper what happened on
everyone thinks that October all October
long is [ __ ] Halloween so by the time
days in Halloween in October it's like
what the [ __ ] Halloween and All Hallows
Eve and I think it's the same thing okay
but we need the day before to prep that
that's like the prep day where it's like
watch out tomorrow like you like you got
to talk about we need an Halloween night
you know what I me I'm not trying like
we need that build up I'm try to touch
your
balls I'm not trying to provoke voke any
bad behavior I'm really not I think this
goes I'm really not trying to provoke
bad behavior dead ass we need more crime
on
Halloween it's the perfect night do not
get cot say that no I can't say that
yeah no you can't but it's true it's
like element of mystery okay evil you
know I
mean to yourself we need this the
Wardrobe that takes you to Narnia
absolutely right absolutely like you're
telling I just imagine the concept of
something like that that mythical like
we go oh we're going to go to my room
real quick and you're a Narnia beating
doy down and then you're back in it
you're telling me you could take a day
trip to Narnia Narnia fire bro I watch I
need to watch that movie but how do you
get out I think you quickly go out the
same door I I I just don't think you can
close it I think you got to keep it open
but then that's that's bad you can't
leave a constant transmission of
teleportation through from one Earth to
the other we need more closets that you
can go in and like if if I was in the
Clos when I in the closet if it was as
Grand as Narnia I would have been in
there a whole lot longer well I'm happy
it wasn't as Grand well that's not true
because I kind of like felt like the
closet was narn enough for me you know I
was like in there and I was like ah this
is all like this is my little world that
I've
created oh [ __ ] he should have been in
here I wish I printed out a
tractor like a farm tractor that would
have been [ __ ] good you are so weird
or a lasso oh a lasso is a good one Nick
you are what alaso has infinite Aura why
is there no Power Rangers on here Nick
because they're my childhood oh I'm
sorry this one you have to get ready for
it's probably the best one on this whole
thing and I think we'll universally be
like smash
yeah first board game
Lun oh like that motherfucker's just
born a
blow like who do you who do we think the
best ones me I think mine were the best
no mine were the best I think my hear me
outs were the best no no no bro I easily
think mine were the best let us know in
the comments who you guys agree with the
most one know I would have put and let
us know and let us know who what your
most surprised didn't make the cake I
regret not putting a venus fly trap Nick
are you a sicko I'm dead serious what's
the one that you disagree with the most
Graham
or H in the hen Graham like when she was
younger she probably a baddie oh my God
I can't do the Graham conversation like
come on bro I can't handle it all right
let us know if you guys want a part two
oh my God that was fun and um dude today
when me and Matt went in the bank oh no
me and Chris went in the bank the bank I
went in the bank and we were joking
around let's Rob this place like really
loud I thought it was funny but I was
like oh my God inside voices let us know
more videos you guys want plan in more
stuff stuff and we're going to hopefully
have more fun cool Friday videos
couldn't sound any more
excited we're doing more stuff we might
have more Friday
videos deep breath
in and if you spread kindness you will
attract Nick AA Nick stop Nick stop
you're ruining the meditation hands in
your pockets are on your sides ready let
Follow My Lead think of being warm
sorry
sorry and
out is there someone else here kid
looking at me think of a warm place is
it too late for donuts Matt Nick yes it
is it is yes I love I think something
warm and he goes is it too late for
donuts I just wanted to I don't think
it's ever too late for
donuts I think it's the perfect time
right now you 30 you disagree with every
single other person that works at a
donut shop uhuh uhuh there's 24-hour
ones and I know them I'll bring you
there all right you want to go yeah all
right let's go why was in a donut when
you're hear me out cake cuz I feel like
fun when I have a donut what about like
a Burger King Shake I feel fun when I
give a Burger King Shake I wouldn't want
to [ __ ] a Burger King
shake and what about a
tractor okay
[Music]
[Applause]