I've always been jealous of Winston
Churchill. There's a quote, by the way,
the history of innovation is the bed,
the bus, and the bathtub. It's always
these moments when we're not really
thinking about work or we're kind of
doing something else that good ideas
come to us. Winston Churchill, he's
sitting in the bathtub and he's
dictating a national address to his
assistant who's in the other room. She's
saying, "Distinguished ladies and
gentlemen, don't call them
distinguished. They're not just, this is
the Gary Oldman version, they're not
distinguished, you know, dear ladies and
gentlemen, we have gathered together.
Get to the point, you know, and I'm
watching this going, I would give
anything to have an assistant who
understood my context and my voice and
my intent well enough that I could sit
in the bath and they could write my
speech. Now, the poorest villager in
PaloAlto can have what only Winston
Churchill used to have, which is an
assistant that has my context and my
voice and my intent available to me so
that when I'm in the bathtub, I can be
dictating my address. That is absolutely
technically possible today.
[Music]
I'm Jeremy Utley. I am an adjunct
professor of creativity and AI at
Stanford University. I've been teaching
at Stanford for the last 15 years at the
intersection of creativity, innovation,
entrepreneurship, and now increasingly
artificial intelligence. The topic that
I'm most focused on right now is helping
non-technical professionals learn to be
good collaborators to or with generative
AI. And then two years ago, myself and
my partner at the time, Perry Claybond,
wrote a book called Idea Flow, which was
the canonical book on idea generation
and prototyping. So super proud of that.
It was the culmination of a dozen years
of leading executive programs and the
leadership program and the
entrepreneurship program at Stanford.
And one month after our book came out,
Chad GBT came
out. To me, the fact that I wrote the
canonical book on idea generation, just
prior to AI is like writing the best
book on retail just before the internet.
AI is a tool to dramatically augment and
amplify our creativity. And the truth
is, I didn't know a lot about it when
the book came out. So, one month after
my book came out, instead of going on a
world book tour, I strapped myself back
into the front row as a student and
said, I need to be learning about this
transformative new technology. So, I
started taking classes. I started
conducting research. which I started
work working with and studying teams
inside of organizations using the tool
to understand the simple question how
does generative AI impact the individual
and the team and the organization's
ability to solve
problems. You can give an AI a prompt.
For example, how should I answer this
question? Or you could give an AI the
question, I want to ask how I should
answer this question. What's the best
way of framing that question to an AI?
So, you see what I did there? I asked AI
for how to ask AI my question. But you
can use AI to use AI, which is you
couldn't use Excel to use Excel.
PowerPoint can't teach you how to use
PowerPoint. Email can't teach you how to
use email. AI strangely can teach you
how to use itself. If you think to ask,
go to your language model of choice and
just say the following. Hey, you're an
AI expert. I would love your help and a
consultation with you to help me figure
out where I can best leverage AI in my
life. As an AI expert, would you please
ask me questions, one question at a
time, until you have enough context
about my workflows and responsibilities
and KPIs and objectives that you could
make to obvious recommendations and two
nonobvious recommendations for how I
could leverage AI in my work. You will
have one of the most enlightening and
illuminating conversations you've ever
had. And it's all because of AI's
ability to evaluate its own work. What
I've seen is non-technical employees are
able to do incredible things. Here's one
example. The National Park Service
called me and asked me if I would
conduct a training program for a bunch
of backcountry rangers. So, they
gathered a group of about 60 backcountry
rangers and facilities managers into a
training session. And I spent a couple
of hours over Zoom teaching folks the
basics of collaborating with AI. One of
the people in that session was a
gentleman named Adam Rhymer who works at
Glen Canyon National Park. And one of
the things I say is you should focus on
parts of your work that you dread, parts
of your work that you don't enjoy, that
you think, h I have to do this again.
And Adam said, if I have to replace the
carpet tiles in the lodge, I have to
fill out all of this paperwork. And so
to replace a carpet tile will sometimes
take 2 or 3 days of paperwork. Then he
thought, could AI help me write that
paperwork? And in 45 minutes, he built a
tool with natural language that saves
him two days of work. Every day he makes
a statement of work. And then listen to
this. Someone got access to that tool
and shared it across the other parks.
There's about 430 parks in the service.
The National Park Service is estimating
that the tool that Adam built in 45
minutes is going to save the service
7,000 days of human labor this year.
That's the kind of impact that normal
professionals can have even without any
technical ability if only they're given
very basic foundational
training. People are wanting to learn AI
and how it can be transformative for
their business but they don't have the
basic language. And so while lots of
organizations are asking me how can we
work with AI to transform our business
where I have to start with them is how
do you work with AI? The research I'm
familiar with suggests that while on the
one hand AI makes people 25% faster and
12% more work and 40% better quality.
It's also true that less than 10% of
working professionals are driving
meaningful productivity gains from
collaboration with AI. To me there's
this enormous gap. I call it the
realization gap. We conducted studies
both in Europe and in the United States.
And what we found is surprisingly AI
didn't help most people be more
creative. In fact, in many cases the
people that we studied, AI made them
less creative. And as we started digging
into the research, we were surprised and
looked at the data we were confused
because you think AI should make people
more creative, not less. And we studied
the underperformers and then we studied
the outperformers. And what we found is
the outperformers had a fundamentally
different orientation towards AI than
the underperformers did. Whereas the
underperformers treated AI like a tool,
the outperformers treated AI like a
teammate. And shifting your orientation
from tool to teammate changes everything
about the kinds of outcomes that you can
achieve working with generative AI. A
simple example is what do you do when it
gives you mediocre results? If it's a
tool, you get a mediocre result and then
maybe you improve it or maybe you say,
"Ah, it's no good at doing that." If
it's a teammate who's given you a
mediocre results, think about the last
teammate who gave you work product that
wasn't sufficient. You gave them
feedback. You gave them coaching. You
gave them mentorship. You helped them
improve it. And so what we found is the
people who treat AI like a teammate,
coach it and give it feedback and
importantly get it to ask them
questions. The fundamental orientation a
lot of people take towards AI is I'm the
question asker. AI is the answer giver.
But if you think about AI like a
teammate, you say, "Hey, what are 10
questions I should ask about this?" Or,
"What do you need to know from me in
order to get the best response?" So
things, for example, like, "You have a
difficult conversation coming up with a
coworker." Did you know you could
leverage a large language model to
roleplay that conversation? You can get
an AI to interview you about your
conversation partner and then construct
a psychological profile of your
conversation partner and then play the
role of your conversation partner in a
role play and then give you feedback
from the perspective of your
conversation partner on how you approach
the
conversation. That's something you can
do today. And there are many things like
that. I call them drills, but there are
many things like that where if someone
will just shift their consideration set
of what are the things I can do with AI,
they end up discovering applications
that I've never even dreamed of. I've
been doing this stuff for 2 years and my
students are regularly coming to me with
use cases I've never imagined that
landed them in a destination I could
have never predicted and they could
never have predicted.
For me, I never thought about myself as
a creative individual. Now, I fully and
fundamentally believe every single human
being has innate creative capacity.
Every single one of us. What the D
school has helped me do is unlock
others. Everyone has this latent
creative capacity. Once I was teaching a
class with a hip-hop artist named LRA.
He's a multi-time Grammy award-winning
artist. And he and I are teaching a
class to graduate students at Stanford.
and we're giving them the assignment,
you've got to go get inspiration in the
world. And what I can see is it's like
looking at myself in the mirror 10 years
ago because all of the business school
students in the class are going
inspiration and I just felt LRae is
clearly the creative legend in the room.
I said, "Lae, what do you think about
inspiration?" And of course, as only a
hip-hop artist could do, he dropped a
bar. He said, "Inspiration's a
discipline."
And I realized in that moment for these
students, it's not even on their radar
as a tool, let alone a routine part of
their life. But the most wildly creative
individuals I know are disciplined about
cultivating the inputs to their thinking
because they know it affects the outputs
of their thinking. And so even in
regards to AI, I push people, what is
the inspiration you're bringing to the
model? Everybody has the same access to
the same chat GPT. How do I get a
different output than you do? It's
because of what I bring to the model.
And what do I bring to the model?
Certainly, I bring technique, but I also
bring my experience. I bring my
perspective. I bring all the inspiration
I've gleaned from the world. That's what
gets a user a differential output from a
model. A seventh grader in Ohio, who I
don't even know what her name is, but
her teacher asked, "What is creativity?"
and she put a post-it note up on the
board that says, "Creativity is doing
more than the first thing you think
of." And that's my favorite definition
because it speaks to a profound
cognitive bias that we hold. It's been
called functional fixedness. It's been
called the Einsteining effect. But the
basic premise is humans tend to fixate
on an early solution and be satisfied.
Herbert Simon called it satisficing. But
it's the idea that if we get to good
enough, it's enough. And that's why I
love that seventh grader's definition.
Creativity is doing more than the first
thing you think of. It's pushing past
good enough. Is the definition of
creativity changing in the age of AI? I
don't think so. The reality is with AI,
it's now easier than ever to get good
enough. If your goal is world class, if
your goal is exceptional, then what you
want to be prompting for is actually
volume and variation. And that takes
time. It takes time to not only read
through it, but to sort it and to
process it. But fundamentally, the
definition of creativity doesn't change
in the age of AI. It's just that the
human's ability or inability to arrive
at a creative state is affected not only
by the technology but also by their
stated or unstated objectives in
collaborating with it. Creators don't
need to be afraid of AI. Creators need
to dive in. They need to lean in.
Creators are about to be unleashed in a
way they've never been unleashed before.
The only correct answer to the question
how do you use AI is I don't I don't use
AI I work with it. When you start
working with AI, it will change
everything.