To be honest, like our first product
looks really rough. We actually only
used two weeks. One day we have over
like 100 people just flowing this
product. Our users actually just you
know like doubled. There is huge
increase in the user and there's huge
increase in the revenue. That is a time
we know okay we hit something right. We
have over 10 million downloads in a year
and we now have over 10 million
annualized revenue within a year. It's
not just about fantastic UI, UX or how
you're marketing it, right? It's more
like what result users are get. You
don't need to wait for the product to be
perfect to launch it. Most of the time
in the AI era, things will change every
day. If you wait too long, you may never
be able to launch your product. So, you
just need to launch it, develop it,
learn from it at the same
time. Hi, I'm Ella. I'm the founder and
the CEO of CRY AI. Criti is the agentic
AI to augment your marketing video at
scale. Just drop one product image and
Criti write your script, shoot your
video and even do the processing for
your marketing video without the need of
full media crew. Cringy is growing
pretty fast. We have over 10 million
downloads in a year and we now have over
10 million annualized revenue within a
year thanks to our network effect
between the influencer and the
[Music]
brands. I started my career as actually
a hardware engineer at Apple. We are
building the first generation of
AirPods. We don't even know what product
people actually need. So we invite a lot
of users to our small interview room and
we ask them a lot of questions like what
do you need actually for the earpods?
What do you actually have the pinpoints
for? Uh things like that. At Apple when
we conduct the interviews instead of
just doing online surveys we actually
more prefer to invite the users to the
interview room and conduct like
face-toface interviews. Right? When you
ask people to fill out the survey
online, people most of time they just,
you know, click the first one, whatever
they see there, right? Because they want
to just jump to the end. No one really
want to get their feedback. So you may
get the wrong answers. And another more
important thing actually is when you are
talk to your users face to face, you
actually get more than what you want to
ask, right? Like people they always have
some assumption that okay maybe user
need A b and C but actually user don't
care about them like at all right like
they only care about what they care
about like D but you don't have that on
your survey so you'll get the wrong
answer that's the reason actually Apple
prefer to have face-to-face user
interview when they are building a new
product and one important thing we learn
at Apple is you know you really need to
understand people's pain points you need
to really know why people need it when
you are building it. We have our like a
lot of fantastic ideas or imagination
but those are not solving the pain
points of real customers and that's not
we want right so meeting people or
knowing people's pain points actually is
the first step when you need to create a
great product. The AirPods project is
like it's amazing uh experience for me.
Many people said I should stay there for
longer. But the thing is that I always
pursue for building something new or
building something I think I feel most
excited for. When I was a child, I found
I get information much easier when I get
it in the form of video instead of like
long text or like blog post or things
like that. So it is always my dream that
in the childhood that if one day we
could turn a lot of communication the
learning the information gathering just
in the video format that will be really
helpful for a lot of people sometimes
you know it's it's pretty pretty hard
for people from the giant company to
actually quit and really doing the
startup when I looking back I really
miss the time there at big company
enjoying with my friends and my family
Still I think I don't regret uh because
I am doing what I really passionate
about and I believe that will help a lot
of people that is more important to
me when I saw the generative AI even
it's back in 2020 I believe that one is
will change the world and it will be the
future because at that time I saw a lot
of people they spend over 80% of their
time just online instead of offline,
right? So there is a huge trend that
people actually are shifting from
offline to online and then people will
definitely need much much higher demand
for the great content online. But on the
offset that I saw it's pretty pretty
hard for people to create great content
right the requirement for great content
actually growing higher and higher. The
supply of the great content actually uh
have a huge gap between the supply and
the demand. I'm pretty certain that you
know it's only the technology which
could like merge the gap and help people
with that. That's a time that I think
okay even though I am not experts I
don't know a lot about software or I
don't know a lot about AI but you know I
can always learn once I find the
motivation I would know what I want to
do and I can shift to that and I can
learn that pretty quickly to be honest
like our first product looks really
rough. We don't have really fantastic UX
or UI. We even don't have the batch mode
in the beginning. But that's totally
okay. You know, like sometimes when the
product is really rough, but users
still, you know, like willing to use it,
that means something. If you have a
really like bad design product, but
people are still using it. They're like,
okay, there's some real value thing in
that one. It's not just about fantastic
UI, UX, or how you're marketing it,
right? It's more like what result users
are get whether they can use it to get
the benefit they want. You don't need to
wait for the product to be perfect to
launch it because you know like most of
the time in the AI era like things will
change every day. If you wait too long
you may never be able to launch your
product. So you just need to launch it,
develop it, learn from it. At the same
time, there's one lesson I learned as a
founder or I will say the most painful
lesson I learned. Our first product
actually is called ZMO.ai. At the time I
was building Zmo. I'm not sure like why
I'm building this like why people need
this. The thing is at the time me
journey is super hot. Everyone is
chasing that right. So just like so many
other founders, I'm like, "Okay, text to
image is so popular. We definitely need
to enter this domain. So let's do it."
But I don't really know why people are
generating those images. So I don't
really understand the users need. When I
was building the product, we actually
don't know what the business model will
be and we even don't know what the next
step will be, right? So the revenue
actually doesn't go that high as the
users grow, right? and we suddenly just
get lost right we don't know like why
people are using it like why some people
pay why some people don't pay for it
when we have this difficulty the only
thing I can think about is talking to
your customers right that is a thing I
learned from Apple we do email our users
or most active users email them like
over 500 and finally we get 300 actually
we have the face toface conversation
with them because I believe talk to the
users is the only way we can find
whether there is a true need or what do
they really need after talking to more
than like 300 users we find that a lot
of people they create the images it's
just out of curiosity the AI is so new
to them they just want to try it out but
they do a small group of people they
they actually do have the need for it
not designers they don't know how to
create all those cool images they do
need actually those content for
themselves for their company uh for
marketing. So we're like okay we finally
find people who have real needs for
that. Most of them who are on Amazon or
eBay or Etsy they actually use their
phone directly to take the photos of
their product. So they hope that okay
the social media is also on the phone
photos and the videos are also on the
phone. it will make him much more sense
if you just build the product on the
model. After talking to them, we finally
made the decision. Okay, we will
reposition this product and we will
build it for people who really have the
needs which is marketing and we will
also shift it actually from the PC side
to mobile. That's the time when the
pivot is happening.
We are building the mobile version of
creati in a way that it's not actually
just a tool but it's more like a
community for both influencers and the
brands. The reason actually we have
features or templates for both
influencers and brands is actually we
find if some brands they want to do
marketing it's impossible actually to
avoid uh the influencers contribution
because influencers they are the people
who actually know best about the social
media who actually know much better
about what content is more engaging and
more attractive to users. So when we are
building creat from day one we know okay
we need to create the actually the
network effect between the influencers
and the brands they they know the
internet so well after they create the
template they will also will post those
videos uh on their own channel on the
social media and if that video templates
actually is a great one that video will
actually go viral it will actually get
millions or tens of millions of views
right and Those viral videos actually is
the best marketing strategy for us to
acquire more and more brands because
when the video go viral that will bring
a lot of lot of users to the
createl the end of funnel there will be
the brands that will really use this
video templates to create their engaging
ads video. So the brands actually when
they are using those brands as video
they will pay more uh to create this
platform so that we can hire more
influencers in the community and the
influencer can create more viral video
templates for the brands. So it's
actually a very nice flywheel actually
we're building between the influencers
and the brands and we believe that is
the key differentiation CR is have
compared to all other like AI marketing
tools is because we believe the
ecosystem actually need both sides. We
need both influencers and brands to help
them to grow marketing at scale.
The AI world just changed daily. Every
day you wake up, there will be new
technology and new product, right? And I
think building in the AI era is quite
different from like 20 to 30 years ago
when people are just enter the mobile
boom. The thing is actually I believe
maybe 99% or maybe all the products that
you saw today maybe not the final
version of what they will be at the end
of AI evolution. The requirement for the
founder in the AI era for AI startup
actually is kind of different from
previously because those founders really
need to adapt really quickly and
flexibility to those changes. And one
thing we think actually is helping us to
adapt to all those changes is we talk to
our users every day and to learn what is
the key thing that won't change even if
the technology change. So the thing that
we find out you know is what kind of
content will go pretty like viral on the
social media is all the things that our
users or our customers care about. Even
though technologies change, the
important thing is once you get those
industry insider data and knowledge uh
for that vertical that will build your
mode and that will actually be your key
value along with those all technology
changes daily or those technology change
will just help you instead of you know
like disrupted to your product.