throw out a big number, see what
happens. If somebody bulks at it and
says that's way too high, you know,
you've at least done the right thing and
figured out what the top of the market
might be. Most founders are shocked at
the market uh will pay for their
product. And especially if you're a
first-time founder, you almost feel like
guilty or greedy asking for certain
numbers, but ultimately for pricing, you
really have to understand the business
value that a company is getting by using
your product.
So, I'm Ben Brookke. I'm the co-founder
and CEO of Transcend. We are a data
privacy infrastructure company. We help
other businesses uh encode privacy rules
across all of their technology. We're
helping them comply with privacy laws
and really adopting the spirit of
privacy and giving consumers far better
control over their personal data. We're
backed by uh Excel Index. We're now a
series B startup.
I think the biggest challenge for us um
like many founders were finding that
first product market fit. As a founder
in the weeds, you're like so excited
about this thing and you think like
we've got it. This is going to land.
People are going to love it. Nobody
wants to buy it. And then like really
kind of learning to trust the data and
test understand what the customer really
needs. like you can't stress enough when
you're building a product to like really
understand your customer. What we ended
up doing was we found a few early
customers. We basically just said like
what if we just automated this for you?
We'll be like your extended privacy
engineering team. Let us build the
solution and kind of just like help us
understand every aspect of it. It was
actually a fairly consultative
engagement with the first two or three
customers and we made sure that like
they were aligned to the fact that yes
we are going to build a product here but
that was how we approached it. So
especially when it's in I think like a
little bit more toward like the
enterprise software motion I think
that's like absolutely a path you can
take where you just kind of let
customers vent their problems and offer
to just find a way to fix them. As for
scaling from you know 10 to 100
customers in enterprise this is when you
need to have your first sellers.
Typically, you can do founderled sales
for the first call it 20, 30 customers,
but not only should you start handing
that off, but also like it's an
important part of proving that you're
able to scale the business past yourself
who knows every nook and cranny of the
product and you've been thinking about
this problem for like, you know, 5 years
or whatever. To be able to have a seller
become successful in selling your
product is an important first milestone.
And we we really spent the time to find
that right sort of first seller. And the
first seller is completely different
from like the latest stage seller where
they're super creative. They kind of do
every sales role alone which includes
generating pipeline, you know, actually
running the deal with as an account
executive would and then even a lot of
like sales engineering in some cases
probably contracting all of the sort of
the full endto-end sales process. And we
found somebody who's just incredible at
this. I I really believe there's nothing
more important than like finding the
best hire. If you need to slow down to
get it right, it's 100% worth it. And
then after that, depending on what your
sort of AR is at around 100 customers,
you either need to scale your sales team
or you probably like if it's way up
market, you probably already have. But
in any case, being able to scale a sales
team really is about if you don't have a
sales background, like you should find a
sales leader. It is such a huge subject
with so much expertise that it is one of
the things where you just you need to
find a great leader who can do all of
the right pieces of like building
playbooks, breaking out the sales
process with like uh sales development
representatives, account executives,
sales engineering, revenue operations
and so forth. There's a whole
organization and that sort of meta
process is very playooked but not
something a founder should do. They
should absolutely find the the best
leader that they can. That's really the
sort of like 0 to 10, 10 to 100 and
beyond. There's a few things I'll say
about pricing. The first is make it
super iterative. You really need to
adapt it and change it until you find
your price point. Even then, like it's
only going to last for maybe a year, a
year and a half before you have gotten
enough data to say certain parts of this
are stupid. We need to change it. The
second is you should start as high as
pro possible because most founders are
shocked at the market uh will pay for
their product and especially if you're a
first-time founder you almost feel like
guilty or greedy asking for certain
numbers but ultimately for pricing you
really have to understand the business
value that a company is getting by using
your product. And it kind of sounds like
just corporate jargon, but this is
actually how companies buy. And so if
you're not articulating the actual
dollar value of your product or if you
have no idea how to even start, the
person who's buying your product is
going to try to create that assessment
themselves so that they can take it to
the CFO and get it approved. And so it's
the the real answer is like, do you want
to be involved in that process or do you
not? If it's going to get approved, you
better be involved in that process. So
you actually do have to articulate if
you're going to drive revenue in the
company, how much can you drive? If
you're going to decrease cost, how much
can you decrease cost? Can you actually
articulate what we call value drivers
and educate the person who's trying to
buy your product who's interested in it
and work with them to sort of build this
value case together? And then whatever
that value is, your price should be
about a quarter, two or one/3 of that so
that they get the ROI number on top for
the remaining three quarters.
The real sort of key to our series B was
proving that we could repeatably switch
customers off of the status quo in
privacy, which is incredibly manual
operational work where data owners are
consistently being interviewed, asked to
manually operate on one individual's
data when that individual asks to be
deleted. And that is the status quo sort
of encoded by legacy incumbent software.
The real bet at our series A was like,
can we repeatably show that we can take
market share? Is there a long-term
outcome where transcend takes that sort
of top spot in the market? And so our
series A to our series B was really all
about building our sales team, scaling
up marketing operation, and really like
delivering a customer experience that
customers would be happy to sort of like
do case studies and and sort of shout
shout about us from the rooftops and
tell their friends to switch as well.
And so we we we really tracked like
milestones around like uh our win rate
against uh the incumbent competitor and
if we could get it to a certain number
we thought that would be really critical
for our series B story and ultimately
kind of like help unstick the market
that felt like it was kind of like
turning into a bit of a cottage industry
around this this sort of status quo way
of doing things. And so we we really
kind of like had a metric driven process
against that and just executed really
really well on that plan. So that at the
series B we could tell the full story of
customers are making this like mass
migration
switch. The current trend in privacy
right now is first governance of AI
systems. There is a sort of mad dash
inside every business right now to adopt
AI and part of that is uh compiling all
of the data into a format uh that can be
leveraged for the purpose of AI for the
those who are technical these are like
vector databases and building embeddings
but there are very few guard rails
around any of these systems and the way
that you know perhaps personal
information may be processed on one hand
there's the way that personal data is
being used uh in AI systems and then on
the other there's the way that AI
systems may be impacting individuals so
like bias and harm fairness uh
particularly when AI systems are being
used for decision-m and so the most
recent kind of landmark regulation was
the AI act in Europe many businesses are
trying to understand how they're using
AI put processes in place around
ensuring that the guard rails are in
place or that they've appropriately
assessed the impacts of using that AI.
And so that's certainly a current trend
in uh privacy today. And one of the
effects of that a lot of the people who
became like the chief privacy officer
are going through a title change uh and
sort of role and scope change to also be
the owner of AI governance. Uh and a lot
of companies are saying kind of like
while we're at it, let's make it like
everything digital governance, all
regulatory policy, all governance of our
systems short of security. And that has
been like a big sort of industry shift.
The customers and the buyer, the the
people that we sell to are undergoing
just a massive sort of change in scope.
And so that's that's a really important
trend right now. And then like every day
there's something with in privacy that's
like wow that's a really creepy thing
and like or there'll be a data breach or
there'll be you know something that is
like always driving the news you know
the news meta sunglasses for example um
it took about like 3 days for someone at
uh some two kids at Harvard uh turn that
into a system which can like literally
just tell like find people's online
profiles as you walk down the street.
it's just like overlaying their like
name, LinkedIn, job title, just by
facial recognition. So there's like all
kinds of crazy stuff um just like in the
the the daily news. But categorically
the shift toward u AI governance and
this broadening sort of supererset of
privacy.
[Music]
What's up?