try to solve a problem that you yourself
have. When you have an opportunity to
build tools that people use pretty much
8 hours a day, you're making a huge
impact. For the first 3 years, I made no
money on Laravel at all. It was totally
open source. I see myself as a very
average developer. Everything I've built
at Laravel was essentially solving a
problem that I had encountered in
reality. When you're building open
source software, there's a lot of
voices. Some of them are coming from a
place of like genuine uh constructive
criticism and some of them are more like
haters of your project. Say you're
Metallica or you're Taylor Swift. If
Metallica starts trying to cater to like
Taylor Swift fans, then they lose all of
their core fans. In the same way, like
if Taylor Swift changes her core sound,
she upsets that core fan base. And so
play the hits for your fans. They're the
core piece of your community. I think it
can be very tempting, especially when
other like smart people try to tell you,
"Oh, I think it should work this way or
I think you should do this." The people
that like sit on the sidelines and sort
of just like shout criticisms at open
source projects. If you were to follow
their feedback, there's always like
another like carrot on a stick they're
dangling out there. They're like, "Oh,
thanks for doing that, but I don't like
this either." And like if you change
this, oh, that would be great. You know,
you keep jumping through the hoops, but
they never actually like become a user
of the product. do the hardest parts
first. This is something that I think a
lot of web developers that are trying to
start new products get wrong. While
they're the most motivated at the
beginning, they build a lot of like of
the easy parts and then once you've
wasted all of your like initial
enthusiasm kind of dancing around, you
sort of lost your momentum. Especially
as a solo founder, I would much rather
fail after 2 weeks than wasting 3
months. It's changing from a solo
developer to running a bootstrapped
company to now VCbacked company and they
all work really differently honestly.
But I think what hasn't changed is
Hi, I'm Taylor Rotwell. I am the creator
of Laravel, an open-source PHP framework
for building web applications. So I
started creating Laravel as a way for me
to build web applications faster. And it
was actually not my original intention
to make it a big popular open-source
framework or community. And so the
community's grown tremendously. We've
gone from relatively a few downloads per
day when I first released Laravel to now
a quarter million downloads per day. Our
first Laracon conference was in 2013 and
we only had 90 attendees. At last year's
Laracon in Dallas, Texas, we had over
900 attendees. Tons of developers around
the world and almost every country in
the world use Laravel to build
incredible applications.
I grew up in Hot Springs, Arkansas. It's
a relatively small town in central
Arkansas. I was always fairly interested
in computers and the web as a kid. I
think I built my first website when I
was about 10 years old. I think I was
one of the only kids I knew that knew
how to build anything on the web, which
was kind of fun cuz like when you're the
only kid in school that can build a
website, everyone wants you to build a
website for them. So, it was a pretty
interesting way to grow up not being
around any other techy people or kids or
startups. It's a very different world
programming and being a developer in
Arkansas than being, for example, in
Silicon Valley. But overall, I think
that being in Arkansas has helped me
maintain a level of focus and clarity on
what I wanted to build that I probably
wouldn't otherwise had if I had been
somewhere else. College was a good
experience in a sense because a lot of
my professors were very old school
programmers. Some of them had worked at
like NASA. Many of them did not even use
like a guey on their computer, you know,
they were like very old school nerdy
programmer people teaching me like core
foundational programming concepts that
apply across all languages. They really
understood the foundational concepts of
building good software which I think was
extremely helpful. So when I was working
just like a day job as a software
engineer, I always gravitated towards
building tools for the other engineers
at the company. like I would always um
try to get side projects or like get
assigned to build things that would make
us as developers more productive. So I
was always finding ways to like optimize
our workflow and I always found that
like actually more interesting than what
the business was about. I had some
businesses that I wanted to build some
startup ideas and PHP is a web
programming language that is very easy
to deploy out onto the web. It's easy to
run and maintain and to ship. I needed
sort of like a toolkit to build these
web applications more quickly. And there
was other ways to do this in PHP. There
was existing frameworks that were
already out there. Many of them were
kind of dated and maybe getting a little
older. And I thought that I could build
a little bit more modern take on how to
build web applications in PHP. Once I
was almost done with it, I thought like,
hm, this is actually kind of cool and
maybe other people would want to use
Laravel to build things. So that's when
I decided to open source it, put
documentation around it and try to, you
know, share it with the world. And for
the first 3 years of Laravel's life, I
made no money on Laravel at all. It was
totally open source. I had sort of
written my own scripts to automate this
on my machine, but I decided to build
user interface around it and build like
a product out of shipping Laravel
applications to the web. And I called
that Laravel Forge. And I released that
in 2014. And honestly, I had no idea how
it was going to perform, like how many
customers it was going to have. I still
honestly expected that I would need to
work a day job. Even after I released
Forge, but within probably a month or
two of releasing Forge, Forge was making
more money than I was making at my
regular job. I was having to do customer
support and I was having to fix bugs.
Then I was in a situation where it was
like very obvious I could not do both
things at the same time. About six
months after launching Forge, uh January
1st, 2015 was actually my first
full-time day working on Laravel where I
sat down in my home office, which was
basically a spare bedroom at the time.
And I was working on Laravel all day
that day and have ever since. The first
couple of years, I was the only person
at the company. So I wrote the front
end, I wrote the backend, I did the
customer support, I did the docs, I did
everything. And we made our first hire.
I think around 2016 2017 I hired another
engineer. I think this is actually one
mistake I made is I put off hiring too
long. This may be common for other open
source developers where when you create
something open source or you create a
product you're like extremely protective
of it like it's your you know it's it's
your thing that you've created and
you're scared that anyone's going to
like come in and mess it up or like mess
up your vision for it. And so that made
me very hesitant to hire but then once I
did I was like oh wow I should have done
this a long time ago. Running a company
by yourself can be stressful and a bit
lonely. I always felt like Laravel and
PHP was a bit of an underdog and web
development. Even when I created Laravel
in 2010 or 2011, PHP was already seen as
like not the most glamorous web
language. That was nothing new. Like
even back then, I think that underdog
mentality of like, okay, well, I
actually think there's something really
great here and I think this is a
fantastic way to build applications
really quickly, it really motivated me
to like prove it over many years. And
all of them in a way were sort of born
out of my own like desire to make things
easier for developers.
This episode is sponsored by Atio, the
AI native CRM for the next era of
companies. Connect your email and ATIO
instantly builds your CRM right before
your eye with every company, contact,
and interaction you've ever had enriched
and organized. That's ATIO. And here's
what makes it even more game-changing.
You can build AI powered automations and
use its research agents to tackle some
of your most complex business processes,
freeing you to focus on what matters
most, building your company. Join
thousands of companies who are already
using to power their businesses. Visit
the link in the description to begin
your 2e free trial with Atio.
I think opensource is powering almost
every business in the world at this
point. It's become the norm. You can
inspect it and read it and you can even
contribute to it. It's almost like the
first thought is to release it on
GitHub. You know that that's like the
most obvious thing you would do if
you're running an open- source company.
The most obvious risk is just other
people taking your open source code, you
know, and building uh alternatives or
competitors built on pretty much
everything you've done over the last
decade or however long you've worked on
your project. I think the way you avoid
that in many cases is how you run the
community and how you interact with the
community. I've always tried to stay
extremely receptive to community
feedback. I'm still very involved. I
actually still the first hour and a half
of my day is getting on GitHub and
managing pull requests to the open
source Laravel framework. I'm actually
still the only person that does that at
the company. I think if you develop an
attitude where you're not listening to
the community and they feel that that's
when like you start getting grumblings
in the community, people get unhappy and
then you like run the risk of a fork in
the open source project. Forks the
project, renames it. this is now a
better, more community-friendly version
of your product. That's the biggest
risk. When you're building open source
software, there's a lot of voices. They
all have an opinion on where you should
take um the framework. And some of them
are coming from a place of like genuine
uh constructive criticism, and some of
them are more like just sort of like
haters of your project. One really great
piece of advice that another open-source
founder, Adam Wavin from Tailwind, gave
me was that just like when you're in a
band, say you're Metallica or you're
Taylor Swift, if Metallica starts trying
to cater to like Taylor Swift fans, then
they lose all of their core fans. In the
same way, like if Taylor Swift changes
her core sound that her fans love and
that they come to her concerts to hear,
she upsets that core fan base. And so
play the hits for your fans. They love
what you build. They're the core piece
of your community. I think it can be
very tempting, especially when other
like smart people try to tell you, "Oh,
I think it should work this way or I
think you should do this." It can be so
so tempting as an open source maintainer
to like go down these rabbit holes of
like, "Okay, well maybe if I add this
feature then like this group of people
will finally use Laravel and start
building with it." In my experience, the
people that like sit on the sidelines
and sort of just like shout criticisms
at open source projects, if you were to
follow their feedback and like jump
through that first hoop of what they
want you to do, there's always like
another another like carrot on a stick
they're dangling out there, they're
like, "Oh, thanks for doing that, but I
don't like this either." And like if you
change this, oh, that would be great.
You know, you keep jumping through the
hoops, but they never actually like
become a user of the product, which it
can be incredibly frustrating. So listen
to just your core audience that's
already building with Laravel and they
love what you're doing and they have
businesses on Laravel. It's important to
hear outside feedback too, but just use
caution with how far you stray from like
your core beliefs and what you think
your product needs to be.
I had never really considered taking
outside investment before Excel. I used
to get emails about that pretty
frequently and I would always just
delete them which Excel found hilarious.
The reason for that honestly is just
like we were happy at the company as
just a small team working on whatever we
wanted to work on, not wanting someone
to mess up what I had built. So that
fear of messing up everything we had put
so much work into made me hesitant in
both regards for hiring and raising
money, especially as developer
expectations have risen quite a bit
since 2011. like the user experience and
the tooling that developers expect. They
expect it to be really really good. The
bar just like keeps getting higher for
how polished and how productive and how
great your products have to be. And I
knew that if we wanted to like take
Laravel to the next level, it was going
to take a lot of work and it was going
to have to be some pretty ambitious
projects that were far beyond anything
we had built before and it was going to
take a much bigger team to build these
things. And so that's what sort of led
me down the path of raising money with
Excel. It's been a gradual process
changing from a solo developer to
running a bootstrapped company to now
trying to lead a VCbacked company. And
they all work really differently.
Honestly, when I was bootstrapping the
company, it was extremely flat. But at
the same time, when you go from 10 to
50, there are just new new layers of
organizational hierarchy and management
that comes with that. But I think what
hasn't changed is our core mission to
build awesome developer tools. Like
that's still the mission we're on. And
so like our underlying mission of
building great products, nurturing a
really great community with community
events like Laracon and Laravel lives
and meetups, all of that is the same.
But I feel like I should have grown this
kind of team much earlier, but I was
scared to and I didn't know how to
really. and bringing on people that can
help us build these products and help us
grow this community beyond what I'm
capable of myself. And I'm super excited
to see where we can go in the next few
years.
When I first released Laravel, we had,
you know, like discussion forums about
the framework where people could ask for
feedback or give ideas. Every day I was
in those forums myself, like answering
questions, asking for feedback on new
features and I always try to be really
involved in the community early. We
built sort of like a very friendly,
welcoming vibe where everyone can pitch
in and get help. And there wasn't a lot
of like posturing or judgment on what
stage people were at in their journey
with Laravel or with development in
general. We were just all trying to help
each other and kind of be a part of
building businesses and building
products where people feel like they can
come and learn and and build something
cool and they have other people kind of
have their back. Everyone wants to be a
part of something like they want to
contribute to something and it if they
feel like they can actually have an
impact on the software which you can I
think for a lot of people that creates a
very strong like sense of belonging and
community. If you were to pull up a
contributor list of Laravel, like their
name is now on the list forever. I think
of people like Jeffrey Wei that founded
Laracas creating video content and
educational material about how to use
the framework. He was actually the first
person to build a full-time career
around Laravel even before I did. By
embracing and encouraging those
relationships, I think it helped build a
really vibrant, strong community. And
it's good for us as well because people
are constantly making content about, you
know, our framework.
I've always said I see myself as a very
average developer, which that sounds
bad, but I think it's actually been a
really good thing because there's a lot
of average developers in the world, and
I feel like I build tools that helps the
average developer do their job quickly.
And that is just statistically a lot of
people. When you have an opportunity to
build tools that people use pretty much
eight hours a day at their job, then
you're making a huge impact like on
someone's personal enjoyment of their
life, I think is really interesting and
amazing and like this huge privileged
and it's something very few companies
and software tools really get to do. The
most common advice I give first is try
to solve a problem that you yourself
have. These are the problems that you're
going to understand the most deeply.
Everything I've built at Laravel was
essentially solving a problem that I had
encountered in reality. Many of them are
things that I needed. And I think that
if possible, you should try to build a
business that way to where you are a
customer yourself. The second piece of
advice I would give would be do the
hardest parts first. Um, this is
something that I think a lot of web
developers that are trying to start new
products get wrong. while they're the
most motivated at the beginning of that
idea, they build a lot of like of the
easy parts. Like they might build, oh,
I'll build the login form first. And you
spend a month or two building all of
these really easy parts, and you're kind
of procrastinating in this like clever
way of tackling the core like hardest
problems you need to solve to really
make this product great. And then once
you've wasted all of your like initial
enthusiasm kind of dancing around, you
sort of lost your momentum, especially
as a solo founder. And so for me, when I
have a new product idea, I absolutely
try to build the most impossible part
first. Like the part I'm not sure that I
even have the skills to build or
understand or whatever. I'll just try to
get that working. Even though it's the
hardest part, if you do that at the
beginning, you're the most motivated.
And if you crack it and you nail it, the
other part is just like it's all
downhill from there as far as building
the product. If you fail, you would you
would rather fail earlier, you know,
like building the product. I would much
rather fail after 2 weeks than wasting 3
months. So do the hardest part first and
try to solve problems you deeply
understand being customer number one
yourself.
[Music]