As a founder, you are taking the biggest
bet and risk on yourself and your life.
Being born in Algeria, my moonshot was
New York City and went straight to New
York. I don't have a proper education. I
don't have a proper sort of route to
becoming a founder. For me specifically,
I don't have the option to to fail. And
so giving up is absolutely not on the
table. Every decision I make, I doubt.
But then there is a stubborn persona in
me. So, as long as your vision is the
same and consistent and what you're
delivering is clear to the world, how
you get there, it doesn't really matter.
What is truly imperative is the
reinforced principle of believing. You
really have to believe that your product
is helping people. And I think
perseverance and any hardship I had
going through life helped me become a
better human first and then a better
founder.
My name is Khaled Maneri, co-founder and
CEO of Selfbook. Selfpoke is really
providing the infrastructure for travel.
So if someone is on the website and have
intent to book that hotel, we should
eliminate as much friction as possible
to increase conversion. Before self
book, no hotel in the world could accept
Apple Pay for instance. And so we
brought in the digital wallets into the
industry. And then now we're adding much
more features to streamline the
experience even more.
Being born in Algeria, obviously
geopolitically we were restricted. We
couldn't travel. When the pandemic was
an example for a lot of people how to
they felt the need to travel but they
couldn't. So imagine a world in Algeria
where you actually can't travel because
it's impossible to get a visa or
especially as a young kid. So when I was
able to finally leave my moonshot was
New York City and went straight to New
York.
I walked up Fifth Avenue and discovered
the Apple
store. It was beautiful. I remember the
first iPod ad on Fifth Avenue or in Time
Square. That was a big iPod ad and I
remember how beautiful that product was.
I then learned design because they're
open for 24 hours. They let you use the
Mac. So that that changed my life
because I was really inspired by the
design and was really inspired by truly
obsession of excellence and product
excellence and so made me want to learn
how to design and maybe a better product
founder. Uh my business was purely
accidental. As an immigrant I had to do
any job to survive. I really wanted to
design products but I had no education
or network or any sort of background to
earn the benefit to go and work for
someone. I think not going to school
here or at all and not having a strong
network when you first move in to a
foreign country. You have to start
somewhere and so one friend can become
your network, right? When I was
fundraising, I didn't really know a lot
of people, right? I knew two or three
people. That's it. And the three of them
specifically that I have in mind helped
me with a build a network, fund raise.
They're still my close adviserss and
investors and even help me hire and get
new customers. So, you really can't go
at this alone, right? Some will change,
some will come, others will go. But
whether they will end up there or not,
they will always be part of your story.
We're going to touch us with our
fingers. When the iPhone launched in
2007, that sparked an idea to design an
app. No one had designed for mobile
before. So that was a really opportunity
for start as a starting point and that
was six agency. I called it six agency
because I was working out my apartment
6A. So the name was easy to come up
with. This app in particular, an idea
that we wanted to push to some of our
clients to say you don't need a full
catalog of products in front of a
customer on a small device. The app
would show you only one product per day.
Sometimes it could be a pencil from
Japan or it could be a beautiful watch.
It was highly curated. This is before
Instagram, before Tik Tok. And some of
the products and experiences that we
started adding is travel experiences.
When we showed these experiences,
engagement went up 70%. So people really
wanted to learn about an experience or
buy an experience. But it was really
hard to book on the app just because
there was no proper booking
infrastructure at a time. You had to
leave the app and go find the experience
somewhere else in some other marketplace
to book it. And that's what inspired us
to launch the travel app. It was an app
designed where you can easily discover a
hotel and book it right there and then.
But the month we were officially
launching it, the pandemic
started. Every hotel in the world shut
down. Yet I was thinking beyond that.
When the world comes back and they would
want to travel again. For me, every
decision I make I doubt. But then there
is a stubborn persona in me and a
relentless drive to create something
seamless. And so we had to think of ways
where we can pivot. Two key insight
points that I received during that time
was that no hotel in the world could
accept Apple Pay at the time. And
secondly is that launching a consumer
app is really really hard. So for us was
how can we leverage everything we built
and still provide this unique customer
experience to compete against OTAAS was
an impossible mission. Big OTAAS use
Apple Pay and they have a really
streamlined booking experience some at
least. Hotels didn't have that. So they
didn't have a leveled playing field. So,
Selfbook provided that to hotels instead
of them just continuing to give 25%
commission to OTAAS because a lack of a
streamlined booking experience. We were
able to bring that to them. Our view was
that if the guest really wants to book a
hotel and they are on the hotel website,
there's absolutely no reason for them to
leave the website and go to an OTAA to
book that same hotel. They should book
it right there and then. And that's
where Self really comes in to provide
this booking infrastructure married with
uh an end-to-end payment layer. We
believe that building a guest first
experience is so much better than just
building another B2B product even though
it was a B2B company. When we think of
the industry and we think of hotels as
clients, obviously the industry is left
behind from a technology perspective and
every product that they have was really
antiquated, especially on the guest
experience, right? Some of these systems
were built in the '60s. User behavior
was moving fast, but the change was
really slow. Our rapid growth since
launch was mainly driven by really being
charmingly relentless. You have to push
an agenda to an industry that I felt and
I still feel like the word sleepwalking
towards a precipice. A modern payment
solution like Apple Pay that uses a
cryptogram doesn't really work with a
system like Saber. And so we had to
build layers that allows a hotel that
still uses Saber to accept digital
wallet. And that was one of the
challenges that we solved. But then as
we kept on going, we've discovered a lot
of other challenges. And one of them is
providing flexibility in rates or even
providing a single API for platforms to
sell travel without having to build
every single component from the ground
up. And as a payment company at a core
or fintech company at a core,
transaction volume was key. And so we
had to achieve high GMV early on because
we were on growth mode. So you know we
went for hotels with higher average
daily rates or in the industry we call
it ADR so that we can achieve that
higher volume. Now again we scale beyond
just luxury but that was the starting
point and that's what helped us grow
really fast. Last year 2024 we 3xed our
revenue. We also helped hotel increase
conversion on their websites by 40% and
we also reduce cancellations by 44%. So
these are some of the ideas that we're
working on. If you go to an agentic on
AI search like Perplex City and you
search a hotel, the best hotel New York
City or I want to stay downtown or in
Soho, what if you can book them right
there and then without leaving
Perplexity? Bringing that to life, it's
so powerful. We're suited to build this
and we're super excited to deliver
it. Murakami says, "Pain is inevitable.
suffering is optional in his memoir. And
it's true as a founder, you're
constantly debating different ideas. A
key word that you know we hear every
hour of the day is trade-offs. You're
constantly trading off different ideas
and different assumptions. So sometimes
you get it wrong. Our biggest assumption
was that we could replace certain
systems, but that was more difficult
just because hotels are set in their
ways or perhaps they use an on-prem
system that it will take decades to
shift away from it. And so we had to
pivot our ways of thinking and work
cohesively with these systems and
integrate with them as opposed to
completely replacing them. really
focusing on what matters most and
focusing on what we are good at or we
are the best at. So a perfect example
Muse uh they are a cloudnative property
management system we're integrating with
and we're really excited to work with
them. We don't have to replace anything
they do but working together with them
we enhance the booking experience and so
building an integration layer across the
industry was key for our success and our
scale. The first customer on self-poke
is a resort called Nemain. This is a
time where almost every hotel in the
world was shut down. In July of 2020, I
flew to Pennsylvania and went to this
resort called Neolin and met with the
team, met with the owner and they were
really passionate about their product.
They were really passionate about
hospitality. Despite the fact that we
didn't have a full product yet and we
didn't have uh any track record at the
time or any client, they really believed
in us. They believed in the vision. It
wasn't because it was technical or it
would convert better or anything like
that. It was because we were obsessed
about providing guests a better user
experience. And the owner really cared
about that. She said at the time, if it
isospitable, we want it, right? And so
that's what we aimed for. And uh that
was our first client and they're still
our client. We're proud of that. Travel
is a human connection. Travel is a
gateway to culture. When you walk into a
store, you don't see just a sheet of
rates. You see products and you have a
conversation. So I think Self has big
visions of its existence, provide the
hospitality that the industry is meant
to provide anyways from day
one. Schumaker Formula 1 driver said
once there is passion, motivation is
there and I feel my passion was always
travel. So I was motivated to do so. I
think leaving Algeria was allowed me
to continue to dream bigger. Having that
freedom to create regardless of your
background or education or lack of which
in my case was really beneficial. It's
it's easy to give up. Um but you can't
be a quitter. You have to continue.
[Music]