In the first day, I think we added like
60K. I remember one of our engineers was
like, "Guys, we added 60K today. Oh my
god." And you I jumped in was like,
"Yep, it's cool, but like this is, you
know, this is like launch day. This is
going to go away." And that didn't
happen. Every single day, we kept adding
more and more ARR. In the first 2
months, we went from 0 to 20 million of
ARR. Everyone we were talking to had
never seen anything like it. We were
actually we were going to go out of
business last year. You know, we spent
seven years building out the core
technology of the product. couldn't
figure out how to actually effectively
monetize it. We had one last experiment
that we ran um is it's a product called
Bolt. Finding product market fit. It is
purely how many people you talk to. It
is purely that you people there maybe
early in their product career to kind of
have lots of cool ideas about things
they could build and whatever that are
not really attached to the reality of
the actual end user customer using the
product, what they're trying to do with
it, the challenges they're currently
running into with it. One of the things
we really invested in early on with Bolt
was like community. You know, we've
hired in a couple of folks who their
entire job is just talking to our users.
And so I think that's really the only
way you can meaningfully scale the full
cycle of user feedback is just having
great people that are in your community
or on your actual core team. That's
their entire job and they're all working
together. You have to learn how to be
intellectually honest with yourself. And
it's like, am I not giving up because
that's what people say you should do, or
am I not giving up because I actually
really like I have conviction in this
and like I just want to see this I I
really want to see this made possible. I
I think the only way I learned how to
determine when it was time to pivot
versus time to iterate was just
I'm Eric Simons. I'm the co-founder and
CEO of Stack Blitz and we're the
creators of Bolt. new. People went to
bolt.new, typed in the idea of a website
or whatever that they wanted to make,
hit enter, and 30 seconds later, they
had a a web application ready to go.
First two months of launching Bolt, we
went from 0 to 20 million of ARR. The 3
months since then, we've added another
20 million of ARR just about, and we now
have almost 4 million registered users
and are continuing to grow like a weed.
I like computers from a pretty early
age. I was like building computers like
be gaming computers and that sort of
thing. That was actually when my
co-founder and I met was when we were
you I think around 12 or 13. The first
product that my co-founder and I built.
We basically built a version of Dropbox
before Dropbox existed. And this is back
in like 2006 or 7. At that time, the way
that you kind of bring your digital
documents between school and home was
like USB flash drives. You're like 12 or
13 or whatever. You're going to forget
this, right? You're going to leave this
at home. Happened all the time. And so
we had the idea of like, hey, let's just
make a digital storage service that
people can upload their homework to or
whatever. And it took off like wildfire
like the entire many school districts in
Illinois and just kind of across the
Midwest started using this thing. I
think at that time I was I was like 18
or 19. I for come out Silicon Valley. We
had gone through one of these
accelerator program. At that time they
would give you like 20K. So we went
through that money and then we're out of
money but we the product wasn't ready to
launch. And so I was like what do you
do? We just so happened to had access to
the AOL building at that time because
one of our investors said was renting
office space out of there. So I had a
key card to get into the AOL building
and so there's couches here, you know, I
could sleep on the couch, there's a gym
and so they have showers. I was 19.
Expectations for quality of of living
are pretty low, I think, at that age.
And so I I ended up just, you know,
starting to live out of out of their
headquarters. I I would I was just
coding from 9:00 a.m. to 11:00 p.m.
12:00 p.m. I did that for like I think
like 4 months um until they they
eventually someone like someone finally
caught on that I was living in their
headquarters and they they found me and
threw me out at like 5:00 in the
morning. I didn't know anyone in Silicon
Valley. I'm not from California. I went
and like slept on a table at Starbucks
until they opened.
Thinking was a company that we didn't
really intend to be a company.
Basically, we had a whole bunch of
different startup ideas we were trying
on the side. We were building lots of
different web applications as a result
for each of these startups to stay
afloat. We were like, "Okay, you know,
we actually know a lot about building
web applications cuz we're we're doing
it so much. We could probably like teach
folks online and, you know, charge for
like our courses and and make money to
keep us afloat so we can keep trying
other ideas." Kind of the funny thing is
like of all the things we were working
on at that time, Thinkster was the most
successful of all of them. We were
teaching a lot of people. We had like I
think it's at like 100,000 something
people that were you know using this
site uh to learn how to do web
development. And the biggest problem the
people learning were having. I mean this
is common with anyone that's learning
how to program is not even like learning
how to write the code but it's actually
setting up your development environment
which is basically mean setting up your
computer to be able to even like run
code. That is a huge huge huge challenge
whether you're like a beginner or you're
an advanced developer. We were running
into this problem with the people using
Thinkster of they they just couldn't get
the stuff set up in their environment to
even learn how to write the code. And we
had the realization like okay actually
it should be possible theoretically to
just kind of like run an entire dev
environment inside of the browser
itself. You know not using servers, not
install anything locally like we can
actually run it in a web page, you know,
inside of a browser tab. And we were
looking at all these different
technologies that have released in
browsers and we were like someone must
have done this already, right? Like cuz
we we were just trying to solve our own
problem. We weren't trying to start a
company like we were just trying to
teach people on Thinkster. We looked
around and there was just nothing. There
is nothing that could actually do it. I
kind of knew that this is like something
very different at that point because it,
you know, it's like I'd never run it
across something like this where I kind
of technically knew the underpinnings
that this should be possible, but yet no
one had gone and done it. That key
insight was really what led us to start
stacks cuz we were like, "Okay, well
that would be huge for people learning
how to code to not have to set up
environments. It would make it way more
accessible. people could just use this
as an environment to just keep building
in like why would you even need to set
up a local environment necessarily. So
that was kind of the origin story of
stacks and it came out of thankster
directly.
We had spent half a decade building
building out this technology. The the
problem is that anyone that really
understands how to write software
already knows how to get stuff set up on
their local computer and will tend to
actually just gravitate towards that
because they are super familiar with it.
The issue is if you're going to build
something that's web- based that is
getting people to actually leave their
their environment is a huge challenge.
We tried out a whole bunch of different
experiments um over the course of the
past, you know, 2 years or whatever. All
of them were very cool. generally like
the people that that try these things
out thought they were really awesome but
it didn't move the needle from like a a
monetization standpoint. My co-ounder
and I have like talked about you know do
should we pack it in shut down the
company and so that was you know like
last year we made the decision my
co-founder and I um with our with our
board and stuff of like okay we're going
to spend the rest of this year going and
trying everything that we think is cool
idea and and if that doesn't work out
we'll have left no stone unturned and
we'll go and kind of prepare to kind of
start spinning things down. How would I
walk away from this knowing that I I
gave it everything I had? Like last year
when as this was kind of going on with
the company, I also had my first child
and if you talk to anyone that has a
kid, you don't get a lot of sleep. It's
pretty high stress. So, I had a lot of
challenges kind of going on just from
the personal side, the work side. I woke
up one morning last April after my
daughter was born and I was like, I'm
going to do an iron man, like a full
iron man. And and I and it was like 6
months from that. I never ran a marathon
or whatever. the six months um you know
of last year I was kind of bringing full
intensity to every part of my life like
physically going and training for this
thing mentally with with my job uh going
and you know really figuring out leaving
no stone unturned and just trying a lots
of different experiments etc and so kind
of bringing full intensity to those
things and and I got to tell you I've
never been happier in my life um I've
never been happier in my life really
investing in in myself my co-workers and
my products and my family and my
business with just such uh intense
dedication and I is okay with whatever
the outcome was. If we end the year and,
you know, our destiny is the same, so be
it. Let the the universe, you know, let
the universe decide, right? Um, I've
done everything that I possibly can do.
And Bolt was like the last the last
experiment we had before we're going to
kind of start winding things down. Uh,
what Bolt allows you to do is like to
actually, you know, using just text, you
can type in an idea of an app or a
website you want, it'll build it. The
launch strategy for Bolt was like we put
out a tweet. Like that was it. There was
no blog post. There's no press release.
So there's just like a tweet and and
that tweet ended up going viral. So what
ended up happening is people they saw
our tweet, they went to bolt.new, typed
in the idea of a website or whatever
that they wanted to make, hit enter, and
30 seconds later they had a a web
application ready to go. In the first
day, I think we added like 60K. I
remember one of our engineers was like,
"Guys, we added 60K today. Oh my god."
And you I jumped in was like, "Yep, it's
cool, but like this is, you know, this
is like launch day. This is going to go
away." And that didn't happen. Every
single day, we kept adding more and more
ARR. In the first 2 months, we went from
0 to 20 million of ARR. Everyone we were
talking to had never seen anything like
it. It was, I mean, just an unbelievable
shift in the destiny of of our company.
This episode is sponsored by Atio, the
AI native CRM for the next era of
companies. Connect your email and ATIO
instantly builds your CRM right before
your eyes with every company contact and
interaction you've ever had enriched and
organized. As an entrepreneur, every
email and meeting is an opportunity to
learn more about your client. ATO helps
you do just that. ATO's call
intelligence feature records your
meetings and gives you AI insights both
during and after your customer calls.
That's not all. You can use the AI
research agents to qualify leads,
identify expansion opportunities, and
more. You can then build AI powered
automations to tackle some of your most
complex business processes, allowing you
to focus on what's important, building
key relationships while ATIO does the
rest. Join thousands of companies who
are already using Atto to power their
businesses. Visit the link in the
description to begin your twoe free
trial with Atio.
So I'd actually had the idea for Bolt
about a year ago, February of 24. At
that time, the Frontier models like
OpenAI or whatever have you. You we had
actually tried to build a prototype with
Bolt. We spent a couple of weeks doing
that. What we ended up finding was the
output just was not good enough. Like
you would tell it to build an app and it
just oftent times it would be broken or
it wouldn't look good. it wouldn't
function properly, which kind of like
ruins the experience. So, we we put that
project on the shelf and we're like,
"Okay, maybe we'll come back to this at
some point in the future when when these
AI models get better." Back in May, we
just so happened to kind of get a sneak
preview of the new stuff that was coming
from Enthropic with Sonnet 3.5 coding
model that has changed software
development period. You we got a kind of
sneak peek of it and we were like, "This
is good. I mean, this is going to change
everything we think." And so we kind of
pulled the pulled bull off the shelf and
yeah took the the latest APIs from
Enthropic pulled them together and
launched it within 90 days of that back
after chatbt had launched a lot of
companies were just kind of like adding
AI stuff to their products and not even
in a very thoughtful way but it was kind
of like people just wanted to be like
relevant and kind of you know show that
they were had an AI strategy and we
didn't cuz we were just like we don't
see the value of this. it's not clear
how this is actually going to make the
experience that much better, right? And
all of our competitors went were you
churning on AI ideas. We held off u
because we just didn't see we didn't
have conviction on it. I think in in
retrospect the right move and when we
did find the right thing, we went all
in. And you kind of look at like the
competitors that we were going up
against then versus now it's like a lot
of them have either shut down some of
them have kind of started to pivot to AI
but like from like a user and revenue
perspective it's like bolt is the number
one thing
you know we get thousands of emails and
tickets and tweets and etc per day
sorting the the signal from the noise is
is you know very difficult challenge But
one of the things we really invested in
early on with Bolt was like community.
Like we have a very great community
around Bolt where you know folks really
love the product and there's these
people that that are really smart,
genuine, awesome folks that have stepped
up and really became like kind of
leaders in this community. Yeah. So
that's really how we've been able to
scale the both the support but also the
product feedback function because these
are folks that are like in our Discord
or Reddit or Twitter or whatever and
they're hearing what people are running
into. then they themselves might be
running into it and they'll and they'll
be like, "Hey, this is something we're
hearing a lot of. Here's maybe how you
you guys go about fixing it, etc." And
we also have people on our team who, you
know, we've hired in a couple of folks
who their entire job is just talking to
our users, helping them get unstuck with
stuff, hearing their feedback, etc. And
so, I think that's really the only way
you can meaningfully scale, you know,
uh, support and and the the full cycle
of user feedback is just having great
people that are in your community or,
you know, on your uh, actual core team.
That's their entire job and they're all
working together. You know, just bring
in all the data points, make good
decisions, and get the proper things
prioritized in the product. We like to
work on things that users have
specifically either like really asked
for where it's a big a big pain point or
alternatively, it's something that we've
validated that people want. I think it's
very easy for entrepreneurs and yeah,
people that are maybe early in their
product career to kind of have lots of
cool ideas about things they could build
and whatever that are not really
attached to the reality of the actual
end user customer using the product,
what they're trying to do with it, the
challenges they're currently running
into with it. And so a lot of this comes
down to just experience and like
fortunately we've been doing this for a
long time. Like my co-founder and I have
been building stuff for almost 20 years.
You know, having a good sense of these
are cool ideas, but we should probably
get to them later. These are really
important ideas. We should do them now.
These are really important high priority
things. They need to be fixed and you
know uh sorting accordingly
and and one of the interesting things
too actually about what we did is we
actually open sourced the core version
of bullet when we launched and like even
today it's like I think it's like the
most popular AI product you know by
users of revenue that actually has an
open source version. Like there's
nothing else out there that really has
that other than us. But it was clear to
us was like this is this is knowledge
that someone's going to open source this
at some point and we think it'll just be
actually a lot better for us and the AI
model providers etc. if this is
available for people to try out and fork
and improve and whatever have you which
ended up being a really key decision cuz
a lot of people use Bolt because they
can play around with the open source
version and fork fork it and make it
better and you know whatever have you.
We've invested a ton in the open- source
world in large part because like our
product really wouldn't work without
amazing open source software that's been
built for web development and and
otherwise. For us, it's you it's also
really important that that those people
building different web development tool
chains like Vit or whatever have you
also care about us and they want to make
sure that their these open source
projects work well in our technology and
our environment. And that's been really
key for us. Yeah, we became the largest
backer of Vit back in 2021. We have
multiple people on our team that all
they do is work on open source full-time
you. So I think uh developers love our
products. I think in some part because
we genuinely care about open source and
ensuring that folks uh working on open
source get compensated and have a way to
actually continue working on it in a
sustainable way.
I I think the only way I learned how to
determine when it was time to pivot
versus time to iterate was just trying a
lot of startup ideas. like that was you
over the course of like a decade through
that I kind of I I ended up building a
good gut instinct of when when we were
kind of at the end of the line on a
certain idea and it was like okay we
need to like pivot and try something
else instead. So my recommendation would
be to to if you think you need to go
deep on something and go along, do it.
And typically you're gonna you're you're
eventually going to find out one way or
the other if you were right or wrong and
then you learn from that. And and then
then if you were wrong, if you're like,
"Hey, we went really deep and it didn't
pan out." You have to just take that as
a lesson as part of the journey. When I
was younger and heard people give the
advice that I'm giving right now, the
takeaway that I would take then was
okay, so just don't give up like like no
matter what, just kind of like hold on
to this idea and don't give up, which is
like like I think generally
directionally good advice. But there's
actually like kind of a line where you
have to learn how to be intellectually
honest with yourself and it's like am I
am I not giving up because because
that's what people say you should do or
am I not giving up because I actually
really like I have conviction in this
and like I just want to see this I I
really want to see this made possible
and then seeing it all the way through
right cuz I think when you're when
you're starting and you're trying to
find that passion in that's kind of one
challenge and then the other side of is
you know we saw which is okay we built
this amazing thing Now, how do you
actually turn into a business? The
important part there is, you know, when
you're driving through hell, don't stop.
If you're going to go and and build a
business, go and try all the way through
and don't leave any stones unturned
because what you don't want then is to
look back and go, "Ah, man, we had this
really cool thing. I think it could have
been really, really important, but we
didn't actually we didn't do a full core
press and really make sure that we
exhausted all options before, you know,
spinning down or whatever.
AI's impact on software development is
uh I mean huge like I think I think it's
it's clear at this point that software
development is going to be probably the
number one application of AI that as far
as like a high leverage uh high impact
high revenue sort of thing. All the
world's software I think is going to be
meaningfully written by AI in years. I
think I think probably you know
singledigit sort of years. That doesn't
mean that software developers are going
away. There's a lot of things in
software development that are just
monotonous and not intellectually
challenging, right? It's just common
stuff that you're having to do to build
an application and AI just kind of
obliterates all that. Can just take care
of all that stuff for you so you can
actually work on like more complicated
high high value intellectually
challenging sort of tasks. And so I
think we're continue to see more and
more of that, right? We're see more and
more software built and it's also it's
enabling people to that are not software
developers to actually go and build
software, right? Whether you have an
idea for a website or an app like you
can go to Bolt today and do that. The
next 5 years of Bolt I think is it's
it's going to be something that from the
Fortune 100 to 10year-olds people are
building the future of how you you know
stream movies online, how you check your
bank account using a mobile app to a
game that a 10-year-old had the idea of,
right? All these things and some of that
stuff you can even do now with Folk,
right? But the the quality and the scale
of which you're going to be able to do
this stuff is going to be giant, right?
compared to to what you can do now.
Yeah.