okay
um Mac you go check that we have to
seriously the theory relies on who
checks right now no match I'll go I
never go I'll go I'm because I feel like
it might change something well we have
to introduce this as like the second
part
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
what's up guys we're back and we're
filming the second part of what we just
filmed because we all have more thoughts
and want to talk about it so we were
like why not just keep filming because
this is what we do every night but we'll
just leave the camera on and let us know
if you like like I don't know like
what
what I figured it out
this is crazy shut this off Nick shut
your AC off like I was just thinking
about oh dude he sounds like a dog from
Back to the Future like I figured it out
because the reason I'm thinking about it
is because I'm definitely just talking
about a movie right now
Back to the Future No that's what no the
future is he's going back to the future
no
but what I'm saying is they just made
that Netflix movie that we went to watch
the premiere of
but look both ways and it was that one
moment whether or not you became
pregnant or not affected her whole life
correct and it showed the two different
but it's like we're talking more than
that we're not talking more than that
but I'm but I'm just thinking that's why
I have this thought which goes back to
my proving point that nothing is fantasy
everything happened correct because that
probably actually happen to someone oh
my God yeah we're talking about the
government and [ __ ] if you didn't watch
last week's video watch last week's
video first crucial and then come back
right away okay but I just think like
like you grow up with like favorite
things this is my favorite color this is
my favorite book this is my favorite
movie this is my favorite thing parents
but then you look at that too correct
who's influencing your parents your
grandparents but also hold on you also
think Matt can you get something out of
you I don't know cause hold on think
about it those things when you're a kid
you grow up may forget about them all
it's one of them might stick but you
might forget about a lot of them but it
still matters deep within what your
favorite things were like it may not
matter as seriously as you think but all
of those things that you consume as a
child like the internet like all those
things have a lasting effect on what's
happening to you now I don't know why
Nick's Antics are just making me laugh
right now
like what do you think like where are
you in that moment
do you ever feel like you could do
something like like hold on orange juice
like over the top no let's get out of
that that's okay think think I have one
no I have one hold on hold on okay hold
on I'm not gonna let you talk the whole
time I'm gonna say one more [ __ ]
thing let me go no all right think about
it if you're like if you're like goal
you're on a walk right bro
what are you looking at can I finish and
then you can speak my thought is if
you're don't do that if you're like if
you're walking on like a path and your
goal is like trip someone walking
towards you oh that's a bad goal like
you just want to trick someone you gotta
you have to trip one person what if you
trip the wrong person
everything could change
do you know what I'm saying like if
you're going like like if you if you're
like well you're debating oh I'm gonna
try oh and then you just let them walk
past when you trip the next person
huh it could be so different I use you
ready for this the street light Theory
every single time I know what you mean
hit a red light I hear you if you if it
was yellow and you went through it you
could get in like a car accident and die
like five minutes in the future and not
even know it or if you hit a red light
and you're all mad
because it's like imagine you get to a
red light and you're like oh [ __ ] I
missed that red light yes but you would
be saying oh [ __ ] I'm dead in five
minutes correct like isn't that I think
the same thing I think of that all the
time like when we hit like a red light
or like if we leave the house and Mom's
like wait one second boys I want to like
give you something I'm like what if mom
giving us this thing puts us in a crash
like no puts us like not in the crash
like imagine we were about to leave and
get in a crash but then Mom just asking
us to like stay in and grab one thing
didn't like perfect timing that's a
perfect timing no perfect timing yeah
like the stars yeah
we flooded with diamonds like I just
think of I don't know what the time is
hold on I think I'm like nav shout out
my brother I think I'm like even bust
down Rollie flutter with diamonds enough
can't tell what the time is I just know
it's perfect I don't know like uh piano
man man oh man what give me something
else I don't know because I like these
theories but it's like I don't got
enough of them to keep going right now
talk about like everything happens for a
reason
that's you bud but I know but I believe
it but I just want to give you a chance
to talk about it before I do I don't
know like what you want me to talk about
okay wait I have a question go do you
guys do you think
no cause you talking Talking Tom
okay so I'm gonna right now do you think
there's certain people set in our paths
by like a higher being like the
government and [ __ ] like ascending
people into like local places just to
like survey the area no oh my God no
like you don't need to go get that
AutoZone now we need to see what's going
on no really no no I feel that way a lot
like do you ever think I think I think
there's a dog if there's a thousand
people in a Target there's no way one's
not one can you wanna hear me out oh my
God
I think there's a difference in between
thinking this Theory but then also being
a paranoid schizophrenic no and I think
because we're not paranoid if we don't
let it alter I think I just think of
like
what Alters life because Nick will walk
around and he'll I just think like oh
we're going to Home Depot if you go to
Home Depot right and you have the goal
oh I'm buying a hammer today because I
need to hammer now that's your end goal
for going into that Home Depot with that
hammer you're going to get a hammer so
you can hammer now correct yes then I
think oh someone else could be walking
around Home Depot
placed by the government holding a two
by four on their shoulder and they're
just like oh walk around because we need
you to find John oh my God I was looking
for a hammer because John is gonna
hammer a nail and then that nail is
gonna go through the wall knock a poster
of the other neighbor neighboring
apartment wall and it's gonna hit their
kids
hospital because they just know I don't
even think it's like the government like
they know what's good like I think it's
more of like Time Travelers that come
back
is there time travelers that like lurk
this because then they could have the
orange juice from the previous video
they could be like the guy could just be
like hey if you see someone walking
through in Home Depot with a hammer
right now because you need to stop him
ask him his name like oh John like yeah
John and then they take the whole they
take the two by four and side swipe his
feet knock him over now John can't go
home with the hammer I got it wow I
really you want to hear something crazy
yeah this is like your little Theory but
on a way less after my lips sorry I need
to go you want it you don't talk like we
talk we need you to be empowered go
because I'm not that empowered right so
[ __ ] get empowered go drink it
hold on your little stupid theory that
you have oh my God here's what I want to
say I'm not letting you continue to
speak to me okay then go die no I don't
have anything to say I just want you to
say
yeah
that you have going on right now okay
it's this it's like the same idea same
what not you know the whole thing
played back a little bit different right
did you know this is a proven fact by
the way very very true by who this is
real life but this happens see my thing
is I don't trust proven facts
you'll be like oh yeah that's true
because people have confirmed that that
work there you ready
jelly beans what I thought you were
gonna talk about like a candy factory
people at like carnivals and fairs pay
people just normal everyday looking
people to win the games no no not to win
the game The Walker revises he'll walk
around with the biggest stuffed animals
all day long just so that it looks like
the government that's like how the
government that's the government on a
minor scale correct yeah it's putting
false hope right in front of these
people's faces and then dangling it away
I'm choking them out and killing them
like some guy that working what if one
day I was just walking down like a
series oh man some dude working at a
carnival said that he got paid 25 an
hour to walk around holding a a four
foot teddy bear for like hours
open to close because if you walk by
that person twice I'm gonna be like you
need to get the [ __ ] out of here because
I know you're up to something no cause
like you just sit he'd sit just by the
game that he wanted at on on a bench for
like two hours too I'd walk by the bench
twice a week this guy's need to go home
I've seen him so many times but like
like they must have such a specific
routine tonight what if I was walking
down there
what
did you just sniff that no I looked oh
now listen to me listening listen reels
I don't like to listen when someone
starts with that okay can you listen to
me for a minute of course okay
imagine this right hold on let me get
comfortable oh
if you imagine if hold on I'm gonna put
in this parking lot imagine if there was
someone who started like over there and
they were just walking past us and we
were all like oh look like I walk and
walk or whatever and we're all just
chilling and we all like looked like
this way for a second because like
something went over there and we look
back nowhere to be found like he like
vanished from thin air no do we believe
in time traveling I I believe in like
some like there's definitely like
something that just like can happen like
do you ever walk up like the eye is such
like a deceiving thing because you can
like we can see this AutoZone but we
don't know what's going inside think
about this hold on every single one of
these places around us every single one
was put there built serves a purpose
painted colored put exactly how it is
right where it is right now have you
ever been in that building no how long
have you lived in the city my whole life
they could be running the government in
there and none of us know about it right
under Arc noses or I just go to a
different Auto Body well I'm just
talking like in general
every single like you could walk by like
every I think every person never walk by
Time Travelers but yeah I know
yes yeah I'm on to you the one in L.A um
you just walk by and be like I'm on to
you no because it's usually like what
would be oh my God what are the top
three dead giveaways to you that that
person's a time traveler go I have mine
one the way they just walk when they
walk up in the step when they walk no
way we should make this a guide after we
talk about it we'll say hey
when they know when they're on a clear
path like up on this know where they're
going correct like if someone's like if
someone started walking from there to
there full speed not even like looking
other directions just no like even for
checking for cars I think crossing a
street without looking both ways isn't a
sign of weakness it's a sign of strength
you oh my God
I couldn't walk oh my God and you know
there's no cars oh my God I feel you I
hear you and everything hold on this is
a big the confidence in the walking it's
style too and like something about
slightly being out of place because you
don't want to be too in place
you know if I if we're at the beach
right and there was no no hold on you're
jumping you need to say one everyone
needs to say one no I'm saying what I'm
saying is that's what it is it's like if
you're at the beach and some tribe
traveler walks by in just a bathing suit
you're gonna be like no that's because
that's like too obvious they try to
blend in but like not that much so
that's like a a bathing suit and maybe
like flip-flops holding a beach ball
that's more time very time travel so
it's like
too much I don't think the time
travelers I personally this is two this
is the second one
how to catch a time traveler I think the
second one is more of like a
I don't think they change as often as
you think like oh they're going to like
the beach so they get a beach towel a
Beach Blanket Beach shorts like all
those things I think it's one universal
it's like an outfit that could fit in
any scenario yes like a weird pattern
but like long and like not like you know
I feel like they'd wear like a very
specific article clothing that could
just fit in any scenario I got a really
good right like that the need from horn
here's who like you could use that for
everything not that in general every
time traveler is gonna have on and it's
a dead giveaway sunglasses no
a long coat nope it's pretty obvious
ly headphones no once I said you guys
are gonna be like yep yeah tell me you
need it tell me
a wash a watch not even a walking band
like anything like they gotta know what
time it is they need to know where they
ended up oh my
[Music]
oh my God they have to be like oh 8 45
and then like but it's gonna be like
it's gonna be an old yes it's gonna be
like an old-timey Beach
we should do like a time travel triplet
prank on people don't say this because
they're gonna want it and we can't like
I can't orchestrate right now no in the
farm for our future I want to watch now
on my wrist I don't have a watch but I
want one now I like a vintage watch that
like makes it look it has to fit in
every era that you look like no not even
just like really old I feel like that'd
be the one dead giveaway they wear like
an old watch everywhere yeah that's what
I just said no because it wouldn't fit
in every hour I feel like a time
traveler
oh my God I need an old watch now I need
a vintage watch I need what I need to
look okay okay whatever dude but listen
wait but we're only on two I feel like
if it's I probably had a vintage watch
if they went to the Future it'd become a
future watch
an adaptable watch an adaptable watch
that's a good thing that's like the one
thing they want to keep like the same
yeah I feel like sunglasses are huge I
agree
I feel like a time traveler also another
thing I hate to say this I feel like
you'd be born actually I don't exist I
think you'd be born into like time
traveling like the world of it you know
what I mean yeah like your parents would
have to be Time Travelers and stuff and
I feel like it's kind of like you can't
have too many time travelers watching
this you can't have too much like you
and they travel back in time to erase
this video I feel like the time traveler
couldn't have like this is the third one
about a time traveler I feel like they
couldn't have that much uniqueness about
them yeah and I'm saying that in like a
way of like they couldn't have like
what's it called like a lot of freckles
on their face because that's kind of
obvious like they just like it's a
unique looking person like a time
traveler could never be one of those
people like a blue and brown eye no it
has because it's something that stands
out so much to you like it has to be
like a very basic looking like like you
just talk about like
a human being and that's what it is yeah
like anyone that looks like just like
very human like you're just you yeah
like but so like I dropped an ice cube
you're just that you know you can't have
too much going on for you you know yeah
like if you guys had a time machine what
would yours be but wait can we talk
about the three main things
hold on we have to go back we're gonna
talk about the amazing we have to just
say it in order walking this sort of
like the three ways you could find a
time traveler out of the ordinary space
no the three ways that you could find a
time traveler right in front of your
eyes go the pep in the step with no
hesitation
the watch the watch they have a watch on
at all times
and then slightly in the ordinary they
look very normal and basic yep the
fourth one was sunglasses sunglasses not
even no it's like they have the attire
that can fit in any situation and then
sunglasses okay
good
what would be your like the DeLorean in
Back to the Future she just wanted to go
back to the future so I brought that
girl into the lion tell us from Back to
the Future
do you know that Nick I don't care
what would be your time travel vessel go
mine would be a cup
now this is where I lose myself this is
where I lose my mind no that was my
final [ __ ] straw why
you have the option of any vessels okay
no you're right you're right she's a cop
you're right you're right a bike a bike
oh that's a good one I can see Matt on a
time travel too clunky they're too
clunky
it has to be like uh well I'm just
thinking you gotta find it you know if
you have to go back to the pilgrims
you're not gonna bring a bike you know
like what the [ __ ] is that that's like
oh oh I know next like a coin a coin yes
yes
next would be a coin I said that before
and not a staff because that wouldn't
fit I know hold on I know I'm always
talking about staffs yep a cane a longer
like a good hook no because
I changed mine no it'd be like a pocket
okay I changed mine oh my God I changed
mine no one asked yeah go ahead I care I
just like giving you [ __ ] go
a key
but the the lock part is the star at the
end and then the handle part is a moon
and then oh my God
not because then I think you're an alien
you gotta revisit that one okay star in
the end normal key okay yeah yeah Matt
what about you maybe it's star in the
clock
I have another question after I'm making
my watch yes that's a valid take I love
it great one or maybe like a ring I feel
like oh a ring yeah
or you just take the ring and you tap it
on the watch and like tap oh my God a
ring that you take off and it clicks
into the wall now retwist it I think I
think hold on
okay last question last question well
for me yes go for yeah for this video
last question what would be your time
traveler agent name super important
question agent name like I just know
what mine would be no I don't I don't
know mine I Wanna Know
click first and last
no they'd just be like agent star time
because I was thinking oh that's cool
start time for Christopher's like his
star with the clock on the key star time
was my agent name for Chris Starkey star
time Starkey star time works better no
Starkey Starkey sounds stupid Starkey
but short like connected like a dog's
name like a star key yes
agent Starkey oh I like that oh yeah I'm
gone no mine would be last name Ender
first name Cal calendar
stabs you time travels and he's gone no
it'd be more of like OJ
Au calendar that is great
you need a normal middle name because
right now you need no middle name
that that was like you've ever said in
the car I love that that was awesome
calendar
wow thank you
Starkey calendar and Starkey yep oh my
God these are all so good
calendar was great you guys both were
giving yours
oh yeah but someone come up with mine no
I don't know and I came up with mine as
well what would mine be a little bit I
feel like there's nothing you'd want
you'd be like
[Music]
agent goofball no
no something you would know beforehand
like I feel like I'd just be like the
owner of time like I'd know it all so I
feel like I gotta pick like an overall
good name for it you know the timekeeper
oh my God yeah just like that like
something just like that covers it all
yeah the time keeper like it's very like
out there and obvious but I'd be like in
control like I don't think like if
somebody wants a time travel they have
to check in with you not even if they
have to check in I mean I don't think
that I'd go on like the missions like oh
hit someone with a 2x4 claim you think I
think I'd be like oh he's the time you'd
be like the administrator yes so I think
the time keeper works okay he has to be
like wait I'd send you guys on like a
job yeah like oh I got an old [ __ ] she
needs arms
television Target who needs orange juice
to the face calendar and Starkey go and
then you guys go like all right time
keeper we'll be back in a minute with
that thank you guys for watching this
Friday video we'll see you in a minute
and be be safe if you time travel and
just yeah you know all that see in a
minute