If you're not embarrassed by your first
version, you shipped to late in AI. I
would even go as far as to say like if
your first version works, you're not
thinking big enough. You should build
for the future generations of the model
so much and the models are improving so
rapidly that the current generation of
models should barely support your
vision. Just barely. If you spend any
time on Twitter, you feel like there is
so much competition in AI agents. You
feel like there is a new a new company
coming out every week. And yet when
you're out in the market like us, you
don't run into competitors that often.
So I sometimes compare it to like
there's like trillions of trillions of
stars in the universe and yet the
universe is 99.9% empty space. It's the
same, right? There's a lot of us
nominally, but somehow it feels empty.
And I think because the market is just
so enormously huge. These people have
gone about their entire life hearing
everyone tell them the reason why they
couldn't do things. But actually, if you
do it, you're going to be very, very
successful. You're going to make a lot
of money. you're going to build
something very impactful with the twof
world. It becomes addictive. It's like a
ha like tell me you can't I can't do it.
I'll show you I can.
I'm Flo Killo. I'm the CEO of Lindy
which is the world's easiest way to
build AI agents with no code. Lindy is a
setup of building blocks that you can
put together to build your own AI agents
and to get them to do anything. One big
use case that we have is a customer
support. Step one, customer support
ticket arrives by email. Step two, you
can have a condition building block that
basically branches up the agent. So you
can be like, hey, is this a customer
asking a question or is this a customer
asking for a refund? Step three, for
example, if they're asking a question,
you can use our knowledge base building
block, your FAQ, your website, a PDF,
your notion, whatever you want. Then you
can ask maybe finally step four to
answer the support ticket based on the
knowledge that it extracted in the
knowledge base. We have quintupled uh in
revenue over the last 6 months and
roughly doubled the size of the team
since then.
I think it's Jeff Bezos who said
something like people always comment
about how fast everything is always
changing like he likes to focus on what
doesn't change right in a world thing is
always changing it finds these pillars
of stability to hang on to and I think
what doesn't change is the user and a
lot of preferences of the user will just
immutable that really surprised us. We
released the platform and we started to
have quite a few users ask us for HIPPA
compliance which is this regulatory
standard in the US that allows you to
work with sensitive health information.
So people started to be like can you be
HIPPA compliant? Can you be HIPPA
compliant? I want to use legal for
healthcare use cases. And we were like
why like what do what do you want us to
be HIPPA compliant for? And that's when
we we understood the use case which is
turns out it's huge and it's a big
industry today. There's a lot of really
big companies dedicated solely to this
use case where doctors spend a lot of
time taking notes during patient visits.
They call it charting because there's
like a very specific standard of notes
that they call soap notes. Some of them
started building Lindy's to help them
build get their soap notes. So they use
Lindy on a mobile phone and they
recorded the conversation using the
record feature that we have and then
they would prompt Lindy to give them the
format of notes. In the case of AI
agents, the user wants something that's
easy to use. We want something that's
effective, something that works,
something that's simple to use,
something that's affordable, something
that's fast. These things are always
going to be the case. And the problem
that the user is trying to solve is is
fairly constant as well.
LinkedIn's founder Hoffman, who said
this famous thing, if you're not
embarrassed by your first version, you
shipped too late in AI. I would even go
as far as to say like if your first
version works, you're not thinking big
enough. You should build for the future
generations of the model. so much and
the models are improving so rapidly that
the current generation of models should
barely support your vision just barely.
That was very much our case at Lindy
like for a long time the product simply
did not work because the models were not
good enough. The very first version of
the product was just a prompt. So
instead of building this AI agent using
these building blocks that I mentioned,
it was literally just writing text.
Because it's just a prompt, you're just
trusting this AI model to basically
follow your instructions. It may not
follow the instructions. You're you're
like praying the LM gods. Even to this
day, even to the frontier models, like
fast forward two or three years, to this
day, Claude Opus 4 or OpenAI, I use the
very most frontier models right now,
even they very often struggle. We are
building for the next generation of
models. The current product doesn't work
and yet we keep building because we
expect that the next generation of
models will make it work. And the way I
characterize it today is it's it's sort
of AI in turn. It can perform simple
enough tasks. Anything that you can
describe in a step-by-step uh fashion is
something that that Lindy can do. Over
the long term, the vision is to build a
full-blown AI employees, an AI agent
that can do anything that the human
employee can do on a computer. So,
that's my piece of advice is like skate
for the puck is going to be in in Steve
Jobs world and skate for where the the
next generation of models is going to be
and build with that in mind.
Don't build a mine until you've you've
found gold. I really identified these
two different distinct phases in a
startup life cycle. One, you prospect.
You look for the right mining site where
you can find gold. And once you've
struck gold, but only then do you build
a mine. And building a mine is basically
hiring a team and raising money and all
of that stuff. It is really hard to move
a mine. And so if if you build too large
a mine and you haven't found gold, what
you need to do is you need to destroy
your mine. You need to fire your team.
So I started at Uber as a software
engineer. I took a six months break
after Uber. So COVID breakout, everybody
was stuck at home. So I was just on my
computer at home and I I read a blog
post by John Palmer called the spatial
interfaces sort of extolling the virtues
of of spatial design. And there's almost
a call to action in that blog post
that's like I wonder what a special zoom
would look like. I was like oh it's a
good question like I started like
hacking it together and in the span of a
couple of hours they just had like a
prototype of like a special zoom. It's
like you see your video in a bubble. You
can move the bubble around on like a two
dimensional canvas and you can only hear
and be held by people around you. And
again, this coincided perfectly with
COVID. And so I started hosting virtual
happy hours in there with my friends
like, "Hey, join me in that space. I I
built and I sort of got sucked in little
by little. I just kept adding features
and I realized it could be like a
collaboration space. I added a
whiteboard and so forth. And then I
realized like oh my god, like
everybody's working remotely right now.
Like you know this could be a virtual
office. Like there is a market here." I
released it. It got traction. like bunch
of users started sagging up, raised some
money and then like the company was just
after the races. When COVID subsided and
when people returned to the office, Team
Flow started not going so well and the
growth stalled completely. What finally
convinced me that there was simply no
market anymore was like looking around
and seeing all the competitors of which
we had many like good teams like really
good people and they had raised a lot of
money and none of them were taking off.
So that's when I just realized like
there is no there is no market. That's
what I did. It was extremely painful,
but I fired twothirds of the team and it
coincided with the release of the GPT3
API. So, it was before the GPT. It was
like mid 2022 and we built a meeting
recorder in team flow and we were very
interested in the GP3 API and so we were
like what can we do with it? So, we we
did what now a lot of applications do
which is a meeting summarization. And
then sales team came to me and they were
like flow can this thing also update our
sales force after sales calls and we
were like sure I don't see why not. And
so we basically kept building and kept
fleshing out that like Salesforce
integration and then HubSpot integration
and and that's when it clicked for us
like we realized like wait a minute we
can get the LLM to not just generate
text for us but generate API calls like
generate actual actions for us and so
that's when we were like wait a minute
like this can be like an an entire AI
employee basically we got sucked in to
that and again it coincided with first
team flow stalling out we got excited
about this AI thing jp came about in the
middle exploded and like oh my god like
AI is real it's happening and so we just
decided in 2023 to completely fool the
team flow and just focus on the AI
opportunity and and I I did that very
deliberately and it's painful as a
founder you need to deliberately
mismanage your team you need to let them
alone and they're going to hate you like
where is our CEO what's he doing all day
I'm looking for gold like the mind
doesn't matter the mind is so very
mismanaged right now and you guys are
lost at sea and I decide not to care
because I'm going to spend my time
digging for gold um that's that's what I
Don't don't don't build a mind before
you you found the gold.
My leadership philosophy is the job of a
CEO is to win. And so that that's my
guiding light. Epistemologically that is
how I will define what is right or
wrong. Perhaps I would compare it to
gardening. You know it starts with like
selecting the seeds. So I really do
believe like half the job is just
recruiting like getting the right people
into the door. Like again I think it's
Kra Boy who said the people you hire is
the company you build. and I'm reminded
every day of how true that is. It's half
the job. So just getting the right
seeds. If you don't have that, the plant
won't be good. And then giving a
direction to the team and to the seed
like that's the sign. You grow in this
direction, you know. So that's that's
the second big part of the job is just
setting the vision and guiding the plant
as it grows, but you can't grow for the
plant. Plant won't grow the way you want
it to. So you've got to fire people.
There's this amazing book by Bill Walsh
called The School Takes of Itself,
right? And so the philosophy of Bill
Walsh is like success consists of just
two things. one, identifying the right
inputs that lead to success. And two,
nailing each and every one of these
inputs perfectly, right? If you do these
two things, you will win. If you don't
win, it means you either don't
understand what it takes to win or
you're not doing what it takes to win.
That's just one of these two things. And
so, it's actually funny. We on boarded a
new employee this morning. He's the
first one of his function. And I spent
the day yesterday, Sunday, like
literally seven plus hours just writing
an 18 pages long document about this is
precisely exactly we we call it a
standard of excellence. Step by step by
step. This is the job. Again, that's the
plan. It's like if you if you see them
doing something wrong, it's like no.
It's like your guard is like, "No, this
is not what you this is not what this is
what you do." And you just keep putting
these guardrails and you refer back to
the dock that you wrote. Absolutely, you
should micromanage. The reason why you
are in a position of of of authority is
because someone with capital most likely
trusted you and your taste. So you you
are entitled, you are in fact obligated
to micromanage. That that's why you're
in your seat. You exercise your taste.
You exercise your judgment. You exercise
your your knowledge about your business,
your industry, your user, your product,
and you guide the plant. That's my
philosophy.
I view building a company as a way to
bring an ambitious bold vision to
reality. I don't think the Lin startup
model leads you there. I'm a huge fan of
Peter Thiel's thinking on this. He calls
it definite optimism. It's like a 2x2.
You've got a definite and indefinite and
optimism and pessimism. And so definite
or indefinite is like do you know or do
you not know? There's a lot of
indefinite optimists in tech. I view
crypto as the the eternal indefinite
optimist industry. It's like we don't
know what's going to happen. We don't
know why things are going to go well,
but wag me, we're all going to make it.
You know, everything's going to go so
well, but we we can't exactly tell you
half. Instead, Peter Tiel pushes for
this vision of a definite optimism.
Like, you must have a crisp opinion, a
well-defined opinion of what the world
will look like in the future, what it
should look like, what it must look
like, and bring that vision to life.
What percent of your time did you spend
in 2022 speaking to an AI? It was 0%.
Today in 2025, it's it's a lot more than
that. And I think the trend is going to
continue and continue and continue. AI
agents are basically in the short term
going to turn us all into managers.
Instead of doing individual contributor
work, you're going to manage a swoop of
AI agents doing your work. I sometimes
describe it as like imagine if any
random 25year-old could have the same
impact in the world as Google. And so I
I think that AI agents are going to do
to the world of business at large what
the internet has done to media. It's
going to be a very powerful leveling of
the playing field. It's going to unlock
opportunity to for everyone regardless
of their network or their capital or
their access or their geography. It's
just really going to come down to their
vision and the ideas they have and their
ability to leverage AI agents.