The worst thing that can happen to
someone who's making anything in the
world is
apathy. You put something out and nobody
cares. The second worst scenario is you
put something out and everybody is very
happy with it because that means there's
nothing else left to do. When these are
your most dedicated user, they have a
thousand things to complain about. In AI
especially, if you can do X, people now
want to do Y. Unlike traditional
products where you know okay this has
feature A, B and C and this is how
feature A interacts with feature B like
you know the whole state with large
models people can do anything in it.
People can generate anime. People can
generate videos of a tomato rolling down
a hill. With large models you don't know
what your users are going to do and
there's no physical scenario in which
you could test all the capabilities of
the
model. So you really have to see what
people are doing with it, where it's
succeeding, where it's
failing. Hey, my name is Amed. I'm one
of the co-founders and CEO of Luma AI.
At Luma, we are building multimodal
general intelligence and that starts
with building world's best video models.
We have so far raised $200 million from
Andre and Horovitz, Amplify Partners,
Matrix partners, Nvidia, AMD, as well as
Amazon. Lumi is training models that are
able to learn and generate video, audio,
text all together. Our premise is that
by building models that train like human
brain, we will be able to not only
generate worlds but actually solve the
limitations of
LLMs. I grew up in India. As a child
growing up, I was mostly very deeply
interested in in physics from from very
early on. Actually I spent majority of
my time honestly uh you know learning
about advanced physics and trying to you
know understand how the world works.
Honestly I studied math and physics in
college. I was about to go for a
graduate school PhD in in physics.
Around the same time I also started like
building iOS apps. My first one was
actually uh uh this one for solving
differential equations got actually
relatively popular uh in the app
store. That was very interesting like
you know once you make something that
other people find useful doesn't matter
large number or small number that really
kind of changes you then a couple of my
friends uh started a company I left to
join them instead and as time has gone
on a few of my friends uh their company
was acquired by Apple at Apple I started
working on this agent system called
shortcuts or workflows when we shipped
that I learned that there was this part
of the world where in Apple where this
new thing was being built some of my
friends had gone there already and they
got completely silent about what they
were doing and it was this insane secret
like if you don't want me to know
anything don't tell me it's a secret. I
really wanted to figure out what the
hell was going on and turns out they
were building this new thing called the
vision pro. So I joined the team that
was working on this really ambitious
project for 3D capturing the world with
vision pro. The idea was if you're
wearing this thing we can take you
anywhere because we have full control
over what your eyes see. And this was
really close to my heart because like
you know anything that has to do
anything with simulating reality that
really draws me very close. I started to
work on that project and I worked on
that for about 3
years. This was around also the time
when huge things were happening in
language model. In 2020 it like really
hit me in the head because uh the two
things came out. It was the Delhi paper
uh from OpenAI and this paper for 3D
instruction called Nerf neural radiance
fields. And honestly like that was
really interesting to me because all the
things we were doing procedurally by
writing like you know a handwritten code
and for rendering and for for capturing
and reconstruction if these two things
work you can learn to represent the
world you don't you don't need to do any
rendering you don't need to like write
any graphics algorithms and what Dali
proved was that from
nothing you can generate images you know
that was a huge thing for me Nerf gave
you like static 3D worlds and Dali gave
you images But our world is extremely
dynamic. There's like a lot of stuff
happening right like you know we walk
around cars move around clouds move all
these kind of things. The question was
how can we actually simulate that world?
So I started experimenting with these
things. All I did was really like you
know experiment with these methods write
all kinds of networks train them. In
about like you know 3 months time I was
extremely convinced that this is how
most videos things humans see will be
made. And at my work, I was doing all
these traditional techniques, right? So
my choices were stay at Apple, right?
Try to convince this big giant
organization that like, hey, this is the
future and and that we should do this
and that like, you know, I need $100
million to actually do this or go find
15, 20 of the most brilliant people on
the planet who can actually do this for
us. I tried this at Apple first like,
yeah, this is not going to happen here.
Uh, I left and we started Lumi in 2022.
In 2023, we built a 3D generative model
actually called Genie. At that time,
large scale infrastructure for training
and coders and things like that didn't
exist. So, we had to build and invent
all these pieces basically. So, we
started that work. We built a lot lot of
large scale data collection systems,
large scale training systems, all those
kind of things. It took us about a year,
year and a half actually. We started the
work on the first video model that Luma
had released in 2024 called Dream
Machine. At that time, our chief
scientist Jaing had joined our team,
right? like you know Xiaaming was a
leading image and video generation at
Nvidia. At the time these new graphics
cards were coming about or these new
training chips were coming about from
Nvidia H100s. When we looked at that for
the first time we were like okay the
cards are capable enough the chips are
capable enough I think we can gather
enough data and the algorithms are there
from our previous work on 3D generative
models and things like that that we can
actually do this. So we started that
process and it took us like you know
about five or six months actually about
four and a half months to be honest with
you to go from this first place where we
had some of the infrastructure and
things like that to training a proper
model that we could actually release to
the world but it came after a year year
and a half of work on encoders of
learning models of building
infrastructure all those kind of things
so it was also at the heels of open sora
so open had announced sora in February
and that was actually really interesting
Because you know before Sora our video
efforts were a little bit smaller
because we were very small company at
the time. We were barely uh we were
barely like 20 people. We had good
amount of compute but we didn't have
anywhere open AI level of compute. So we
could not have scaled it without knowing
that oh scaling could work. Once that
evidence was in front of us like we just
scaled our efforts significantly at that
point. 3 months later we had uh the
first dream machine model which was
really funny. It was like very first
early model. Today you wouldn't consider
that to be very good, right? But at that
time that was huge and got so popular.
It was on Good Morning America. It was
on CNN and then people were absolutely
astonished and mesmerized by it like oh
you can generate video. So that made
Luma into a very well-known household
name at that time and then now and gave
us you know all the resources we need to
continue our research to continue our
work. So yeah that was the first
streaming machine. Whenever you're
developing a new capability into the
world, when you're developing a new
technology, oh man, it never worked the
first try. It never worked the 10th try.
I would really say if you have found a
good market and you want to find what
fits into that market, iterate like
hell. Anything that slows down your
iteration velocity, avoid. If you're an
engineering mindset like myself, you
want to like, you know, build a very
stable system, right? Extensible system
with like, you know, all all good
technologies and all these kind of
things. But sometimes those systems
really slow you down because you you
build this monolith and it's good. It's
very scalable. It's all the things
right. But the problem is to change one
thing you need to now change like you
know five modules compared to that just
a barebones thing you built in Python
and like you know you just put it up
there. You have no allegiance to it.
It's already so you don't care. You
just iterate. You change it all day all
night right? Like you know and I think
that's really really important.
This episode is sponsored by Atio, the
AI native CRM for the next era of
companies. Connect your email and ATIO
instantly builds your CRM right before
your eyes with every company contact and
interaction you've ever had enriched and
organized. That's ATIO. And here's what
makes it even more game-changing. You
can build AI powered automations and use
its research agents to tackle some of
your most complex business processes,
freeing you to focus on what matters
most, building your company. Join
thousands of companies who are already
using Atio to power their businesses.
Visit the link in the description to
begin your 2e free trial with
Atio. The dream machine created by tech
company Luma featuring a new tool that
lets users turn images into video.
Honestly, we thought not many people
will try it because you know it's a
really new thing. We know eventually the
demand will be huge but initially we
thought like you know not many people
would try it but man the number of
people that tried it was insane. So we
put some pricing on it. It was only
because I was like okay well let's see
you know how much are people willing to
pay for it. So I had this extremely
unscientific way. Let's make it really
expensive like you know we'll give a
small number of videos for free and then
it will be 30 bucks and then 100 bucks
and then 500 bucks and the reason was
solely to discover customer bases
discover who is willing to pay for it
because if someone is willing to pay $30
they are getting something out of it if
someone is willing to pay $100 they're
clearly making money from it and if
someone is willing to pay 500 bucks
right I need to go talk to them because
I need to understand well why are you
paying so much per month to to use this
product so we took the approach of
putting something out there in very
unpolished state. If someone found it
valuable, we would know a lot, we would
learn a lot and we did. Uh so this was
one of the people who were paying like
100 or 500 bucks. I was curious what are
they doing with this thing. I got on the
call and and like you know this person
was um very happy grinning like you know
uh ear to ear at that time and they were
like oh I'm really great to meet you and
I was
like is that you? They're well known
especially if you know like the art
directors and and like you know people
in the world who make movies. What I
learned was that they were trying to
create this scene in one of the more
famous movies, right? They weren't able
to do that with their traditional
techniques. They tried Dream Machine and
they got a really great scene out in
like 30 minutes and now this person was
talking to me because they were asking
me to release the rights so that they
could use it in the movie and I was just
blown away. First version of the model
like it was not good enough to be used
in movies generally like really it
wasn't. But here was someone who
actually found even that useful early
days. Put it out. Talk to your users.
See what they're doing, what they're not
doing. Talk to them like, "Hey, how are
you using our stuff? If you're not using
our stuff, how are you not using our
stuff?" Right? Do you know about our
stuff? How did you find out? How did you
not find out? We have a group of about
like, you know, 2,000 3,000 of our most
engaged users in Discord. Myself, but
also our research team, our product
team, our engineers, they're all in that
chat all day. When these are your most
dedicated users, right, like you know,
paying users, people who are like, you
know, spending a lot of time on your
platform, they have a thousand things to
complain about and that's very good. The
worst thing that can happen to someone
who's making anything in the world is
apathy. You put something out and nobody
cares. That's the worst scenario. The
second worst scenario is you put
something out and everybody is very
happy with it because that means there's
nothing else left to do. Generally, if
everybody's just really telling you all
good things about it, that probably
means they just want to interview you or
or they're lying to you. Unlike
traditional products where you know,
okay, this has feature A, B, and C, and
this is how feature A interacts with
feature B, like you know the whole state
very well, with large models, people can
do anything with it. People can generate
anime, people can generate videos of a
tomato rolling down a hill. With large
models, you don't know what your users
are going to do. And there's no physical
scenario in which you could test all the
capabilities of the model. So you really
have to see what people are doing with
it, where it's succeeding, where it's
failing. We are not a video model
company. We are not building video
models or image models. We our goal is
very simply to solve multimodal general
intelligence. What does that mean? Our
belief is that people don't want image
generation models or video generation
models. What people want are
worldbuilders. Every video, every movie
is a world, a universe that like, you
know, someone created. Whether you're
talking about high fantasy like Lord of
the Rings for instance, that's a whole
universe with different laws of physics
with like you know different characters,
their their personalities, all these
things. Or if you think about a YouTube
video or Tik Tok, they they create a
personality, a persona, all these kind
of things. We need models that let
people
create worlds and then hit play. For
that, you need to build a very different
kind of intelligence. To build that kind
of intelligence, text alone is just not
enough. Think about the way humans learn
a concept. We see it with our eyes and
video. We hear about it with our ears
and we reason about it logically in
text. Everything humans learn from day
in and day out doesn't just happen in
text. It happens in all these
modalities. So if you want to build
intelligence that can collaborate with
humans digitally and physically that can
understand us that can entertain us you
need to build intelligence that is
trained on all the data human brain is
trained on right so video is a big part
of that so we believe that multimodal
intelligence or multimodal data actually
is on the critical path to
AGI when you're working on a problem
that is worth solving doing that really
motivates you. I find anything
interesting but finding something
interesting and finding something you
are just so mad about like you know that
you want to do it right it's very
different passion could be a moment in
time and it can come and go oh this
problem it would be so great if you
could do that and you can imagine that
oh I'm going to spend all my life doing
it generally that's not the case my
suggestion would be really try a lot of
things and try to go deep into them and
what you want to find is not that you
were interested in the depth of the
problem but whether that depth gets gets
you more excited or less excited. When
you go deep into it, you have to put
effort. Sometimes when you're putting
effort into like, oh, this is as boring
as it gets, right? Don't do that. If you
found something, when when then it gets
harder, you get more excited about that,
right? That's a unique thing. Honestly,
I can guarantee you that most people
around you will just quit. Try a lot of
things. Try to go deep into them and try
to see, can you stay excited, not
artificially, even after you're you're
done thinking about that problem, right?
you know but you can't stop thinking
about that problem like it comes to you
at night it comes to you like oh but how
do I do that right like you know that
kind of thing if you can find that and
somehow magically or or luckily that
happens to also be an opportunity in
which a company can be built that's it
[Music]