too many of the same projects doing the
same thing just about money just about
Finance I think myself and my team wish
we didn't have to be associated with
most of the people in the industry what
you see when you go to conferences most
of what people are talking about is
either nonon or incredibly dull
development dollars could have been
better spent on improving the technology
blockchains need the ability to handle
much more data and more computation this
means that people can build rules that
say you wanted to create a truly
uncensorable Twitter a way to do this
would be using a blockchain but you
couldn't handle all of the users and
data so you need to take that do that
computation somewhere else if I could
Truly find the score of a two-player
matchup I can create a betting Market
between the world's largest Gamers
people started using Bitcoin in places
like Venezuela to hedge out insane
inflation there's not too much you want
to do actually on the blockchain there's
not too much you can do on the
blockchain hi my name is Hugo fillian
and a co- and CEO of flair Flair really
is the only blockchain which we describe
as third generation it enshrines data
directly into the chain first generation
being Bitcoin simple transactions second
generation being ethereum adding logic
to those transactions third generation
flare adding data to the logic has just
hit about a million wallet 100 to
150,000 daily active users so they're
bringing value from other blockchain
ecosystems to flare to be used on flare
with the data provision services that
are provided by FL within the blockchain
environment you shouldn't be doing
anything based on trust because you
don't know the counterparty and you
don't have any legal recourse
essentially what defi is doing today is
it's using a trust-based model which is
very similar to trafi except is that
trafy are bound by laws whereas an
oracle provider has no laws in order for
defi or any other application that
relies on data to be valid you need to
have a way to secure those oracles that
is clear open and provides a similar
sort of safety as the blockchain itself
we think the best way to do that is to
put the oracles fundamentally into the
chain bring defi actually
decentralized I grew up in London which
is pretty much the world's Financial
Center at the time when I was growing up
very small startup Community very little
technology Community the financial
markets were the only choice and
obviously a place where one could
potentially make large amounts of money
which is very interesting to think about
when you're 17 I suppose the
macroeconomic and that's always been a
things I like to think about so I
studied risk and financial engineering
worked at a number of hedge funds in
London after about 7 years I decided
that I was just trying to eek out
Financial returns in order to make uh
essentially myself richer so I left
Finance went studying machine learning
at UCL in London and that's where I met
my two co-founders and I knew knew I
probably wanted to be a founder and when
looking at machine learning it's heavily
dominated by very large companies and
therefore gives you no opportunity
really if you look at open AI he ran y
combinator I certainly didn't have
anywhere near his Network to do anything
in machine learning one of our
co-founders had built inter vehicle
Communications based on a distributed
Network like Bitcoin and I'd had some
exposure to blockchain from people I
knew in the financial Community
ultimately it was a very interesting
idea to me that we could do everything
especially Financial things without
having to care about the counterparty
and I think that was one of the
fundamental reasons why blockchain at
the time and still does promising
technology so we started flare in 2018
and we had a very small office in the
basement someone's photography studio
but as we were a team of three I think
one and a half desks at the time they
didn't enjoy the benefit on ethereum of
smart contract essentially the largest
source of Bitcoin was know as wrapped
Bitcoin which is managed through a
custodian essentially antithetical to
the concept of Bitcoin meaning you're
relying on a middleman in order to use
your Bitcoin on a smart contract
platform we started looking at okay well
how can we get the data around Bitcoin
we devised the protocols to be able to
get that data from Bitcoin to build a
bridge that is over collateralized
meaning it has more value securing it
than than the amount of Bitcoin that has
been bridged using that bridge and in
order to do that we needed price so we
ended up with these two data protocols
the first being a protocol that allows
you to quickly and securely get data
from another blockchain and also to be
able to prove that a particular thing
hasn't happened on that blockchain and
that's pretty
key so originally we designed the data
protocol just to be able to build this
bridge for Bitcoin ultimately we very
quickly realize that there those data
Protocols are much more interesting that
we could bring in data from any open
system pretty much any system in a
decentralized way that's the key point
it's decentralized and it has security
so this allows you to do everything you
can do in defi today but with Flare
that's just the first step what really
interests me is then okay what can we
build with that this means that people
can build rules of an application
they're building second aspect is then
for us off chain compute far more data
from other sources than can be used by
the chain so where are you going to use
that very very large amounts of data
that you need to be able to use that off
chain in order to build applications so
I think the blockchain today is at the
limit more or less of what can be built
until you add in further compute and
that's when we can start building
applications that people actually want
to use so for me the first and most
interesting thing to do is genuinely
decentralize and make uncensorable
social media or news platforms or video
platforms we see an increasing set of
issues in the world where there is very
High censorship where people are
struggling to express their opinion
another set of application is around
gaming ultimately the experience the
blockchain has offered to gaming has
been so inferior to the web 2 or
existing gaming product it really hasn't
taken a tool but there are interesting
things you can do when you essentially
financialized components around gaming
if I can truly understand what has
happened at in each computational step
of a game then I can give people skins I
can give people asset based on exactly
what they've done and those assets can
be real and tradable as opposed to
Simply ingame I do have a third thing
there suppose the last area that really
interests us as a team uh is probably
machine learning or as most people call
it artificial intelligent there are some
very interesting things you can do with
distribution of users again there's a
there's not too much you want to do
actually on the blockchain there's not
too much you can do on the blockchain I
suppos the decentralized and
economically secure substrate of a
blockchain provides a very interesting
place for machine learning to be
expanded and to be made safer through
having multiple
participants some people may believe
that Bitcoin shouldn't have value and I
understand that mentality you have to
differentiate between the technology and
the value it has some logic to it
Bitcoin is only backed by hashing power
in it's not by the ability to Levy taxes
nor is it backed by the ability to force
other people to use your medium of
exchange Bitcoin doesn't have either of
those two things but perhaps it has one
other thing rather than forcing people
to use your medium of exchange but to
get them to voluntarily use it and
that's interesting but you'll never
convinc people that don't want to be
convinced especially as an awful lot of
people have a reason a financial reason
not to be convinced about that thing if
you take away the it's a monetary asset
side of the equation it's fairly nent
technology I think being able to
distribute computation and consensus
will become more and more useful over
time essentially there is value in being
able to come to consensus cross some
item of data across various different
vertical you know our biggest space the
space we're most interested in
researching thinking about is around the
outputs of machine learning models
probably provides the answer to what is
blockchain useful for my exposure to
finance was really post the large
financial crisis the ideas around what
something is worth fall apart when
currency is printed people were making
trades based on an expectation of
government action rather than based on
any fundamental strength in the economy
the sort of large excess of capital that
was put into the markets host the GFC
really led to a position where where
valuations were massively out of whack
and so when you spend your days thinking
about the idea of taking the fundamental
thing that values assets is a very
interesting thing because it removes
that ability of a group of people to
pervert essentially the entire
transmission mechanisms of all financial
markets and that's what has happened the
idea that could be a technology that
removes that from the equation is very
very appealing people started using
Bitcoin in places like Venezuela to
hedge out insane inflation that was
collapsing their currency crypto broadly
has solved the question of how can I
move dollars across the world really
quickly and easily without having to
enter an iban the defi that is built
fundamentally around essentially a
dollar based stable coin system and
Native tokens because that's essentially
what defi is and I think that could
expand as people use crypto tokens more
whether it be stable coins or the native
so if we're lucky flare will be one of
the key components in how people use
data on blockchains that's what we're
building that's essentially where we're
going we're not a smart contract project
focused on Ripple we have a much much
larger ambition and that ambition
revolves around data and offchain comput
so in 5 years time I'd like to see a
non-trivial percentage of the data that
is used in blockchain being sourced from
Flair regardless of whether it's being
used on flare as a chain or whether it's
being used on ethereum or any other new
chain that comes up success to me would
be that the data came from flare moved
from flare in 5 years it's feasible that
our offchain compute strategy could
result in applications that go Way
Beyond defi Way Beyond having value for
speculative reasons and much more
involved in people's daytoday lives
because it's a valuable application in
and of itself for