I think it would be foolish to believe
that if you're competing against
companies with thousands of employees
and hundreds of millions of billions in
revenue and you can just show up with
like a threers Founder team and after
like one year of work you're just better
right that's just not how it works right
you start out by not having very much of
a competitive Advantage other than you
the founders and what you can bring to
bear with a product for very small
specific Niche and so then over time
what was the initial Niche the smallest
Niche God man
hi my name is TA I'm a partner at altto
ventures we are very excited to have
Daniel Lang here from mango mint welcome
Daniel thanks for being here thanks so
much for having me I'm excited to be
here I'm Daniel Lang I'm co-founder and
CEO of mangement mangement is software
for salons and spas what that means is
that we provide an operating system that
allows Beauty and wellness businesses to
do everything from scheduling
appointments taking payments marketing
to clients all the way through to
Payment Processing actually we should
probably rewind a little bit to your
journey up to Mangan share us a little
bit of that Journey that you were on
sure so I grew up in Austria which is a
for those of you who don't know a very
peaceful quiet small country in the
heart of Europe know sometimes you hear
these stories of entrepreneurs that had
to overcome all of these obstacles and
challenges in their childhood I really
can't say that that was the case for me
but what I will say is that my dad had
like a small business it wasn't so much
much what he was doing it was more so
the fact that he ran his own business
and that that was a possibility that I
think opened my eyes to that being
something that you could in fact do and
then at the age of 12 I just fell in
love with programming started my first
real business with employees at the age
of 19 but at the same time being in
Austria it always felt somewhat limiting
because Austria and Europe for the most
part is not a place that is conducive to
entrepreneurialism taking risks and all
of that stuff so the first time I came
here to America it felt like wow this is
a totally different world I mean just
like in Austria failure is something
that has a big stigma attached to it
whereas here it's almost like embraced
it's not that people enjoy failing like
failing still sucks but it's something
where if you fail as an entrepreneur and
you give it your everything nobody is
going to judge you for that right like
in fact they might high five you so I
was like immediately struck by that knew
that this was the place that I wanted to
start my business share with us a little
bit of the the early days and in
particular what was the journey to
saying I must build software for the
salon and spa industry totally one of
the things that was really important to
us when we started mangement is to find
something that we could truly be
passionate about for 10 15 20 years for
like the length of the journey you know
we spent about a year just looking for
different things and staying open-minded
during that time my wife and I we went
on this road trip I think we visited 32
different states basically visiting all
of these different places the one thing
that I noticed is that every town in the
America no matter how big or small tends
to have a lot of these like small
businesses local businesses that are
literally everywhere and at the time
this is 2016 coming from La I was
already used to using Uber and you know
Uber Eats and all of that modern
technology and yet when it came to
booking a herir appointment or booking a
wellness treatment it felt like you know
it was back in the '90s where you had to
call at a certain time and they had to
get back to you so we started to notice
that there might be an opportunity so
you go on this tour you wrap it up with
your wife you come back to LA and then
you say what we the co-founders and I
made it a point to spend several months
going out and talking to who we thought
would be potential customers and we
basically said if we can't get to them
now why would we be able to later so how
many customers pre-product did you in
some sense convince to use your
non-existent product yeah so one of the
challenges that we identified early on
was that none of us Founders had any
industry experience so none of us had
worked in a salano or Spa before I mean
everyone's a client in the salano spa at
some point in their life but we didn't
really know how these businesses worked
in order to build a great product for
them we had to go way deeper than what
we could learn in like a 1-h hour
conversation with an owner to solve the
problem we decided to use a trojan horse
approach where essentially we offered
free marketing Services we would
literally just like walk into salons and
say hey we have nothing to sell but we
have a background in marketing and Tech
and we'd love to just you know hang
around here and in exchange we'll build
you a new website we'll do your email
marketing honestly in the beginning it
was actually hard to convince people
because they thought we were scamming
them and way but you keep trying and we
found our first 10 20 eventually 30
customers that way two years later in
fact we had a software product that
somebody would actually be like a normal
person would pay for without being
friends with us so so you studied the
market quite intensely you talk to
hundreds of salons before you go into
the space so you probably some really
deep conviction that this could work but
that doesn't mean that it will work and
so as you were selling the first few
dozen software tools to these customers
were there any points where you're like
maybe I'm wrong like maybe maybe this
wasn't a good idea I'm still thinking
that every
day no the space that we're in took us
about 2 years to build the first version
of the product and that version was very
incomplete as I mentioned it probably
took another at least 2 years maybe even
longer to have a product that I would
consider competitive and so that's a
very long time and you know in the early
days we didn't raise funding at the very
beginning so it meant that as Founders
we had to basically put in money
ourselves not only not getting paid we
put in money for several years I think
that is why you really need to focus on
alignment with your co-founders as well
and making sure that they also
understand the length of how long this
takes there's so much in my opinion bad
advice out there for Founders you know
the stories that sound really we oh we
met on a weekend hackathon and like you
know 3 weeks later we had shipped the
first version and 3 months later as AOA
invested what not right like yeah sure
that happens once every 20 years maybe
but like the reality for most Founders
is different right like the reality is
like in the early days you put in
everything you can and a lot of times
you know the initial idea is not the one
that works out and so you have to stay
Nimble and many cases pivot we were
fortunate in the sense that our thesis
didn't actually change but there are
definitely moments where you kind of to
convince yourself to just keep going
there were already a lot of players in
this category of Salon and Spa software
so it's a relatively mature market in
terms of software penetration yet you
found there to be a need for mango mint
to exist and flourish so how would you
characterize the fundamental competitive
advantage that you have in mango mint
yeah it's interesting cuz you know
having started other businesses before
and been around Founders you make a
choice or on like what kind of risk you
want to take and a lot of Founders take
Market risk where they have some great
technology to have an idea but it's
unclear whether there would be a market
for it we did not want to take that risk
we intentionally chose a market that had
a lot of incumbents already we saw that
as a positive characteristic about the
market rather than a negative one a lot
of times you know when you talk to folks
and you tell them the idea they're like
wait but doesn't this already exist like
yes that's the point it exists and
they're doing well and there's many
companies that are making lots of money
that's a good thing because then it
allows you to focus on strategy and
differentiation and how you can carve
out initially like a wedge and then over
time grow that wedge into a real
competitive strength I think it would be
foolish to believe that if you're
competing against companies with
thousands of employees and hundreds of
millions of billions in Revenue that you
can just show up with like a three
person founder team and after like one
year work you're just better right
that's just not how it works right so
you have to really be smart about okay
better for who right and like you know
probably start with a very small group
that's what we did and so you start out
by not having very much of a competitive
Advantage other than you the founders
and what you can bring to bear with a
product for a very small specific Niche
and so then over time what was the
initial Niche the smallest Niche it
wasn't actually like a a niche in terms
of like segmentation of the market it
was a niche more so around what people
wanted from it and so for example when
we launched we did not have Payment
Processing we did not have reporting we
did not have a Shopify integration so if
any of those things were important to
you we would not be a good solution for
you but what we did have was a calendar
that beautifully designed fast
interfaces intuitive I feel like a lot
of people who don't have a plan don't
have a strategy make the mistake that
they say yes to everything and it
dilutes them so much that you can't
really tell after a while what they're
actually good for and so I feel like you
know one of the things that we've always
done well is being very clear who is our
ICP who are we for who are we not for
what are we willing to say yes to and
what are we willing to say no to and
it's actually hard because when you have
somebody knock on your door and wave a
lot of money in front of your face and
say hey I need this thing can you please
build it for me it's very tempting
especially when you don't have a lot of
Revenue yet and you know also don't have
funding but it's those moments when I
think it really matters to be clear
about what your strategy is so that you
have the permission to say no in those
moments what were the most painful NOS
you've said today oh man usually the
ones where somebody shows up and says
hey I got 70 locations we love your
product we've already used it we've
already done the troll and we just need
this one little extra button or this one
little extra report or something can you
can you please build it and we'll be a
customer those are the moments where
it's really difficult to say no but so
far we've managed to do that uh but
certainly not with without like you know
feeling wow like a man that would have
been nice actually right right this is a
question from one of your close
colleagues Daniel has exceptional
intuition for building a great product
how would you describe your personal
philosophy of what it means to build
great product I love the question
because intuition is such a thing that
is underappreciated in traditional
product management for those of you who
don't know product management is a lot
of like lot about prioritization
which features do you build how do you
weigh them there's all kinds of systems
that you can use you can assign points
and impact scores and whatnot right and
what ends up happening is you end up
with unremarkable products because when
you apply such a rigid system to the way
you build product you end up optimizing
for a lot of boring stuff I think the
most exciting products the ones that
really like inspire people make people
truly feel love for a product are the
ones that have intuition in then where
somebody had a feeling that something
was a good idea and went with that gut
instinct that intuition if you call it
so now the question becomes what does it
take to have intuition and I think it's
with many things in life where to
develop intuition for anything you just
got to put in the Reps you just got to
see a lot right so if you want to be a
product leader you have to try a lot of
products you have to be in the products
you have to be willing to try every
product and analyze it and form an
opinion what do you like about it what
do you not like about it why is it good
why does a product make you angry why
does a product make you excited what are
those like you know things that are
going on and a lot of times it's not
stuff that you can perfectly capture in
like spreadsheets like it's like the
little things right and that's what I
mean with intuition right like you need
to see a lot of products try smell taste
products to be able to tell when a
product is good and then also be able to
judge whether an idea or a feature is
good and I'd much rather make an
opinionated decision and be wrong about
it then crowdsourcing these decisions
and then always making the safe decision
so I I believe like you know being
opinionated having a philosophy with
what your product should be is very
important to building a product that
people at will really love at the end of
the day are you still involved in
product at the stage very much so do you
feel like you have to stay involved
there for a while or is there a point
where you think the system has to be set
up such that the PMS or product leaders
have the uh empowerment to make their
own decisions the short answer is yes I
think it will always have to be involved
I think it's actually crazy to think
that the CEO should not be involved in
product I mean product is literally what
you're selling and it's in some ways the
most important thing about your business
so how could you not be intimately
involved as a CEO that's the way I see
it now that being said you don't want to
create an environment where you
micromanage everything of course right
so you want to put in place people who
are able to act with conviction
themselves right but I think that's
different from letting them completely
decide what is getting built and not
being aware of it I think it is very
important to stay plugged in to have
that sort of cohesive vision for where
the product is going and keep doing that
I also believe that the way software is
built in many companies is not conducive
to great product outcomes and what I
mean by that is a lot of times you know
a PM product manager comes up with a
feature they spec it out they work with
design to create like a UI design sign
and then they hand it off to engineering
and then engineering builds something it
comes back there's some Q&A maybe some
back and forth but then it gets shipped
right we fundamentally believe that this
is not a good approach to building great
great products I think you can actually
build really decent products with it but
if you truly aspire to build the world's
best software you have to do it
differently you have to bring the
engineers the ones that are building the
codes that the ones that are living in
the code base into the mix and they have
to understand why it is they building
what they are building they have to
understand the customer and so many
times when they make decisions the
little of things they will spot
opportunities that a product manager
could never identify so it's really
important that you bring them on board
and some companies call it product
Engineers I think that's just like a
title thing but at the end of the day it
means that the product manager is not
the owner of the product they're not
dictating what gets built and how and
all the specs they're more like a
research function that is there to
assist the product development which
happens with engineers and designers and
the product manager informs that by
providing insights and perspective from
talking to customers and the market and
competitors and all of that stuff but
they are not like the mini CEO as
they're sometimes called for a feature
or a product they're more in like this
research and assistance role so in the
early days you bootstrapped you figured
out ways to earn some marketing dollars
here and there and you tged along and at
a certain point you decided to raise
some Capital so what was that moment
when you and your your co-founder said
let's go talk to some fec's I think it
was always obvious for us from the
beginning that the vision was so big
that at some point along the journey we
would have to bring in some outside
Capital to you know just like make the
necessary Investments to hire the team
build the product and do all of that
stuff so it wasn't so much that we were
trying to figure out should we raise or
not it was more like okay when do we
feel like you know there's enough there
that we feel comfortable taking someone
else's money it's a big responsibility
you know if you take someone else's
money and beginning it's like you know
they say family friends and fools right
for a reason uh a lot of times they lose
the money right and we just wanted to
make sure that we felt really good about
it before we did that and did not lose
the money frankly what was the early
iteration of those pitch meetings like
what was the feedback I'm sure you
remember some of the NOS that you heard
like what was that like I mean it sucks
right like you know fundraising as an
early stage it's funny because in the
beginning when you start out doing your
pre-seed your seat round man it's such a
grind right like as a Founder unless you
have some prior background unless you
already are super connected and know
everybody in the industry if that's not
you then chances are it's not going to
be a fun experience it's just not how it
goes right even like you know getting
into a meeting is difficult in the
beginning and then later once the
business starts to take off a little bit
there's this interesting moment where it
completely shifts like all of a sudden
like you know the VCS and the investors
are the ones that are trying to get a
meeting with you and now you are in the
position where there's like way too many
many emails coming in and you're trying
to figure out like how to spend your
time so you actually start to appreciate
what it was like for the investors so
now you're in the driver's seat you can
make some decisions with all these VCS
knocking on your doors how did you go
about that process like what did you
optimize for and ultimately how did you
pick the right type of Partners to work
with over time you know for the series a
um which we did 2022 we actually ran a
very very short process I think it took
us like two weeks from first meeting
until we had term sheets and then like
another week to actually sign a term
sheet for C then series a rounds at
least in my experience it's all about
like you know do you have traction and
is the investor excited about the idea
and usually you know pretty early right
like 20 minutes into a conversation the
person who ended up doing a series a
Sanji from open view he literally like
20 minutes into our first conversation
stopped me and said all right what does
it take to win this deal like I don't
need to hear anymore like I've heard
enough like what does it take to win
this deal right and I feel like it's
almost obvious when you have that
meeting and you know oh wow like you
know this could be some something that
could work out I guess later on like you
know for where we are now it shifts a
little bit right because now it's no
longer the question of are you going to
get funded yes or no but more like okay
who is the best partner to help us
fulfill our vision and make this like a
really big meaningful company for the
long term right so even like you know
with Altos you know the long-term Focus
that you guys have that was really
important to us right and getting to
know you better and the team here and
how everybody thought like that was a
much bigger consideration than when we
raised our seed rant several years ago
for example if you're on that road trip
with your wife talking to the salon
owners maybe even before that as you
were thinking about maybe starting a
company what would you tell Daniel what
now8 nine years ago I would say the
thing that I did not appreciate at the
very beginning of the journey is how
incredibly long it would take to get to
a place where it really you can really
see the future you know everyone
understands it intellectually when you
say oh it takes like 7 to 10 years for
any company to be successful right but
when you're in it when you're like a
year three year four it can feel really
long and it's almost like this thing
where for the longest time you're just
trying to survive and then it hits you
finally where it's like hey I think
we're no longer fighting to to survive I
think you know now I can actually shift
around how big could this be but before
you hit that moment it's a real grind
and I would say if I could go back and
talk to me at the very beginning I would
just like really emphasize hey make sure
that you embrace it it's like part of
the journey don't get discouraged I mean
we didn't but still like it would have
been nice to hear that and and and to
know that this is what it takes
[Music]