I think startups are basically like
getting slapped in the face probably
over and over again. That's basically
it. I also, you know, interestingly, I I
actually like failures a lot. One of the
things I hate the most is doing
something and not knowing if it's
working or not. And it's actually very
it's very freeing to know when something
fails because that's very obvious. I
like when decisions are obvious. Like
when something fails, it's obvious you
need to do something new. And the faster
you fail, actually, the faster you can
decide to do something new. And I think
for a company like us, like we're at the
frontier of the technology, we should be
imagining we are failing at a lot of
initiatives. In fact, if everything is
working, we're operating at less than
potential of the company. We should be
failing. Like that probably means we're
not betting. We're not taking enough
bets if we're not failing enough. I I
think it's like a required part of a
company that you that you fail. I'd say
like be more humble about your ideas.
And I wouldn't say that I was arrogant
at the time, but probably a lot more
idealistic about our ideas being
correct. And you need some amount of
idealism as I said before, but at the
same time, it's that there's no reason
why an idea is great if you haven't like
validated it. be honest with yourselves
about, you know, the viability of your
idea and be willing to pivot very
quickly. I feel like a lot of a lot of
founders hate the word pivot, but it's
it's awesome. Like, it's awesome. You
know, what sucks more is like doing the
wrong thing and just failing. Even right
now, I would say one of my regrets is
probably not doing the pivot 3 months
earlier.
Hey, I'm Verun, CEO and co-founder of
Windsurf. So, Windsurf is an AI powered
ID uh that provides agentic capabilities
that enables developers and
non-developers to build apps really
quickly and also modify existing
applications really quickly. A million
developers have actually used the
product. We have hundreds of thousands
of monthly active users on the on the
product right now and it's growing, you
know, exponentially faster with time.
So, I graduated from MIT in 2017 and
after that I actually worked at an
autonomous vehicle company in Mountain
View called Nuro. there sort of got an
early taste of what deep learning could
do for other industries. Started the
company actually in 2021, so it's been 4
years. At the time, the company didn't
do anything relating to code AI. It
actually built out GPU virtualization
and compiler technology. We did that for
over a year and a half and were able to
get to a couple million in revenue. We
had eight employees at the time. One
thing changed very very materially in
that time. In the middle of 2022, GPT
3.5 came out at that point and we
thought that generative models would
fundamentally transform many different
industries and we needed to make kind of
a pretty big decision at that point to
pivot the company because we
fundamentally felt everyone was going to
run generative models for everything.
And at that point we believed a lot of
the value would acrue to companies that
were applications almost like in the
early days of the internet the companies
that proved to be very valuable were
companies like Google and Amazon and we
wanted to see what would it be like if
we could build the next Google or
Amazon. We were early adopters of a
product called GitHub Copilot and from
there we actually built out a product
called Kodium which was an extension
that lived in all the major IDEs and we
were able to get that to over a million
users as well. Um, and we ended up
serving some of the world's largest
enterprises, companies like JP Morgan
Chase. Very quickly though, sort of
middle of last year, we realized that we
needed to control more of the
experience, especially as these models
became more and more agentic. And that
was why we decided to build our own ID,
which was Windsurf. That has taken off
very quickly as well.
[Music]
It's actually kind of interesting. I
think MIT is very different than
Stanford. I think most people don't go
to MIT to kind of immediately start a
company. I don't think my aspirations
were to start a company. I did
progressively intern at smaller and
smaller companies. So I first interned
at LinkedIn, then after that Quora uh
and then data bricks. Data bricks at
that time was a very small engineering
team. They were not even a unicorn at
that time. But I think I didn't actually
end up working at any of these companies
because I think the thing that motivated
me was can I be a meaningful part of a
visionary company working with motivated
people. That's always been what's driven
me and that's sort of why immediately
after MIT I decided to go work at an
autonomous vehicle company. I thought
that could be the future of where just
robotics was going to go and I think for
me and probably the other people at the
company we want to work on the future of
technology and that's what truly
motivates us. I think the motiv is just
how do you build products in hard
technology spaces where the technology
is not there yet. You know I I'll give
like a quick just some interesting
numbers. You know, when we started,
obviously, deep learning was was pretty
popular. Uh, but the amount of compute
that these models had access to grew
exponentially year-over-year. You know,
just some numbers here. In 2017, the
number of teraflops on a consumer grade
GPU was 10. By the end of 2022, it was
actually 700. So, it's a massive
increase of in compute that happened.
And I think what we learned was machine
learning models were going to get more
capable very quickly. And you should not
bet on where the technology is today,
but where it could be a couple years
from now, right? And if all you're doing
is working on products that work today,
you're going to be quickly irrelevant a
year from now. And that was like a very
important lesson that we I think a lot
of a lot of people that were in the
autonomous vehicle space kind of
learned, which is now if you were to
look at autonomous vehicles, they're
much more machine learning based than
they were probably 5 or 6 years ago.
Originally, we started out the name of
the company was Exaf Function. Part of
the reason why we called it exunction
was our goal was to virtualize GPU
computations to make it easier to run
things on GPUs. And the the term exa
function means we want to run an exa
number of functions which is 10 to the
18 functions. I think the biggest
learning lesson for us was at the time
was even if we were succeeding by some
metrics we were making some revenue just
accepting that hey like the business
might not be the best business and we
need to go pivot was a very hard thing
to do I would say right it's very hard
when you have like employees you know
you've already raised some amount of
funding I think at the time we had
raised over $28 million of funding to
basically start from scratch overnight
uh but one of the learning lessons that
I've sort of had and probably the other
people at the company is every time you
do a pivot you have an opport
opportunity to maybe 10x the size of the
company. And uh usually when you have an
idea that you don't believe in and the
ceiling is low, it's actually better to
just scrap the entire thing than to like
try to incrementally claw and you know
increase the value of what you're doing
by like you know 20 30%. It's not going
to matter in the grand scheme of things.
So we had gone to a couple million in
revenue at that time. I think the hard
part for us was it felt very ad hoc how
we were adding revenue to the business.
It also felt like with the advent of
these generative models, a lot of the
complexity of running models would
become commoditized. If everyone is
going to run transformers, uh the
transformer model architecture, what is
the reason for us to have a platform
that virtualizes arbitrary GPU
computations? It's not as important
anymore. So, it's a factor of two
things. We didn't understand how we
could 10 or 100x sales, right? I think
you build a company not to make a couple
million in revenue, but billions of
dollars in revenue. So we didn't
understand how to even get within an
order of magnitude of that right that
was one and two we also felt that the
problem we were solving with the advent
of the generative models was going to
get commoditized. So at that point it's
kind of an easy thing once you believe
that something is not going to be big
you have no other option but to change
your mind and do something new that is
very painful because you did commit a
lot of time and a lot of energy and
passion to one thing. You don't win an
award for doing the wrong thing for
longer. I guess me and my co-founder did
a walk over a weekend and I guess we
decided over a weekend and we told the
team on Monday. Um and then everyone
started working on the new thing
starting Monday. Uh yeah, I guess we
just you know one of the core beliefs
that we have about startups is startups
can if they're lucky do one thing really
well. We could not afford to have the
company believe two things were
important. So we would need to rip the
band-aid off and actually make it very
clear to the rest of the company that
the new thing was where we thought the
future was. You know, it's interesting.
I would we were not worried at all when
we did the pivot. We had basically
written off the company is going to be a
zero and at that point anything is
greater than zero. Ship whatever you can
if it sucks you're in the same place
that you are. If it doesn't suck like
great awesome only upside just honesty,
transparency and int like intellectual
honesty with the team is maybe a core
tenant of the company. We don't do
things unless we like truly believe they
are the right thing to do. even if it
like fits some narrative that the rest
of the industry or our investors or
convenient belief we believe things if
from first principles they're correct
and you know I guess one true fact was
after telling our employees there's a
real chance that some of them would
leave but I think like when you build a
highquality culture where the people are
are intellectually honest um good people
don't want to leave if you if you chart
a path for what the thing that does work
is right because you know one
interesting thing about startups is
people talk a lot about moes. What's the
mode of a company? But really, what is
the mode of a company that has 10
people? You know, if you do have a moat,
it's very shallow at best, right? The
number of engineering years that went
into your product is already very small.
So, the real moat is you work on the
right thing with enough people for long
enough. That's like the only moat a
startup ultimately has. And that's like
why you believe in a team. Obviously,
when a company becomes thousands of
people, hopefully the moat is not the
current business. It would be sad if the
moat was the company can just pivot and
do the next thing. In that regard, I
think if you genuinely believe the
motive of a of a company is betting on
the right things and and hiring a great
group of people, then if you are
intellectually honest with your team and
tell them we don't believe in the
strategy we just had, it's should be
totally fine with everyone.
This episode is sponsored by Atio, the
AI native CRM for the next era of
companies. Connect your email and ATIO
instantly builds your CRM right before
your eye with every company, contact,
and interaction you've ever had enriched
and organized. That's ATIO. And here's
what makes it even more game-changing.
You can build AI powered automations and
use its research agents to tackle some
of your most complex business processes,
freeing you to focus on what matters
most, building your company. Join
thousands of companies who are already
using to power their businesses. Visit
the link in the description to begin
your twoe free trial with Atio.
I think we were early adopters of a
product like GitHub copilot. So we and
we were we actually built a lot of
infrastructure. So at the time we
thought that was the tip of the iceberg
of what the technology could actually
build. We thought a lot more could be
built in this category. Right? If all
people were doing was autocompleting, we
could potentially see a world in which
entire PRs would get generated. And at
that time, we were like, okay, the time
it takes to build applications probably
has gone down by a double digit percent.
Why don't we set the goal of the company
to reduce the time it takes to build
technology by 99%. It's a very ambitious
goal, not something we'd be able to do
in the next year or two. But if we set a
very ambitious goal, there's probably a
lot of work to be done in this space. We
believe that technology is always going
to get better. We believe the models are
going to get better. Because of that, we
just believed there was a lot of
opportunity here. Because we were also
an infrastructure company at the time,
we were able to train our own models and
run models ourselves, which enabled us
to build an extension that was entirely
free in all the major IDs. And uh that
was able to very quickly get to hundreds
of thousands of users. It was a
combination of what our skill set was,
also a belief of where we thought the
future was going. I think it took us
less than 2 months to build the MVP and
ship it out. I think as a company we're
probably more of the opinion of if you
are going to do something hard um it is
actually important to have intermediate
goals that you can actually give to
other people to validate your
hypothesis. That's maybe something that
we learned a lot of us at the company
were previously from autonomous vehicles
and I think one of the biggest mistakes
that autonomous vehicle companies might
have made is maybe to no fault of their
own was they built a hard technology
where it's very hard to validate if the
technology is good in the middle. Right?
So for us it's always been it is
actually a feature if you can have a
very very like visionary goal but have
very tractable intermediate steps and so
we actually picked a very tractable
intermediate step to deploy which was
can we build a basic VS code extension
that had autocomplete capabilities uh
with our own model and that was that was
the intermediate goal that we had and we
believed you know maybe it was like a
little bit of necessity we just pivoted
the company people were not working on
anything else there was an existential
dread what the value of the product was
so we very quickly built it. I think a
basic form of product market fit was
when our inbound for the product from
like companies was was more than like
any of us could handle and we did need
to hire a real go to market team. I
think at that point we realized hey
we're actually solving a real pain for
the market and we are providing a lot of
value. So that was that happened very
quickly like within months of the
product coming out we had a lot of
companies reaching out to how could they
run the product uh for themselves and
and use it for their large code bases.
Yeah, I think the word product market
fit is probably something I don't like a
lot because it it creates a lot of like
overconfidence. I think what what you
have as product market fit in one day,
if you don't continue to innovate and
you have competitors, is very quickly
going to become a commodity where you
don't have product market fit. So, you
need to be very paranoid. I always like
to tell the company we're probably going
to fail. And I think the good thing
about telling the company we're probably
going to fail is it creates enough sort
of energy in the company to find the
next thing that keeps you as a
differentiated product and and survive
in a in a space. But I think in general
like product like I feel like if you
have pull from the market, it's very
hard to fake it. It's it's very obvious
when you have it and very obvious when
you don't. And I'll tell you this like
even when we were making a couple
million in revenue with the GPU
virtualization business is very obvious
we didn't have product market fit. It's
not a scalable company. you don't really
understand how you can grow revenue and
find find a way to like provide more
value at scale. So very quickly I think
a lot of large companies were starting
to reach out to us for a variety of
reasons for security reasons because we
were able to run models ourselves. We
were able to run it in a secure way. The
other thing is they wanted the systems
to work with their complicated sort of
code bases. Right? Their code bases are
not simple. Some of our customers have
tens of millions of lines of code in a
single codebase. and we started building
more and more technology to make it
possible that we would give very
personalized suggestions to them
regardless of where they stored their
code. I guess very quickly we started to
get to 100 customers. It went from going
from zero to 100 customers probably
within months um at the company. I think
the feedback that was kind of
interesting to us is how important just
small details were right to the entire
user experience. We started off as an
infrastructure company and we needed to
kind of become a product company which
is a big kind of change. You know basic
things like the latency of the product
how quickly we provide suggestions was
quite important. You know just basic
things if we do too much computation on
the user's machine and it kind of like
makes the machine too slow that's a
unacceptable user experience that is not
something we would think about if we
were purely a server-based application.
So there were kind of new things as a
company we needed to learn because the
space we were operating in was
fundamentally different. I think
basically what happens is once a company
gets bigger it's possible that you start
losing the reason why you had a good
product to start with right you start
listening actually in some ways too much
customer obsession might be bad in that
if you do things that all of your
customers ask you to do sometimes you
might like incrementally iterate to
actually build a really bad product and
it's actually better off to completely
change the paradigm in a way that your
customers don't really ask for because
you you suspect it could be helpful. So
there's like a little bit of a healthy
amount of don't just listen to random
people about what you should build.
Listen to your customers, but don't
listen to your customers in how you
should build it. There could be a way
you could build it in a way that is very
transformational, but not something that
they would even expect. One of the
things about our product is we have a
pretty large individual product and we
have ways in which our users can
communicate with us, you know, either
online on social media. Uh, and I guess
I I look through it fairly frequently to
understand what the pain points our
users have about the product. Also at
the same time I guess like everyone at
the company uses the product almost
day-to-day which is maybe a unique
aspect of the product right there are
probably a lot of AI tools out there but
the people building the tools are not
using them all the time whereas the
people that build our products literally
use our product to build the product
whether it be windsurf everyone builds
software on windsurf for windsurf which
is a unique way for us to actually get
feedback a lot of our feedback is
internal and if no one at the company
likes a part of the product it's
unlikely that a lot of people outside of
the company are going to like the
No, I I always try to run the company as
like the smallest company it can be. But
I think the goal of a company is not to
be a small company. I think the goal of
a company is to actually provide the
most value in a space. If the right way
to do that is be a bigger company. I
think that's like the right thing you
should sort of do. One of the operating
principles we sort of have at the
company is we try to run the company
fairly lean. And that doesn't mean we
have very few people. It just means that
for a given amount of ambition, we are
the smallest company we could possibly
be. And that means that people are
largely speaking underwater most of the
time. Hopefully like we don't have large
amounts of people that have too little
to do, right? The goal is everyone
should have too much to do. And because
of that, that forces rapid
prioritization inside the company with a
lot of urgency that triggers whether or
not we should hire people. And honestly,
that itself is a good forcing function
of how you should scale a company. You
scale a company when everyone is
underwater and the moment people are no
longer underwater, we don't scale the
company anymore. I think in in terms of
just some of the challenges obviously
like as the company gets bigger,
communication gets harder. So there are
some processes in place in terms of you
want to ship a feature, it's no longer
just one person did everything end to
end. There are like many different
parties involved. Uh but I think we
added more process in place to make sure
that even that could happen much faster.
If you run the company in a way where
everyone has their own set of
priorities, I think it's it's cool.
Everyone's kind of having a good time.
But I think, you know, this boils down
to why do companies work? I think they
work if you do one or two things really
well. Maybe even one. Forget about two,
maybe even one. The problem is then
actually if you were to imagine in a lot
of cases, it's very hard to just have
infinitely many people doing one thing
really well. So that naturally reduces
the number of people that you have at
the company. Yeah. I guess I guess the
the issue is naturally when you have
more people, they're going to be more
priorities, right? Like people are not
malicious, but they want to have
something to do. If there are enough
people to do what the original intent of
the company was, they're going to find
other things to do and that's going to
cause problems internally as well. One
of the things that I've sort of done is
I still interview everyone that joins
the company, make sure that they go
through a culture fit. I think that's
actually like quite important to me to
make sure that we are adding people that
are going to like maintain and preserve
and maybe even even just embrace the
culture we have inside the company. So I
think that's like honestly honestly like
a very key thing that I've not given up
even as the company has scaled you know
close to 200 people. I I think actually
it's the same principles that made the
company work when it's small. I I think
big companies are not that different
than small companies. Maybe it's hard to
operate like a small company when you're
a big company but I think if you were to
ask every big company they want to
operate like a startup. I think the very
hard thing is once again intellectual
honesty. It's very hard as the company
gets bigger for for a large group of
people to analyze what they're doing and
to say, "Hey, we should stop working on
this or should work on something else."
It gets very hard because people feel
some sort of safety as the company gets
bigger. But the reality is like no
company is really safe regardless of the
size. And that's how every company
should be operating. They should be
operating as if almost existential
dread. Not in that it's causing
paralysis, but in that it causes the
agency to kind of figure out what the
next thing to do is. Yeah. I think
people get they feel safety,
psychological safety by feeling that
what they're working on is the most
important thing, right? I think, you
know, people it's very hard to keep in
your head, hey, like let me go work hard
on something, but all the while it may
not be that useful for the company. And
I think as a company gets bigger, it's
very hard to have people that just still
don't have the psychological safety.
Maybe one interesting thing about the
company is I think companies have like
two sides attached to them, which is
that you need some form of irrational
optimism. The reason why you need
irrational optimism is without some
amount of optimism, there's no reason a
startup ever wins at anything. A big
company has more capital, more
resources, more distribution. So you
need to believe you can do something
better, right? With great people, uh you
can somehow build something that's
generational. You have to believe that.
Uh which is in most cases not true,
right? So you somehow need to believe
that. But also at the same time,
sometimes that's just not going to be
the case. And you need to be very
realistic. And I think this comes with,
you know, uncompromising realism. Like
you need a healthy amount of both. You
need you need the optimism to go out and
do something when everyone else believes
it's not that valuable because if
everyone else believed it was valuable,
the big company would do it and you
would still lose. But all the while you
also need to agree most ideas are bad
ideas and you need to kill your ideas
fairly quickly as well. This is this is
like this tension that a company is
always going through. It progressively
gets harder and harder. The company gets
bigger. Uh but I think it's a strength
if a company can do that regardless of
what size it is.
Yeah. I think the only thing is that I
would sort of like to say is build for
where you think the technology is going,
not for today, right? And don't build
probably technologies in places that
like are as good as they will be given
where the technology is today. It feels
like it's going to be very hard to
differentiate in the long term. And
that's a hard thing to do, right? Uh
that means you you you actually need to
be willing to work on something that
doesn't feel like it's working for
maybe, you know, an indeterminate period
of time. I think what this means is
these kind of short-term heristics that
you invest deeply in that make a model
today work are probably actually have
massive diminishing returns because the
next model is going to be much better
and the heristics are going to be
unnecessary. I think the things that are
important are how do you actually take
advantage of the fact that you do have a
lot of users and build better
experiences for them and actually
because they are using your product
you're able to build better and better
experiences for them and these
experiences are better and learned in a
way they're actually learned from the
way people use the product and I think
you should be focusing on that not on
kind of cosmetic things that make a
model kind of magically do something
that probably is going to happen anyways
in 6 months.