being a Founder is very very stressful
should I keep going do you have a job do
you have a career that's going to going
to work out my suggestion is frankly if
you feel like you should stop going you
should probably stop going and if you
can't not continue then you should
continue hey you know this is what you
need to be doing you need to keep trying
and all you need is one thing to work
out and then that'll you know blow away
all the failures in the past I have
considered giving up many times but
there was just something nagging inside
of me that wouldn't let me interviews
like this is that hey I'm someone who
already gone through it maybe you can
learn from some of my mistakes instead
of going through the same two years of
pain that I did as well I think you
should stop being lazy and learn how to
build yourself my name is Marie I the
co-founder and CEO of pylon we're
building the first customer support
platform built for B2B companies we're
going to consolidate all the products
that you would get from a customer
support platform customer success
platform product marketing I'm tooling
for Solutions and Professional Services
teams and combine them all into one our
initial Insight was that a lot of people
are talking to their customers not over
email anymore but they're starting to
open up shared slack channels Microsoft
teams channels WhatsApp we got to 120k
in AR within 3 months of having the idea
got our first customer in 14 days we've
raised $20 million from investors like
injuries and Horwitz General Catalyst
and white combinator frankly the vision
is shaping up so fast um because of
what's evolving with
AI might sound stupid but I was
definitely inspired by movies like The
Social Network or Pirates of Silicon
Valley kind of learning about how those
companies got started I guess I could
relate a little bit to the characters in
the movies where like oh I'm kind of
nerdy too I like computers I like
programming and maybe this could be a
path I could go on too YouTube videos
were an early teacher for me and then
started making games and high school
building website then it was only kind
of sophomore year of high school where I
joined our robotics team where I got
really excited about after leaving high
school I went to Purdue to study
computer science I immediately fell in
love with hacker culture there was this
club prod hackers where every weekend
they would spend time just writing code
and just trying to build games or
applications while I was in college I
started to do internships of course so I
worked at places like Qualcomm and San
Diego I worked at Yelp as an intern and
then airb B at airb B and I joined the
payments team there and so I was working
on back in infrastructure helping
basically money move around the world to
be honest I don't feel like it prepared
me that much for startups I actually
think it probably was not helpful it was
anti- helpful I learned all the things
not to do because big companies operate
so differently and so slow compared to
Startup while I was at Airbnb I really
was not enjoying the work I was doing I
was like looking at all these other
Founders who were starting companies on
the side even the ones who were failing
I was more excited about what they were
doing and the pot they were on than what
I was doing at airb be when I left airb
B I started working on one idea which
was a health Tech idea we were trying to
build an app for people with Parkinson's
disease to better understand their
condition it was a terrible idea for a
lot of reasons and we spent a whole year
on it the end I decided to Pivot not
only away from the idea and the industry
of Health Tech in general but also the
co-founder I was working with even when
I started working with my now
co-founders adith and Robert we spent
months pivoting together until we
finally came up with
pylon what we were interested in doing
was building a really big fast growing
company I have considered giving up many
times I think in the back of your head
you're always questioning okay should I
keep going but there was just something
nagging inside of me that wouldn't let
me hey you know this is what you need to
be doing you need to keep trying and all
you need is one thing to work out and
then that'll you know blow away all the
failures in the past pivoting is really
really hard you are going to Pivot a lot
and you're going to Pivot so much that
my co-founders and I we call it pivot
hell now once you actually get into
pivot hell and you start working with
people and every week you might be
switching ideas it becomes really really
hard to keep going your parents are
going to ask you what you're doing with
your life your girlfriend or boyfriend
are going to question hey like should
you maybe start looking for a real job
and you're also going to have this like
creeping doubt that hey maybe I'm not
actually good at this and uh should I
keep going my suggestion is frankly if
you feel like you should stop going you
should probably stop going and if you
can't not continue then you should
continue and that was the case for me I
basically didn't feel like I had a
choice I had to keep going because
that's just how my brain is wired one of
the learnings for us was you just have
to start in a really really big Market
what type of idea you want to be working
on to make something really big that can
grow really fast what we did was we kind
of like observed the biggest software
companies in the world and turns out
there aren't that many public SAS
companies if you look at them like
they're probably 76 uh Billion Dollar
Plus public software companies that are
B2B and of them almost all of them are
horizontal SAS products meaning hey
they're selling uh products that can be
sold into almost any industry so think
like payroll it sales marketing customer
support Etc we decided okay let's to
make sure we don't get stuck in a market
let's go after something really big so
we chose kind of post sales customer
support as a category to go explore what
we did was we went on LinkedIn And We
messaged uh 40 people a day that's what
LinkedIn would let you do let's say 7%
of those people respond you know would
create a cycle of us just cold
interviewing people in Customer Support
roles that we wanted to learn from I
think you need to be very clear with
yourself what type of company you want
to build we wanted to build something
explicitly very big and for us that
meant a $10 billion market cap public
company that was making let's say a
billion dollars in revenues and also
fast growing meant that usually there's
some sort of emerging Trend that's
happening in the world where you can
capture that and grow with it so where
we saw this emerging trend of B2B
communication moving away from email to
kind of new channels if I were going
through and trying to find ideas now the
strategy we used I think can be
effective for other people we basically
decided okay we're going to explore the
customer support and success space um
you know kind of horizontal category and
then within it we said we're going to go
and cold interview people also at the
same time a was popping up and turns out
all the data is flowing through pylon is
conversational so now for the first time
ever There's an opportunity to structure
it who have newer types of roles so like
new job titles that didn't exist let's
say 10 years ago a lot of customer
success managers support Engineers
Solutions Engineers those people didn't
exist 5 years ago now they did so we
thought hey new roles might mean new
workflows which means new software and
maybe there's opportunity
there the best time to raise a series a
is when you're going to get the terms if
investors are pounding on your door even
if you haven't hit a certain Revenue
Milestone it might be the right time to
just go and take that we raised our $3.2
million seed rone from General Catalyst
in 6 days that's a catchy headline and
and it did really feel like we were
living in an episode of Silicon Valley
the story is we were 2 months into our
YC batch 3 months old as a company
overall we were probably around like
60,000 in annual revenue at the time 2
months into YC that's when people start
to think about fundraising bring on
investors before the end of the batch
well we did was we scheduled as many
calls with VC's in the course of one
week tried to create some sort of like
time pressure between the investors
themselves spreading it out basically
going in with the mentality and kind of
signaling to every investor hey yeah
we're fundraising really hard this week
and there might not be time for
conversations next week so we kind of
need to knock everything out uh right
now all at once every time we got in
touch with an investor it was important
how they heard about us so instead of
just like cold emailing investors
directly saying hey we're pil on like
you should invest in us we instead got
Founders that they respected and knew um
some that were even our customers
already go message them and say hey VC I
know this founder the founder pylon
they're going to YC right now are you
talking to them yet you should because
they're a hot company I think what
they're working on is really good we got
a bunch of really great introductions
through that and that just meant that
the investors were coming directly to us
like basically ready uh to have serious
conversations and we'd skip straight to
partner meetings the social proof was
just already there and at seed round
social proof is everything your business
is still so nent it's so hard to kind of
understand you know where you're going
to go so having Founders vouch for you
who the investor trust is is really
really important to give you a sense of
the timeline here so we start our
initial conversations with investors on
I guess it was a Monday Wednesday is
when we had our first discussion with
General Catalyst who eventually let our
seed Dr Friday we had in-person partner
meeting with General Catalyst uh
investors and then Saturday went to the
apartment of one of the investors uh
went to the roof had like kind of a
social conversation and by night time
that same day they gave us uh a verbal
offer that they wanted to invest the
general advice that we got was hey find
people who are good partners for the
long term who have a reputable brand um
that brand then helps you bring on
employees because you have that social
proof and then we'll also help you you
know close customers they can help you
get investors for the next round so
General Catalyst was basically the top
of our list and so we were going after
funds like them to for for the seed run
the whole process took around 14 days at
the end of 14 days we ended up closing
with andreon um who led a $17 million
series a run the process of like talking
to all those investors was not easy they
actually tried to fill your calendar as
much as possible to make sure that you
don't talk to other people once they
express interest because there's only
downside for them to wait if they
express interest then they know that
other investors will suddenly get
interested just because of that like
social Dynamic low dilution was the
thing that was really important for us
we just didn't want to sell 25% of the
company the only way to get low dilution
is to have a competitive round we want
INRI into better terms then you have to
go to someone else they respect so you
have to go to like a benchmark or
Sequoia and andri has to feel like
they're going to lose you if they do not
lower the dilution amount it's kind of
this like social game where they need to
make the terms better for you and the
company when he was trying to figure out
how to have a good fundraise he
basically was like okay how do you have
a fundraise fast like the Twitter guys
that was the example he gave and so he
asked investors he's like why did the
Twitter guys have such a fast fundraise
there are actually no secrets it's you
have to have a really good team building
in a really big Market with a really
good product that people love and you
know high potential for growth you have
all those things you've kind of already
done all the work here are the numbers
here's the growth rate here's you know
what customers are saying and they're
just going to be convinced based off of
that so really just the fundamentals are
what's actually
important basically riding a big wave
and then we have the founder SL compan
that's a a great Surfer and so as a
result you can surf the the big wave hi
I'm uh tah Nam a co-founder of storm
Ventures and also co-author of uh
survival to thrival I started working in
Silicon Valley in 1985 and then uh
started storm in 2000 we've invested in
uh over 200 B2B software companies since
then of which 12 have become unicorns
probably the best knowns are like
maretto we also have uh unicorns like
Vado techon algolia pipe drive and so
forth want to talk to you about what
happens after you unlock growth in other
words you've spent all this effort to
catch the wave and how do you stay on
the
way I hope that everyone that's in a
startup recognizes that it's a an
emotional roller coaster where you can
go from the highest of highs the lowest
of lows in 5 minutes and so in those
moments I hope you realize life is never
so bad or never were so good and at the
end uh enjoy the
[Music]
journey when you're competing against
incumbent you're not actually competing
with all the employees there most of
them are not working on R&D most of them
actually do not care because you know
they're just getting a paycheck we were
at the time especially living in the
office working 14-hour days the number
of people grinding at Zenda trying to
accomplish the same thing is very few I
think at this stage what has worked for
us in terms of what the founder should
be doing and what leader should look
like is just doing the work yourself so
leadership at pylon is very much just
doing the work yourself and other people
kind of following by example so like 6
months ago we were actually living at
the office it was like Robert had a bed
in the living room and that you know
everyone just had desk surrounding or
our salesperson his desk that he would
take sales calls out was literally like
5T away from had this bed I was like
sleeping in a meeting room for us
leadership just meant doing the work and
then people kind of seeing that kind of
being motivated and excited by by that
being a Founder is very very stressful
at the end of every month that's when we
do our reporting on how much revenue and
how quickly we've grown we keep doing it
and part of me feels like oh my God this
is magical it just keeps happening but
it's very stressful I think the only way
through the stress is by just addressing
the problems and grinding really really
hard so you can more consistently
maintain growth and you know hiring
Pipeline and building great product both
myself and and I think my co-founders
feel very similarly where we just want
to win we want to build a company and so
we just didn't let ourselves give
up I think the really important thing is
to be able to build and solve problems
yourself say heyy I'm just going to go
find let's say a technical co-founder
who will build the product for me I
think you should stop being lazy and
learn how to build yourself there are
lots of resources on how to do it you
could go watch YouTube like I did go to
a boot camp or any free courses that
exists around the world at this point
just learn how to build for yourself
especially with AI it's becoming so easy
then the world is your oyster you can
have an idea make it and then just try
it and see what happens so first off if
you're not like purely set on starting a
company immediately I do actually
recommend just trying to get a job at a
startup you can create a network and
kind of like be immersed in the startup
community so for example you work at
pylon we have events here all the time
for Founders and um other startups that
are coming through so you just have an
opportunity to mingle with a bunch of
people if you are just set on starting a
company immediately I would probably go
live in a hacker House of some sort I
would probably just attend a lot of
Meetup YC has meetups now and events I
would just go to as many of those as you
could find the best people and then try
to get into their networks I would
probably tell myself learn from others
more I think I'm one of those people
that often likes to just go figure
things out on my own which I think is
really helpful but I think there's also
a lot of advice for example I could have
gone to successful entrepreneurs and
been like hey what do you think of my
idea like is this good what do you think
are the risks whatever and I gotten to
the same point 2 years later in months
had I just like listened to their advice
taken that instead of just trying to
like discover everything on my own
interviews like this is that hey I'm
someone who's already gone through it
maybe you can learn from some of my
mistakes instead of going through the
same two years of pain that I did as
well so that would be one piece of
advice is just go learn from other
people who have done it before and are a
couple years ahead of you