can you share the story of hanging out
with Sam Alman I was launching Al's
first accelerator program Sam Alman was
like visiting New Zealand I just like
bothered him in his Twitter DM you like
surfing no answer eventually I got him
like oh that'd be great when I said
something like oh I can maybe get an
investor to provide like a big boat and
we could do a tour of a harbor and so
first of all I didn't have a boat but he
said oh that'd be great I'd love to meet
some New Zealand startup went and found
a boat from some investor in New Zealand
but the investor was like fishing guy he
wanted to go fishing Sam was vegan at
the time I got this boat but the only
way we could use it as if the guy could
take us fishing it's just like oh I'm
sorry we're hauling up all these poor
fish and you're sitting there just like
chilling in the inside of the boat
talking to a few startup he was Running
Y combinator I was trying to launch New
Zealand's first accelerator
program maybe to start could you please
introduce yourselves yeah I'm Matthew
Herbert co-founder and co-coo of trackit
and I'm Connor arold co-founder and
co-ceo of tracksuit tell us a little bit
about tracksuit what this it do what
problem is it solving tracksuit as a
brand tracking platform the best way to
measure top of funnel marketing the
problem that we're solving in in
marketing and brand building is there's
two jobs to be done the 95 and the and
the 5% the two jobs the 5% in any
category there are about 5% of people
who are ready to buy from you right now
and that's one job go and get those
people to buy from your your product and
your Brands but at the same time there's
95% of people who will come into the
category aren't ready to buy from you
right now but what are you doing to
build your famili familiarity and and
emotional closeness and and make people
fall in love with your with your company
and your brand so that when they are
ready to buy they're going to come and
buy from your business over the last you
know 15 years or so the world of
marketing has been so focused and
successful at measuring 5% of people or
the bottom of the funnel the sales the
conversions at the expense of the 95 and
so what we're doing at tracksuit is
building the best way to measure how
well you're building your brands with
the 95% of people that will come into
the category and they're going to choose
your brand essentially tracksuit we do
surveys of humans to find out what they
think and feel about Brands that's novel
because any company in the world hasn't
been able to afford this it's only being
available for Enterprise companies who
have $200,000 to pay for market research
reports that end up sitting on a desk
Gathering dust and we've created a
beautiful dashboard with you know we're
collecting surveys every single day for
7,000 Brands now globally we help those
marketers understand what people think
and feel about those Brands and how did
you two meet we we met at a previous
startup we started on the same day when
we were much younger mat was like the
first SDR ended up looking after all of
APAC I started as like sweep the FL
floors generalist guy ended up as coo
based out of New York yeah tracksuit we
we both moved back to New Zealand many
years later and tracksuit was sort of
started off the back of a weekly coffee
when we were figuring out what was next
for both of us this goes back eight
years colleagues friends and now and now
co-founders having another go with you
know with trackit bring on the all the
learnings from our from our experience
to you know build a company that we
really wanted to do and so yeah 8year
journey and few more to come one thing I
wanted to ask is uh how would you
describe each other and you can describe
each other as friends but also as
co-founders colleagues however you want
to go about this but yeah how would you
describe each other who's going first
all right I'll start I'll start all
right so con and I I've known each other
for eight years now colleagues friends
business partners Founders and so the
way describe Connor as a person as a
leader is just a little bit like a big
grizzly bear and what I mean by a big
grizzly bear okay is that he's the first
one to come over and give everybody a
big hug but every now and then he can
show a little bit of teeth and a little
bit of raw okay and he's the best at
just at at honestly at drive at driving
at driving forward and that's a a big
part that when we came together I mean
compliment child I know exactly what
Connor's going to say so that's why I
wanted to get in first he's like a big
grizzly bear he looks tough and scary
a big S but when he needs to drive he he
can drive really well all right there's
a reason the beard is just growing it
out more and
more all right yeah Matt I'll go I'll go
with spirit animal as well I guess so
Matt um I think like he's the perfect
cross of like a border collie and like
Golden Retriever and that he's the he's
the stick with me here
he's he will make your day every day in
the office like you are stoked to run
into Matt in the hallway Matt is stoked
to run into you in the hallway everyone
appreciates Matt's energy and what he
brings but he also is like in every
meeting he's like okay what what are the
next steps like what are we doing he's
keeping us on task he's keeping us
focused and it's a really yeah it's a
nice combination and we work really well
together he also just like make sure the
team are focused if he sees a ball
bouncing somewhere he runs really
quickly no just
um but yeah it's it's a really nice
combo he's just super kind and always
has a smile but keeps you on task keeps
you focused and keeps you moving you
know I think one thing I think was is
worth touching on here and why this is
working why I just love working and and
leading tracksuit with with Connor is
that it's so complimentary and one of
the the very first I me couple of weeks
as we were coming in to start trackit
what we did is we did not only personal
Behavior profiling but team profiling
and so
this is where you say who do who do I
think I am as a person but what do my
teammates and what do my old colleagues
perceive me as and so you get this
really objective view around not only
what I think but what does my team think
we went through this exercise where
Conor and I both did this and it comes
out to say what is Connor what is Matt
where are our strengths where our
weaknesses but more so what are the
things just to watch out where's Connor
going to go and this is where Connor's
driving and really good and compliments
me and where are there where are the
some areas where you know I'm leaning
into to my superpowers or or My areas
but just knowing where we might cause
tension where we might see the world in
different ways and so having that as a
framework about who we are how we
operate how we build and operate and
teams together I think has had you know
a really impactful and huge impact on
who we are as As Leaders as friends as
colleagues but also the type of culture
and teams that we're building at
tracksuit you know what your role is in
any given team situation which is quite
fascinating if you know that you're the
strongest creative Problem Solver or the
strongest driver you know that when you
see people struggling with a problem
that it's your turn to step in or you
know when you see people kind of
deliberating for too long it's your turn
to step in and drive it forward and just
make a call and so yeah once you
understand how you fit in with the team
you are able to kind of embody that
trait at the right time and so yeah it
was it was is fascinating to do that and
it has helped we've done it for every
single person we're now at 100 employees
everyone knows what their roles are how
they should and can interact with the
team super helpful and then you also
decided to become co-ceos that must have
also been a very intentional decision as
co-founders so maybe help us understand
how that decision was made I I mean when
we started truit we both were doing
everything it was just and because we
were bootstrapped it was just like half
the time you're doing demo if you close
customers they're your customers and you
run it and we're both sort of thinking
about product and iterating and it kind
of naturally started that way where we
were both kind of doing it all and just
talking about the opportunity and then
as we started bringing on team members I
think you look at what we were doing and
it's like this is perfect the way it is
like let's not upset the apple cat I
think Coos is it's a like it's a really
interesting thing that you have to be
intentional with and we redraft our JDS
almost every 6 months I'd say where the
company's changing really fast so we
need to adapt and change really fast and
so yeah it's that relationship has
updated what we focus on at any given
time has changed the main thing is that
we have to be really good at
communicating just maintain that like
solid connection ourselves yeah it's
worked so far and I think it would you
know we can hire better people into a
CPO position or a COO position who've
been there and done that and there's
almost a bit of a hack in Matt can be in
London being a CEO and I can be in New
Zealand being a CEO so it's like 247
coverage yeah it's double it's double
trouble yeah and I mean and I've heard
I've heard a couple times where around
if you're a CEO or a Founder founder CEO
you're the one that gets the least
amount of feedback in the business until
you're really intentional about that and
so to be able to do that together give
each other feedback take on each other's
feedback and have that ongoing dialogue
is so important so that you know really
lines and clear on what we're trying to
do here at trackit but also you know see
the world in slightly different ways and
compliment but it's that ongoing
communication I don't know how founder
CEOs go around building and maintaining
rapidly growing business as well as if
you're going down and raising investment
when we went through that that's that's
two full-time roles and then that was a
great example of when we decided to go
and and raise Capital you know a lot of
Connor time was spent on on doing that
the upwards stakeholder management
investor relations while I was able to
lean into keeping the business going and
maintaining and and the momentum that we
needed so being able to split the roles
we needed with what the company needs to
do leaning to our strengths but being
able to do it together is is fantastic
highly recommend yeah that's great
highly recommend as long as you're good
communicators yeah as long as it works
and you don't let your OS get in the way
right CU you got to I think that's I
reckon that's the main thing that gets
in the way of Coos over time is just
someone gets a little bit offended that
some call was made or they're like you
stepped on my toes and then it's like sh
then everyone's doing best at any given
time and and we're both aligned with
that long-term Vision so keep pushing
keep moving and make it
work you've made the cooco format work
quite well so far and so if you were to
give advice to other Founders on the
structure like how would you recommend
what advice would you have on this
co-ceo idea basically what I recommend
it yes I would recommend it I think
recommend it with a couple of flags is
that we also knew each other we've known
each other for 8 years when we first
came into this we did that teaming
exercise who are we as people how do we
operate in teams how are we going to
work dynamically so that I know exactly
where Connor's going off somewhere like
great I'm going to let Connor go there
when I'm starting to really lean in or
or or fight for all I want Conor knows
that like there's a reason why Matt's
going on on on that area knowing who you
are and how you operate together is
really important we're seeing in new
zealands that the multi CEO is as a
thing I think we looked at sh sharesies
investment they have AO they've got AO
shes and New Zealand have a three EO
there are examples of where it worked if
we weren't really honest with each other
if we didn't really know who each other
were deeply it probably would fall over
and so recommend it but go into caution
just because it works for us doesn't
mean it's going to work for everybody
else but what we do want to do is prove
that we can build an incredibly
successful business but be really well
respected in how we grow and what
trackit is as a place of work and the
impact that can that we can have yeah
everything you jump into in business in
life like there's going to be an outcome
and it's either going to be accidental
or it's going to be designed the coast
of your relationship is not something
you can go into and be open to an
accidental outcome you have to
intentionally design the relationship
your what Your roles are how you
interact otherwise I don't think it
would end well and and people aren't
very good at doing that when things are
busy and when they're hectic people
forget that they leave it for too long
so if you think you're that way inclined
don't do the coasty thing if you're
willing to put in the time and the
effort go ahead maybe even rewinding
further if you go to your personal
backgrounds a little bit of your
upbringing and also what some of the
SEMA moments were that you think LED you
to getting attracted to this world of
startups and Technology I actually
started my career as a corporate lawyer
of all things kind of wasn't inspired by
that uh so much which is probably easy
to
imagine but
I like ended up raising a fund and
almost going into the VC route first
because I started Auckland New Zealand's
first accelerator program and that was
my like risk-free way of understanding
everything I could about startups jumped
into one of the startups that came
through that program and that's that's
when I met Matt now wife and I ended up
running a surf and yoga retreat in
Nicaragua at some point um inar yeah
yeah we spent a year there and so yeah
I'm I'm attracted by you know like kind
of trying new things I've always always
been a first principles thinker and I
think that naturally you lend that lends
itself to being in a startup and and
maybe being a Founder in particular so
yeah I think I was always going to end
up here and have had a nice Meandering
path getting here I also studied law and
science I never went and practiced law
but my first role in the world of tech
was being part of the Uber team that
launched Uber in New Zealand and so that
was you know big Tech Big Brand that was
coming across the other side of the
world and being involved in that and you
know startup mode but the backing of
what Uber was in 2015 2016 that was the
introduction to Tech and I said great
let's get let's keep going in the in the
startup world had the opportunity to
move to Sydney that's where Connor and I
move met on the first day back in New
Zealand Connor was off to New York I was
going off to Sydney that company was a
company called Mish Guru it was looking
after the snap uh Snapchat management
platform and so we were working Keely
with leading agencies and Brands to
unlock Snapchat as a new channel and so
that was the that was the real the the
tow into to MK really helping modern
brands use news new channels we there
for you know 5 years or so and then
ended up back in New Zealand linked up
with Connor have always loved uh brands
have always loved um an entrepreneurial
spirit I guess growing up I ran
Landscaping businesses and and pool
cleaning and and car washing around the
neighborhood so I don't know whether
that's where my entrepreneurial Spirit
came from but then Tech mtech and then
now trackit tell us a little bit about
New Zealand what is it like to grow up
as a kiwi what is the tech scene this is
a it's a great a great question I always
like to get Connor's perspective on this
um Connor brings the the best of the
American and the best of the the New
Zealand
take s yeah I I was born in California
and moved to New Zealand when I was 11
so I kind of have a bit of both matx I
think I can dial up one or the other
depending on what we need at trackx at
any given time do we need wild ambition
optimism and uh Ching those dreams and
drive yeah a drive yeah or you know he
can turn on the sort of the cool chill
kiwi charm and and that's the other side
so I mean growing up in New Zealand is
amazing I always like to tell my
American and friends that like my first
week of school in New Zealand I got in
trouble for wearing shoes that's like
New Zealand culture it's so relaxed it's
a wonderful place to grow up the tech
scene I think is it's an exciting place
if you talk to investors around the
world a lot of them are starting to look
at New Zealand and Australia because
we've had a lot of success recently with
the likes of canva and just like some
big companies coming out of that part of
the world and and we're starting to see
second time third time operators or
Founders coming through we're known for
being highly efficient that's because we
haven't had a lot of capital previously
you're seeing these companies come out
that are highly efficient they've it's a
great place to test and learn and so
it's a bit of a beta Nation because
you've got a highly engaged small
population the things that are coming
out tend to have good product Market fit
they're highly efficient and then they
can kind of take the World by storm
relatively quickly I visited New Zealand
a few years ago and I learned that there
are more sheep than humans who told who
told you that everyone I think cows are
actually the most now cows okay got it a
lot of cows but there there is a big
agretech sector like in New Zealand so
yeah we have we have Rockets we have
agretech and now we have truit y there
we go and does that impact the way you
thought of or think of the way you build
a company in other words do most
entrepreneurs think to go Global from
day one because it's a relatively
smaller Market or are there people still
focused mostly on the domestic Market
the global from day one I think there
are so many different ways to build
business and what the aspirations are
and when you want to to take things
absolutely at some point if you do have
international intentions you need to
leave New Zealand I mean there's only
you know there's 5 A2 million people in
New Zealand there's 25 million people in
Australia so the same it's the same size
as California how many hundreds of cows
thousands of hundreds of millions but
when you look at so when you look at the
size of of New Zealand at 52 million and
and Australia at about 25 it's the same
as California and so depending on what
you're doing and where you're trying to
go absolutely people look you know
offshore you can still build big
business across Australia and New
Zealand for us for you know for Conor
and I with track we were so intentional
about the way that we wanted to grow
track a few scars and burns about trying
to go Global too fast and and and
product Market fit and that type of
thing so with trackx right from the
start we said hey look the back end of
the technology that we're doing needs to
be in a position that we can turn on any
Market in the world when we're ready but
we wanted to be super intentional about
the way that we built do we have product
Market fit are people paying us are we
solving real problems are we building a
great team are we building great brands
that then enables us to go and scale so
we started in New Zealand our New
Zealand customers said can you do this
in Australia great we moved into
Australia we started working with
Incredible Australian Brands like
Culture Kings and Bondi Sands and then
those businesses said hey look the us
we've got a whole lot of Revenue in the
US we're trying to figure out how to
position what our competitors are doing
where we should be spending our
marketing dollars and so we went into
know came into the US off the back of
our our customers the same into the UK
so we've been pulled into the markets
which has allowed us to scale a team
with our customers with product Market
fit but always from the start absolutely
Global from day one but not turning it
on straight away and I think being from
New Zealand and how intentional we are
with our company Matt and I when we
started we wanted to spend 50% of our
energy on what we were building and
creating a great product and and trying
but we also wanted to like spend 50% of
our energy on how we were building and
sort of taking a great culture in our
company and then kind of taking that
culture to the world so we do have four
Global offices now we've got Sydney New
York and London on top of our our New
Zealand Auckland head office and we've
been putting some of our key members of
our early team into those offices and we
try to bring that New Zealand and that
tracksuit culture to the world while
making like a good amount of room and
and setting space for that kind of local
flavor to be a part of that in each
office as well all right we'll end on uh
can you share the story of hanging out
with Sam Alman in Auckland I was
launching Oakland's first accelerator
program Sam Alman was like visiting New
Zealand I think on a holiday not to like
do anything official I just like
bothered him in his Twitter DMS for a
long time like hey you want to we go
you're from California do you like
surfing do you want to go no no answer
do you want to like do something I don't
know and eventually I got him like he
said oh that'd be great when I said
something like oh I can maybe get an
investor to provide like a big boat and
we could do a tour of the harbor and go
so first of all I didn't have a boat um
but he said oh that'd be great I'd love
to meet some New Zealand startups so I
went and found a 70ft boat from some
investor in New Zealand go and we all
went out on it but the investor was like
he was like a a fishing guy like he he
wanted to go fishing and he wanted to
show these American visitors the great
fish you can catch in New Zealand
harbors and Sam was vegan at the time
so like I got this boat but the only way
we could use it is if the guy could take
us fishing and so it was just like oh
I'm sorry man like we're hauling up all
these poor fish and you sitting there
just like chilling in the inside of the
boat talking to a few stups and yeah
anyway so that was that was my
interaction with Sam mman 15 years ago
he was Running Y combinator and I was
trying to launch New Zealand's first
accelerator program and here we are here
we are here we are amazing
Bo thank you Matt thank you Connor we
really appreciate it thanks T thank you