idealist techie you know Stanford grad
student in the garage saying we're going
to make outcomes better those companies
all fail most early stage Founders go to
Partners and say hey like what is it
that you need like tell me and I'll just
deliver for you if you're looking to
them just to give me the answers they
don't know what's possible
technologically often times they're not
sure how the market trends are moving
they're not going to be able to tell you
what the answer is what they're really
really good at is telling you what the
problems are my name is p Tran I'm the
CEO and co-founder of FM Health FM
health is a company that is trying to
make clinical AI tools accessible to the
doctors and patients that need it we
just closed a $16 million series a round
we've raised a total of $31 million our
success is going to occur by enabling
big Tech big Healthcare governments AI
developers by enabling everyone in the
market to be able to collaborate and
deploy AI the way it needs to be
deployed
I was months away from graduating
Stanford Medical School when I actually
decided to go and leave this start my
first company as a medical student hudos
go stford Med for allowing us to be
extremely flexible with our time so I
was one of those students who kind of
had my hand in all sorts of different Pi
where I was doing like device work I was
working on side projects with friends
from the business school and the medical
school and atics was really at the
beginning just one of those side
projects as a medical student I was
working in the county hospital here here
in the barria that was a nightmare I was
there while they were transitioning from
paper records to electronic records
where doctors were losing track of
patients no one could figure out where
medications were people were burning out
and spending three four times as much of
their day on documentation as they were
before and actually back in the day this
was when Google Glass was still emerging
onto the scene everyone thought that it
was going to be the Advent of the
wearable era and that emerging
technology intersecting with the real
pain points that I was seeing in my
day-to-day Life as a medical student we
found dog Medics because we wanted to
doctor spend their day taking care of
patients rather than documenting patient
records Aug Medics and Google Glass
allow a scribe located offsite to
securely see and hear what the doctor
sees and hears during an exam in a real
time video we showed pretty early on
that writing the notes for the doctors
actually allows them to deliver better
care as well 2 3 years into my first
company I was still considering going
back and and still thinking about hey
you know what point do I maybe leave the
company go back to medical school become
a doctor but once we saw our technology
being used to deliver care to thousands
of additional patients a month I
realized wow like I have already had
more of an impact on healthare than I
would have had in my entire career as a
doctor and we went to santel Road and to
the The Venture Capital firms there and
we were able to raise round of funding
off of that idea and we spent a few
years probably trying to build out the
company prove out the idea and
ultimately continued to stay on leave
from medical school as the company
grew so a few years into the augme
journey I think the whole world started
to realize that Google Glass probably
wasn't going to be a thing and so we had
to figure out what are we going to do
with this company and with this Mission
if Google Glass isn't going to be a
thing and if our company's brand has
been built off that so far because we
had that really clear Mission because we
knew hey like you know it's not about
the Google Glass it's about what we
believed the glasses could for
healthcare that we were able to Pivot
and pretty rapidly launch tablet and
phone based versions of our software
that instead of sitting the doctor's
face they would bring around either card
around as a tablet or bring around in
their pocket that still did the same
thing I think what that taught me is
that if you go into a new technology
looking for a problem you're probably
going to get pretty far but ultimately
fail and I think the difference between
Aug Medics which we were able to
continue to grow over time and a lot of
those companies is that we started off
as a technology looking for a problem
but we just happened to find a really
really big and important problem and so
that allowed us to stay alive moving
forward from that I have become really
really careful around new technology
Trends even AI the new wave of gen AI
tele medicine through Co all of those
boom and bust Cycles they all occur
around emerging Technologies they never
occur around endemic pain points and so
gen today yes it it's promising yes it's
going to change the world is it going to
change the world to the scale that
everyone is saying it will at the
Timeline that everyone's saying it well
like guaranteed not and it's because we
always tend to overestimate these
Technologies in the near- term over the
long term they will have an impact but
that that long term is longer time frame
than any one startup is able to weather
during that journey I actually had an
uncle pass away from a late stage lung
cancer that was missed by his doctors
and it was a really frustrating
experience for myself and my family
because I already was a successful
entrepreneur in the digital Health space
when we were providing care for him and
talking to his doctors he was receiving
the best care in the world he was going
regularly for his screenings you know he
did everything right but because his
doctors weren't using the most modern of
tools a lot of these AI diagnostic tools
around lung cancer that have been
launched over the past decade he wasn't
able to actually have his cancer time in
fact it was missed for almost 5 years he
would have benefited so much from
technology from AI tools his doctors
wanted to use those tools but hospitals
not being able to actually adopt AI
themselves directly like at some point
someone was going to solve it question
was how long will it take to solve what
we realized was if we don't start this
company it is extremely unlikely that
someone else will and succeed FM health
is our attempt at trying to solve this
disconnect between the technology that's
out there the need for a platform that
allows for the consolidation of AI
vendors into a single point back when we
first started the company I was really
skeptical about how good these AI tools
actually were some patients and some
hospitals that we worked with in Asia
that we launched our pilot product
initially and that was an open- Source
lung nodule tool something that was a
made available online for public use and
we ran it for 3 Days across their scans
and we basically look to see how many
patients does did this model find that
the doctors didn't find and 3 days later
we're like oh wow like there are almost
50 patients here who have very
significant findings it makes the
mission of the company just so urgent we
happen to have a Tailwind of AI hype
that maybe it lasts one more year maybe
it lasts three more years but like hype
Cycles come and go and so there's going
to be a time when that hype no longer is
there but for us like we solve a real
problem that endure over time at some
point you have to be solving a really
important problem or you will never be
able to claw your way out of that
experimentation early stage most early
stage Founders firsttime Founders that I
meet are overly focused on building a
really good technology product and not
enough focus on identifying the exact
paino and problem they're solving figure
out what matters what are the risks that
I need to drisk and proving that out
even manually right like just by doing
it with an Excel spreadsheet or with a
human being in the background rather
than having to launch the whole product
and spending all that money before
you've tested out those initial
assumptions Co was brutal and this is
not a super exciting kind of thing to
bring up but Co was absolutely brutal it
was especially brutal because the
general perspective was wow if you're a
Healthcare Company you should be doing
great but the actual reality was like
most companies were dying because no one
was able to sell unless you were very
specifically solving a CO problem really
honestly like we don't have that much to
do with global pandemic so we're solving
an AI deployment issue for health
systems and that just was not a priority
so keeping the team motivated keeping
our investors and stakeholders and
customers aligned and engaged and
excited about this problem when nobody
cared about it for years and years and
years was really difficult more patients
died due to delay in care then die from
Co we're going to keep focusing what
we're going to focus on and we're going
to try to build the best business we can
around this and survive until everyone
else kind of gets there I think that
easily could have led to the company
collapse but I think what that has
allowed us to do now that AI is hot now
that hospitales are looking at platforms
now that can all of our original thesis
when we founded the company have come to
bear and we've stayed focused on that
problem for the past 5 years is that we
are just again incredibly well
positioned and we've got such a head
start on the broader Market in order to
actually succeed as a Founder you've got
to be really comfortable with everyone
thinking you're wrong for a really
really long time I still have not seen
one example of a massive iconic company
where everyone didn't think that they
were completely out of their mind for
the first few years a human being you
usually look for societal approval as
Founders like you kind of have to be
comfortable um not just not having that
but being able to convince people who
otherwise didn't see it the same way you
did that you're right and you do have to
just be used to everyone either not
knowing what you're talking about or
thinking you're wrong and just
comfortable just over and over and over
convincing them of why what you're doing
is the right approach and why it's
important a lot of my classmates are now
you know super high-powered specialized
doctors that are making a ton of money
and so it's easy to look at hey like if
I just stayed as a doctor I would be
some you know badass surgeon doing XYZ
thing and especially as my friends all
have now Sav me a ton of lives they did
like it's an incredibly rewarding
profession that I never had a chance to
actually go into but that's probably one
of the sacrifices and trade-offs that I
had to make and I just have to look at
the hundreds and thousands of patients
that are technology is saving and say
like listen like fine like I'm not going
to do it directly but we're still going
to be able to deliver a lot of impact in
society and that's enough for us you
kind of have to start companies at a
young age because your risk appetite
goes down as you get older the downside
of starting a company when you're young
is the lack of Industry knowledge the
lack of Industry connections I think it
is much easier to solve those problems
just by being diligent and by networking
and connecting people and being
open-minded you can solve those problems
as a young person for firsttime Founders
it is really really easy to just go to
hospitals go to Partners and say hey
like what is it that you need like tell
me and I'll just deliver for you but the
real challenge is like these are
problems that Health Systems often times
don't know how to solve and so if you're
looking to them just to give you the
answers they don't know what's possible
technologically often times they're not
sure how the market trends are moving
and so they're not going to be able to
tell you what the answer is what they're
really really good at is telling you
what the problems are and so when we go
in and we work with hospitals we always
make sure to align around hey like what
are the problems they're trying to solve
and it's different depending on the
hospital some hospitals really care
about delivering the best care possible
to the patients and they want to use
these AI tools for that many others care
a lot about productivity by being really
clear upfront about hey we solve the
security problem we solve the patient
safety problem and if those are problems
that you have let us help you and if
they aren't great you are not the right
partner for us we're going to go focus
our time elsewhere and that's tough for
startups to do because you know if
you're looking at revenue and you
otherwise don't have it that can be a
really difficult decision to make but as
a result you know every one of our
customers really love the fact that we
solve a problem that they really care
about I think that's been pivotal to us
being able to have this trusted advisor
relationship with all of our hosital
Executives and faram is not going to be
able to be the one platform that
everyone everywhere in the world uses
for everything our success is going to
occur by enabling big Tech big
Healthcare governments AI developers by
enabling everyone in the market to be
able to collaborate and deploy AI the
way it needs to be deployed and so I
don't think of firm as this kind of
search bar for the internet or as Uber
for taxis I don't think we're going to
be this dominant kind of front Force I
think that we are building the pipelines
we're building the tooling the pick and
shovels that ideally everyone everywhere
is using and if you can make AI truly
fungible truly liquid um truly zero cost
to adopt then you end up with that
future state I talked about which is a
fundamentally transformed Healthcare
System
[Music]