put your seat back a little kid it
doesn't go back yes I'm not gonna lean
back though in the whole video
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you
yeah
[Music]
it's been so long since day from the car
video I'm super excited and we're gonna
jump right into today's [ __ ] topic
immediately because I have no time to
hesitate because I'm sick of that [ __ ]
hesitating this for the week and if
you're not the one hesitating
you're the stronger one that's no that
didn't even like that we didn't even
have like no if you're the one
hesitating you lose if you're hesitating
your opponent isn't exactly
that's not really true either but
regardless today we're going to talk
about
strike first and strike hard you say
this all the time no mercy today we're
going to talk about the
random numbers
correlating situations I mean stop put
the Pepsi down no I'm gonna kiss it
actually so we're gonna talk about
picking a number we're gonna pick a
number pick a number now and then how
does this go hold on Nick
what is here we're gonna say either in a
um a um a scenario or a number and then
say a scenario or a number depending on
what we said
repeat buttons no that's kind of true
okay so basically first thing we're
gonna start off with I'm gonna pick the
number 30 000. with the number of 30
000. we have to pick what do you think
has happened in our life that you have
done thirty thousand times since the
moment thirty thousand is [ __ ]
astronomical okay what's the point it's
like insane okay 30 000 times well let's
think about it I'm 19 years old do we
want to take the like stupid guest route
or whoa my God this dude on the bike
scared the Dickens no the point is we're
supposed to all say it at the exist
because how I think is like 300
we don't want to hear how you think yet
first thanks version to see how far off
we are okay and say three different
topics thirty thousand thirty thousand
I'm gonna go ready yeah no hold on let
me think think fast I'm going blanks
honestly can you shut the [ __ ] up you
stupid what like we're supposed to say
it at the same time oh that's what I
said maybe five times I got it now okay
new number okay twenty thousand twenty
thousand that's so lame okay you pick a
[ __ ] number seven seven yep bro okay
uh three
two I don't have anything bro come on I
got one three seven two
ready
I'm ready Matt okay okay yeah yeah three
two one so go to the emergency room
because you hurt yourself funerals
somersaults somersaults what yeah I've
done seven summer results in a row as a
child I feel like
good old Summer's I used to somersault
down a hill literally straight down
so wait is it somersault vertical or
horizontal regardless you can't
somersault yeah
I'm talking about twist or twirl it's a
twirl it's really not twist that's a
roll oh a roll wait so what's a summer
song straight head first oh that's yeah
vertical yes that's the the vertical is
like this horizontal is like this in my
opinion like if you're laying down or
staying no standing up verticals up
straight jump whatever you want to say
horizontal Horizons where your goal is
I'm good with yeah what was yours going
to the doctor because you like need
stitches like an emergency room visit
seven seven would be accurate for me
okay I think you win that
what was yours yours was crazy funerals
oh no great ones I think that's number
one really yes seven funerals was pretty
accurate all right I thought so I can oh
my ear is a really good spot right there
what now we're gonna like reverse it
let's go
um topic is amount of Pepsi's Chris has
drank
lifetime lifetime
growing up at like Uncle uncle's houses
and like parties at dabble I think I
give myself a solid 100 by 10. okay hold
on no I'm thinking bye bye by 15 years
old which is like around before you
started working at Star Market by 15. I
think huh 14. yeah we're about 14. at 14
years old like
twelve thousand twelve K yeah that's
what four one two comma zero zero zero
yeah one yeah one comma two zero zero
that is 12. twelve hundred so I was
thinking twelve thousand exactly no no
twelve no twelve hundred sorry okay so
we'll go 1200 by the time you're 14. so
wait we need to all take a guess okay
if you're 19 it got bad how many do I
think you're having a day about like
three let's think about it the case is
twelve five years I can crank out two
cases in a week that's 24 a week equals
24 weeks that's like Dude That's like
five years I don't even wanna know this
I don't wanna know this it's about five
years oh my time's about three Pepsi's a
day no times about that's kind of uh
wait up hold on I'm so confused I'm on I
think he's at like Chris is at like 42
000. Matt what are you saying 42
000 yep do you know how many that is yes
I'd say 7
six thousand
lifetime that's insane I should have
counted we're gonna pick next one how
many times do you think you've opened
and closed the door
oh my god well let's think about it a
lot of no we need to say a number okay
is the door hell for you though
sometimes nope you opened and shot no
automatic doors no
you committed the action 200
what last week
light walls
two because lifetime you only open you
just opened it closed my bedroom door
about 12. oh my God car doors count
adore Chris oh my God wait why'd I say
200.
I'd say like 20K I say I think we're
like a five a day minimum
I agree [ __ ] five a day minimum I close
it but you're not really opening think
about how many times listen think about
how many times you go to the bathroom oh
that's five alone oh my God
12 million okay no I'm at like 50k let's
pick some ones that I have my camera
roll and then we're gonna just pick
numbers no reasoning no math okay all
right
how many times have you read books
zero no wait we should play over under
I'm under 30. I'm under 30. um cover to
cover I'm under five cover to cover them
I'm like two she just starts saying a
topic and then one two three number and
then that way we can see how far apart
we are and then discuss and argue yes
okay okay yeah so next
how many times have you fallen down
three
two one 125.
what 150 100 25 Nick Nick
I've never fallen in my life you you
fell the other night okay I like
okay like that's insane why I don't fall
down ever there's there'll be times
where I'm like oh I'll stumble I'll
catch myself I'm never hitting the
ground I think some of the most childish
[ __ ] on the faces are just falling on
like ice it's like come on like when the
winter when like the ice is out it's
like let's just be a little bit more
cautious I've never slipped okay I may
fall but I've never slipped on ice in my
life you're you're most likely to slip
on ice out of us I've never slipped on
ice in my life and I was literally bet
every dollar in my bank account that
I've never slipped you're the type of
guy to slip on Ice Matt is that all your
pretty Pennies on I'll bet every single
one of my pretty pennies and everything
one of my shiny [ __ ] nickels too I
have never fallen on ice and I can
guarantee it falling on ices were
literally like the week with no balance
that's your mother you're talking about
oh I'm actually weak with no balance no
you're very good about it Nick you have
fallen and Mom Falls alone
so where she's going respectfully
my mom falls on ice because she like
tries to bring all the groceries up at
once so why isn't her son taking care of
it because she doesn't tell she's like
oh I just got home with the groceries
I'm on my way down the stairs you're
trying to bring him to the front me and
Chris are such groceries and you are not
me and Chris always did that whatever
because you guys are like Mom would be
like Oh I'm here you guys would run like
I'm going my arms would look like a
purple hose afterwards like it'd
literally be like the wrinkles
laughed at a child falling in public oh
my God one I have a suit oh three five
six five it was great I was gonna say
like 200 five but I really wanted 200.
well every time I'm talking to think how
many times have I seen like so okay
here's the problem you said that you hit
on 25 times in your life but you've
laughed at kids falling 200 times
correct there's no way I see little kids
full constantly I think it's the
funniest thing they have little buoyant
bodies like and they don't actually get
hurt like you know little kids are like
made a [ __ ] phone I think it's so
funny
little kids it's just unreal how little
kids if you feel after like a tumble or
something is solely off of other
people's reactions yeah like if you go
oh
out of their head and they will fully
just come yeah like if a baby gets you
can punch me like oh you're good look
man
especially when
like they're still okay you got everyone
around it's like
the baby's like
every single person looked at the baby
you have to assume the baby's A-Okay
yeah
fake it till you make it situation yeah
for sure because then the kid thinks
it's like way more serious that's what
me and Matt used to do with you
oh he's hiding he's a guy with a dog
exactly what's he gonna do fall I just
don't like men
is he gone no
lock the door lock the door
Hey sir where is he he's over there
how many times have you burped on your
YouTube channel three
um two one oh my God this one they can
figure it out
60 50.
no me pop is different me pop is
ridiculous you coffee I've had a
permacop since I had covered burping on
camera probably 20 on on YouTube videos
there's one
oh here's automatic my [ __ ] was Bob yeah
I can control it I can't control it
smells
um um is that including
I was just thinking how many days have I
lived because that not a lot you could
you could find that out actually because
that's a huge factor in this game
because we dude if you think about it
saying like you farted ten thousand
houses I don't even think I've been on
these ago
plan it for ten thousand days when you
were four are you stupid I'm completely
correct Google it Nick you're so right
Dude where's my phone anyway I don't
know on forever why are you filming
we've only been alive for seven thousand
one hundred and oh my God so young
you're 30 000 Pepsis are you for real
7167 hats probably like shave off like 2
000 of that Pepsi why Pepsi
oh well you thought I wanted to just
shave two thousand yeah okay can we like
get another question where's my phone
that is not that many this is the
question you need to answer to where's
your phone
that's crazy okay what are you taking
photos back there for I'm not ow get up
don't [ __ ] violate me how many times
have Nick overreacted in his life one
million okay all right let's talk my
reactions I've ever been valid no it's
not correct your your actions speak
louder than words you want to talk about
how dramatic Nick is no we're not gonna
do that we're gonna move forward okay
yeah I don't know why we would digress
from progress in this video
that was such a good word bro how much
money to eat a whole bin of potato salad
yourself
list of top 10 fears literally you could
put it on Fear Factor in that like I
could be on the season finale of [ __ ]
Fear Factor already suffered through a
pile of grasshoppers 10 stinging
scorpions a bat last thing eat a bucket
of potato salad count me the [ __ ] out
I'm done I'm tapping out put me with
like a hundred African bullfrogs
poisonous spiders and I'd be like okay
this is good like a little [ __ ] oh my
God over the rainbow
salad it actually
oh my God that's so terrifying
bro I literally rather
you couldn't jump scare me better you
could jump scare me better like a
[ __ ] horror movie like imagine they
put like a sharp to it you could either
be the babadook or the potato salad I
wouldn't winch at all potato salad I'm
running oh my God it's like a chunky
coleslaw oh potato salad is a salad dish
made from boiled potatoes
okay hold on hold on hold on you ready
imagine this right a bucket of mayo or a
bucket a coleslaw or a bucket of
potatoes no listen listen Nick ready I'm
gonna put you in a scenario and I want
to see how you react here okay you you
find a man you fall in love with them
right you want to get married and he's
like all right before we get married you
need to come to my house and meet my
parents for dinner right you go over his
house
you're all you're all sitting there it's
nice you met his parents they love you
already they they can I guess where this
is gonna go yep they have a world famous
potato salad that's the mom's Famous
Recipe she loves cooking it for all the
guests and he didn't tell you this can
you get this reaction you get there
the mom
the boyfriend you the dad
the brother comes in
potato salad I feel like I'm watching a
movie
what's your reaction oh that's awesome
you guys all like potato salad
yes
it's a crowd yeah he's talking about his
favorite like oh she like it's her thing
I'm like oh that's wonderful
you want some no no you sure
it's like it's the best no I promise the
best meal no I promise no babe you have
to try Mama salad
wow well at that point I'd become
ruthless because I'd want to break up
right after that experience yeah now I'm
good [ __ ] the potato salad [ __ ] your
dumb mom and I'd walk out
you always ever talk to you like that
yeah no look mama salad yeah
but regardless please try the salad oh
please try this out I'm like oh no I'm
like severely like deathly allergic
no you aren't I know oh absolutely what
okay different scenario they bring out
mashed potatoes first you just ate so
many mashed potatoes okay oh my God
those mashed potatoes were soaked all
right next thing next segment yeah I'm
finding a way out of this no matter what
do you guys think you could win a
reality TV show
depends the reality TV show okay well I
don't care I don't want to talk there's
it's so no I really like I was just
hoping like yeah I think I could win
this like the depends yeah I think I
could win something I don't want to lead
the sure yeah I do okay that's good how
boring was that well no it was just like
I was hoping you had an idea for
yourself
I know I was hoping for you to say like
yeah I could win like Survivor or
something and like you would just do it
on your own but you were like yeah it
depends I'm like
I didn't think that far into it so I was
like oh no I can win Big Brother bro how
many days could you go in a row strictly
off rice like if you rice yeah if you
were on Survivor oh my God right only
for the rest of my life if there's
enough rice rest of my life right no
who's making sure everyone has different
license plates
the people who administer that I
wouldn't give out the same
um
we're not I'm done what do you mean
you're done we're done we're done I'm
done we're done I'm done what's the
difference with LED and fluorescent bro
I can't get into this I don't know you
do know
oh you know the difference between like
RGB how are you gonna tell me no because
you're always like a tech nerd with the
RGB lights and that's that's literally
you so I don't know what you're saying
Chris literally always asks questions
like the oh my God shut up I just
literally asked questions but the only
way you could answer them is if you
worked at the place or like worked for
the company of like people not true yes
it is true you're always like oh who at
Apple and it's like bro why the [ __ ] are
you asking me and Matt
to say
life goes by
all right we're done we said we're
we're done that was this Friday's video
Yeah Nick's like oh we're done is that
my quarter what it's St Patrick's Day
maybe that was like good luck did my
quarter fall today St Patrick's Day
tomorrow or something next week I don't
know you're just saying it because we're
in March I don't work here bro it's soon
insane yeah
[Applause]
yeah
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things