actually the advice I would give to
people trying to create their own
company really work in the field a
little bit like work in the field you
think you have an idea for some new
service or product work in that field
and get insight that's something I got
out of my Stanford experience you maybe
you have an idea of what's really
valuable and useful as a product but the
best approach to creating value is first
that you get insight into what the
problem is my name's Chris qualty I'm
the CEO and co-founder of Mitra we're a
2-year-old company based out of South
San Francisco a little bit about my
background before starting Mitra I was
at Tesla for 7 and A2 years before Tesla
I had various positions in renewable
energy and Consulting I was electrical
engineer undergrad but at Tesla I joined
to lead product and hardware for the
supercharger team and I launched various
products like paid supercharging and my
name is Ahmed Bal I am the CTO and
co-founder and Mitra Mitra is building
robots for warehouse material flow of
trying to solve a fundamental problem
with theerror flow in in warehousing
Logistics and Manufacturing as
well so I joined Tesla in 2014 I think
this is after the dual motor b s was
launched or was announced you know
there's a lot of skepticism are electric
vehicles going to be successful is fully
battery electric vehicle or plug in
hybrid you know Tesla versus Fisker a
lot of uncertainty in the market then
but you know I joined Tesla to to solve
a very clear problem I was working on
more traditional wield Automation and of
course a lot of the fixed infrastructure
projects that we had a tuss it
beforehand and then you know this
challenge of let's build a humanoid
robot was was given to our team because
we had an integrated robotics team but
the challenges of a humanoid are are
very different than building a wheeled
robot on the floor legged Locomotion
grasping and manipulation the kinds of
of of decisions that this robot has to
process a perception systems are are
wildly different and so first Tesla had
precisely zero expertise of humanoid
robotics at the time so I had to go and
figure out who the experts were meet
with them try to establish a recruiting
pipeline try to find the internal
experts within Tesla who were willing
and able and also had the foundational
skill sets to be able to solve this
problem I had to get myself a two month
crash course in human orotic so that was
really an interesting time but you know
I think one of the things that Tesla
teaches you to be very resourceful that
wasn't the first time I've been asked to
solve the problem which I had no really
like deep or meaningful background in
but you structure the problem you go
find the information you need hop on a
plane to meet with the experts as you
need you do what it takes to to figure
it out you know neon laid a mandate out
that we needed to get a some robot
walking in three months it's so between
internal experts talking with some some
folks out outside the company with to to
get accomplish that goal I think as a
whole though all robots are not created
equal all robot challenges are not equal
anytime you're talking about Led
Locomotion or just Advanced grasping the
perception that the type of data and the
consistency of data the frequency of the
refresh rates like I'm not just looking
at a hand like I need to understand like
the forces and yeah there's there's
literally infinite ways I could grab
something the difficulty of of repeating
that and making that some sort of
industrial process is many orders of
magnitude more difficult than just
driving a bot around the floor of a
factory and you know if we think about
how difficult it has been to do full
self-driving cars or autonomous vehicles
you know you could argue that that
problem is not a solved problem yet
because we don't have ubiquitous cars no
driving highways and and surface streets
yet right you do have companies that are
driving like you can walk outside of
this building you will see a car
unmanned car drive by this this facility
probably in 30 minutes but it's not
ubiquitous right hasn't been adopted
building a humanoid to operate at full
scale in Factory or a home at the
comparable productivity of a human is a
very very challenging problem to solve
I'm confident it will be solved I think
the timing is everything right is this a
one-year problem is this a 5year is this
a 10e is this a 30-year problem unclear
so after spending a year there it was
it's a fascinating problem where again
was able to work with some of the best
and brightest at Tesla and and Beyond
Tesla was fortunate to be able to to
hire some wonderful people to work on
these huge challenges but ultimately I
join Tesla to ship you know millions of
products to the public to make real
impacts and I felt that most of the
impact by the humanoid is dependent on
solving effectively some research
problems with what we're doing at Mitra
this is not in the research domain this
is a very like we're solving tangible
problems with technology that doesn't
require moonshot levels of of innovation
to have meaningful impact on the economy
after Tesla I I tried to just focus a
little bit away from manufacturer let me
think a little bit you know do something
else derivatives trading and try to
learn more about Ai and financial
systems but the bug of manufacturing
working on Hardware gotten me again and
the things I did at Tesla were very
applicable to rev and I thought I really
wanted to help one more us auto
manufacturer get off the brown I was
really excited about rivan trying to
help them out so I went and you know
spent time at rivian helping them scale
their manufacturing assistance as well
that's the journey after that I was at a
beach in Hawaii I still have the video
while I'm recording the beach and I was
going like wonderful this is great I'm
done I don't want to do anything else
I've solved every problem I want to
solve as I'm recording the video I get a
call from walty and he's asking me about
hey do you remember the problems we went
into Tesla during manufacturing let's
really solve it at the beginning I was
like I don't want to do this I don't
want to do manufacturing again I want to
be stay at the beach but the more we
talked about how we would solve the spot
go back to the fundamentals let's not
just build another automation company
let's do something completely different
the more we talked about it the more I
got excited because it's it wasn't just
another implementation it's a complete
rethink and that was very excited so I
said okay yes let's start this company
let's find the best people that we can
find from our Network and pack a this
B with the global Venture Capital volume
decreasing dramatically startup must
find a better way to stay informed of
investment sentiment to survive hi I'm
Si from you and we know that many of you
watching are startup Founders that's why
we have something to share with you guys
that's going to be helpful for you the
startup Capital annual report from
HubSpot for startups is their newest
report on where startup capitals are
flowing the metrics investors care about
the most when deciding on investing in a
startup and the best tech Stacks to help
you manage investor relations in
addition to the detailed surveys of 500
Founders I found an in-depth interview
with seasoned investors from sequia
Capital HS with venters and more to be
especially interesting and packed with
insights the report is free to download
through the link in description
be sure to check it out and take your
startup to the next round and thanks to
hpot for sponsoring the
video so Mitra was founded because am on
and I having seen a lot of these
different types of challenges at Tesla
and rivan wanted to find a problem that
we could solve we uniquely positioned
knowledgeable to tackle but also was
just simply not being solved right you
think of the lowest hanging fruit in
your tree and again material flow is
most of the work across industry just
moving things around yet it's clearly
unsolved I can go out and buy an
industrial automation system to do
almost anything I need the problem is is
it cost effective is it simple is it
extensible is it flexible and we said if
we can design something that's just far
simpler iPhone's a great example Tesla
there's lots of great examples of
History where to follow a new scurve
scurve of adoption right a new tech
technology it starts off slowly it then
you know there's some acceleration then
it kind of tapers off but to truly
continue like linear adoption and
Improvement of Technologies it's
comprised of a whole bunch of small
s-curves right we needed to create that
new s-curve for industrial aeration
there needed to be a new paradigm and to
do that again when you look across
history It's usually the simpler thing
Waits how do we find the absolute
simplest way to do this work and what we
realized was that that no there is no
system that was designed that was
physically or kinematically
unconstrained meaning I want to move
things in 3D how do I move it up down
left right from any cell to any cell in
full 3d that was just an unsolved
problem at any payload weate so we
simulated said this is a solvable
problem and if we can do this we've
created a system that is of immense
value to the industry so that's uh
that's why we decided to tackle this
problem fundamentally the material
movement for warehouses and
Manufacturing happens on pallets pallets
in my view are the uh red blood cell of
the global GDP everything that you see
around you has been on a pallet you know
the cameras are clothes or pieces of
furniture all of that has been on a pal
yet the pallet movement technology has
been the same for the past 100 years
it's a pallet it's generally the same
size it moves uh it's made out of wood
and it's moved with for CLI
operated by humans it's the same thing
and so there hasn't been an optimization
on that for quite some time and in our
experience when I worked with with wki
we saw that the biggest problem
hindering the manufacturing process was
just trying to move material from one
product with Factory to the other and we
were thinking well let's improve that
how can we build something that is super
simple if you were to look at the need
the basic need of moving a pallet or
looking at 3,000 lb you're trying to
move it from one location to the other
for you to do that today you have to get
a forklift a forklift has to be at least
3,000 lb just to balance out cuz it's a
forklift heiring something in front of
it it has to be at least another 3,000
lb so you're moving 3,000 to 9,000 lb
the forklift itself and then 3,000 lb
that you want to move it just makes no
sense we're we're moving 9,000 to move
another 3,000 and we thought about it
and we said okay this is such a
unoptimized system it's nobody's
touching it and it's kind of a given
people that go into warehousing and
Logistics called manufacturing and you
see this it's uh they kind of look at it
and they go okay this is our lot in life
this is how things are while we saw that
was like no something has to improve so
we're looking at you know designing a a
new primitive something completely new
let's rethink the problem our Bots are 7
pounds they can move 3,000 but they're
700 lb so that's it and it doesn't take
a larger footprint than the pup itself
now when you start from there I can n
3,000 lb forward backward left and right
up and down in full 3d with 700 lb robot
that is a different math compeat and
that's the approach that we're taking
with Nitra now if you limit the
variability of movement to the three uh
Dimensions now I can start to solve
things with software the boss can only
do the three movements and they can uh
access any part of the warehouse uh
within a structure now I can start to do
things with software if I want to build
a
conveyor I don't have to build a
physical conveyor I can tell the Bots
move in the direction of a conveyor or
lift and so it makes your Warehouse
completely software addressable which is
a completely new approach to doing any
of this and it applies to warehousing
Logistics manufacturing anything that
moves your standard pallet and that's
why we wanted to focus on the pallet
because that's 90% of material movement
around the
war kind of my take on Founder mode is
is effectively as companies get larger
the gist is do you still kind of
maintain your level of awareness and
involvement in the details of your
company right very large company mode or
manager mode it's like I fully rely on
my team to do almost everything and I I
have this little function maybe I'm just
attending dinners and selling customers
at a very high level I think you know at
a company like Mitra you know even
though we're 74 people Aman and I have
no choice but to be in founder mode
there's just too much going on there's
too many aspects of the system you know
every time a customer walks in we have
one this afternoon and between the two
of us we need to be fully versed in the
technical stack we need to be able to
answer questions of like why did you
make this decision for this actuator or
this design what other reliability
issues how do you plan to lower the cost
like things like that if you can't talk
intelligently about that you're not
going to drive confidence in these very
sophisticated potential buyers of
Parkers so for us like there's no choice
but to be found or M but you know as I
think about what I love about this job
you know I love being in designer riew
so I love the product and the
engineering aspects and I know I'm onos
too and that's that's something that you
know as you get older as you get company
gets more mature and larger there's
natural pressure to say like you need to
de from that you need to let your team
do that and I think there's there's a
balance that can be achieved where
Founders are still in the
details not making all the decisions but
in the details enough to be aware I mean
Tesla's a I don't know if it's a good
example it's an example of where you
know Elon had you know when he met with
Tesla for his one or two days a week it
was like 12 meetings in a day and like
every hour some different technical team
would come in and like walk through
here's what's going on here's the
challenges what should we do boss right
and he would be making calls on like how
electronic sourcing and then we'd be
making calls on like wind tunnel design
optimization they'd be making calls on
on a whole bunch of different aspects of
the business not suggesting that's what
every company should do and that is not
what we're going to be doing but I think
it does show you that it's not like one
or the other you can exist as a large
company in founder mode you can exist in
manager mode for us you know we're much
more towards fure mode and probably will
stay that way for as long as we to
really understand the technical details
which as far as I'm concerned doesn't
end actually the advice I would give to
people trying to create their own
company really work in the field a
little bit right work in the field you
think you have an idea for some new
service or product work in that field
and get insight that's something I got
out of my Stanford experience you maybe
you have an idea of what's really
valuable and useful as a product but the
best approach to creating value is first
that you get insight into what the
problem is the reason walty and I
started working together is we met at
the uh the model 3 production ramp and
we were customers of the systems that
were there manufacturing and Logistics
and material flow systems that were on
the system that were in production we
met there and we experienced Insight we
saw what the problem really is people go
hey add more automation add more
technology here fine okay but the
Insight that we got that the fundamental
problem that needed to be solved is
moving the material without you
experiencing it for firsthand you miss
it you think oh I'm going to work on
Warehouse robotics you're going to build
this nice you know articulated arm it's
going to look nice and neat and great
are you really really solving it no and
the reason you're not solving it is
because you lack the insight into what
the fundamental problem is for us it was
oh the thing that would unlock
manufacturing is to move the material
efficiently without stopping in a very
reliable Safe Way You Move it in that
way figure out a way to do it and it
would unlock value for you in
manufacturing without that Insight I
think you're you would be on a long path
so my advice would be get immersed in
the problem Firs head and then try to
come up with a solution I'll give you
another very practical example today
everybody in the company today everyone
almost no exception has to work in the
warehouse using our system interacting
with the warehouse operators at our
customer site everyone even web
developers uh marketing everybody has to
do it and the reason we did that is from
my experience when I was at Tesla and
building the software that I told you
about it the software for the uh the
g410 the way I built the software is I
went to the line and I started working
on the cars I started you know putting
volts head and talking Fasteners and the
hood on the model 3 and I experienced
what the operator was experienc what
kind of software was needed what did I
need to finish my job pop and then I
built that software and that software
infected everywhere that gule that is
the Insight that you need to get before
you can say oh I'm going to build a new
manufacturing software first work as a
user of that supposed system or product
that you're trying to create get deep
Insight so you fundamentally understand
what is the thing that you're trying to
create what is the value that you're
trying to create and then go okay I have
enough Insight that I know so much about
this I understand it at a basic
fundamental level now you can come up
with the new value creation after that I
think that's the best advice I could
give before somebody says I want to go
and build Hardware there are many little
tiny startups that have YouTube videos
or videos that that have amazing
wonderful devices and you go but what is
it solving is it practical are you
solving a problem it's because they did
the shortcut they said I'm going to
build something that looks cooler great
go build it but you're not really
solving the thing you need to go and
immerse yourself get insight and that's
why we have everybody here at the
company work at the warehouse with our
customers and so when they come and
build a solution they build it as a
warehouse operator they go oh I'm a
warehouse operator who happens to know
how to build applications how to build
robotics you know here's how I would
build it for me that's the best way to
build
products I mean if you look across the
tech Spectrum most companies and you
know Andre's famous quote heart software
will basically eat the world is very
true I think you know when you look at
the economy you realize that 85% of the
economy or GDP is driven by physical
Industries physical problems 90% of the
value in the tech economy has been
created by mostos software there's a
huge discrepancy so when we look at the
problems yet to be solved that haven't
really been touched by software they all
involve some sort of actuation or
manipulation of the physical world iot
Internet of Things has been around for
few decades and that starts to solve
some of the problems around Hardware it
gives you signal back from the physical
environment into some sort of brain or
software but ultimately the actuation of
that requires people or something else
but when you think of Robotics as
applied to the physical world that
closes the loop like I can build an
actuator a thing to move a physical item
up down left right that's hardware and
the combination of that actuation Clos
in the loop along with the software
capabilities that can be applied to it
there's a ton of potential there right
this is the next Frontier the next
several decades you know you look around
you and you see look at all the
inefficiencies in the world you look at
how the trash is picked up you look at
how houses and buildings are constructed
you look at how telephone cable is laid
you look at how physical Goods must be
you know manufactured and there's a lot
of opportunity for for software applied
to the physical world and that's why all
of of us here at mitro we're super
passionate about software fly to the
physical world and that comes in the
form of Robotics and that is a that is a
hardware hardware company the second
reason why Hardware is is perhaps more
exciting today than it might have been a
few decades ago you know when you think
of Hardware you think of silicon like
making silicon ships that was really you
know most of the hardware opportunity
but companies like Tesla and SpaceX have
come along and they said look these are
Legacy Industries the script has been WR
for how to build Automotive vehicles and
what margins for for decades and Tesla's
coming and saying we're going to do it
differently everyone told you know Elon
and Company they're crazy for doing this
there's very low probability for Success
there's lots and lots of ways that this
go poorly for them but built an
architecture that's significantly
simpler 10x simpler or more than the
existing products right there's bar your
parts and shown that you can disrupt
some of these industries it's hard
Hardware's hard but if done successfully
and done correctly there's huge
opportunity to make meaningful advances
in building you know electric
vehicles is for some people it's much
more rewarding than you know optimizing
some age on a on a website or or
increasing ad spend by 5% or something
like that so there's been a bit of a
blueprint in a Playbook that says you
can disrupt very large Industries
through Hardware uh through some of the
more modern successes like you know
Tesla WD rivan SpaceX andal couple balls
like that