because
to you oh I thought he said something in
a foreign language
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
[Music]
I think a good warm-up to our video so
that we laugh and keep the spunk is
everyone has to say a joke and we have
to like fake laugh yes I'm not famous
yeah I'm not doing that if the joke's
funny I'll laugh okay why does Frosty
the Snowman
not have a nose
the reindeer ate it off
he ain't [ __ ] with the haters
low-key I agree with them I feel bad
like you don't even [ __ ] with people you
had me at the hook like a lot of people
like they put on cologne perfume they
want people to smell them Frosty even
want to smell you bro I love that all
right moving on we're gonna basically
talk about specific ways that we think
would make someone go crazy or like how
to Gaslight someone I don't know why
this is kind of like a video topic we
have but I think it's
have like like they like carve into the
cement wall how many days in they're
gonna they're like they're into their
sentence they are and they like carve
into the wall I'm gonna start doing that
on my wall when I wake up in the morning
like every day just like I wake up draw
a tally that's kind of terrible I was
just Cherry that's not a league for you
y'all bought it yeah no normally I love
Pepsi Cherry can you [ __ ] all right
yeah I'm going to my [ __ ] thing okay
do you guys let me hear online yes yeah
okay I would hide a paper clip and like
say it's the Nick in your room every
single day until you find at least one
and then you just like they just keep
popping up out of nowhere
like a paperclip like under your like
you're like playing I don't like this
one why I don't think it'd make me go
that crazy because I have so much in my
room that I genuinely would just be like
oh when did I put these here no like
wanted like each pocket of your clothes
one in like like under your candle I
wanna know everything you touched like
it's funny or your phone I think if you
did this to me I'd find the first
[ __ ] what is it per clip I was like
toothpick I would find the first paper
that would be good I find the first
paper clip within 24 hours that's not
true I can almost get we're doing I will
literally make a video I will at a
random day this month start doing it to
my room no a random day this month I'll
hide a paper clip somewhere in your room
and I promise you you won't find it
within 24 hours okay how much money put
money on it no put your money where your
mouth is oh my God
however oh yeah we can what's your bet
the yesterday we made it in the hot tubs
however many toothpicks you can hide in
my room every 24 hours until I find one
I'm catching you off guard I'll give you
just tell me when you start June so it
will be in June okay listen
made a bet yesterday and I think that
it's [ __ ] hilarious so we're gonna
share with you guys basically I what was
the context
I went under water in the hot tub and I
scared Matt because I was under for like
45 seconds I don't know what came over
me but I felt so much peace no you said
that you saw a tick tock on some guy
that is true he does underwater
underwater meditation and he trains
himself every day to to feel more and
more
like do you mind he trains every single
day to feel like I want to get more
light in here like I want to feel the
light it's bright no he trains every day
to like try and stay underwater longer
and now like he's been training for like
a month
seven minutes so Nick's convinced that
if he goes to the pool every single
night then he can keep his head under
the water and train himself to get to
the point where it's like he can be
underwater for like a very long help so
me and Matt have a bet that the day
summer starts like the day that sounds
like summer switches to Autumn whatever
when summer switches to fall so by the
Fall I have to to gain the ability to
train to stay underwater for three
minutes at a time and basically I owe
Matt 600 and that's like a crazy amount
of money I know like if this is the most
comfortable bet someone could ever know
I'm a hundred percent I'm like
going to train and do and you guys don't
even know there's like rules and
guidelines to this [ __ ] like Nick
literally has it set up so that if like
someone jumps in the pool he gets like a
reset date like they ain't fully run in
them
I said I'd I'd befriend someone who uses
a white noise machine and then buy the
exact same white noise machine but
replace it with an audio file that's
slightly different from the one that's
in there so it'd be almost exactly the
same but it would occasionally throw
something in that he didn't know was
there she didn't know was there it's
like throw them off like in their sleep
yeah
this seems premeditated
Nick had this no because I sleep with a
fan noise that I pull up on YouTube and
if I played like the rock have you seen
the guy like an ad popped up I'd wake up
afraid so I thought when we thought of
the video idea I'd take someone's like
white noise machine by the exact same
one and then replace the audio you want
to know what's actually insane what you
have hooked me to use fan noises because
I never needed anything I never did it
but Nick and Nathan both of them need
fancy sleep so every time I would sleep
but then they got me used to it but
there's this YouTube video
[Laughter]
what I don't know I thought of a joke
but it was like every six hours it just
cuts the fan and I think that my body is
auto waking up the second it ends
because like oh it's good I'll wake up
every night when the fan is over bye
every morning and it like never stops
right but like I genuinely think I'm
waking up the second it ends do you know
a little water drop thing that you put
in the water and you squeeze the end
that goes up the tube like the
penicillin thing like the old yes yes
I would take it by that and fill it with
water and then go to someone's sock
drawer and dampen every song just a
little bit like like just like two drops
so that they can feel it enough when
they put the sock on but it's just like
in one spot there's a list it would dry
by the time I put this on I agree
no like every like I know like say
you're you put socks aside to wear those
and you like walk away real quick like
to brush your teeth and get them a
little damp every time like just plan
ahead like this is like too strategic I
think dude can we just go with the video
like okay that's fine no it's good cool
okay all right the only reason I
wouldn't like that is because like I
only put socks on to like start my day
right after I shower so my feet are
already like kind of like that level of
dance yeah like I wouldn't notice okay
sorry it was a terrible idea no no no no
no no no no no don't beat yourself up
about it it just wouldn't work I put a
speaker in the corner of someone's
living room and then just play like
whistling sounds like everything
wind blowing you know what I mean
oh you got something sticking up in like
your hair or like oh you got something
in your teeth to someone who doesn't and
then just keep saying like oh you almost
got it like keep going like this for
like 20 minutes or like going like this
for like 20 minutes and there's nothing
ever there that's a good thing it's
about time they go to the bathroom to
like fix it themselves because they're
like exhaustive just trying to figure it
out if they go to check and it's gone
it's just like oh you just fixed it like
you can say you just got it yeah yeah
but it's like let them like really all
right hold on that's actually a good one
hey seriously I want to read I only have
so many I'm so hot dude okay what would
y'all do right y'all know where we live
obviously familiar back back home our
house okay right imagine you put now you
confuse me where are we back home like
Massachusetts yeah
imagine I'm driving home to our house
and then I pull into the driveway that's
one before our normal house like the one
before our drive that's so and then I
just go oh sorry I forgot and then I
pull out and then drive into the other
one dude I like actually really check in
on you right because I've been driving
to that other one for how many I
actually have a really similar one
thousands would it be I think I'd
immediately start panicking because if
you think about it think about this
think about this you're like never in
someone's driveway unless you're like
their friend like a driveway is kind of
like an intimate place to be
if you accidentally driving to someone's
driving
are you ever driving down straight years
like go the other way it's like pulling
someone's driveway for a second yeah I
feel like I'm trespassing I'm doing too
much I feel like I'm in this person's
way link driveways are kind of intimate
that's really weird sure that's not
weird
like no but it's not like I'm being
rushed or anything like I'm the only car
in the road and I just pull into that
one oh my bad I forgot no it'd be really
weird what do you no um a driveways for
cars only like listen imagine someone's
just standing in your driveway like nah
you get home and they're just landing
something crazy and they're just
standing okay hold on let me read
another one myself that's actually
terrifying okay I get it if someone
pulls a car in but if someone was just
standing at my driveway I'd [ __ ]
freak the [ __ ] out
imagine imagine you had like a clock
Chris imagine you had like a clock in
your room like an alarm clock or a
digital clock anything and I changed it
three minutes every three days oh my
like it went three minutes I forgot to
throw the clock out before I would catch
on way too quick I don't think you
before you beat like 10 minutes I'd
throw the clock the second I set the
alarm and I was waking up at like a
different time I'd be like what dude
like if I didn't say like alarm I said
clock yeah but if he used that he
changed it by three minutes it was like
you said it was like an alarm clock so
if I had an alarm clock and it said like
9 30 and I went in the shower came back
at nine like at 10 and it didn't say 10
I'd be like oh it's off by a couple of
minutes okay whatever this is a bad one
I guess whatever I don't even know I
don't know
until you explained yourself I would
know right away the second my alarm
clock has changed three minutes okay
okay that's a little insane I would go
on my phone and be like oh it's wrong
literally like this year during like the
daylight savings things you didn't
realize that it happened and when it
said from like 2 A.M to like 3 A.M well
that's a lot more reasonable because
it's one hour and it's Universal for
everybody's clock not just mine
everyone's clock went forward an hour
not just mine yeah but if you can't even
realize that everyone's clock's going
forward all right way different story I
disagree that you're wrong
we don't have to argue about it anymore
because I know my stance and you know
yours let the people speak
like you're saying yeah
voice your opinion shut the [ __ ] up
idiot let me talk let me go listen if
just my alarm is changing by three
minutes and everyone else's is the same
I'll probably notice that mine won't
change by three minutes but if every
[ __ ] clock worldwide changes by an
hour then everyone would be on the same
page they'd be like oh it all changed an
hour and even if I'm not you're I'm
saying I'm denying you even realize that
it doesn't matter if I realized it
because it doesn't matter okay are you
dumb or stupid let us know like legit
it's almost crazy
[ __ ] you Matt okay I was doing your
laundry and I cut tiny little holes in
your shirts I know right away again too
but like every microscopicles and
where's the location I don't know
Microsoft no like a pin un pinhole that
would freak me the [ __ ] out like little
microscopic but where would they be I
just do one every single time oh my God
somewhere
you would need to be a legit
Mastermind to pull this one off okay
okay but it's like replace so set
let's get there
start with like a weird item of clothing
like underwear or socks I'm hooked right
and then start just making them small
just making them making making them
shut the [ __ ] up
smaller every time they wear it so like
they wear socks and like when you put
them in the laundry like say like you're
in the perfect world today
like no don't even shrink them a little
fully replace them with like a size down
it's like if the underwear is like an
extra large buy them large and then just
replace it oh here you go and like but
scrape off the L so they can't tell and
then they'd wear it again oh it was a
little tighter that time to replace it
with a medium and then but it's they're
gonna get to like all their clothes it's
just like get Dumbo this actually works
better every time they wear it like that
would freaking get the [ __ ] out better
this works better if that person's owner
does the laundry because then they can't
blame it on like oh I'm like if my
clothes were like rapidly like lowering
in size like all of them like every time
I wore it it was just coming I'd like it
so mad at who's doing my laundry when
you meet someone for the first time
saying like oh you know who you look
like but never remember whose name
you're oh my God what do you look like
that actor like oh like that person and
that's like that conversation like oh
I'll get back to you when I think about
it and then you know I [ __ ] hate
people that like I don't want to even
know who I look like I feel like that's
such a anyways regardless another one
another one
direct directly attacked another one I
have is every single time someone every
single time someone you're with suggests
these are all more entertaining than
yours have been yours have been [ __ ]
stupid every single time someone
suggests a restaurant say ooh of course
that's my favorite place no matter what
the restaurant is so if this person like
suggestions
oh I love that place yeah
like every single time drive me crazy I
just take the first it's very powerful
you literally said that like this was
your favorite place the other day yeah
but it's funny because it's just like if
you never
ever or just
would say you've never been to every
place ever yes
for me that every time I eat when I'm
just like it didn't really like oh so
you need a real you need the golden
tomato he needs a memorable maybe next
time you eat a tomato [ __ ] ass
he's like crazy
you can see I don't remember the last
time I ate a tomato or if I ever did
okay bro a BLT would alter your life do
you think call them the same name call
someone the same name every time but
then correct yourself right away but
like give them the wrong name so like
say say I'm like best friend not follow
me listen okay cool I'm gonna explain it
stupid have a little bit of Hope in life
literally
[Music]
imagine if like me and you were friends
Matt but every time I saw you I was I
gave you like give me a name any name
Eduardo Eduardo I'd be like oh hey Matt
and every time like like every once in a
while like so like I'll see you in a
week and I'm like oh I'd wanna oh no
Matt but like just call you of the same
name wrong but I have no relation to it
Eduardo at all like I have no idea who
he is
that's like really crazy I feel like
it's like just like weird like keep
accidentally calling you a name that
just has nothing to do with who you are
or like who the [ __ ] Eduardo and I'm
like oh no no don't worry about it again
like I I don't know any Eduardo like I
swear to God and you're like really
nervous yeah like nervous like I don't
know it could be a good movie like you
know and they just like even like like
Mark like like like if I was if I went
up to a friend of Mark I was like oh
what's up Matt all right Mark
and just like I didn't get that whatever
[ __ ] you it's like just I said let the
magic eight ball decide what I'm gonna
do when I'm in arguments but like with
people if you can't agree like have a
magic eight ball to decide it but have
like a rigged magic eight ball for like
no matter the scenario so it always goes
to your favor
so you want to be a douchebag
no I think it'd be funny if you're
always like oh let's let the eight ball
decide but like it's never enough you're
the type of guy to like just walk around
let the eight ball decide literally so
like for anything I think it makes a lot
of sense for me okay you're crazy like
imagine how funny it would be for like
no he doesn't have that like I'm the
type to have an eight ball on me that's
like a that's like something I'd carry
around like I like you go oh it's in
your bag and I'm like Oh my camera I'll
do the eight ball on you is instantly
enough like you don't have to do like
that
like he starts the sentence and you
don't see the eight ball like imagine
he's like who's gonna pay for dinner
I used to bring a pocket watch
everywhere but I don't know where it
went there's a lot of things you could
carry with you that's weird like even
like a Capri Sun like imagine you're out
to dinner and you like pull out the
capris not that weird at all that's not
weird a fully topping hot dog relational
imagine you're in
with someone and you're just like
getting in first floor at like a random
place like an office space and there's
like
hey just take a bite of a hot dog like a
random hot dog fully like toppings and
everything I feel like food but you
didn't see it coming food and drink is
normal I feel
whatever Matthew giraffe out of there I
don't know I feel like the eight balls
no no
his best friends it's it's awesome it's
cool it'll make you a lot of friends
there's nothing like it yeah I'm talking
about the ball and they're like this
they're like oh Shaggy the coolest
mind-mending ball ever and they're just
like I imagine
[Applause]
it's literally a ball
okay
promotion I don't know what the [ __ ] it
is it's cool
[Music]
I
think
gravity ball
maybe an illusion you decide this looks
like exactly what they were promoting in
the Power Rangers all the people to turn
bad you couldn't understand even a
grocery bag and every time you help
someone carry it from the store
no no imagine you should
[ __ ]
Listen Hold On
hold up
your man was but sometimes you say one
you give us like a glimpse of what
you're about to get into say the whole
goddamn maybe that's what you really
should do take that with life okay
what are you talking about you look like
the type of guy to not even say a
sentence fully in a cart video because
you you're like
let me put a mirror right here like this
you're like a record high of 10
sentences a video so I'd zip your lips
at least mine makes I have more room
[ __ ] you you have more room for error
because you just black if I went up to
bat a thousand times I'd probably strike
out more than you if you went up to bat
a hundred times correct so if you
straighten your probability okay would
you rather
anything more
[Music]
yeah
I do often feel like can you say
something Matt and you lose me and then
you give up at least Chris tries again
exactly I don't I've got that driving me
I got that dog in me bro I'm ready
you're like oh I don't even say it okay
he's not like so where the [ __ ] are we
at with this grocery bag okay imagine us
we go grocery shopping every time and
you have that memorable item we went for
like say like shut the [ __ ] up
this is all real [ __ ] it's like I'm not
making [ __ ] up
go to the grocery store I bet you you
want you know what I mean
I think it's funny that your [ __ ]
stories always have to include like a
must-have like in order for us to make
sense
okay listen listen listen
We're not gonna go into a grocery store
unless someone wants something like so
it's like okay
okay this is a really good one really
weird though what take the exact make
and model toothbrush they have and
replace it with a lighter shade I was
gonna not a different not a difference
we're going like
right there like what's it called jungle
green okay four screen to like lighter
barely can tell but and then like keep
going and figure out like neon green but
like just demote the shade like hair but
I like it I like it I was gonna put the
sound actually I make it seem this one
dude like where you were gonna put that
down I love everybody I love Matt I love
Nick I love okay they don't care happy
Prime
happy Pride one
can you say and then what you're saying
how you miss me yeah you miss me and all
the things that we do
we travel from the island we had a lot
of plans today