There is this sort of psychological
fallacy as a founder where at one point
your logical brain needs to be switched
off because obviously you're working on
a problem that nobody else sees. I was
working on the proof of existence
protocol where we worked with an
Ethereum node and I told people that I
believe in a world where there will be
100,000 nodes that will be run by
institutions by 2020. That's what I
said. And people were laughing at me. I
knew one thing for certain that if I
hold on and deliver this, it'll be a
massive win. And when I told other
people about it, they didn't believe it
at all. They were telling me we won't do
that. And then Block Demon itself now
runs 250,000 nodes, you know, and so you
need to be stupid enough to also hold on
to an idea that most smart people around
you will tell you is a very bad idea.
I'm Constantine Richtor. I'm the founder
and CEO of Blog Demon. Blockdemon is the
leading institutional gateway for
institutions to connect to really
blockchains and the web 3 ecosystem. And
so we're one of the market leaders and
staples of the crypto industry that it
has JP Morgan, Goldman Sachs, and City
Bank as investors and customers. Out of
the top 500 companies active in crypto,
70% are customers of block demon for
infrastructure. Ultimately, what we do
is the purest form of infrastructure we
run in a decentralized network. One easy
way to think about it is that the
internet ultimately functions via
different gateways and so do
blockchains. And so one way I used to
describe blockchains to people was you
have ultimately nodes. A node are the
different members of the network that
contain a copy of the ledger. Nodes are
actually like cell towers. It's these
groupings of individual ledgers that
make a blockchain. And Block Demon
manages the individual ledgers. We
basically run these cell towers for
blockchains for institutions. We assume
that we run around 10% of the global
institutional volume of nodes around the
world. Block Demon has raised around
$430 million. The last valuation we've
had was $3.3
billion. One memory I always have is
when the wall came down in Germany. I
was a teenager at the time. I remember
the cold war ending when the world
somehow got a lot closer and also in the
context of the history of Germany from
the second world war being very aware
that it's important to have systems that
are uncorruptible in order to establish
truth. And so I remember that time as a
really important moment to think about
how do we become closer as humanity? How
do we communicate and then how do we
ensure that the forms of communications
are uncorruptible. What I found really
exciting about Bitcoin specifically was
one the immaculate conception story of
Satoshi ultimately a value system that
basically gets birthed by itself and
then the people who can control it
vanish in the background and leave it
for the community. And I like the
encryption and a little bit the sort of
hackery nature of it. I did like that it
was a currency of the underdog. Bitcoin
was started as a result to the financial
crisis in 2008. And the whole idea was
to basically take control of money away
from banks into a system that's
transparent and fair and accessible to
anyone. And um that excited me and I
felt I can actually contribute to it
because I know how to build and scale
software companies and I know how to
corral capital together to work on
succinct problems and belief is
important. I believed Bitcoin is one way
to make the world better, but you also
have to be an active part in creating
that world. I didn't just want to make
money. I also wanted to change the world
a little bit. And I understand there's
also lots of concerns and some of it
might be bad, some of it might be good,
but the system in itself I really hold
very dearly. And so I was thinking what
company in cryptocurrency can you build
that is part of it but not so
susceptible to the short-term velocity
of tokens. And so that's why we started
with
infrastructure when I was working on the
proof of existence protocol where we
worked with an Ethereum node and saw
that the physical node and
infrastructure was very unstable and
there weren't any tools available. When
I started researching that subject and
talking to my friends about it, I saw an
opportunity and I got really excited
about it. You know, it feels so great
when you see a gap in the current
product landscape. What was very
apparent was like you couldn't go
anywhere online and say, "Hey, is there
a tool that helps me to run an Ethereum
node really efficiently? Okay, if this
is hard for us people who are really
passionate about crypto and blockchain,
how are institutions and banks going to
engage in this if there's no tooling,
nothing available?" What I saw is a
world in which institutions would want
to run these Ethereum nodes. And when I
told other people about it, they didn't
believe it at all. They were telling me
we won't do that. But the more I learned
about the structure of transactions, the
cost of transactions, the more I saw the
future in which blockchains become an
integral part at this, I knew one thing
for certain that if I hold on and
deliver this, it'll be a massive win. I
believed in the vision of the company to
a point where nobody else believed it
because obviously you're working on a
problem that nobody else sees. I think
that's the resilient part is then to
continue to work on it while people are
telling you this is not a problem. Why
are you working on this? I remember
raising money in 2017 2018. I told
people that I believe in a world where
there will be 100,000 nodes that will be
run by institutions by 2020. That's what
I said. and people were laughing at me.
And then Block Demon itself now runs
250,000 nodes. Uh you need to be stupid
enough to also hold on to an idea that
most smart people around you will tell
you is a very bad idea.
Within 6 months of starting the company,
the markets of crypto fell down a cliff
which we call the crypto winter which is
like when the tokens that drive a lot of
the momentum in blockchain suddenly
devalue by like 80 90%. Everybody
stopped investing. Banks started
exploding. We had two banks at the time.
One bank went bankrupt and so a lot of
the inherent growth for the business
dried up right when I started the
company. You know, quite frankly, at
that point in time, everything was so
bad. We ran out of money a few times.
Uh, I had to subsidize payroll, for
example. The only way for Block Demon to
survive is if I put in everything I have
without a clear promise of a better
market environment, and I just have to
make it last as long as I can with as
much output as I can. And so there were
a lot of moments where it felt like wow
I don't really have a believable path
forward but still I have to convince
people that there is one. As an
entrepreneur that's your job ultimately
you have to find resources where other
people can't. You have to keep people
motivated and inspired when uh it looks
very bleak and uh you just have to keep
on leading by example.
[Music]
The first one was block demon was very
small. I think the second time around
was unique because at that point we
raised a lot of money. So we had a lot
of capital. What was difficult is that
we started 2022 by raising a lot of
money buying companies to build a sort
of really cohesive product suite that we
thought we could sell within the year to
institutions. And what happened is that
market just died. There was suddenly a
lot of pressure on ultimately scaling
down the projects we worked on that
created operational pressure on the
company to how do we rightsize the
company? How do we losing money in
developing products that currently have
no market? It was a lot harder because
we had to make the hard choice to also
let go of a lot of block demons and
people that worked with us in order to
um ultimately be operational efficient.
changing strategies and letting go of
people in order to adjust for a longer
period of time without any growth of a
more mature company. And so I'd say that
crypto winter felt harder to me because
obviously um losing people from your
team because of that is really really
hard. The way I describe it to people,
it actually just felt like another
Wednesday. You just take it on the chin
and are like, "Okay, now I need to solve
this problem." So you have to maintain
an illusion of um competence and vision
where like hey this is not a problem.
This is just a little bump on the road.
I know exactly how we're going to solve
it. It's challenging because as a
founder you know that a lot of the plans
and thoughts I had very early on are
assumptions. I don't know if they're
right or wrong but I have to pretend I
do. But you know I mean like anything
else you just try to not tell yourself
it's so bad and you just keep moving.
and we found solutions for it. You know,
um having a really strong team and
people who uh have good integrity is
really important in moments like that.
And I'm very lucky that I do have a
great team and people who stuck it out
with me
basically in a world where it's so hard
for us to develop consensus between
human beings when news and social media
and everything is so um polarized and
it's hard to know what's true and what's
not that systems that are I want to air
quote infallible and always true are
really important. When the internet was
created, people scammed people on the
internet. I never thought the internet
shouldn't exist. I thought there should
be regulation and rules and education to
protect people from scammers, but that
the benefit of the technology of open
access and trade outweighs the downside.
If done correctly, crypto is the
antithesis to scamming. It's fully
transparent. It's traceable. You can see
every wallet that's active on the
network. And so it's actually the most
scam resilient system at its core. I
think it took us 3 years before
institutions started engaging with us in
order to engage with institutions. I
think we also made the decision at the
time that the only way institutions are
going to engage with us is if they also
own part of blockdemon are part of the
governance of block demon. And so JP
Morgan and Goldman Sachs for example
have uh participate in the board of
blockdemon. So they're basically also my
bosses which means that they get to see
the inside of the company. They get to
question my choices. They're not just
outside customers. They also in are
parts of creating the company. And so I
think that gave them a lot of
confidence, right? And so that was an
important initial step for the first
customers. And the US has uh started to
look very very different than it did in
2024. We see a huge shift that's uh
materializing very quickly. The
landscape of crypto will look really
really different in the US with a lot
more enterprises and institutions
actively launching services uh for their
respective customers around crypto. Uh I
think in a complicated convoluted world
that we live in transparency and
efficiency are really really important.
They're not a luxury. They're
requirement for fair governance and
efficiency. And so I think it is indeed
a golden age for cryptocurrencies. Yes,
I've seen it from it being the underdog
to now becoming basically the not the
main dog, but the standard, right? And
so I think we're halfway there. And it's
so exciting to be a fundamental part of
something that I want to see it through.
[Music]