every time your company doubles in
headcount size it breaks especially
within the tech and the startup
landscape we're all attracted to Big
names and big dollar signs and big
markets but focusing on a core product
and a core user in a core use case I
believe that that breeds excellence in a
product the riches are in the niches and
that's a difficult thing to do it
requires a lot of discipline and this is
a secret that I would recommend to
everyone I'm Alex Beller one of the
co-founders of postcript postcript is an
SMS marketing platform for e-commerce
businesses and the idea from the start
was SMS marketing for Brands built on
top of Shopify make a really easy really
powerful solution that lets people
retarget transact converse with their
customers over text message postcript
found product Market fit very early
customers wanted to send text messages
to their and subscribers to their
Shoppers and as long as it generates
clear Roi they're going to want to send
more and around this time we decided to
apply to Y combinator and we did that
for many reasons uh we were kind of
Outsiders we were based in LA in Arizona
we weren't very connected to the tech
scene and I went into our application
after we filed it every few days and I
would update it with our new Revenue
number so that when they logged into our
application to review it they would see
on this date this was their revenue on
this date the revenue was higher on this
day the revenue was higher and this was
like our second or third month and that
was the time when our Revenue each week
was was going from like $200 a month to$
800 to 2,000 to 3,000 I believe that the
reason that we got in to YC was because
they saw this growth trajectory and all
that growth was coming from word of
mouth and it was coming from the Shopify
App Store it was all inbound to us we
were in the right time at the right
place with the right product that
generated value for our users and by the
time we left YC combinator we were past
a million in annual revenue
approximately 6 to 7 months after we
launched we've raised several rounds of
funding since then then through series C
we bought a company called fondue and we
are now about 270 or 280 people spread
out across the
US you know we were talking about
different startup ideas me and Adam our
third partner Colin they started
building what became postcript our early
customers were amazing they're very
funny they were small e-commerce
entrepreneurs so a couple of things
worked for us really well in early days
we did something that in hindsight we
like hadn't put much thought into but
ended up being a really good idea and
this is a secret that I would recommend
to everyone we put a live chat widget on
our website and inside the postcript
application and we set it up so that
whenever anyone chatted in whenever any
User submitted a chat it would call all
three of our cell phones NE and Adam
calling it would ring us and we would
immediately stop whatever we were doing
and we would like to we would drop it
and we would go log in Andy try to help
that person we would answer their
questions we would take feedback from
them we would help them use the product
whatever that turned out to be an
incredible secret that accelerated us so
much and there's a bunch of reasons why
first we learned so much from these
early customers I mean they were giving
us feedback on holes in our product and
and what we needed to build next and
pricing they're giving us feedback on
everything and so then we could just
build exactly what they were asking for
and they'd be happier but the other
thing that came out of it is people were
getting great amazing Hands-On support
from the founders and we would be super
open that we were the founders of this
tiny little business and people really
like that and so they started to tell
their friends or other people they knew
about the post trip product they started
leaving us good reviews on the Shopify
App Store that then had our application
listing rank even higher there and so us
just talking to our customers as much as
possible and being super available I
mean we would wake up in the middle of
the night when our cell phone rang to
help customers we would leave leave the
ringer on and that created a lot of our
ground swell that led to our early
growth and so our first 100 users a lot
of it came from being hyper available
from being public but listening to our
customers talking to them and just
providing completely over-the-top
support it's actually a lot of what Paul
Graham talks about when he says do
things that don't scale you know now
posted his 18,000 customers I cannot do
the chat support for all of them anymore
but doing that for so long we spent
months and months and months we were the
only ones who did support for postcript
and we did it all the time live that we
learned so much the product advance so
much and and we got to spread a lot of
Word of Mouth came from that
too so uh we launched really with an MVP
that directly grew into postcript we've
enhanced it and we've expanded it but we
never pivoted it was SMS marketing for
e-commerce on Shopify and that's still
what it is today in early days of
postcript we had had Brands come to us
big brands that heard about us that
weren't on Shopify and they wanted to
give us a lot of money to send text
messages right so they're an e-commerce
brand that's SAR sweet spot they want to
use postcript for exactly what everyone
else uses it for but they had a
different underlying technology they
weren't on Shopify they were using a
different
platform I'm the revenue leader of the
company that's a hard thing to say no to
right that's hard to walk away from a
huge prominent brand who wants to pay us
a lot of money and be our friend and do
a case study with us but we decided to
pass on that and we said you know what
we'll we'll see you later on down the
road but right now we're focused on this
one thing and that's a difficult thing
to do it requires a lot of discipline
but it would have taken us off track it
would have led to distraction we would
have been building in many different
directions then with limited resources
and it would have been a mistake because
of that Focus so much of our value has
been created and so yes we've considered
expansion many times we've considered
expanding markets we've considered
expanding use cases outside of SMS but
what we keep coming back to is that
there remains more opportunity in this
core space and no one has really solved
it yet we think we're doing an excellent
job but there's still so much more to BU
build and so much more value to deliver
to these customers we want to do that
first we like to be the one that goes
deeper I think there's many traps and
many mistakes that all of us fall into
in the early days myself and and US
included but focus is one that is
underrated especially within the tech
and the startup landscape we're all
attracted to Big names and big dollar
signs and big markets but focusing on a
core product and a core user in a core
use case to start not forever but to
start I believe that that breeds
excellence in a product the riches are
in the niches I I really believe and
that's paid off for us where we've been
so laser focused on E Commerce marketers
that use Shopify and delivering them an
amazing SMS experience and that's really
paid off for us and I think that anyone
who uses postcript or works with the
postcript team experiences that craft
because they can tell that there's so
much expertise there what makes great
CEOs and great leaders is the ability to
look at your resourcing look at your
organization look at the all the
opportunities in front of you and
sequence things properly so that as much
lines up as possible
so there's a common framing that I hear
from a lot of other late stage Founders
or investors that I believe is true
which is that every time your company
doubles in headcount size it breaks and
I've really seen that to be the case you
know when it's 10 people everyone's
connected to everyone and it's all
automatic and then suddenly it's 25
people and you need management layers of
some kind and then it's 50 and it's a
completely different company and 100 and
200 they're totally different companies
and they require different styles of
communication and man agement and they
require a lot of different things from
their Founders when you advance to the
growth stage the people challeng is
really set in your organization becomes
so much more about how you can direct
the resources at your disposal instead
of how can you as a Craftsman or a
practitioner build product or work with
customers and those are very different
skill sets when I think about some of
the biggest lessons or tips that I could
give entrepreneurs thinking about
scaling uh what comes to mind more than
anything else is values when we started
the business we didn't create a set of
values and the reason for this was
because we'd all worked in companies
before that you know had values but
maybe they weren't that important or you
know they just they hung on the wall but
no one really knew them or was connected
to them and so we just thought it was
Superfluous but Tim Brady who was one of
our partners at y combinator when we
were about to hire our first team member
he said to us create a couple values
it'll help you anchor the culture in
something and that's what we did the
three of us sat down and we banged our
head against the wall and we got the
Whiteboard out and we created a set of
values that value set has been core to
the culture that has been built a
postcript for now almost 7 years the key
tip that I would give people is not just
to create a set of values but to make
sure it has a great acronym this is
actually the hack because what's more
important than what the values are it's
that everyone knows them like the
specific things I'm sure everyone can
pick inspirational good values but
what's more important is just that
everyone can remember them and that they
uh reflect how you believe work should
occur so to get specific the values at
postcript the acronym for them is Fe Fe
it's kind of a funny word it's f a c h
it's Fearless
Excellence animal customer first
humility every time a new person joins
postcript they go through a training
with me where I walk them through all of
our values what Fe stands for the story
behind each one how we believe it should
show up at work and then people get
recognized for living these values and
it comes up in their annual reviews and
we have a slack Channel going where
people get shouted out for living within
these values and that has really helped
guide our culture and keep us all
together as we've grown remotely but I
believe that the values that are going
to be relevant to an organization are
going to change over time they're not
always the same I'll give you an example
the e in Fe of our company's values
today it stands for excellence it didn't
always stand for that it used to stand
for 8020 8020 meaning we wanted people
to be operating from an 8020 mindset we
didn't want folks to focus on Perfection
we wanted to be moving really quickly we
wanted to be doing whatever we could to
capture as much value as we can with 20%
of the effort and then move on to the
next thing and that was great that
helped us move quickly and that helped
us inform how we built product and that
helped us inform how we built process
and that was an amazing early stage
value I mean I would recommend it to
many folks but after a while we realized
we were running into issues because of
it we were well past 100 people and we
needed more robust processes and systems
we needed our product to be sturdier and
more stable right and less about just
shipping everything that's new and
making sure what we had was really
robust as we were serving bigger and
bigger customers and at that point we
went in and we changed the value from
8020 which starts with an E to
Excellence which also starts with an E
and that way the acronym for our value
stayed the same but we got to change the
DNA of the company and we haven't done
that many times it's probably happened
three times but each time it's been
really valuable and it's kind of a weird
quirky little learned secret but I would
really recommend other entrepreneurs as
they as they're scaling think about
doing something similar be comfortable
going back and changing your company
values sometimes it's incumbent on a
Founder to reset something and to make
it clear that you know I'm hearing all
this feedback but actually I disagree
and we're going in this direction here
and values are a great way to do
it about what's going on with AI today
with generative Ai and when I think
about what's going on uh what's been
going on for a long time with predictive
machine learning what I see is a future
where on to many marketing goes away and
where it becomes highly personalized and
in the SMS space highly conversational
since the beginning of the e-commerce
use case marketing has been generally
one way it's I'm an e-commerce marketer
I am pushing out a notification to my
audience to try to get them to go by
that works it's fine but that's not how
we actually use messaging we all text
one another back and forth in
conversations and at postcript we've
always believed that there is an
enormous opportunity for Brands to see
even higher performance and for
consumers to be even happier if the
interactions are conversational between
them first more of a push marketing
Approach at postcript we've been
invested in this for a while we built
and launched a product called SMS sales
it is the only part of our company that
is in person and we have a huge office
in Phoenix Arizona that is filled with
e-commerce salespeople who work on
behalf of our Brands to sell and drive
more trans actions over the SMS channel
it's kind of old school it's like if you
walk into a retail store and someone
helps you shop or buy or answers your
questions it's like that for e-commerce
and we've been doing this for several
years and we built up an enormous amount
of expertise in it and many of our
largest customers many huge brands are
using it to drive more sales and to keep
their customers happy and we are so
excited at the opportunity of bringing
that to further scale with new
advancements in Ai and the data sets
that we've been building and the
conversational training that we've been
doing over the last several years uh we
believe puts us in a unique position to
capitalize on that Trend Ai and
predictive machine learning together are
not only going to unlock the
personalization I was just talking about
but they're also going to allow for a
much more conversational marketing
experience that phrase conversational
Commerce has been like floating in The
Ether forever and no one's really done
it and I believe now it's actually going
to happen