first time Founders like you just don't
know we we didn't have to pitch so it
was like we're stammering fumbling over
slides like we didn't know how to
actually present the opportunity and
package it the second one is like we
just didn't understand what VCS were
looking for like I legit thought Venture
Capital people were gamblers like I
thought that there was here's 5 million
go see what you can do you know I just
thought they were just gamblers and then
it took us many many pitches for us to
realize like oh they actually want to
see like there's a business here and
there's you have to understand your Tam
and what does the growth potential look
like all these things I mean the bottom
line is this it's like if you're
building something that everyone
recognizes a value in there's really no
value in it because everyone's probably
doing it if you really believe that
there's something valuable and nobody
else can see it and the gamble is like
are you wrong are you crazy right and
that's what we had to reflect on but if
you're not wrong there actually is a lot
of value there because if because no one
else is doing it right and that is what
value is so especially as a young
founder you're like am I crazy like is
there really no no way we can beat Mind
Body here is this like it's so clear to
me but no one else can see it and you
want to believe that these people are
smarter than you they probably are right
but they just don't understand your
business or the opportunity and the
thing I didn't realize at the time is
like in one hour they're trying to
understand what you spent 5 years doing
right and you think about it every day
for 5 years and they're trying to get in
one hour and there's just no way they
can right part of that's on me or the
founder because if you can't relay all
that information in an hour that's on
you but at the same time as a first-
Time founder it's like it it takes a lot
of reps to get to the point where you
can explain it and you're going to get
told no for every single rep that you're
building that ability right and that's
okay it really is okay but let it be a
chip on your shoulder because that'll
that'll fire you up more yeah
great uh my name is Tay I'm a partner at
Altos Ventures we are here with Dan the
CEO and co-founder of push press we've
been working with Dan for the last
several years after we led the series a
and it's a pleasure to have you here
with us today thank you T it's going to
be exciting conversation we're about to
have so my name is Dan we Mora I am the
CEO and a co-founder of push press we
are a gym management software platform
uh and really it's like our job to help
a gym owner focus on the one thing that
they really care about which is their
clients and helping their clients get
Fitness and strip away all the other
complexities of business through our
software platform and when did you start
the company oh so we had the idea in
about 2011 um started writing code
around 2011 it took us about 2 years to
get enough code written to have the
first client which was my gym on boarded
2013 so about 11 years ago well I guess
you have to predate the gym ownership I
was an engineer I spent about 10 years
writing code and building stuff so you
know Builders always look at things from
the lens of like how was this built I
open the gym I looked at the software
that was available and I could tell
pretty clearly like this was built a
long time ago Andor I don't know it just
wasn't up to like modern standards now
that I've built it all I can realize
it's it takes forever to build this much
software so I get it now why it wasn't
but at the time I was like there's no
way I can use this software so for the
first gym we just kind of rolled our own
just piece Meed some stuff together on
WordPress and then kind of from there
there was just like this organic
Inquisition from my peers who are gym
owners of like what are you using how
can I use that type stuff that kind of
like lit the light bulb of like we
really should do this so you open the
gym what year was this again the gym
itself the gym opened in 2010 2010 okay
and why did you decide to open the gym I
had been coding for about a decade maybe
a little bit more I didn't really
realize it at the time but when you're
an engineer well now it's like there's
High leverage with coders right and
obviously my bosses knew this so it was
like they would put dinners in front of
me Italian dinner they put Coca-Cola and
coffee in front of me and i' just be
coating all day and in that 10e span I
probably put on like 30 lbs I got I was
getting a separation from a marriage at
the time and you know that's when you
actually look at yourself in the mirror
and go oh I'm single I'm going to have
to go on a date and I'm a slob so I uh I
I started I and and I guess I didn't
really know about this about myself at
the time but entrepreneurs are generally
obsessive compulsive I believe and so I
basically went for the fastest thing
that can get me the most results which
put me pretty much in a direct path
right into CrossFit and I fell in love
with it became like a RAB rabid CrossFit
fanatic helped people open gyms got my
coach's certification and then I got
laid off at Myspace and just said I'm
going to take this money and go open a
gym give it a shot I was tired of coding
I guess you know it was it was in a in a
time when the industry itself was trying
to figure itself out so everything was
uh you know fast-paced but also very
under optimized and so when you opened
your own gym did you do anything
differently like how did you organize
the gym what was different about your
gym so and again so in during this time
this is when it was like I don't know if
you know much about CrossFit culture but
back then it was like pukey the clown
and dudes with their shirt off and just
like crazy masculine toxic masculinity
type stuff which you know is is the
brand but we we actually opened our gym
thinking like we want to tailor to
40-year-olds who are brand aesthetic
appeal you know like who appeal to a
brand aesthetic we picked colors that
were non- shocking and and so our whole
brand was was more around inclusivity
and for for everybody when we opened it
that was kind of you know I was older at
the time I was probably 30 33 or
something which was you know back then
CrossFit was like a 20-year- old thing
so we were trying to get it to be uh
more
inclusive I I look for software
immediately I think with most founding
stories there's a lot of things that
lead up to it right and so one of the
things I led up to it was and this is
when I was still at Myspace I was like
spending a solid hour a day negotiating
our payments rate for this gym we're
going to open with the payments company
and man they put me through the ringer
it was like fact in stuff give me
supporting documents dating back for 10
like all of this stuff that I had to do
I was a really bad employee but I even
remember feeling guilty like I'm
spending so much time faxing stuff doing
things to make this payments thing
happen it was just ridiculous and
anyways I I negotiated all the way down
to 1.9% and Brian was a worked at a bank
and he came in and he's like it's
impossible you're not paying 1.9 he told
me to give me I gave him his my our bank
statements he looked he looked over it
brought it home came back next day he's
like you're paying 4.8 and so I was so
pissed off that like I spent spent a a
month of my time trying to negotiate
this right down I got lied to and then
and then I had to find out because
someone else like fact checked it so
that was a reason because I was
connected to the software but I was I'm
a software guy so I was looking for
software immediately to run the business
yeah that's that's that's kind of the
Genesis of it yeah and what was the
issue with the existing tools you
mentioned they all looked old but like
what what was the Practical issue in
terms of using them for your specific
gym yeah so the the biggest issue was
every gym runs a little bit differently
and that's because in Fitness you have
CrossFit you have MMA you have karate
you have kids Fitness Sports training
just so many different things and when I
pulled up the existing software the form
field was like a mile long like every
page was like a mile long of options and
things that I had to like every form
you're like what does this mean what
does it do if what happens if I change
this what are the ramifications on you
know like where where do you think what
happens and that thought process just
blew me away like I can't manage this
and so practically speaking it was like
when one software tries to do two much
for everybody it ends up doing nothing
for anyone and this was granted um you
know I'll cut them slack they built this
before like the iPhone came out and I
think the Paradigm of the iPhone changed
everyone's mind because the iPhone can
do anything for everyone but they
compartmentalized everything into Apps
and it allows you to customize the phone
to your own experience what you want and
that's what I now expected because this
is post iPhone like I'm like why do I
have to have all this stuff I just want
what I want right and so I think the
iPhone changed the game for how we
approach software I believe in that way
m
you're scaling any Milestones that you
remember in those early days that you
were anchored on like oh I need to get
to 100 customers or 1 million of AR
whatever that is so the the one that
like we'll never I'll never forget it's
uh will from mucker a venture capital
firm so we're pitching all these VCS
early because I'm like this is going to
crush we get payments money like like
there was so much to this I'm like this
is there's no way this is going to fail
all the players suck like we understand
it blah blah blah and we got laughed out
of every Venture room for years and one
of them this guy guy named will from
mucker he told me he's like hey this is
a great idea uh why don't you come back
when you're at 10,000 Mr because then
we'll know you have escape velocity I
remember these terms exactly and so
right when we hit 10,000 I called him
he's like yeah come down show me what's
going on blah blah and I was like cool
and we we were excited cuz I'm like dude
he's going to invest cuz we did what he
said and he's like this is all cool why
don't you get come call me back when you
get to 100,000 Mr because then I'll know
that you escap like literally told me
the same thing again I'm like oh all
right and so we called him back at
100,000 and he's like we pass like we're
not interested and um I just remember
like we it gave us a clear line in the
say like okay we have to get 10,000 Mr
and we're going to we're going to call
him back but the the irony is he's
actually an investor now because he
heard that we were raising a kind of a a
safe through another another party one
of our connected friends it was another
fraternity brother of ours was investing
cuz he did he's done well in some stuff
and he's friends with him on the side
he's like hey will you should check out
this company he's like oh I know them
and and then will called me and he's
like okay it's time let's do this and
I'm like oh now it's time that's funny
yeah so uh yeah if you're thinking about
getting investment money from from uh
Venture capitals they're not they they
uh you got to show them some social
proof first like they're not just
throwing money around like I thought
they
were uh when did will invest and what
was the scale at that time I think we're
at 1.4 million AR or maybe maybe 2
million probably around 2 million
it honestly was probably it was a really
good deal I'm sure this was like late
2020 so it like during Co we grew we had
built a free product and like we were
doing we were actually building brand
because we were the most authentic like
gym owner Centric uh company and we grew
quite a bit and it was like the signals
were good the social proof was good the
the numbers looked good um and but I
didn't know how to raise money and so
this uh anti- VC type company com fund
came to me and he's like hey I think I
can just get some LPS together and raise
some money but it's got to be at this
valuation and I was just kind of like if
I can do no work on this because I don't
believe you're going to raise it like I
had no belief like I'm like I'm going to
do no work on this you can have that
good valuation but I don't want to do
anything like you know and he's like
cool and he got heo he did it in a
weekend like got it all closed up and
that's when will heard of the circle so
anyway that first round uh we were at 2
million in AR roughly 2 million in ARR
and I think it was like at 11 million
valuation so it was like 5x at a time
when people were getting like 50x or
something so I just didn't think it
would happen wow yeah so you reflect on
the many con Sation you had with the
investors and a lot of them were just
not going well what do you think just
was missing like what what happened
super good question for firsttime
Founders like you just don't know and I
remember like so some of the early ones
we pitched so one the first thing is we
were playing rotating CEO so like for
the first pitches I think Chris was the
CEO and then Brian was CEO for a while
and then at towards the end like at the
2020 stage it was me but I remember them
coming out we would come out and they'd
be like we we don't see any passion and
I was like what like dude we are like we
are so passion like I I couldn't believe
it but really what it was was we didn't
know how to we we didn't how to pitch so
it was like we're stammering fumbling
over slides like we didn't know how to
actually present the opportunity and
package it um so that was early problems
for one the second one is like we just
didn't understand what VCS were looking
for like I legit thought Venture Capital
people were gamblers before like I
thought that there was here's 5 million
go see what you can do you know I just
thought they were just gamblers and then
it took us many many pitches for us to
realize like oh they actually want to
see like there's a business here and
there's you have to understand your Tam
and what does the growth potential look
like all these things and then once we
actually got to the point where like I I
knew how to pitch and I can actually get
to the point of term sheets I started to
realize like I don't really want to work
with investors they're all like they're
all going to make me do the things that
I I could see all of our predecessors
are doing that don't work like when
you're obsessed over the money you're
just squeezing them for more Revenue you
don't really care about them as
customers they numbers to you like none
of that stuff I wanted to do so it that
irony is once we got to the point where
we actually could get term sheets I'm
like I don't even want to do this so
yeah I felt uh I don't know the word for
it right now but basically very
disconnected from the fact that like
something that I could see so clearly
was not obvious to other people so that
that made me feel disconnected for one
it put chips a huge chip on my shoulder
massive we joke about it all the time
that like and I wish I did this but we
call it the list of all the people who
didn't believe in us like I wish I
actually kept the list because okay so
let me tell you the story actually this
is a good one so at at one point
throughout this journey I had to keep
taking jobs because I just didn't make
enough money so it's like I was running
a gym had to go take a full-time job and
doing push press like three things at
once and one of the jobs I took I
actually had to drive past the house of
an investor who turned us down like he
we went to his house we sat there and
pitched him I thought it went really
well and then he went back to the fund
that was he was representing and he's
like oh they suck like don't don't
invest in them and so every day for like
a year I had to drive past his house and
I flipped off his house every day like I
was so pissed off at like like he became
the personification of like everyone who
said no to us I mean the bottom line is
this it's like if you're building
something that everyone recognizes a
value in there's really no value in it
because everyone's probably doing it if
you're getting like if you really
believe that there's something valuable
and nobody else can see it and the
gamble is like are you wrong are you
crazy right and that's what we had to
reflect on but if you're not wrong there
actually is a lot of value there because
if because no one else is doing it right
and that is what value is so it was um
very challenging especially as a young
founder you're like am I crazy like does
no is there really no no way we can beat
Mind Body here is this like it's so
clear to me but no one else can see it
and you want to believe that these
people are smarter than you you they
they probably are right but they just
don't understand your business or the
opportunity and the thing I didn't
realize at the time is like in one hour
they're trying to understand what you
spent 5 years doing right and you think
about it every day for 5 years and
they're trying to get in one hour and
there's just no way they can right part
of that's on me or the founder because
if you can't relay all that information
in an hour that's on you but at the same
time as a first- Time founder it's like
it it takes a lot of reps to get to the
point where you can explain it and
you're going to get told no for every
single rep that you're building that
ability right and that's okay it really
is okay yeah but let it be a chip on
your shoulder because that'll that'll
fire you up more
yeah so how did you fund the company for
the first several years it was
technically bootstrap yeah there's
there's a few different angles to it
we've always been Scrappy and there's
like two pretty impactful moments I'll
I'll highlight the first one we printed
a poster we actually partnered with a a
weightlifting coach who's here in San
Francisco and we we brought her down we
did a photo shoot it was very
inexpensive and we printed this poster
of like weightlifting technique and it
was like Chris co-founder Chris had this
brilliant like design eye and like
visual representation eye so he
basically got a high-speed camera and
took like the movements of a cleaning
jerk and a snatch and broke it down into
like frame by frame what your feet
should look like from a top down
position you know from all this stuff
put it on a poster it looked awesome and
uh we sold it to the Comm actually we
gave it away to the community but it was
like $10 shipping and the shipping only
cost us $3 so like we made $7 a thing we
sold like a thousand of them because
everyone wanted it in their gym but we
also it was a double dip cuz we're like
this will get our brand into to the gyms
as well so you had push press on the
yeah it was a push press poster so it
was like got them aware of our brand but
we made like seven Grand which and at
that time was like massive money the
second thing we did is we built a timer
which still works to this day like the
timer's still out there but what
happened here was like Chris designed so
many things for us to build and we
couldn't keep up we couldn't code as
fast as he designed and so he was like I
got nothing to do we went to some
conference where it was like a bunch of
developers were there and we met some
guy from like Vietnam who does mobile
development and Chris is like I have
this idea for a timer can you build it
and he's worked up a bunch of mocks and
the guy built it and Chris had like
three months of nothing to do so he just
like Managed IT we built this timer and
it was it's still it's still awesome
it's still I think it's like one of the
best timers out there still it was like
10 years ago it a it's a workout timer
so so here's the hook it was like a
workout timer and you know it it was
specific to CrossFit so you can easily
build like count down count up timers
blah blah blah but the hook was like I
was building all these Connections in
the space so I'm like I went to all the
like celebrities on the CrossFit world
I'm like Hey we're building a timer can
you add your voice to it and so we built
like this language pack where it count
it goes like 3 2 1 go and then the
person can say something motivational
like hey you're you're halfway there
keep going and then we had like 20
different voices on it and so people
really like that cuz the voices were on
it one of my early members at my second
Gym came in and he was an ad Network ad
specialist and he's like dude show me
the numbers on this timer and we were
doing like a million workouts a month
like it just we just put it out there
and we didn't do anything it just it
just like started getting used getting a
million workouts a month and he's like
yo if I put ads on this like we can make
some money and so he did and you know
for the first like six months he was
like actively cuz I guess it's like you
have to actively manage the ads I don't
know and we're getting like 30 grand a
month on it like pretty decent money and
that like funded the company for a while
but then he he got busy he stopped
looking at it the ads started crashing
the timer like it just made it a
terrible experience so we ripped all the
ads back out and like all the ad Revenue
declined but like for a good year we
were probably making like 20 to 30 grand
a month on this timer that we had built
for free yeah and it was the same thing
we built the timer cuz we wanted Jims to
use it so they they would learn who push
press was yeah yeah
so if you reflect on that first chapter
of push press what was the most
challenging moment and I'm sure a lot of
software companies had this point where
like you get enough clients using or
customers using your product where it
would be foolish to walk away from it
but you're not you don't see a clear
line of sight to the type of growth that
makes you go like hey I can actually get
paid to do this cuz it's just all
volunteer work and Sweat Equity right
and there was a time in 2017 where I
remember turning around to Chris in the
gym and I was like hey I think I'm going
to hang it up I'm going to give up on
push press and I'm going to just focus
on the gym because I I see how the gym
can actually pay me to make a living
here and I'm tired of working three jobs
basically and uh him and Brian I think
kind of talked me out of it at that
point like dude just give us some time
like we you know we've got clients we've
got customers there's fit I don't really
remember exactly how they talk me out of
it but I remember being pretty much like
I think I have to like give up on this
but I didn't want to and I think
ultimately that was it so like there
those moments will come when you found a
company where it's just like you you
have to just kind of like see it through
there's something about your guys's
philosophy that that resonates with me
it's just like you're the durability and
like until you really are dead you're
not dead and you can find a way to get
through it but you've you just have to
know it's going to suck yeah do you
remember how many clients you had at
that time probably like a couple hundred
couple hundred yeah so you had real
customers real usage but it's just like
not there yet just didn't feel right
this this was probably after we were
making after will said no to the 10,000
come back at 100,00 you know it's like
you have these like demoralizing moments
where like dude we got a 10x from here
even for you know and like I don't even
see how we're going to get there so yeah
there there's one I think key tenant to
operating uh any business and it's just
like um if you stay alive long enough
you will be able to start to manufacture
luck we didn't know it at the time but
like Co was kind of around the corner
and that was like our like I wouldn't
our L our lucky moment I guess like we
couldn't have created but that was a
moment for us to like really rally into
yeah let's talk about that cuz um you
guys accelerated growth during Co which
is very ironic when all these gyms were
shutting down so how did that happen so
I think the fir the like immediately
when it happened I was like oh it was
like existential oh my God right I think
it was two things one I was part of a
mentorship group at the time and I was
on a call his name is Dan Martell I was
on a call with him and he was like he
said something that I will never forget
to this day he's like never waste a good
crisis and I was like what do you you
mean and he's like like these are the
moments when the winners win you know
and then I thought about it and I really
reflected on it I'm like yeah dude like
you don't win races on straightaways you
win races on turns and so that mindset
shift like changed a lot for me we had
just released free um our free version
without knowing that was going to happen
so that that was incidental luck right
in terms of timing but I think what
really accelerated us was we were like
okay and I just decided at that point
like we're putting the foot on the gas
with Co and we just did everything we
can to like circle the wagons protect
our gyms protect the indry like it
didn't even matter if you were a client
of ours or not and we just got really
vocal right this was right around the
time I started a podcast right around
the time we were like learning how to
express ourselves to the market and so
you know we gave money away to people
like we got a PPP loan and we uh turned
around and just gave a lot of that away
to our gyms to help support them we just
turned it into a grant a lot of the ways
I like to think are kind of like how do
you create a good scenario and everyone
wins but you get something out of it
like we got a ton of publicity but we
got we gave money away and my argument
to my Founders was like well we can
either spend money on on Google paid
clicks or we can just give the money to
the gyms let's give the money to the
gyms you know you can kind of like
create a lot of Goodwill moments if you
think like that I think what was the
impetus to creating that free product
that happened to come out at the right
time yeah well the right time this was
just pure luck honestly but the free
product was was born like so a lot of
this is just born from the we understand
our our customer and the industry really
well cuz we come from it and we
understand like when you start a brand
new gym 250 bucks a month is a lot like
that's your first two members right off
the table gone when you might be trying
to like fight to get 10 members you know
so it's like that hurts so really it was
just like if we know opening a gym is
the most painful time financially but we
also know that's the easiest time to get
on a software system and learn it why
not lean into both of those and just say
like we'll give it to you free UPF front
and then we'll create a situation where
like as we grow trust as we build your
business you'll you'll become a paying
client because we're so customer-centric
and we always have been a lot of our
energy and our our payment comes from
the energy of our customer
so and and really I think a lot of gym
owners flaw at this because it's like
they don't make enough money to live but
they they show up every day cuz our
customer energy makes them feel full uh
we were probably a lot the same so it
was the revenue was growing the
customers growing like we were bu like
we were making some key hires and some
and doing some good stuff but like just
the energy around the company and the
community and the people's response to
our co co reaction or proactive steps
very filling to us so I think I think we
we were we were amped at that time so
you then go raise your series a so safe
happens William finally invests yep what
is that Journey from there on for a year
or so yeah so I think I think the um I
guess the overarching theme from like
that from like 2019 or maybe even 2018
through is just a continuing
reinvestment in education so in 2018 is
2019 we joined SAS Academy which put me
in rooms with other Founders you it's
same thing it's like you're sitting
across from a table I I remember this
actually this happened here but this
happened at first SAS Academy went to we
were we were just at a million in
revenue and I remember being at the
table thinking I was like like badass
cuz I was like cuz they were like say
your name say your company say how much
revenue you're at I'm like we're at a
million like super cool and then the guy
next to me is like oh yeah we're 14 and
they're like we're at 18 we're at 26 and
I was like oh my God like we're nothing
and that happens here too like I'm like
we're at 15 and they're like we're at
100 we're at 260 we're at whatever and
you're like oh wow we got a long way to
go but like so getting in those rooms
list just having mindset changes of like
oh that's how you approach marketing oh
that's why you want to do sales this way
like changes the game then we we got
mucker and will would just bring me in
every month just sit down and be like
okay let's focus on something what you
you know like I never had that before
like someone actually like let's get
real tactical and focus on something
that changed the game for me right and
then being with mucker got me more
exposure to other CEOs who are going
through you know like I get to talk to
if you're starting a business it's like
how fast can you change your mindset
because you don't know what you don't
know so you need to be around people who
have been there you know and and again
that continues on today like we just did
this stuff this week where like I'm
listening to people who you know their
current problem is like how do I get
from 100 million to 300 million a
different problem set that you have to
be aware of early so I think investing
in your education is super critical as a
Founder
[Music]
yeah what do you charge your customers
what types of products are you selling
what is the economic model of push press
yeah I mean in general the basic idea
with a vertical SAS platform is you want
to build enough Goodwill and trust with
your customers because you're handling
you're helping them handle their
business more efficiently to the tune
that you can help them in every way that
can be digitized or maybe not maybe not
even digitized there is now a concept of
service as a software have you heard of
this mhm yeah so uh that's kind of how
we see ourselves these gym owners have
opened Fitness facilities all they
really care about is helping their
customers get in shape find fine Fitness
and fine Wellness they do not care about
accounting they don't want to do payroll
they don't want to find someone to
service their rowing machines they don't
want to do any of that stuff they just
have to and so I think the value ad that
any vertical SAS can can bring to their
Niche and their industry is to strip all
of those unnecessary jobs that get
created when you open a business away
and either you know give them ways to
systematize it create process around it
or even automate it or just take it away
that's my vision for vertical SAS and I
think that's why we were talking about
this earlier this concept of trying to
understand what the Tam is for vertical
SAS is a fallacy because the Tam is
literally as big as their expense their
expense line and their p&l in my opinion
for each gym yeah let's talk about that
a little more because there's this
notion in vertical Market software in
any business that tries to go after a
niche market that the T is not big
enough to build a great business I'm
sure you've heard that PTSD yes um what
are your views on that I just saw the
CEO of service Titan talked about this
yesterday if you can open up the p&l of
any small business and look at where
they spend their money and understand
like which of these can be productized
in software you actually have the right
to take all of that off an owner's plate
and and turn that into business because
as long as you're providing more value
than your charge and you're you're doing
so in a way that creates more Goodwill
and more Trust as you sell more products
you're actually doing them a service by
bringing it all into one house in
especially in the SMB space these owners
want I heard this term recently I love
these owners want one throat to choke
like they want one relationship that
they can trust and buy into and have
full confidence that you know they can
hand all of that business off and then
just focus on what they want to focus on
if when you think of Tam in in the
simplest sense of like oh there's only
100,000 gyms in the world and you can
only make $150 per gym CU that's what
your software class that's wrong because
it's like what about insurance and what
about payroll and what about health
insurance and benefits and Banking and
servicing and lending and you know
payments like there's a million pieces
to the stack that you can provide value
to that are just like overlooked by this
Tam conversation yeah so which part of
the stack are you addressing now and
what are some areas that you want to get
into in the future I want to get into
all of it Tay all of it and and it's
purely from the lens of like the it will
help JY so much if if they can control
it all from one Central Dash word right
and the relationships like we we bring
Network effects to the to the equation
here like I can pre-negotiate better
rates for water than they can get from
their local distributor because we we
will be negotiating on behalf of
everyone in the network right so um
right now we we've we built our whole uh
system around payments which is a whole
another funny story because when I was
pitching people back in 2014 on push
press they didn't people didn't even
know what payment like they they didn't
even count payments it didn't matter but
payments are so critical to this entire
stack we do some of their frontend lead
generation website development local SEO
marketing um and CRM tooling yeah it's
funny we built a branded app which
allows every gym to have a branded app
in the app store and we thought nobody
would use it but what we come to find is
like almost every gym buys it because
they actually want to stand out against
Orange Theory like this single gym has
no way for them to have their own app
otherwise and it's really cool for them
to be able to say like oh yeah we sit
next to Orange Theory in the App Store
so we do a branded app we have a we have
a platform called train which was
basically an early test of this uh App
Store concept that we're building into
push press that will allow for the mod
this is the the fix to that one form
field that creates you know that solves
everything for everyone is building
modular apps you know may or may not
come with the price tag but extend the
functionality push press in a very
specific way you mentioned the customer
support being such an important part of
even the early days um how how are you
carrying that on as the company grows
let's talk about that you have to deal
with board members sometimes who like
push you on things that you know are
nonsense to to kind of lay the to lay
the thing there's like these ranges that
you have to operate your business in so
like you guys want gross margin in
general to be like 75 to 85% rough or
75% or better right and for those you
don't know gross margin is basically
like your Revenue the amount of money
you spend on servers and you know things
that make the product happen and then
customer support because they're keeping
the lights on I've built my company
intentionally around the fact that
customer support is a go to market
strategy so I don't think it should be
part of gross margin that's the argument
I will forever make our customer sport
team and the the way our people interact
with our customers kicks out pass so
much that it turns our customers into
raving fans that become a referral it's
a turn reducer and a referral creation
and I'm sure you saw it when you're like
investigating us it's like what gym
management software should I use and it
should be a whole bunch of people saying
push press absolutely hands down use
push press an interesting way for
Founders to think about this is like
there are industry standards for most
businesses to run their thing but that
doesn't mean you have to do that and I
think it took me a couple years working
with you to understand that I don't have
to do everything you say I respect
everything you say thanks you know but
but yeah every business is built
different right and like uh you know
respectfully like you don't live you
don't live and breathe push press to the
not even close to the tune that I do so
it's like the stuff that we you know the
big picture you know the industry you
know the trends you know the averages
but fight for a long time to say like
our customer sport team needs to be
overstaffed well trained highly tooled
and and amazing even if it means our
gross margin is 70% for now yeah yeah
which I think we actually talked about
at length at some point where I actually
told you guys don't worry about it
right and I think that was really good
alignment the early days you were
extremely customer obsessed maybe out of
necessity but you came from the gym
industry so you understood your
constituents really well how did you
maintain that culture until today when
you now have what close to 100 employees
yeah so I mean it starts with like
understanding what you want to build
your business around and what you feel
is important part of this is I felt it
was super important because as a gym
owner it's it sucks to like call into
your you know your software and have
them have no clue what being a gym owner
is like like I don't even know how how
you support that but on the other hand
of the equation I realized I was a
superpower like if all of our big
competitors were just oblivious to what
it was like to run a gym why don't we
lean all the way into that and just know
what it's like to run a gym so we and
and also out of necessity because we
were broke and we're bootstrapped we had
to hire whoever would work for us and
most people that really really want to
work with us are people who are
passionately Mission aligned so like
yeah I'll work for like way less than I
should work for because I actually
believe in what you're doing too there's
something speci about that mission
alignment understanding the customer
paino and then you know having the the
support from you know the companywide
support of saying like we lean into this
that has created something magical with
us where you know our team even our
Engineers are like they're not gym
owners for the most part but they're
like through osmosis or whatever they're
feeling that customer L Obsession and
they're becoming that you know and it
starts to build some cultural things
like now our VP of engineering is like
when you onboard as an engineer you
spend two weeks in customer support and
you get to learn how they get their
teeth kicked in when you make a bug
right like you have you have to live
that customer Journey with them so it's
it is affecting our entire culture in in
a very positive way we're an empathetic
company like we 100% believe in our
customers and and anytime a customer has
a pain you'll see like people are
running towards the fire the flip side
of that that's dangerous is that creates
potentially a hundred different
directions people need something fixed
in every day because there's like
different things happening different gym
types everything so it's like you have
to develop this muscle of saying no and
also being balancing your empathy of
like ooh that that's painful but we
can't do it right now and I think the
mistake we made before was like every
paino gets fixed that's a problem in
multiple ways one the focus becomes
fragmented in terms of like what the
company's doing but two it ends up
creating like Frankenstein code where
it's like oh I just bolted this thing on
real quick to fix this thing oh I just
bolted this thing on to fix this thing
and then your your software sucks in the
end because it's like just a whole bunch
of boltons and no real architecture you
know yeah
why did you start Instagram
H
content let's
go so again this um this there the
multi-pronged answer here the first one
which is a recurring theme of what I'm
going to you know always keep saying is
like my competitors are not gym owners
the CEO who who even knows what the CEO
looks like has no voice has no passion
is not there for gym owners I am so why
why wouldn't I put that out there right
but two I think we live in a so two we
live in a day and age where people
expect to learn about things that they
want to interact with through various
mechanisms and one of those is Media the
younger generation maybe not our gen My
Generation but definitely younger
generation like they go on social media
to learn about products they want to buy
and do that's how they do research like
we might use YP they use Instagram I
also believe people buy from people
especially in the SMB space so putting a
face to the actual thing you're buying
is important it's it's costly to build a
brand that's why I want tracksuit to
help me but it's very costly to build a
brand but it it's much easier to say
like I'm Dan I'm the founder founder of
push press and this is what I believe
and this is why I'm here for you and
then the brand will inherit that
Goodwill that I can I can build you know
and I'm just saying what I believe so
it's it's not hard and lastly straight
out of Nal we live in a world where like
you get free leverage like social media
has created free leverage and in
business leverages everything so like
why wouldn't you take it if you if you
can now granted it's an investment of
your time it's investment of money but
how else could you get a million people
to see something in a month without
spending millions of dollars right like
you couldn't do that 10 years 20 years
ago so for all those Reasons I'm I'm
very very bullish on content yeah were
you comfortable filming those things in
the beginning absolutely not yeah AB not
dude it's like as a Founder you've got
to do stuff that you have to do M um and
you feel like this was something you had
to do had to do yeah yeah and even to
the point where this is founder mode
stuff but even to the point where like I
bugged our marketing team to like hey
get someone to work with me on this and
they were just too busy doing other
stuff so I just found my own guy and
just did it myself you know yeah I felt
like you you have to do it and it's
going become increasingly more important
as the years go by MH so you're building
your personal brand how do you try to
check once in a while whether this is
working or if it's worth it really good
question and is is it's one of those
things where you can easily doubt
yourself and in fact you're not going to
see unless you're actually posting like
and getting a million views on YouTube
or something a lot of the results you
get are intangible or hard to measure
and the the tracksuit guys actually
explained something in one of the
breakouts so we did that I thought was
great and it was basically it was the
iPhone example so he gets up on stage
and he says like everyone who wants to
buy an iPhone the next 5 years raise
your hand or not maybe not an iPhone but
a smartphone right everybody raises
their hand and you go okay everyone's
going to buy a smartphone in the next
year keep your hand raised everyone's
hand or maybe half the people's hands go
down right and he's like okay who's
going to buy a smartphone in the next
two weeks and then it's just like 1% of
the hands stay up and what he said is
like the 1% is who you're doing paid
search ads for you're doing like direct
paid marketing because they're in the
consideration set to buy right now but
the 99% of the people who had their hand
up before will buy eventually and they
need to know who you are what you stand
for why your product matters you know
like the things you're solving they need
to know the general big picture but they
don't need to know what the latest
megapixels on the phone is you know like
those are those are buying consideration
points all of this content in my opinion
is a channel not the channel but a
channel that you can passively
continually put out like who I am what I
stand for why I'm doing this and and
just let people know that you're there
the T big Tipping Point for me with
content was there's a mentor in the
space that sent an email out every day
day I didn't read a single email for
years I didn't read one but when ever
anyone asked me like who's the who's the
best Mentor in the space I would say him
and I asked myself why did I say that I
don't know anything that I don't even
know what he wrote like I just read
subject lines and it's because every day
he put something out I knew he cared
that's it so I think I think it it Ma it
just matters to do were there any
concrete examples of it paying off like
in a business context oh yeah that was
the question huh I just totally didn't
answer that I mean the the real short
answer is no but I do go to events I I
go to events frequently and at every
event I go to multiple people multiple
people will come up to me and say like I
really love your content please don't
stop doing that you know something to
that degree I do get I've also gotten
feedback of like oh I didn't know about
push press we just joined and became a
member but I found one of these reels
you did blah blah blah so I guess that's
kind of concrete idence but it's not
there is no direct like I saw a real I
bought push press it's usually like
months later and it's just part of the
like General consideration process my my
goal with content is like I want my
sales team to like get on a demo and
have someone basically like I'm
completely sold just tell me the
information on how to buy like that's
kind of the motion that I'm trying to
build for them how would you
characterize yourself as a leader like
what type of leader are you I used to be
uh very insecure like why would I be the
leader why is my voice more important
than anyone's uh every decision would
turn into a committee like hey what do
you guys think what do you think I am
now much more becoming there are certain
decisions that I will just make and I I
don't don't feel bad about that anymore
I don't feel insecure about that just
because I see how much bureaucracy and
Chaos it creates when I start asking for
everyone's opinion and we start tallying
votes and then we have debates and
discussions that go nowhere it just
doesn't help so I think I'm evolving as
a leader I think no matter what I'm
always going to be empathetic I'm going
to care what people think I'm going to
listen to people's opinions but I'm
becoming much more um able to just say
cool I heard all your opinions this is
what we're doing and is there anything
that you're actively working on to get
better at at this moment the the the
real answer to this if you're looking
start a company is like you're going to
be actively getting better at whatever
the biggest fire is at every moment of
the company and it will never stop uh
right now I'm trying to become better at
the financial and operational end of
things it's something I'm absolutely
horrible horrible at I know very little
of so just understanding like how does
annual planning work and and what really
got me into this was like for us to like
think about a three-year plan and start
to look at like what three years looks
like I realize I had to build stuff now
to be able to even get close to having
this three-year plan and I liken a lot
of this stuff to like farming I don't
know why I always think about farming
but you can't like Harvest your grapes
if you haven't planted them and it might
take a whole season for the planting the
seeds for the grapes to grow and then
another season for the you know the
grapes to whatever and so when you think
about that way it's like you really have
to get ahead of all this stuff to be
able to get the grapes in three years
you know yeah my big Focus right now is
like how do you become operationally
more sound how do you run better
meetings how do we do like better board
meetings better monthly Recaps annual
planning all that stuff is kind of where
I'm at what about the the mission cuz in
the beginning there was no mission to
empower the fitness industry there was
no mission that was that grand and then
it became that and so how has the
mission of this company changed over
time the mission honestly has forever
been something Loosely formed around
like be I remember one of the first
board meetings we came to here it was
like or maybe it was the first CEO
conference or whatever but we left with
a mission of like we want to help a
billion people become fitter but then we
kind of were like how does how do you
measure that you know it just became
really weird or should they be you know
like all this stuff so we've always had
this loose idea of we're really here to
make the world fitter and again this is
part of like maybe some people have the
skill something I'm developing but like
in order to be a good leader you have to
be able to pack a lot of amorphous ideas
into very concrete like eight-word
sentences you know what I mean like you
have to be very clear and it's got to be
memorizable and repeatable and I think
I'm getting better at it but yeah that's
why it like it went from something that
was like very hazy into like we are just
here to make the world fitter by helping
our gyms become better businesses that's
it do you have a view on what the
fitness world would look like in say 10
20 years and how does technology play
into that Journey oh that's big this can
go so many different ways because the
problem with Fitness is it's an IT
everyone looks for easy buttons and
fitness is not the easy button and so
right now what you get is you get 10% or
5% of the people in the world who are
okay pushing the hard button because
that's what they're into doing it but
we're missing the mark on the 90 to 95%
of people who just want OIC you know or
who want the Easy Button I'm actually
starting to generate this thesis which
we should talk about sometime okay that
gyms should sell community and we should
solve loneliness first and the fitness
is the byproduct people show up at the
gyms that they that we support because
they're showing up for their friends as
much as they're showing up for themsel
and it's almost like church where church
for the body you have this you know
every day I go I pay my penants or
whatever you know I do my thing and at
the end of the result is like oh wow I
got fitter but really it's like you're
loneliness in the moment and the easy
button is loneliness which I think is a
is a real thing it's I don't know maybe
weird to talk about but the community is
something actually very impactful in
these gyms so if we can figure out this
easy button and you can flip it and get
90% of people in the gyms like we could
have literally like 20 times more gyms
in the world just overnight so to me
it's like there's a big growth
opportunity if we actually attack the
problem that's stopping people from
coming into the gym yeah that's powerful
how how do you want push press to be
remembered after your time uh hopefully
not remembered cuz that means
dead or how do you find people to talk
about push press yeah near
2300 um this one might not this so this
might not answer the question directly
cuz I haven't thought about that to be
honest but it does it Loosely will so
one thing I have noticed in the fitness
industry that that annoys me is there
are very few multigenerational companies
and if you look across like I think
Fitness is a tested tried andrue
industry but if you look at other ones
Automotive entertainment whatever
like there are companies that have been
around for 100 years and I know Fitness
is newer to some regard but there is no
50-year-old Fitness Company really um I
guess maybe like 24-Hour Fitness
although they're kind of on the decline
and and the reason is I think it's
because the Easy Button problem oh well
you know like what's the newest fad
we'll do Shake Weights like okay let's
sell those on TV let's do jazzer size
and everything turns into like a DVD buy
it now for $29.99 and it dies in a year
and I think like what we need to start
having in the fitness industry is like
multigenerational companies that live
because they're not built on hype and
they're not built on fads but they're
built on something real and that's
ultimately like where my mind has
started to go like this company
definitely should outlive me and it
should support an industry that is
outliving all the people who open the
gyms themselves