Fuse. We're on a mission to accelerate
the world's transition to fusion energy.
One of the only fusion companies that's
actually making revenue. Started a
company almost 6 years ago now. I was 19
at the time. Yeah. Never went to
college. I never even submitted an
application. Why do I need to convince
an admission officer to like let me sit
in a classroom for 4 years to then get a
piece of paper that says I can
potentially do something versus just do
something and prove you can do it. life
is too short and there's like 7 billion
or more people on earth. So you just
always ask yourself like why am I doing
something that actually matters or like
how can I contribute and I felt that
there's a a real way to contribute to
work on something that could be um
civilization altering starting company
was the fastest way to make progress I
thought I'm Jes I'm the founder and CEO
of fuse we're the only fusion company
that has delivered experimental results
of a new technology ology that was no
one has built it before and published
the results in nature. We've raised over
$50 million of capital. We work with the
US military and US government. March 13,
we we've proven the machine at scale and
now we have contracts to commercialize
[Music]
it. My father's a nuclear physicist, so
growing up was just very curious about
how the world works. You know, I've
always liked to work on hard things and
explore research topics. And then I very
quickly learned that maybe spending time
in academic environment was not the
fastest way to make progress on
technology. So that's why I decided to
start you know my own company. I had
started a nonprofit in education. The TS
as a teenager things it was really hard
to you know build things. It's you can't
even get a credit card as under 18 which
is you know pretty funny. you know, you
cannot open a Shopify online store if
you're under 18, which is kind of
ridiculous considering all the other
things you can do. So, I started a
nonprofit to essentially liberate
teenagers to dare and and to create. And
we were funded by Google.org, the
Canadian government, and and others. And
we built that into pretty uh successful
program. And we had some teenagers that
now are off to doing great things. What
I've done to date is a good example for
others to realize that it's possible. If
you really want to build something and
you truly have the grit and tenacity,
you can. A lot of people, you know,
being young is has a competitive edge
because you're naive and you've got a
lot of stamina and energy. Definitely
those early wins give you an early taste
at freedom. You know, choosing to start
as early as possible maximizes, you
know, your chance at getting it right.
And even if you fail, you make you burn
yourself a little bit, as long as you
don't die or don't go to jail, I think
everything else can be tolerated and
repaired. You know, I felt that there's
a a real way to contribute to work on
something civilization altering like a
civilization scale and and history.
every technology progress or
civilizational development has been tied
to like how much kilowatt hour is
available per capita. So when you think
about the industrial revolution and how
that enabled the whole human prosperity
and and technological advancements and
you can tie that to coal afterwards and
chemical era and I believe that fusion
would unlock the next level of human
prosperity you know the rise of the
social middle class the rise of AI of
quantum technologies like all of those
critical technologies they need energy
and without energy we can't have AI like
how would you power all the data centers
do you want it at the cost of people not
being able to turn their lights on at
the house. I don't think so. And so we
will need significantly more energy and
fusion is not the only ways to actually
make that. So Titan is the world's
highest power and highest energy
impedance match Mars generator of its
kind. What that matters to think about
it as a giant battery that releases all
of its energy really fast like in a
billionth of a second. It's a very
important question to ask. Is this a
scientific nonprofit or is there a
business here? cuz a lot of time people
solve are building companies and I I
wonder if that's better to be like a
scientific research that's like
nonprofit funded or grandfunded versus
is this a business or a real company.
Then the second is like really to
question the fundamentals and what we've
done for Titan was built in-house like
over 80% of the Titan subsystems and
components were built in-house at Fuse
and so we took on the project knowing
that we have the capacity to solve a lot
of the problems and we vertically
integrated which meant that as problems
were arising we were able to solve them
inhouse. building companies like you you
always are updating the operating system
is like an app you know and you you have
to constantly debug and upgrade the
operating system and you need different
version for every 6 months or so. So you
know very intentionally taking time to
be introspective and to think about you
know what has changed now. This is not
the same company that it was before.
Obviously the core fundamentals are the
same but you know the way it operates is
is different and bringing the right
resources you know around you. You know
there's people who are really good at
the early stage and then you need a
different type of skill set and and
culture for growth stage and bringing in
different people at the right time and
having the introspection to think of
what needs to be changed, what bugs need
to be fixed and how to upgrade the
operating system for the next phase is
very
important. Certainly the company has
come close to running out of capital at
few moments in time. you know we we had
some you know technology that at some
point you know did not go as we had
planned or we had run out of capital and
we had to make really hard decisions but
you know these are the moment that
really define who we are you know just
building this connective tissue as a
team and this resilience the one thing
that has been really awesome is like I'm
young myself but we've built a team with
you know some really experienced people
from different aspects uh of the
government I had the fortune to work
with some really smart people with some
of the best people I've met fortunate
enough that they're now part of one team
and we're multiple vectors pointing in
one direction and just if you're humble
and you bring people that really can
compleiment you that's a strength not a
weakness. It's really important to be
audacious and daring but also humble and
it's your challenge to figure out how to
overcome that will save you a lot of
peace and help attract some great people
where you recognize your weaknesses and
vulnerabilities and build around them.
that team is that mindset like most
people actually want to be in
environments where you know they're all
contributing and learning from each
other that's at least a healthy
environment. We also really care about
you know people who are just focused on
getting done and you know getting
the job done whatever it is versus know
just talking. So we we have a really
default for people who take agency who
are autonomous and just want to get
done who are really curious and third
just give a you know like the
people on our team really care. They
stay up till 4:00 a.m. when we have a
mission. They work on the weekends. They
just go out of their own way to to do
the job and like pick up the trash if
needs be. You know, give a and care
and just want to get done and just
focus on that. I think you can get a lot
done. It's It's actually really funny
when people think that entrepreneurs are
very big risk takers. I think like great
entrepreneurs are really good like risk
hedgers. Like the day you start the
company, you've taken the most amount of
risk and then your job all along is to
retire risk and like choose very
selectively which risk to derisk first
and how to sequentially do that. for
founders to think about risk mitigation
as well as know equipping yourself with
the right tool and most importantly with
the right people.