all right guys welcome back to yet
another Friday car video it's your
boy have you seen that video it's like
the universal the longest it's your boy
and then it's like 2 minutes what it's
the longest yeah boy not it your yeah
boy I thought you said it's your boy no
no it's yeah whatever yeah buddy
remember that stop there's this one girl
that we went to high school with and
like are we doing this no we can't yeah
no don't do that all right guys her
beauty is crazy I watcha from the crab I
wrote a couple things down that were
just in my brain that I thought of I
love
Citrus anytime I can get my hands on a
citrusy fruit I want it the juice the
flavor it's delicious oh God like a
lemon what's considered citrus lemon
lime grapefruit orange grapefruits in
there I think so of course it's just a a
grapefruit is a big orange wrong Big
Orange okay it's a grapefruit yeah but
it's like in the same Orange not it's
citrusy I don't correct I don't buy that
I I just like I could I would I could
eat a lemon hole like peel the lemon and
eat the whole entire thing okay Google
search it that's really sour that's
really sour would you rather eat 10
limes or six
lemons six lemons I don't know limes are
less is it it's sour I always get sour
and spicy confused you're an idiot no
I'm not it's yep you're probably the
only [ __ ] ever not true
yesterday when we were doing the
In-N-Out thing the In-N-Out thing I
almost called the pepper sour you're a
[ __ ] idiot yeah that's real that's a
common mistake I make I was you're wrong
no it's not it's like just like one of
those things that's like oh they're both
describing things they're both it's
completely different sour and spicy are
EX on like full opposite yes but they're
both describing food words thank you so
punch punch and kick are both different
way not true not true that's basically
what he's doing say
yeah but you can mix those up because
they mean the same thing spicy and sour
they don't no they don't punch and kick
don't mean the same oh I I I don't know
why I thought you didn't say punch what'
you think he said I thought I was
thinking of fruit punch I think oh my
God oh my God I don't even know if what
just occurred made sense I don't think
it well now that I look back on it it
makes zero sense but when when it when I
was in the moment of what I was saying
it made perfect sense another thing I
wrote down if you litter pick that up
what are you doing throwing your trash
onto the the ground the highway the like
if you litter or like if you leave trash
out pick that up for me what the [ __ ]
are you doing dirtying the Earth you
chum no I'm not even like that I'm not
even like at trying to save the Earth
folk I'm just think well no I am I
didn't ask I didn't ask I'm just saying
more along the lines of like you have
trash how do you feel things that are
biodegradable big fan love that love it
are you cool if somebody litters that
though oh like an orange peel sure go
for it well that's good for the Earth
actually that's compost you're compost
if I'm with someone and I just met them
and they litter and they throw their
trash on the ground there's I I I want
to leave you faster than I've done
anything ever I want get away from you's
the most what's the most that you would
litter like on a bad day like if you had
to litter if I had to litter something
it would be like a a a thing that has
some stupid [ __ ] watch it's not stupid
at all go ahead you're just you think
what I think you're the type of guy
would be like if I were to litter
something I'd do 100 lb ice because the
ice will melt into the water and then
the water will help the Earth like
you're just like always on some dumb
[ __ ] thanks I'm always on some dumb [ __ ]
you are if I had finish your thought
this is the Box mat I think right here
slightly outside the box answer this
question I would say if I had to litter
something it would probably be like a
bottle cap if I like dropped it I might
not pick it up nope if I had to litter
something it would be a um it would be
like a a water bottle or something with
liquid inside if you can't find the cap
cuz then it could has spill potential
like if I'm going to LIT or something
it's cuz it has like spill potential or
ice cream like a like a like a ice cream
I just jumped ahead to the next sentence
I forgot to finish the first one even
like I would never get rid of like a
paper bag full of junk what are you
talking about this is like a fear of
mine that's probably nobody else has
okay when I go to like CVS or like
Walgreens or
something it's mostly it's CVS now when
you go you can buy whatever you wanted
to self checkout and then they give you
the option no receipt or print receipt
and I always said no receipt because I
know how much I get is worth and I don't
need to read it and I don't want to
throw it away so I hit no receipt and
then my biggest fear is being accused of
stealing right after that moment of
hitting no receipt from walking from the
self checkout to the exit I pray for the
day someone checks me with that [ __ ]
I've come to find out something recently
I think I'm an
oversharer really yes I think it's cuz
you never stop you have a motor mouth so
it's like I I don't think you're an
oversharer I just think you talk way too
[ __ ] much which then needs to
overshare don't I don't even think you
overshare cuz a lot of the things you're
saying isn't like you're oversharing
about your personal life it's just it's
like some Fant someone ask did you guys
watch Lazy Town as kids we did watch
Lazy Town as kids and I just remember
the Apple I don't remember the Apple at
all Apple yes that was the main part the
dude had a wall of apples no Lazy Town
yes the guy in blue was hot yeah he was
the apple eater I don't remember him
being an apple eater that's his whole
jig what search up The Lazy Town intro
right now please dear God it's he's the
biggest apple leader I just remember him
being attractive he was ugly as [ __ ]
you're wrong I remember that edit when
it was like to the windows to the walls
and it was like the Lazy Town people
dancing
yeah next not a single Apple inside
you're not no no no lazy swn has nothing
to do with apples yes that blue guy had
like a layer and he had a ton of apples
in it and he would always eat an apple
to be healthy Lazy Town blue
guy with them apples look
[Applause]
it oh my God
time for
breakfast like he has the wall of fruits
and apples remember I don't remember
this at
all how do you okay how do you cut the
banana with the things there oh is he
going to that's the susus thing I've
ever seen in my life he's just pure
throating
bananas I could ever be an adult and act
like this
[Music]
I don't think we real that was the most
unbelievable [ __ ] [ __ ] I've ever seen
in my entire life I agree what the [ __ ]
was going on I told you he Lov time for
breakfast and does a back handspring and
then he's throat goating a banana flying
out of the sky after he [ __ ] peels it
with a pingpong
racket and then it's not called a
pingpong racket whatever and then he's
like oh no apples for breakfast in my
[ __ ] Pure White modern home bizarrely
like where's your furniture throw up a
photo of someone in the sky yeah in the
sky he's like in a [ __ ] ship oh no no
apples on the ship let me bungee jump
and dive let me [ __ ] Swan Dive to the
convenient Apple Forest beneath yeah
just grab an apple oh no apples inside
don't worry the the the ship is parked
above [ __ ] Apple Andia let's just
head down there and get an Apple that
that is a little crazy it's like you
just ate an entire banana in a
millisecond in less than a second
throating it throating the banana like
it was gone in a second where did the
peel go that's what I just said I just
said yeah he did yeah if aliens came
down to earth and took volunteers to go
with them would you volunteer [ __ ] no it
depends it depends how hot the alien
pick I was about to say it depends
completely what the alien looks like
yeah there's a there's a couple I I'm
good really yeah do you think that
aliens would just look like us but be
all robotic no that's probably robots
yeah thank you robotic would be the last
thing I'd expect aliens to look no I
feel like an alien could just look just
like us except have like a weird like
antenna like one little thing that
stands
out you blow my mind every day yeah I
can't
even oh God someone said favorite melon
melon your
mothers your
mother no what I was gonna say is um is
cand op melon yes of course that's a
main Melon No yeah
that's in the name though it doesn't
have melon in the name you're my main
melon someone said what would you do if
I came up behind your car and scared the
living [ __ ] out of you I'd call the
police and get a restraining order on
your Sucker Punch you into the [ __ ]
concrete I just reverse see you pancake
on the ground you're not com you're not
going to come up and scare me dude
someone just asked if we massage each
other's feet that was such a weird thing
we used to do what like when we were
kids I'd always like put like a foot rub
on the line I'd be like no if you don't
do it I'll give you like a foot rub like
why do we want that so bad you know what
I mean I feel everyone loves a foot rub
yeah how long do you think it takes to
make minute made lemonade anything that
can make me feel just a little bit more
relaxed I
love want to know it's something that
does that for me what hot chocolate made
with milk
ew [ __ ] nasty like warm milk I can't
even hear you talking warm milk with the
hot cocoa powder and then the little
marshmallows I can get behind that that
makes me feel a little like but like it
kind of like C what is it curds curdle
curdles
guys stop dude I'm being honest dude I
can't believe that like hot chocolate
can be made by water like something
about that justes just doesn't seem
right if you robbed the Milkman would
you take his money or the milk
definitely his money why the [ __ ] would
would you take the milk give me all your
milk and you take all his milk cuz if
you take it doesn't matter if you take
it all cuz what are you going to do with
all that milk if it expires within 2
weeks you're not going to drink all of
that I'm putting that on the
shirt what what you doing with all that
milk if it's going to expire no no no no
cut it right there what you doing with
all that milk I hate that I love it
that's sick but actually though like
it's got a timer that I think the heat
in this car is making me like illusional
like you know like when people in like
the desert like they like they think
they see water cuz they're going crazy
yeah I'm like seeing ghosts right now
cuz it's so hot in here it is really hot
I see dead people dude what was that
from a little isn't that like a little
girl from like a horror movie oh my God
what's your favorite food from a
concession stand I just thought of
mozzarella sticks and had to share uh
cly pretzels curly fries pretzels never
surprise curly fries that was a great
trch clip dude um you're I'm not a huge
mustard guy on my soft pretzels mustard
I do like mustard on hot dogs though can
you stop oh I love
mustard no you don't someone said
Pineapple with mustard or pizza with
chocolate sauce oh I'm not eating that
[ __ ] um have you ever met someone with a
fear of
cheese no I don't hang around weirdos
literally one of my favorite things
about like that I think is just so funny
is when people ask me a triplet related
question like oh like whatever [ __ ]
some dumb [ __ ] like yeah the dumb
triplet questions like oh can you feel
each other's pain can you read each
other's mind all that dumb [ __ ] you had
each other's name tattooed on your
forehead they always are like oh it's
probably so annoying like you probably
get this all the time but and then they
go on to proceed to ask 15 plus
questions all the time we should do
another YouTube video I think we have
one from forever ago like the most asked
questions about triplets well it's just
like dude if you're going to say out
loud like oh you probably get this all
the time you're probably so annoyed and
then you're going to continue I've never
got that I've never understood that if
someone's like oh this is going to be
annoying but and then they proceed to do
something or like someone comes out to
me day this is probably annoying but and
then one of my biggest triplet P stop
announcing you're going Anno my biggest
triplet pet peeve is when two of us are
away from the other one where's Matt no
wrong that's one of mine well that's
that's definitely one of mine but it's
when people call us twins when one of us
after they know that we're triplets like
you know we're triplets that's fully in
your head but then you call it like I'm
I'm not a twin no I think my biggest
thing has to be everything I do and
Matt's not there they're like where's
Matt where's Matt where's Chris where's
Chris like what are people can
understand Matt doesn't leave the house
like you don't like leaving I like my
solitude o that was cool that was really
swag of you thank you you to write an
album called Solitude and release some
songs I will
only time I don't like
Solitude is when I'm with your
mother that's all I got it's the opening
line that's hard thank you how do you
feel about people that wear visors I
think the best people I'm going to be
honest spit on my chin I'm going to be
honest here I'm going to be honest here
what I'm going to be honest here love
them or hate them yeah what does that
mean Matt I I've never met somebody with
a visor or that wears visors that I like
somewhat like you're either really
annoying or you can be my best friend I
don't know why this really coexists in
my brain when I think of someone with a
visor but you're in the
way what like move over I feel like
every time someone has a visor on
they're in my [ __ ] way you know what
I mean or am I insane this is the
craziest thing like I feel like I'm
always at like a touristy place and
someone has a visor on and they're just
standing in my [ __ ] way I don't
understand how belts keep your pants up
it's cuz it's cinching your waist yes
Queen the other day I was in the living
room M and my ear started uncontrollably
ringing it's someone's talking [ __ ]
about you like Bing in my head and I it
was just my right ear I went like this
like I pinched it as if I had something
that's how I feel sometimes when you
just speak that's how I
like you got SAU you got sa play what
was I going to say that was just some
lame [ __ ] for to for someone said waffle
fries or straight fries waffle waffle
every day I like n straight I like this
is gon to sound bizarre
I like like licking the waffle fry like
my tongue goes between like each
CR you could have totally kept that one
up here I know I that one was that's
like one of the crazier things I've ever
heard like you know when you like play
with your food and you like stick your
tongue on it or something and it's like
yeah I poke my hole through one of the
holes of the waffle fry no never had no
one does that okay whatever I hate the
heel of a waffle fry the heel yes like
the edge of the potato oh [ __ ] I did it
to myself oh yes oh shut the [ __ ] up
we're talking about no no we're not no
we're not we're moving on we're moving
on how do how do potatoes get brought up
so often I know I don't know I don't
know people just constantly ask if I'm
actually gay like I need to just like
what do I have to do to prove
it what do I have to do to prove it my
God I'm like sweating like I'm like I'm
a disgusting beastly creature cuz it's
10 million de in here and in order for
my gu not to be exposed on the camera I
have to wear sweatpants so
dying I'm
dying my God I can't do that I feel like
in in another world a GU is like a nice
bag like I don't know I feel like it
really fits like if a designer brand
dropped a GU and it was like a pouch I
would be I wouldn't be surprised at
all stop talking Nick my wallet's
actually in your gu what
what your bag my wallet's in it I need
you to Gra grab me that carrots or
celery carrots carrots carrots WIP the
floor with celery's [ __ ] dead body
completely agree no way absolutely
you're dead [ __ ] wrong add a little
RIT of ranch on that carrot no I'm like
a little reindeer no I like I think I
like that I'm eating vegetables and it's
healthy but I can't taste it's just
water celery is nasty as [ __ ] and it's
not healthy it's nothing do you think
something that's at the bottom of the
ocean knows that it could get to the top
it can't why not cuz it it's living at
the isn't it crazy like if a fish is
born in water it's just like here you're
you're starting your life in the middle
of the
water like if a fish is like born in
water you're just like in that level
when you were born I was birthed I don't
remember somewhere on the land all right
get out of here bro no flash no no no no
no no get that out of my face bro get
that [ __ ] out of my face bro stop
recording me bro chill chill chill chill
chill chill chill y
[Music]