do we even have a single thing to talk
about today no nothing I like the videos
that we don't have anything to talk
about more okay cuz then I get to say
anything I want oh no that's my least
favorite thing ever I have nothing to
say so I don't know what I I don't want
to
start I'm nervous to start um anyways
welcome back guys happy Friday today's
another car video we clearly have
absolutely no topic today we just the
chocolate's really good can I have a
bite let's go what
don't say anything nobody say a word why
nobody say a word this is before the car
video and before we leave and Chris
isn't in here yet okay million dooll bet
that he's going to ask me for either a
sip of my drink or a piece of my
chocolate
bar we are what 30 seconds
in here's your piece idiot you baited me
though I know I was trying to no if you
didn't say that I wouldn't have asked no
yeah you would yes no I wouldn't have ch
you shouldn't have said that in the car
for another 40 minutes with this drink
and this I guarantee was going to be
aast or guarantee I guarante you baited
me you baited me you said oh it tastes
really good like of course I was going
to it tast good tastes great I knew
there was some sort of setup going on no
you didn't yeah I did I thought Nick was
going to surprise me with my
belt okay guys Chris Chris lost his belt
and me and Matt we were going out to eat
tonight or not me and Matt we going out
to eat we're all going out to eat
tonight and me and Matt were waiting for
Chris which is never the case Chris is
always waiting for me or waiting for
Matt every single anything Happ you know
that and and we're ready we're waiting
for Chris in his room and he's like oh
give me a minute I I can't find my belt
my first question was how many different
places are you taking your pants off
yeah not many your belt should be EAS to
find but Chris hasn't been able to find
his belt but he sleeps in my room
essentially every single night it's not
in your room and I said Chris just go
check in my room I would never wear
jeans up to sleep though you know what I
mean you take them off and go to bed
correct but if I'm going up to bed for
but I would never I would never even
walk to where I sleep to get with a with
jeans and a belt on I would never even
do that anyways Chris can't find his
belt and now he thinks that one of me or
Matt are going to miraculously surprise
him with it when it's never going to
happen his belt is gone till he finds it
I have no idea where it is where did you
take your pants off last my bedroom at
so where the [ __ ] is the belt like where
did you want me to answer the beach I
got I took him off at the beach that's
not what he the answer is not last time
I took my pants off was when I was
getting in the shower probably or like
changing into like pajamas I checked
every pair of pants that has belt loops
in my room and it's not inside of a pair
of pants cuz that happens a lot I think
I this is a skill issue well look what I
brought is my drink of choice tonight we
love it I felt the bubbles like in my
throat oh I hate the conversations that
you have with people when you're
like you know that there it's like um
there's nothing else you're not going to
ever do anything else but this
conversation you know what I mean yeah I
don't live life like that I'm an
opportunist I never see not I never see
the conversation I'm in as the possible
last one at this point no neither do I
but like I hate like the initial
conversation like like the um chitchat
you're not a chitchat I'm not a chitchat
guy you ha and that's something I've
learned I feel like this I feel like the
second time or like the like like the
it's like the more Awkward part cuz you
know them but like you're not like you
don't know everything about it you know
so it's like an awkward in the middle of
like it's like we're close to the bridge
yeah where what's going on what are you
do you gave me a piece of that heres for
and I have so much almond stuck in my
teeth for like the little piece you gave
me and I'm like did he just give me all
nut like what happened like I just feel
like it's all like just like nuts okay
the crazy thing to me
said all night no no no he he thinks
that and finds it funny to create a
laugh I would never laugh at that no
like you gave me the littlest piece ever
and there's so much stuck in my teeth
like that's what's funny to me is just
like how did that happen what just wait
a second I have to burp and I don't want
to disgrace You by doing it towards your
direction right out there look at this
video Robbie realizes what's happening
that his wife is pois poisoning him but
he's still stationed in Germany and
wants to report the crimes in the US so
he pretends to keep drinking the coffee
that's all I needed to see this lady was
putting bleach in her coffee maker
pouring bleach in her husband's coffee
maker so he died guys I really like and
I couldn't believe like imagine marrying
somebody that's what and then they
poison your morning beverage I really
like well I just where why is there a
security camera cuz he cuz he cuz he put
it there because he caught her doing it
and every day she just slowly adds
bleach like every morning he's like set
up cameras in the house cuz now it's
like he's caught her doing it like 90
times and then she'll like go outside to
like go out and then like he'll like she
left the house I'm going to do this real
quick and he'll like Vlog his experience
and what he's not like vlogging it but
he's like filming evidence Nick it's all
evidence and hey guys welcome back to
the Vlog no cuz he's going to report all
the crimes which he did and then she got
Ed but end of like hold on and he added
water to the coffee maker and it was
like bubbles and like Suds everywhere
like like it was like soap obviously
bleach inside of
it there there it is oh I probably
shouldn't have searched that
up gave me a suicide hotline because I
said how much ble bleach do you need to
drink to die like a Coke size like a can
amount oh yeah rips right through your
stomach that's insane like if I was
married to someone oh my God God forbid
I found out that they were poisoning my
beverage now if she if he stabbed her
would he go to
jail what he's defending himself no he's
not okay okay next next next like we're
we're good what wait what the [ __ ] am I
the only one that just saw that
sprinklers no the time timer went up 2
minutes like really
fast I know I'm not tripping it went
straight up to two I feel like I'm in
Back to the Future did you see that if
you hit 86 miles right now I think we'd
go to
1950 what would you do if you went to
1950 what's the first thing youd do I
know what I'd do buy as many Cokes as I
can they're only 5
cents you're insane you're actually I go
straight to a vending machine and ball
out give me all the soda I wonder how
much a case of 12 was if soda is five
wait that's actually crazy that I just
thought about no no it's not yeah it is
like a a soda can from a vending machine
is a dollar but a 12pack from the
grocery store is like six or like five
where are you going what grocery stores
they're like nine now no way yeah yeah
how much is a case of soda what are you
what are you using a
walkie-talkie how much is a case of soda
over like sounds like some's going to
reply through there
$10 I don't like that at all it's not
even a deal anymore like I remember when
I it was never a deal deal inflation yes
but like if I were to own a vending
machine now I'd have to buy so much bulk
soda to profit from my thing if I'm
selling them for a dollar which I feel
like is classic like every soda used to
be a dollar I miss so I can go to a
convenience store and get a drink for $1
bill now it's like I got to dig for like
50 cents never have it that's another
thing if something is a $1.75 just
charge me $2 I don't want the quarter I
just can't believe I just can't believe
we've gotten to a point where there
where like there's like cashless places
like I go to pay cash and people are
like oh we don't accept this I'm like
you don't expect you don't accept money
yeah yeah that's a little insane it's
like where the [ __ ] am I am I in Mars
and I don't know how the [ __ ] I got here
you don't accept like cash
dollars I'm like everyone that's the
most ridiculous thing to me when you go
to pick cash oh we're like a we're do
cashless service now I'm like
what you don't human you don't expect
USD currency craziest the craziest thing
is the craziest thing is you can afford
it you have the you have that is money
that's valuable you would walk out of
there empty-handed it's just crazy to me
that a debit card has become more
valuable than if I had a $100 bill the
bank and I went somewhere I love when
like a place is like oh we don't accept
50s or hundreds it's like oh there all I
have and they're like yeah we don't
accept hundreds it's like okay thanks
for the free
groceries the fact that you don't have
enough money to give me like a skill
issue sounds like that's your fault tell
your manager to open their wallet you
need some more money C no the cashless
[ __ ] is the craziest no that's
mindblowing that's actually mind blowing
where were we the other day and they
like Dunkin Donuts I think cashless
Dunkin Donuts I'm like what no the
craziest thing about Dunkin Donuts was
when you order munkin and you can't what
wait what can't you can't pick the the
doughnut flavor online no one day we're
all going to one day one day everything
is just going to get charged to you as
an individual person and all you have to
do is scan a fingerprint I am jumping
like 50 years in the future that's how
it's going to work one day you know that
cuz also everywhere you go it's like you
just scan your finger and then they're
like okay you can have it and then they
charge it to your tab of Life enough
your tab of life that's going to be real
what I think of with cashless [ __ ] is
how how do like homeless people who are
literally like begging for money on the
side of the street they get cash going
how do how do they if a homeless person
ask you oh can I have five bucks so I
can go get like a sandwich and you give
the homeless person $5 to go get a
sandwich and they go to a cashless place
how how is that a thing energy drinks
only give me the energy to speak they
don't give me the energy to like move
quick and about like when I'm drinking
an energy drink all I can do is Yap more
bra they give me The Chronic fear that
I'm going to have a heart attack sh I
think the term eat the curb when beating
someone up is so funny eat no eat the
curb
no eat the curb bite the curb you you
know what it means bite the Cur no it's
like curb stomping someone thing you
don't ever say like eat the curb yeah
I've never heard hold on I search it up
um stop Googling sh your phone this
isn't funny this you're good to just
like stop and we'll change the topic
here um you want to know something
that's really frustrating to me and I
feel like I feel like a lot of people
might get might get a little upset or
disagree with what I'm about to say but
quite frankly when you say that it
really scares me no you don't have to be
worried at all cuz you're going to agree
with me 100% okay I saw an ad the other
day mhm and this girl is she goes I'm in
my graduation era right now oh my and
then it was like an ad for whatever to
like get ready for
it the same amount of time that it's
going to take you to walk across the
stage grab your diploma and get off the
stage and go home and be a
graduate I could take a [ __ ] for that
long so am I when I go and take a [ __ ]
am I in my [ __ ] era or or am I just
taking a [ __ ] [ __ ] the whole you know
what I mean so so so what when do we
classify something in activity than than
than an era I completely we need like a
timeline of I know it is an era an era
has to be longer than a year and like a
half to me a
decade I'm talking like you are not no a
insane I'm talking like I'm like Matt
can we go I'm in my wife give me a
second
you take [ __ ] to another level I would
never use it no matter what but I'm
saying if you do say era whatever I
think like freshman year sure that's one
sophomore that's another like that can
be it's all thing like that can be a
thing I don't even believe that I think
I I think you can cover it all with the
word High
School the era [ __ ] is corny it's like
what are you like counting like like
like er era to me is like an era era of
like the Egyptians building pyramids or
like the era
of US Presidency like I don't think of
like the word era is in my brain wait
hold on reset this Chris an era is a
period of time that lasts several
hundred million years correct correct
it's the largest division of time and is
made up of two or more periods for
example the I don't even the mesos zoic
era lasted 252 million
years if we in the US go in like a
drought for hundreds of years we going
to be like oh the US is in its drought
era but no need like an era of like the
era of which the US went without water
like we I just need to say like when I
saw that I got a little I got a like a
headache and a little sick and I was
like you are not in a graduation I feel
like that era is just it's just it's
that's something that I do like that I
say that I instantly regret is like
whenever I'm like oh that was like an
era of time like I instantly like I will
use that and then I regret doing it but
also like when I think of like us
touring we've gone on tours and we've
been on tour buses for a month long I
would never look back and be like oh the
versus tour era because that's still
were that's still not enough time for me
in my brain to consider that an era like
I think of era as like Mesopotamia and
what ancient Mayans and like lit like
the a like that's what I think of when I
the word erae I agree I'm think like
what was the era how long do it take for
them to build pyramids in ancient Egypt
that's where my brain goes or when like
the people are telling their kids like
get off my arm when people are telling
their like daughter or son that they're
having another baby and it's like Big
Brother Big Sister era it's like no all
right all right at that point they
becoming of you're gaining a sibling
Forever For Life yeah all right can we
stop
I like it Matt you did great today give
it up for Matt I hate when you do that
[ __ ] thank you though you were less
annoying today you were maybe we can
clap for that let's do it yeah let's
clap for that let's clap for that thank
you Chris if you were to like hit the
gas right now would
it Matt why would you do that okay okay
okay stop what stop it it's freaking oh
yeah I had one other thing um Nick hit
me again I'll kill you I thanks I think
why is it open cuz I Wasing you think
put bleach in there you'll be fine I'm
good you're
good that was the weirdest going in for
a high five only two more thirds of a
can did you see did you see how many how
how far away he spread every finger to
give me that high five do it widespread
high
five terrible horrible what were you
saying I I still have nut in my teeth
get out of here is in his nut teeth era
I actually don't want that clipped ever
cut that out in his nutty teeth era Nick
don't say that okay what's look at this
mini pizza I had the other night was it
good delicious oh my God Nick you didn't
see the guy's shirt at the bar tonight
Chris was dying laughing because we went
out to eat and some guy had a shirt on
that had six packman on it and it said
six pack p and Christmas every and there
was like one for each like thing six
pack beer like yeah what was
six pack of beers the joke is what I'm
saying
noack like ABS six Pac-Man like on his
stomach that's terrible it was so funny
what was making me laugh as he was at
like a bar like it looked like a nice
restaurant yeah it was just like a
little kid with a Pac-Man shirt on like
at a bar I had a cool Pac-Man shirt when
I was in high school dude I don't know
why whenever I see like a bush I have
the urge to jump in it oh you want what
I actually want to do that I'd be really
scared to do but i' do it for like the
bucket list put on one of those dog bite
suits and let like a dog just bite me I
would never allow do that no i' [ __ ]
killed the dog if a dog was attacking me
like I'd punch it in the [ __ ]
nosey ran up on us if we could what one
of you speak there's nothing more that I
want in my life that a pet cool my turn
do you think that if a coyote ran up on
us and was so devious and angry we could
take care of it co my turn I'd be
running how how how awesome would our
videos be if we just ended everybody's
thing with cool my turn that'd be pretty
fun if I ever need to laugh I just got
to look at
Matt I to laugh I'll just look at Mat
cuz Matt always makes these
faces I've never thought this always
like if I ever have to laugh I'll look
at the clothes you put on in the morning
I'll look at your haircut no it wasn't
like a mean thing it's just like you
always give me this look of like such
disappointment cuz I I genuinely am I'm
like oh my God here [ __ ] goes again
stupid
[ __ ] like what is so funny what was the
look I'll see it okay awesome all right
I have like tears in my eyes that's good
do you have anything to
say yes I do okay all right Chuckles
let's go come on I want to do that thing
where us three like do you know those
videos of the guys that like race to
chop down like trees and stuff and then
like they climb the tree
have you ever seen it I don't care guys
already all of that for what like like
CH they chop like an edge in the tree
and they stick a sck yes but then they
like do like a chopping race like it's
like cut down the tree and then they run
and cut the ropes and then they like
like I want to do that with you guys and
like see who can do it the Qui totally
that's what you had to say yeah guys I
swear to God I'm getting Vertigo Vertigo
are you 60 I see things oh no 60 too
young are you 80 I see things vertigo
seems like a color to me like when
someone's like oo I have vertigo I'm
like oh my God a cute top in like a
vertigo color sound to me it sounds like
a purpley red I don't know what I don't
know what it is I see things move in the
corner of my eyes all the time 24/7 I
don't know if I'm paranoid maybe you see
dead
people I want to start like buying
flowers and putting them in a nice
vase hey guys the camera just died but
we were basically at the end of the
video anyway so they sound like really
boring do you want to say it what's up
guys we just finished the video
essentially but the camera died right at
the same time unfortunately but we were
done talking anyway
so what I just can't believe the [ __ ]
y'all give me [ __ ] for you talk like
this like a robot who's reading a poem
[Music]