[Applause]
First in the tank are sisters seeking to
share an old family recipe with the
world.
Hi Sharks. I'm Casey and I'm Vanessa.
We're from Boston, Massachusetts and
we're the two sisters behind Jaju
Perogi. Today we're seeking $300,000 for
8% equity in our company Jaju Perogi.
Wow.
Okay, I'm actually not a
perogi. So, Sharks, do you know what our
love language is? It's perogi. Perogi
are Eastern European dumplings
traditionally made with potato, cheese,
and dough,
boiled, and fried in butter. Growing up
in Western Massachusetts, we always had
perogi from our grandfather's deli in
our freezer. There was no mac and
cheese. If we were hungry, grab perogi
and fry them up in some butter. When we
went off to college in Boston, our mom
would hand deliver these same perogi to
our dorms and all of our friends would
ask, "Hey, where'd you get those?"
Inspired, we dusted off our
grandfather's handwritten recipes and
got to work creating Jaju perogi. We use
the same ingredients our grandfather
used. Our dough tastes like it was
rolled out on the kitchen table. Our
perogi are pre-boiled, flash frozen, and
ready to eat in 10 minutes. They're
great for families and individuals
alike. So Sharks, who wants to come
smell like butter with us and make
perogi a household staple? In front of
you, you'll find our lineup of flavors.
Potato and cheese, sweet potato,
caramelized onion, jalapeno, cheddar,
loaded baked potato, and kbasa red bell
pepper, as well as with some sauerkraut
and sour cream for dipping. So Vanessa,
I'm Eastern European. If I had if I was
on my deathbed and God said to me,
Robert, you can have one meal, it would
be perogis. Oh, I grew uping I grew up
in progress. I grew up in Pittsburgh.
Yeah. Yes. All right. Here we go.
This Wow. is a good perogi. Yum. Let me
just tell you, one of the beauties of
perogis is it's greasy and gooey. This
loaded baked potato is greasy and gooey.
I mean, it's so good. Thanks. It has a
lot of umami. Vanessa, why is it called
ja zu? It is not a Polish name. So, Jaju
is the phonetic spelling of grandfather.
So, in Polish, Jaju is like an
affectionate way of saying grandfather.
Is that your grandfather there? Yes, our
grandfather is here. Um, so the whole
inspiration for this business is that we
grew up around his deli. In 2016, we
went back to the deli, took our
grandfather's handwritten notebook with
all the delies from like 1960 and
started tinkering around. And we didn't
really know what to expect. The first
market we went to, we brought 40 boxes
and we sold out in an hour. We're taking
names, phone numbers, addresses, like
trying to deliver. But up until the end
of last year, I mean, it's still the two
of us. So, we're in 2500 stores and it's
been the two of us, no brokers. No
brokers, nothing. Wow. That's good for
you. Let me give let me give you some
good news cuz I've done a lot of
research in this space. Pot stickers,
dumplings, perogis are the fastest
growing convenience food in America
right now, beating pizza growth. Yeah. I
invested in it into Brooklyn Dumplings.
When I saw the growth numbers, I
couldn't believe it. And you're in the
frozen section. Yeah. So, and who are
you in? Do you mind staying? So, we're
nationwide with Whole Foods, uh, with
Sprouts, and then we're in Mom's
Organic, we're in Harris Teter, we're in
Fresh Market. Our sales this year will
be 2.7 million. Are you guys profitable
with that? So last year we actually lost
um $100,000 and we would have been
profitable, but we um we didn't
negotiate for our contract with a large
grocery chain like we should have. We
were very emotional about getting into
the chain. I knew middle of last year
that we were going to run out of cash.
So I knew that that was the first time
we had to go raise money. Obviously had
no idea how to do that, but my back was
against the wall. So, I felt like at the
end of last year, my organs were like
falling out of my body because cash flow
is such a problem like with food, right?
Like you put you have you're growing and
you're growing every year and then and
there's no money. Do you have money?
Exactly. So, last year um we raised
$400,000 at a $2.25 million valuation.
So, you've given away about 20% of the
business. 18. And Vanessa, today your
valuation is what? 3.75. 3.75. So in
less than a year when we raised money,
we were not national with Whole Foods.
We are officially national with Whole
Foods and so we're projected to do 2.7
2.8 this year. We've been in Whole Foods
for 3 weeks nationally and we are moving
like between 12 and 15 bags just
starting without any demos, nothing a
week. That's very high. Are you
impressed by that? Yeah, it's very
solid, but I'm not sure that it
justifies that $3.75 million shark.
Listen guys, um I don't see it as the
right business for me right now. So, I'm
out. Thank you, Lori. Per package, what
does it cost you to make and what does
it cost you to what do you sell it at
wholesale? Okay, so for the retail bag,
um it's $3.89 for the bag to make and
how how many frog is in it? There's 12.
Okay. Um, and then the cost to the
distributor is 633. Wow. That's not
great. That's not great margins. That's
not great margin. What is the sell at
retail? Um, suggested is $9.99 to
$10.99. That's your problem right there,
isn't it? Cuz you don't have a lot of
wiggle room. You need to knock off 35%
off your manufacturing costs. This is a
great product. I love them. I eat too
many of them. That's part of the
problem. I balloon to 600 lb. I have no
willpower when it comes to stuff like
this. And I'd rather be a a customer
than an owner. So, for those reasons,
I'm out. Ladies, I'm going to crown
myself the perogi king. Yes, I love
them. Couldn't love him more. Here's my
offer. If my fellow friend and shark,
the food king, Daniel, goes in and he
wants me as a partner, I will go in with
him. So, if you can talk him into it,
Yeah, we I'll come along.
Two sharks are out. Robert is interested
in Casey and Vanessa's frozen perogi
business, Jazu, but he wants to partner
with Daniel for his expertise in the
food space.
Guys, you got to talk Daniel into this
deal. I I am so excited about
everything. I just think we need a food
guy in this. That's how we when we heard
that you were a guest shark, I like
cried. I've always admired and wanted to
work with you. Keep going. Keep going.
And like yeah, I've watched you from
afar and like what you did was kind and
then you sos and like but I think you do
this deal with them and we will find a
way to cooperate together and introduce
them and then if it makes sense we join
forces and if not my my friend amigo
they they cried they cried their heart
out. Are you not human? Did you watch
the episode last season where I did a
deal with Toasted? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So,
it's a sister pair like you. In some
ways, it' be kind of fun to do the
sisters frozen space. In other ways, I
feel like it might be competitive
because No, I
um I really don't think it'd be fair to
my partners at Toasted to do this
without certainty that that it won't be
seen by them as competitive. We think
you'd be a great partner, though. We do.
And it's tricky because I do think there
could be synergies, but I am not sure.
So for those reasons, I think I'm out.
All right. Okay. Thank you. Thank you,
ladies. I Daniel's out. I'm out.
All right. All perogis lead to Mr.
Wonderful. That's what happens. Here's
my offer. Listen carefully to it cuz
it's the only way I would do it. I work
with the largest c-ackers and
distributors. Number one. Number two,
Luten Libre makes the most inexpensive
pot stickers, dumplings, and perogis.
That's how you would get your cost down.
I own that business. I bought it just to
give me vertical strength in Brooklyn
dumplings. Those are dumplings. They're
all the same. We'd add this to it. I
don't know how tied you are to Jadu or
not, but I'll give you the 300,000. I
want
20%. I have the distribution. I have the
c-acker. I have the protein maker and I
didn't bring up the fact that I do a lot
of sales on QVC as Chef Wonderful in
this category. In fact, I own this
category on QVC. You don't own perogis.
They're all the same. Pot stickers,
perogis. Listen, you understand what I'm
talking about. The manufacturing of this
category of convenient food is all done
in the same mold factory. Whether it's a
perogi, whether it's a pot sticker,
whether it's a dumpling. I have a
question. What if I went in with Kevin?
No, I don't want that. Lori. Lori, will
you make an offer? What if I went in
with Kevin? No.
So, the offer that we have right now is
because we have a lot of chatter is a
20% for 300,000 and then you want to
take the production to the the place
that you No, I want you to meet the
management Brooklyn Dumpling and you
decide which of the elements you're
going to use. I don't want to do the
deal unless you're using my
infrastructure. Otherwise, what am I
doing this for?
When you see the synergy of what they're
building over there, you'll realize,
wait a second. I want to get into the
stores across America. I want Walmart. I
want Costco. I want it all. By the way,
you've achieved something. Was it 2100?
You have 2500. That's nothing. So,
because you're bringing us into the
infrastructure, would you be willing to
do um $300,000 for 10%. Why would I do
that? It's a plugandplay, right? I'm the
only offer you
have. No, I I appreciate it, but the
answer is no. And Robert, you're
completely out. I can help you eat them.
Sometimes it's really great to do deals
with other sharks, but I have everything
you need. Everything. What do you want
to do?
I think uh I you know, you can speak to
the numbers, but I we think that our
valuation is is fair and that that 20%
fine is too much to give up. That's how
we feel right now. Yeah, good for you
guys. Good for you guys. You guys are
very impressed. You will do great. Okay.
Well, thank you
guys with us. Good luck.