Next into the tank is a nutritional
product from experts in physical
fitness.
[Music]
Hey Sharks, I'm Brandon Faulen and
Sharks. I'm Jay Cutler, fourtime Mr.
Olympia and this is Daisy and this is
Capone and we're here seeking $50,000
for 10% of our company. Sharks. Pet
owners like to treat their pets like
they're their babies. Case in point, and
we love to share everything with them,
including peanut butter. Unfortunately,
most commercial brand peanut butter is
full of things that just aren't good for
these little guys, such as salt, sugar,
hydrogenated oil, and even xylitol.
Sharks. For over 20 years, I compete at
the highest level in professional
bodybuilding. I paid attention to
everything I put in my body, and I
thought, why not for my babies? Also,
introducing Jay's Pet Butter. So Jay's
Pet Butter is a unique line of pets safe
peanut butter made with the best
ingredients such as glucosamine for
joint health. Banana, blueberry, sweet
potato, vitamin E, and biotin. All to
make our pets happy and healthy. You can
use it as a healthy treat, a food
topper, a cover for medication, or a
distraction while bathing. The
possibilities are endless. And Sharks,
it comes in four unique flavors. And
listen, my happiness is my pets. I do
everything with my pets. They travel
with me, so why not? Treat.
Let me try some. All right. Oh, yeah.
All right. Shark. So, who's ready to
spread the love and change the lives of
dogs everywhere? Little guy.
I twice the size of his body.
Jay, I don't I don't think you came out
with a big enough. I don't I I don't
think people I mean everybody watching
will I mean you're Jay Cutler. Like you
are the man. I know. He's a beast. That
picture of you was insane. Jay. Yeah.
Jay, how many years ago was that? Is
that real? 2009. Oh my god. How many
championships have you won? Four. Wow.
That's insane. That's incredible. Wow.
All right. I I probably missed half the
pitch. There you go. So these are them.
So we have three. Clearly Clearly though
for humans, too. Yes. So it's it's human
safe as you saw. I mean, this was his
secret all along. Um, and we encourage
you to try them. Everyone talks about
essential fats and things that are good
for you. And that's one thing. We've
added a lot of things in this product
which I took as supplementation. I mean,
I'm an owner of a supplement brand, a
very large supplement brand. What's that
brand? It's called Cutler Nutrition. I'm
very active on social media. I have
about 16 million social followers. A lot
of it's educational, whether it's
nutrition or training. Does that
translate well into selling peanut
butter for dogs? Well, everyone knows me
really for my dogs. I mean, the dogs
have their own Instagram. I
see. And by the way, Jay, this is really
good. Which one you have? Which one you
want? I have the sweet potato blueberry.
I use this instead of using any kind of
other peanut butters. So, why couldn't
you just feed them peanut butter? What
makes this special and unique is the
fact that we do put the additives that
are good for their health. You know, a
lot of people give their pets vitamins
and minerals and special foods and stuff
like that, but this was something
unique. And with his background, you
know, in in nutrition, it it made sense
to put the two together. Let's talk
about the business. What does it cost to
make this? What do you sell it for? Sell
it direct? Is it in retail? Let's get
into it. Uh, so we started the business
last year. We had success right out of
the gate. We did some launches to see
how it would do. Again, getting into a
pet product. We wanted to see how his
market and my market at the same time
would. Brandon, we didn't ask what do
you mean your market? So, I'm an
influencer also. So, I have a following.
I had a a base in the peanut butter
industry. Uh, I ran a company for 3
years. I had some success with that.
But, your influence is concentrating on
what area? Fitness and lifestyle. Um, I
I I show a lot of my my relationship
with my son. I have a six-year-old son.
He's There you go.
I'm not a slouch. He's being humble a
little bit, guys. No, man. You look
great, baby. Look at that, buddy. Okay.
So, I mean, you guys are very credible
from this perspective. Keep going on the
business. So, we launched in in
September and we had a success right out
of the gate. Uh we had Hi come to us
right away and they wanted to put us in
some of their test stores to see how we
would do. And then we had a big big box
um warehouse come to us right away. What
did you sell it for? Uh we sell them for
$14.99. Wo.
Um that's expensive. Yes. What's a
normal cost? Peanut butter a high-end
jar of peanut butter will sell within
that range. So what's it cost you to
make this $14.99 item? So currently it
cost us $310. Oh, those are lip smacking
margins there. So, the thing that
happened up front is we had a little
success with with HY. Okay, we're in 80
stores. Then we landed some smaller
nutrition stores and then from there we
got the call from the big box warehouse
and they said, "Look, we're really
interested in you for 80 of our
warehouses in the Northwest region of
the country." The order itself could go
anywhere from $500,000 to a million
dollars. So, Brandon Jay, where are your
sales up to date? Our sales up to date
are um $39,000.
Oh. And and what period of time was
that? In about a 10-month period. Well,
here's a question. Jay, you said that
you have 16 million followers on social
media. Have you put out any videos, any
postings saying, "Hey, check out my
Jay's." We we have and we've had great
success with that. Um is that how you
got the 39,000 in sales? Mo mostly, but
we just were having delays in shipping.
We just weren't ramped up enough. You
know, for me, the most interesting
question is, if Mr. Wonderful starts
calling you cockroaches or anything like
that, will you demonstrate some of your
prowess? I'll put them in a head box for
you and you can you can take care of
them from there. I agree with you. Dogs
love peanut butter and I agree with you.
Sodium is not good for the dogs. Well,
it's it's a good opportunity that you
take. Have other people uh entered this
space? There's a few other companies out
there. The largest uh actually contacted
us asking if they could cack for us. Um
they are a smaller company and they seem
to be happy with what with that. So you
don't have any large competitors. No.
Jay, you have a you have a really
successful supplement brand which
basically you're looking at the same
profile of a consumer, right? Somebody
who wants Yes. Which I have not even
tapped that market. Why aren't you
putting it through that distribution? It
it's a little different. And we just
have not put those wheels in motion
because of the manufacturing has been
our biggest hiccup. I can do supplements
all day long, but was a little different
because of where it was made. Yeah,
guys, look, I think it's a great
product. I liked it, right? But the
challenge for a product like this, it
takes time for pet owners to really
appreciate the benefits. So, I see this
more as a slow burn product as opposed
to an investable product. So, for those
reasons, I'm out. Thank you. Thank you.
Unfortunately, I don't eat peanuts. They
don't really agree with me. I do have to
love and I think participate in what I
really get involved with in a business.
I wish you good luck, but I'm out.
Listen, guys. Um, it's an honor to meet
you. Those pictures are very impressive.
I'm a little bit intimidated that uh if
we disagree, you might put me on the
headlock, but in all seriousness, this
is just not my type of business. So, for
those reasons, I'm out. Thank you. Hey,
my my biggest challenge is uh I'd be
doing this just for training.
All right. You know, there's nothing I
can do here in this one. I don't think
you need a shark. I'm out. Thank you. So
guys, I don't see it as a company. I see
it as a product within your sphere of
influence because clearly you're a very
successful guy in the supplement space.
So it's very difficult to invest in this
as a business. However, the direct to
consumer play is a very good business
because I think your customer
acquisition cost given you have 16
million followers is going to be low.
I'll do the deal 50,000. The margins are
good enough to give me a royalty. No
equity. I'll do it for a buck a jar.
Buck a jar? Yeah. How long? In
perpetuity. You guys came in here to the
Shark Tank. Everybody said, "No, I don't
see it." I see it. I'll do the deal for
a royalty. What do you say, guys? day.
[Music]
Probably not something we'd like to do.
We appreciate the offer.
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much. I appreciate it. Would you like to
counter, man? You can counter to say,
"Look, you know, we'll do that till you
get two times your money back." Or
Why would I do that? Cuz you get two
times your money back and you get to be
friends with Jay. Oh, I make $50,000.
I'm thinking about doing it just because
I like these guys. Just do the deal you
guys think is right.
Yeah, it's that's not the right deal for
us. I I thank you for the offer. Thank
you. Thank you guys. All right, guys.
Good luck, guys. Appreciate it, man.
It's a pleasure to meet you. Thank you
so much. Thank you.
We wanted to present a great product. We
believe in the product. I know that it's
going to be successful. Uh, and you
know, we couldn't get a deal done with
the Sharks, but we're gonna make it
happen. I hope he comes back and kicks
your ass, Kevin. That's what I was
hoping for.