[Music]
Hello Sharks. My name is Derek Burr and
I'm from North Adro, Massachusetts. I am
the president and CEO of Quickhand
Curtain Rod Brackets. Now, I'm here
today seeking an $80,000 investment in
exchange for a 20% equity stake in our
company, Sharks. As a police officer and
a former Marine, I faced many challenges
in my life, but none mightier than
hanging a curtain rod. Now, our unique
curtain hardware is going to change the
way that you hang your curtains, making
old curtain hardware obsolete.
Introducing Quick Hang curtain rod
brackets, one-of-a-kind patented curtain
rod brackets that you can use to hang
your curtains in a matter of seconds,
leaving no visible damage. Now, our
proprietary brackets set themselves
apart from anything else on the market
by eliminating the need for nails,
screws, drilling, measuring, or marring
up the face of your woodwork. Now, we've
taken the trouble and aggravation out of
hanging your curtains. Allow me to
demonstrate just how simple it is to
install our curtain hardware. Blink
sharks, and you might just miss it.
Give it a few taps on this
[Music]
side and a few taps on that side.
You just tap it and you're done. It's
that easy. Now all you have to do is
hang your
[Music]
curtains. Sea Sharks, I wasn't lying
when I said they install in seconds. No
fuss, no mus, and no plaster dust. But I
know what you're probably thinking right
now. Will they hold? What I'm going to
do is I'm going to hang two 10 lb bags
of potatoes from the curtain rod. I
often do that.
Sharks hang curtain hardware is the
fastest, strongest, and simplest way for
you to hang your curtains. So, don't
leave me hanging out here all by myself.
The window of opportunity is open for
you to invest in our company. Thank you
for your time and I'll now pass out some
samples. Cool. Good job. I love the
demo. Very effective. So be very careful
because there's very sharp pins on
these. But Lor's are the white. The
white. Thank you. Thank you, Mr.
Wonderful. Of course, you get gold.
Thank you, Damon. Silver. Thank you,
Mark. Are we going to do it? Yeah. Thank
you. Thank you. This is a very thin hook
here. Correct. What about curtain rods
that are one to one and 12 inch in
diameter or larger? Do you have
different sizes of this? We do have
different sizes. So right now we can
have we can hold curtain rods from/ in
all the way up to an inch. What why
don't you have the capability of going
bigger? Basically my dad started this
company and he gave the customers what
they wanted. But this is a piece of
metal right that's like stamped formed.
So why couldn't you just form it to be 1
and 12 in? I mean it's it's very
possible. It's just the tooling is
expensive to do that. So we're just
working with what we have right now.
Correct. And your dad started the
company. He did. Is he still part of the
company? Uh, unfortunately, we just lost
him this past April. So, uh, I'm sorry.
My dad was in business, uh, was in the
jewelry business his whole life, and he
worked for a gentleman that had a
similar idea. So, my dad started a
little company on the side, started
selling them, and he started having some
success. So, my dad went back to his
boss and said, "Well, what if I go out,
I apply for the patents, I get the
inventory going." So, my dad's boss
basically laughed at him and said,
"You're never going to make any money.
Go ahead. And that's the wrong thing you
say to my dad. You never challenge my
dad because he's going to prove you
wrong. And so he started the business.
He did. You have how long ago? 2013. And
he was so proud of those patents. And
Derek, what are your sales? It's been
about 3 years. 120,000.
All right. What are your sales just this
year? And what were they last year? So
this year, year to date, we're uh
31,000. Last year 42,000. And what do
they sell for and what do they cost you
to make there? Singles uh landed are
$3.15. We sell them for $10.95. Doubles
are $4. We sell them for $17.95. How do
you sell them, Derek? Everything's
online. So for my website, eBay, and we
just signed a deal with House. So what
do you do full-time? Cuz obviously
$31,000 is going to pay the bills,
right? So full-time I'm a police
officer. And who's running the company?
I am. But Derek, you're making money. I
mean, your margins are good. On the
31,000 you probably made what 18,000
something like that. So, off the 31,000,
we've uh made about 7,000 because I've
been trying to grow the brand. The
business was in my dad's apartment. I
got us into a warehouse space. I started
having the packaging done. So, the real
issue about getting this in broad
distribution is getting the packaging
right to tell the story of what this
does, which is going to be one
challenge, and then getting a
distributor that sells curtain rods,
right? Sell them
together. But the trouble is, you're a
full-time and thank you again for your
service. police officer. You're not,
this is not a crazy deal. It's not
overvalued or anything. It's just who's
going to do the work. You're looking at
him. See, me running this business is
the one last link to my dad. This
business meant everything to my dad, and
this makes me still feel close to him.
So, I would retire from the police
department to run this business.
Wow. Dan, I got to ask you a question.
Um, are you motivated to do this because
it's in his honor or are you really want
to grow this business? Because those are
two different things. I'm passionate
about the business because it was
started by my father and my mother and
this is the only thing that she has left
of my dad. This is the only thing I have
left of my dad. So, this is basically
everything for us. Would you have the
same motivation to go on with sales of
30 40,000? You can't live off that. But
Kevin, with all due respect, this is
only with me doing this part-time. If I
had a shark behind me with the marketing
and exposure, this I have a I have no
doubt in my mind at this point, it would
take off the way you would expect it to
because there's still blocking and
tackling that has to take place. Right.
Right. And so, while what you've
accomplished is phenomenal, what your
dad has accomplished, but at the same
time, you're not you're not investable
yet because you're still figuring all
this out. I I don't think you're ready.
And and honestly, it's not my
wheelhouse. It's not really my strong
suit, these types of products. So, for
those reasons, I'm out. Thank you. Thank
you. And look, people have been doubting
me my whole life. People told me that I
would never make it through Marine Corps
boot camp. Told me I didn't have what it
took. Said I was too small. I served
four years honorably as a United States
Marine and I earned a Navy and Marine
Corps achievement medal. People said I
would never become a cop. Said it was
not possible. I've been on the police
force now for almost 5 years.
I continue to chase my dreams. Good for
you. To honor your father is a beautiful
thing. And you've already done it.
You're you, right? So, I think here I
would take pause and stop and think
about is this the life that you want to
live dayto day because it's a huge
commitment, right? You have four
patents. To me, it's a licensing play,
right? And getting somebody to buy that
and then actually they have the manpower
to put it everywhere to me would be the
greatest legacy you're ever your father
ever had. Right. And I for me I know
what it would take. I mean it's huge.
It's huge amount of effort.
Um for those reasons I personally need
to be out. Thank you. There's a theory
out there that I need to quit my job and
I need to just go you know all out. And
what you do is then you you can't pay
the bills and then you can't put any
money into the business. You need to run
this business, but I don't think you
need to quit your job either.
It wouldn't be in your best interest for
me to help you because you need to
slowly grow this. So, I'm out. Thank
you.
The right path here is going to find
that that licensing deal that Lorie
suggested to you, right?
You want to make him proud, go get a
royalty check of 50,000 a month because
you have these patents, right? That's
the gift you really.
It's one of those deals that it's it's
just a beautiful story, but as a
business extremely hard to invest in.
I'm sorry, Derek. I'm out.
Derek, I I love the dream. And you have
great purpose. Great businesses are
started with great purpose. You know, my
dad was thrown in jail 23
times. And uh when I was 21 years old, I
was uh I didn't know what I want to do.
I was a bit of a mess. Partying, hang
out. People say, "What do you want to do
with your life?" I go, "Ah, it doesn't
matter." My dad sits down with me and he
says, "I went through hell so that you
could have the opportunity I never
had." That was it. That was it. And for
the rest of my life, people said, "Oh,
how do you work so hard? You only sleep
3 hours a day. It must be hard." And I
always used to say, "Anything I do in my
lifetime will never be as hard as what
that man went
[Music]
through." But you've got to have
something that you can apply that to in
order to build a bigger business. I
wouldn't quit the job today. The price
point is just too small. But maybe
you'll figure it out. I I can't be in
today, but I wish you all the best. I'm
out. Thank you all for your time. Derek,
can I shake your hand? Sure. Thank you
very much. My pleasure. Thank you very
much. Wish you all the best. Thank you
very much. Congratulations. Thank you,
Derek.
It's a good guy right there.
Yeah, I'm disappointed. I got a little
knocked down today, but my dad never
gave up on this product, and neither
will I. I'm going to definitely prove
them wrong.