The school doesn't like AI. They don't
really allow it technically. But what I
think is over the past few years,
there's been the rise of AI products.
Naturally, over the past couple years,
we all use AI on a daily basis at school
like notes sometimes or for like general
answers. And I think the rise of AI like
in schools like uh try CBT and those
types of things. I think that also kind
of inspired me to do flow because it
opened up a new bridge. My name is
Michael and I'm the founder of Flow AI.
Over the past few months, I've been
building something by Lucer, a general
AI agent that actually gets things done.
From booking flights to cancel
subscriptions to making presentations,
Flo can do it all. This is one step
closer to AGI and a glimpse of the
future.
Um, my name is Michael Goldstein. I'm 13
years old. Uh I live in Toronto, Canada.
I'm the founder of Flow AI. Flowey is a
general AI agent. So it's an agent that
can do a wide variety of tasks, not only
one certain thing. So a couple months
ago, I had the idea and I reached out to
multiple developers to ask if they
wanted to help. And none of them really
said yes. I don't know, probably because
my age and a bunch of other things. So I
started building it myself using like a
bunch of AI tools to help. Um so I also
I do coding lessons now every week so I
can in the future do it myself. No help
from anyone right now. I'm actually like
a paying user. Someone else said I
should do normal a normal kid life. But
what I think is just build build
like I have a group of friends right
like our little bubble and we all are
kind of have a similar spirit for
entrepreneur. So, a project we did and
still do more of is weather balloon
launches. Um, and those are really big
balloons that go to 100,000 ft and then
come back down. And the first one was on
CNN. Yeah. For the solar eclipse, we did
it during there. And I think it's fun to
see it actually working. So, my friends,
they they they know I have this a
spirit. So, they weren't that surprised.
And I think my family, I think it's the
same. My family knows that I have this
type of spirit. Uh so I think um they
weren't surprised also when I launched
it. They were very excited and happy and
I don't know if they expected it to work
also.
I had extracted all the emails of users
from Subbase and I sent an email to
everyone giving them everyone a discount
and I woke up and I got a response from
one person who was saying the code
wasn't working.
Um, so I had to fix that glitch and I
responded and then I got the message
from Stripe. I got my first sale. It
happened when I was walking downstairs.
Um, so I was very excited. I told all my
friends and family and parents. So I ran
into my parents room. I was like, "Ah, I
made it. Yay."
So uh, my experience has been good, I
guess. Um, of course there's advantages
like when I when I posted the launch
video that did pretty well and I bet my
age was a factor of that. A lot of
people are also more curious because I'm
younger. Uh, so I think it opens up a
lot more opportunities like this
interview for example. I don't know if
it would have happened if I was much
older. Um, so a lot of opportunities
open up when I'm younger. Uh, like
Founders Inc. also that's a very big
accomplishment also. Um I'm the youngest
accepted there. Also I was invited to a
summit in Paris, one of the top AI
summits. So that was that was something
that happened from the interview. And
the disadvantages are probably
um it's hard to get people to trust you
also. So on top of the advantages that
some people don't really trust me, for
example. And I guess like I mentioned
earlier, uh recruiting is really hard um
when you're much younger because I have
no capital, right? I guess my birthday
money, right? So I think that was the
hardest part. It took a couple of months
before I could recruit two developers
and one guy who does who helps with
strategy. They actually reached out to
me first, all three of them. Uh they all
reached out saying they're interested
and they would love to help. uh right I
reached out to a lot of adults and
mentors and all types of people to help
and a lot of them helped. So I think I
have to give back to everyone not just
them but everyone.
We're all interested in AI. Uh we all
use AI on a daily basis at school. Uh I
think not only my friends I think the
whole everyone at school all the kids
now use AI. So I think we're all
interested in in it in terms of my
friends and the school. There's a lot of
AI tools available but I really think we
only use one main one which is CHBT. I
think a lot of kids at school don't know
about the other tools and I think you
have to be more involved in AI to know
the other tools. So yeah I think most of
the school or the kids or my friends are
using child only which is unfortunate.
Um only recently really is when I really
learned in depth about AI and how it
works and for the idea of flow it came
when I when I realized that there's a
big gap and that there was something
that wasn't being done which is
automated tasks. Uh I think it it can
really help humans with efficiency. uh
like my parents for example, we all
waste time filling out forms. But I
think that's the biggest one because
there's not many platforms that are
doing that like claw doesn't do that or
open AAI. I think that's the biggest gap
that there is. It's the browser
automation. So I think in general by
next year I hope to have many more
features in it and I hope for it to be
more smooth of course because there's
many many bugs still which is uh going
to be fixed over time and that I think
in terms of more of the money type. I
set a goal on Twitter for $10,000 in
recur monthly recurring revenue and it
might take plenty of years. I'm not sure
how long it will take but I hope in a
year we can get somewhere close to that.
So I hope Floy is able to you know
become part of everyone's life almost
right um I think the goal that you'll be
able to do that can be automated right
we get to see how AI evolves and that
kind of stuff I think the longterm goal
for me is in some way to help people you
know give back Almost.