the world changed and the reason is AI
ignoring that change and saying we set
out to do this and therefore we going to
do this just makes no sense and it's
good to be honest with yourself when
you're changing the plan communicate
this to your investors board employees
and then to yourself when you look at
yourself in the mirror that the plan is
now a new plan and that's okay
understand how the world changes around
you to take advantage of those
opportunities now how do you take
advantage of those opportunities the
thing is that
my name is Nikita I'm CEO and founder of
neon this is my second company so my
previous company uh single store at Peak
it was valued at 1.5 billion neon is a
database company and a developer
platform where do people get databases
today they either download them and
install them themselves but neon says
we're several as postgress we're saying
don't worry about servers here's just
the URL and the URL is all you need to
know to build your application neon is
expanding its Mission from being a
database as a service to platform as a
service so back as a
[Music]
service I'm building databases all my
life so at Microsoft I joined the team
called SQL Server so when I joined
Microsoft soft person all it's an
incredible cheap but it's also a very
very old and stable product I joined in
2005 and by the end of 2005 Microsoft
released the product SQL Server 2005 the
previous release of that product was
2001 during that time there were people
that would come to Microsoft work on the
product leave Microsoft and never ship
software at all at the time I had a you
know phenomenal offer from Facebook and
then took a Facebook off offer and moved
down to the Silicon Valley at Facebook
look culture was very different from
Microsoft and the speed at which things
were happening was absolutely insane a
lot of people just committed to the
Facebook mission that engagement was a
lot higher and once I experienced it I
realized that this engagement exists in
startups and it does not exist in larger
companies naturally I was very
susceptible for entrepreneurship and
then when my co-founder Eric is like
well shouldn't apply to why combinator
and we got accepted so my previous
company uh single store at Peak it was
valued at 1.5 billion you know I spent
there 10 years when I took overover
single store we probably at a 7 million
run rate I took it to North of 20 and
then for the first time in my life the
amount of operational work reduced
temporarily I'm not the most important
layer right so you can just remove me
from the organization and the
organization will probably do just as
good and then added this to the craving
of learning breath and make the plunge
started another database company uh
which is neon that's why I left single
store and it kind of panned
out you know it doesn't matter how good
your technology is if there's no Market
fit do people want your stuff the best
feedback of course is people are willing
to buy this product right but even
before that you kind of want to to throw
it out there and see that this product
is needed by the world and then you put
all this energy to makeing that product
and making it a high quality product you
want to validate this hypothesis how can
you do that and how can you do it as
earlier in the startup cycle as possible
we started to do those things open
sources one then we put together a
website we were building in the open all
the code was available on GitHub and
moreover all the code was available on
GitHub with a very permissive license
and then about about 11 months in our
the number of GitHub stars on that
product started to go vertical meaning
if you like plot them on the line the
oldest people staring our repo which
means they kind of interest in what
we're doing and and that was our first
product Market fit signal and then we
put the website out we didn't put a
password on it and we thought we were
going to launch in about two months but
between that time and the launch
somebody leaked our website ne. on
haacker news and there was a lively
discussion you can go and find that
people going and saying well this is a
good idea or this is a bad idea and
whatnot you know think about a product
and a company like you creating your
movie and then your website is a trailer
right and that's how you kind of know if
a movie is going to be well accepted by
the audience or not because the trailer
is out and you're starting to collect
very early signal about the interest of
an audience to that particular product
or service I think that Tech is one of
the many not that many good choices
andte I think is fairly new and that's
why a lot of them were available and
neon was available as well so we bought
that one as an advice for future
entrepreneurs don't worry about it until
your product hits product Market fit
notion waso for for a long time and then
now now everybody uses
notion here's Silicon Valley it's
littered with technology that nobody
wants or needs and that's totally fine
because when you start you just don't
know and it's good to be honest with
yourself when you're changing the plan
communicate this to your investors board
employees and then to yourself when you
look at yourself in the mirror that the
plan is now a new plan and that's okay
the world is is what the world is and
the world changed then in technology the
world changes quite often ignoring that
change and saying you know we set out to
do this and therefore we're going to do
that just makes no sense but being
formal about the steps that you're
taking and the wise behind those plan
that I think is a very useful and
important thing to do and I kind of
strongly recommend everybody who's doing
that to be formal or semi-formal and it
doesn't mean that you need to like write
six-page documents it could be as simple
as like 1 2 three kind of like Tesla
right I'm going to build a rooster and
I'm going to build a Tesla S and then
I'm going to build a a mass Market Tesla
3 it could be as simple as this but then
the world changes and then introduces
for Tesla the opportunity to create full
self-driving and that becomes kind of
like a huge emphasis for the whole
company so not only you need to be
formal not only you need to be executing
very very fast you need to look around
the corners and then understand how the
world changes around you to take
advantage of those opportunities now how
do you take advantage of those
opportunities when you have your one 123
plan you architect your team against
your one 123 plan and then the world
changes and something in this world
becomes more important or becomes an
opportunity and then because the team
you build is the company you build is
another thing that V Coosa says you
might even not have the capacity to
understand how to change the plan and
even if you do you might don't have the
capacity to evolve the company into that
direction and therefore I think you must
bring people from that world that you're
locking and if the world changing in a
particular direction try to get the
people who are experts in the direction
that the world is heading because if you
don't have the right people around you
you won't come up with a good
plan the hardest things are about people
the other hard things are when things
are just not working and when the things
are not working you spend an
extraordinary amount of energy to make
them work and then they work for a
period of time and then they stop and
they stop because even either you know
have a product Market fit or technology
is not good or competition is kicking
your ass and so you're burning a lot
more money to make it work and it takes
the highquality team to work through
those moments ideally you work through
them without losing your cool that's
when then the stuff is tested and people
lose patience people quit blame each
other we had it all you know living
through this once uh hopefully had made
it a better founder and compared to
single story me seems like L smoo
sailing there's the length and then
there's the growth it only feels long if
the growth slows down or stops and then
you start looking in the mirror and
asking yourself is that what you signed
up to do is like is this grind is ever
going to stop or it's growing and in
this year we grew over six times in
revenue and when you look at this it's
like w like the scenery really is
changing and the stuff that we're doing
now is like not the stuff that we were
doing in the beginning of the year as
long as we're in that state it's forever
the fog of War usually clears as the
company goes along and right now it's
pretty thick with NE you know the
company is clearly working there product
Market fit our customers love it more
and more of them coming every day onto
the neon platform we reach into things
that we almost didn't think we would
even consider in the AI space and in the
broader platform space and if back in do
a service it's when the growth slows or
the world moves on in a different
direction or a competitor kicks your ass
that's when the music stops playing as
long as the music keeps playing I think
it's it's just a lot of fun to keep
dancing to this music