I think there is no one siiz fits all
for an exceptional entrepreneur one of
the key characteristics though that I
often see in great Founders is they have
this really strong sense of always doing
what's best for the company in many ways
can be sa self-sacrificial that they
always put the company first and the
mission first if you want to be famous
this is not the place for you being
famous versus being paid a lot versus
being having an easy lifestyle all of
which is not true
hi my name is Eric Kim I'm the
co-founder and managing partner of
goodwater capital goodwater capital is a
global Venture Capital firm that we
founded in 2014 we're entirely focused
on consumer Tech investing so today
goodwater Capital has grown to over $3.3
billion in committed Capital we're in
close to over 50 countries at this point
through our Genesis portfolio which is
over 700 seed portfolio companies and in
our core portfolio companies that's for
our early stage fund and our growth
stage fund that's about 80 companies at
this point in about 20 countries our
thesis is that consumer technology is
changing the world and there's an
opportunity to use the internet and
digital technology for good our mission
is to empower exceptional entrepreneurs
everywhere change the world for
[Music]
good I'm so thankful to my parents my
mother and father lived through the
Korean War they came to the United
States to seek a better life uh with one
suitcase uh with the little money they
had uh in their pockets uh but what they
did have was an education that they were
both trained as medical doctors at that
time the United States had a severe
shortage shortage of medical doctors and
they were inviting overseas doctors to
come even if they didn't speak English
very well I think in my school we were
the only Koreans and I remember
distinctly one day my father calling me
in to his room to his bedroom I was 12
years old old at the time that's the
same age my as my oldest son at this
point and my father just sat me and said
hey Eric I need to have a talk with you
at that time my father with these
intense tears in his eyes told me Eric
you're growing up now you're 12 years
old you're about to become a teenager
and life is going to be hard because
you're an Asian American because you're
Korean because of the color of your hair
the color of your eyes the shape of your
eyes the color of your skin life is
going to be difficult you will
immediately be discounted and I think
part of this was my father's own
experience in the workplace facing
racism uh there or uh maybe some bias as
well but he understood that for me as an
Asian-American that it was important for
me to understand that because of that
discount he instilled into me that we
really needed to be 12% 150% better so
to speak to uh really compare with our
our peers who didn't have this Asian
face or this background or so and that
really had a tremendous impact on my
life in many ways I felt a sense of
urgency that I had to perform that I had
to just be better in many ways that was
a really important lesson I think as
I've grown up and as I've matured I
realized that in many ways yes that bias
exists and yes the Prejudice exists and
and racism exists and yes education hard
work all those elements were keys for me
to be hopefully successful in life over
time what I've realized as well is that
I also need to embrace and not always
just perform for the sake of trying to
be better itself what if humility was a
superpower what if as myself I could
Embrace that and not be afraid of that
that's something I'm really interested
and excited about going forward
too as an undergrad I had the
opportunity when I was at Yale to also
intern at McKenzie and Company during
the summer so in 2002 I I graduated from
undergrad and I was expected to start at
McKenzie right away I eventually I went
back to McKenzie and spent time there
for 2 years as a business analyst and
consultant I learned a lot I did a lot
of global projects I spent over 6 months
in China I spent time in Southeast Asia
as well spent time all over Europe and
so that really helped provide a Global
Perspective which is something you see
in goodw today as well then went to
Stanford University in 2005 and that's
where I met my co-founder chihua Chen
who was class of 2006 so we overlapped
for a year so in 2007 I had the
opportunity to join Maverick Capital
they were starting to build out their
private investing practice and so myself
and a gentleman named David singer we we
work very closely together from 2007 to
2014 and during that time we invested
all over the world and uh from early
stage to late stage we were part of the
YC y commentator Venture Capital
Syndicate so we invested in every single
y commentator company to really late
stage companies as well pre-ipo
companies too and that really gave me a
sense of the Art and Science of
investing and and really to adopt an
investor mindset
[Music]
actually our first deal in Korea was
coupon it was March of 2011 and then
soon after that we invested in cacao in
their series a yeah when we first
invested in Kong they were the 28th
social commerce company to launch in
just South Korea itself we launched a
survey in South Korea and we asked
dozens of people asking them to compare
Ticket Monster we make price coupon
others your retail experience as well
and over and over again for specifically
women in their 20s 30s they loved coupon
because of their customer service why
was that so important was because it
then created loyalty that if you had
really really strong customer service
consumers would come back to you because
they knew that they would be treated
well and that was a strong philosophy
that kpong had from the first day was
how do you wow your end your end
customer if you are doing something that
the market generally agrees with that is
a really hard way to make a profitable
investment because the the rest of the
Market's already there you have to have
some kind of contrarian or
differentiated insight and usually
that's through some kind of primary
research that you've done that no one
else has done itself and that was a key
to making that investment back in 2011
caca is a really interesting story I'm
I'm very thankful to Han Kim who's a
very close mentor and friend of mine
that helped introduce me to the company
prior to that we had an overall thesis
about mobile the the power of
smartphones and this whole transition
away from desktop to mobile Computing
and how there opportunity
for gaming for Commerce for
communications to happen on mobile and
we were looking for that killer out what
prompted me to really become interested
in caca and and to seek out the company
was a really close friend of mine
actually was visiting from South Korea
at the time that person had a Samsung
smartphone and I asked her why did you
buy this Samsung smartphone and she said
so I could use caca it actually saved
her money at the time every time you
sent a text message you were charged per
text and cacao made that free buying a
smartphone which was very expensive that
upfront cost was an investment to save
money over time because it provided this
core utility to everyone to be able to
communicate for free and that was an
Insight that it really struck me is that
people were willing to buy 300 400 $500
smartphones so they could just use caca
because they were saving money on the
other end of that that love that
customer love was something we saw
tremendous potential in so I remember
approaching the CEO the founder the
management team at k C once I got
introduced I remember flying to South
Korea and practicing the night before
presenting in Korean and the next day
actually when I I visited the the caca
headquarters and there was only like 20
people I remember pitching in Korean to
the to the the team there they w't
pitching me I made this whole
presentation about our thesis and the
research we had done all the consumers
we had talked to it was in Korean so I'm
sure it was terrible and it was uh with
a lot of stuttering they were maybe were
impressed by that and uh they were
willing to take our Capital early on but
we really saw not from the outside in
but through the consumer voice the love
for the product I remember at the time
there's a lot of people who thought that
investment in caca was crazy maybe even
some of the early team members weren't
quite sure about the future but when we
talk to Consumers when we talk to people
who actually use the product they loved
it so so much often times one of the
things I love to do when I go to cities
whether it's London or New York I just
like to hang out in the subway you can
see what apps they're using just the
color the icons they're using and when
you go to Korea a lot more people were
starting to use this yellow icon cacao
and then you would talk to them why did
they use it I can save money I can
communicate with my friends there's a
group chat that becomes my community and
so that was our key Insight is that you
could scale this and create a powerful
Network effect that as more people got
on the platform it would benefit all the
pre-existing users as well that's it's a
really powerful phenomenon that
increases retention that as more people
get onto the product the product gets
better how many of those can you name
there are very very few companies that
do that and so once we saw that Insight
we felt a very strong Comm uh conviction
to invest in the company they were both
very early stage deals series a for the
caca and kind of series a plus for kpong
the returns were massive on kind of a
venture scale kind of the 100x 300X type
scales
I think most Venture Capital firms in my
experience do great work but they don't
necessarily have a strong sense of
mission and that's what was important to
us when we started goodw was to have a
really clear mission statement again to
empower exal MERS everywhere to change
the world for good good water had a
tremendous impact on the Venture Capital
ecosystem because we changed the mindset
to go from a Ecentric mindset where you
have individual venture capitalist being
celebrated for how much money they made
shifting that there's nothing wrong with
that but shifting it more to a mindset
of how can we as a vendor Capital
industry have positive impact itself if
good water many many many years from now
is known for that capital is a really
really valuable resource that you have
to Steward and that's why we're called
good water we think water is similar to
technology and capital water is the
source of life for every living organism
but the lack of water or too much water
can lead to destruction it's itself and
technology and capital is the exact same
thing that you have to Steward it it can
be the source for so much positive
influence in the world but it can also
be used for not so good things too that
technology and capital isn't always the
source of goodness in the world too so
we want to be the good water in the
Venture Capital ecosystem we also
thought that the world didn't need
another venture capital firm there are
so many great Venture Capital firms out
there sequoia Benchmark you know Excel
Partners there there are so many great
Venture Capital firms out there the
world didn't need necessarily another
venture capital firm but what if you
could create a venture capital firm that
was not only Mission oriented but
focused on consumer internet consumer
technology itself a lot of venture
capital firms at the time and still
today Diversified away from consumer
Tech they went to Enterprise SAS or
security or Hardware or climate Tech or
biotech if you think about the best
Venture Capital firms where they started
was by investing in companies like
Google like Amazon like eBay six out of
the eight large companies in the world
are all consumer tech companies like
Facebook as well not only are there
great Equity returns there but if you
own that end cut customer relationship
then you can create so much Innovation
that backward integrates all the way
into the Enterprise as well so we had
this thesis that consumer technology
consumer internet was incredibly
powerful that owning those End customer
relationships was very powerful that
would span not just social networking
not just e-commerce but that span also
Financial Services Healthcare education
all these big Industries would be
increasingly consumerized because you
could own those End customer
relationships through digital technology
that was our big thesis when we started
the firm in 2014 at goodwi our
philosophy is that investing is both an
art and a science and so we leverage our
technology and our software to get to
the truth of the science part as quickly
as possible of our 65 66 person team
two-thirds of that team are actually
data scientists product managers and
engineers and since day one we've been
building an infrastructure a software
layer to enable us to look at consumer
technology companies so we find so much
value in looking at the data being able
to have this infrastructure to see
companies on a global basis we track
over 10 million companies in real time
so we have very very accessible reports
consumer research analytics benchmarks
that allow us to understand a company we
think better than any other firm because
we have so much data around it and we
know how to apply it so when we see a
new opportunity to invest in we're very
quickly able to assess is this company
Best in Class not only on growth but
also retention customer love what's
their differentiation all the hard
science of investing we've really locked
into a very strong process and a
platform itself what's as important and
it goes with it is the art part and
that's really understanding the
entrepreneur understanding that person's
will and desire to win that person's
desire to have impact Itself by taking
all the science and being able to really
get to truth as quickly as possible then
you can spend a lot more time on
spending time with the entrepreneur
understanding their M motivations
understanding what their long-term goal
is their vision for the company so if
you have seven days in the week in the
old process it used to take six days in
the week to do all the science and then
you have one day to maybe understand the
soft part or the art we've reversed that
is that it takes one day to understand
the science part of it the analytics all
the components that you can have
software and our data platform really
understand very quickly and spend the
other six days to really understand the
entrepreneur can we partner with this
person they have a similar philosophy
around putting the company first are
they open to feedback doing reference
checks deeply those soft elements of
what makes for a great entrepreneur
we're able to spend the vast majority of
time because of this dual approach
between Art and Science and so that's
been the harded soul of good water since
day one and something we continue to
innovate on
too we interview a lot Venture Capital
Associates VPS principles and partners
one of our screening criteria if you
want to be famous this is not the place
for you the goodw approach is one that
is obsessed with finding generational
companies that will have tremendous
impact one firm that I admire greatly is
seoa capital and they had this saying
that they were just one away if they
just missed one great deal then that
would lead them to potentially being a
mediocre firm and so they had this
obsession with finding great companies
if that is someone's singular purpose if
that is their Obsession as well which is
to find great companies and to invest in
them that's what we look for in young
Venture capitals and I think that's what
young people who are looking to get into
the Venture Capital should ask
themselves is this something that I'm
really obsessed with that I would go the
ends of the Earth to I will fly over
200,000 plus miles going back and forth
to countries to visit entrepreneurs it's
a really hard lifestyle it's not
glamorous but you do it because you love
it that you are obsessed with finding
that insight about a company that will
lead to investment that no one else in
the world might see and if that's
something that young people really want
to do and they're willing to put in the
hard work to have the discipline it's
like playing a sport you have to be like
an athlete you have to be able to invest
in your craft day in day out and get
incrementally better every week and it's
not something that will ever be handed
to you maybe some venture capitalist
just get lucky that's certainly possible
but to sustain a franchise and to
sustain a career over the long term it
really takes a lot of discipline hard
work and an intensity that is driven by
a passion to find and invest in great
companies and support them throughout
the life cycle of growth I teach a class
on this at various institutions but how
do you have an investor mindset that is
a able to see the big picture always
having that big picture that home run
Vision in your mind B understand what
are the key components that allows that
to come true what do you have to believe
for that big Vision to come true C
understand what are the key risks to
those and being able to D then research
those and underwrite those risks and
ultimately e taking a leap of faith that
allows you to put it all together to
have conviction in your idea whether
you're an investor or whether you're a
Founder having those key components and
being able to break it down I think
having this mindset for the key
decisions you need to make is something
that we talk about internally we
certainly teach it for our investors and
also I think great CEOs also have this
investor mindset too because they're
doing Capital allocation and they're
making decisions so how do you go
through that framework and be able to
follow it and then also know when not to
follow it when do you know to break the
rules too that's really where the Poetry
comes up about that you can able to
innovate and create new things when
you're able to have exceptions but to do
that you actually have to know the
Frameworks and the rules first we preach
both that the Frameworks are really
helpful but also really importantly
knowing when to break the rules too is
really important too
[Music]