hey everyone
thank you
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my God
hey guys a lot of the clothes we wear
from Rags wrench and it's actually a
thrift store located in Texas and we're
in Texas imagine just right outside the
tour bus she sends us a lot of stuff to
our house and we're very grateful for it
so we're so we're stopping here and
we're gonna go shop and such so guys
we're inside we're looking at some
clothes what's your name yes mean yes
and we are inside the shop we're gonna
look around pick up some things then do
a haul for you guys and then there's
this location that we're at which is in
Austin Texas and then I have one in
McAllen
Texas yes and I'm gonna put the link
charge revenge in the description below
and I'll put like the address of both
locations if you want to come shop or
reshop you can and we're gonna look
around and show you guys what we got
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
[ __ ]
I don't understand
foreign
[Music]
what's up
all right thank you guys so much have a
beautiful rest of your day thank you
very much
[Applause]
for her again
we're at the Chicago bean and these kids
are throwing snowballs at each other
okay
not any not at me
you got me right in the face
no did you actually yeah I just got lit
up it's a big old snowball fight the
trail hit me in the head
still got evidence right there they lit
me up
yeah they got my man my man's got
dropped by it was it was a good fight
Valiant effort on both sides we hit him
so hard he put a scarf on
now we're going to lids
are we we're gonna get some hats okay
we're going to get hats up top
running Maddie's favorite part of the
day getting hats I'm so excited
Chicago
foreign
I don't look good in hats but I'm buying
this [ __ ] hat
75 80. you actually call me a cockhead
seven bro they don't have my size I'm
getting this hat oh
do you like getting that it's crazy
seven and one fourth bro all the hats in
stock that only got my size and toss
into them damn I had I don't have a
classic Boston hat yet
big head those sizes are all too big uh
stupid
watch out
kid we're in Chicago you're gonna get a
random Boston hat kid is where I'm from
okay but like we're in like forget this
when we go home most of my days you
could get this and go home
that's the seven one eight that's kind
of tight though we're going into a donut
shop right next to the lids and I bought
a [ __ ] hat crazy purchase I never
thought I'd make ever but I did
[Music]
oh
what's up
the news
do you use they're so quiet
hit the gritty
you think you can do better
what is this what is this conversation
where are we
oh my God
look just
yes
oh my God
that was crazy self-defense Riley I
thought I broke my arms
bro what the [ __ ]
my arm hurts [ __ ] you [ __ ]
it hurt bad it hurt me
don't try to hit me again
it's kind of like a funniest moments to
be because we've just been recording so
much that like I don't think he in an
edit
all right we just kind of like don't
have we didn't really plan what the Vlog
was gonna be we just recorded a lot so
that was whatever that was
um I hope you enjoyed it
I was thinking
okay
but we did 10 shows already and we have
five more
imagine looking back at that moment yes
yes but yeah we've been doing our thing
and we're excited for the rest of the
five shows again and edit
yeah eight more days that's crazy let's
see those feet Chris no what
my [ __ ] ankle's still swollen from
when I broke my foot
gritty he's literally hitting the goody
right now literally grittying
super goody super goody
super goody witty
bro thank you in an edit I don't think
he didn't edit it bro it's editing and
he think he didn't edit don't you don't
know