oh God I just wish I had a pumpkin spice
drink oh my
God that what is that is that video that
lady get hit with a shovel last time I
was here I couldn't walk by this path
cuz there was a turkey in the middle of
the road and I was just like oh my God
what did you do when the turkey crossed
the
road I'm about to [ __ ] suck the
face this way wa taking us off the trail
woohoo
wow this is like sternol aesthetic movie
really what are you taking us man I
don't know there's just like cool views
in here like we can like go this way too
hopefully we don't get
ticked guys what would you do if we just
saw like Bigfoot [ __ ] a bear like I
thought you were going to stop at
Bigfoot I would have been already the
pornographic detail I'm like oh my God
now I'm
amazed imagine we saw Bigfoot no no
imagine we saw
and he was mounting a [ __ ] bear in
the woods yeah why what do you eat
that's blue me open that mouth what
e oh my God what did you eat that's I
can tell digital footprint is never
worth that never I couldn't do
it oh what oh my [ __ ] God I'm trying
to take photos and I thought that there
was something attacking me I heard I
heard a fish he goes oh my God I did not
say yes you did I heard say it's on
camera there's some type of creature
that's living in that hole you think so
yeah cuz you can tell cuz they covered
it up with a couple leaves thinking that
they're going to get away with
it it freaks me out cuz imagine a little
rat just comes that's attached to the
tree by the way that you're yanking can
you take the phone so I can get
it like you're never going to get this
off a tree oh my God oh my God it's CRA
How much Wildlife is just around us and
we really don't know
it you know like every Who whoo whoa
whoa
whoo don't hurt the nature Chris I
understand that branch cuz it was
already falling off but be a
little oh the tree caught it wow this is
a beautiful moment I want to stand over
there so that I'm part
it who loves the fall say fall
me wait this looks like a horror movie
no around
no hey
hey hold on don't hurt
him help Nick help
Nick can you get off me help me help me
use a tree too much swag
yeah far not enough
hey oh my god get that it's not a bug I
thought it was a
bug it was a little
Flint
oh can you do
it air ball air
ball they call me Santa cuz I got that
sack on me right next sack on
we have merch going live and and because
of that we're going to we're going to
give gifts to our fans and we're going
to make them holiday
season roll the clip of me and Nick and
Michael's buying stuff for the gifts got
cute stickers yeah definitely done what
about a happy 30th birthday yeah that's
good okay 3 16 no that's fire okay um we
making progress yes yes I think these
Nick seriously those are ugly no oh
there's a Nick we should get a big d
sticker a big d sticker yeah look like
we should just put like a big D in one
of them why would we do that that's not
a sticker is it not oh it is a sticker
yeah got to get that like that though
but we can say it's for like delightful
Delight Big D for delightful yeah let's
do it yeah right but we should do it in
cursive cuz that is delightful yes Big D
for delightful yes ooh out of this world
oh that's awesome phography you did that
y remember the photography club Club
photo yeah I do
rock and roll yes super Punk putting
effort into that oh we should do a zoo
themed one because Chris CH Chris look
at the zoo because we did the we did the
zoo video no I don't like the squirrels
but I like the pigs no like we can say
like dinosaurs we hope you get your
merch and like it's
nuts
Chris we should do a funny we should no
no no you're not we should do a funny
bird one and an aquarium
one I am the king of Michael
get off of that before you get yelled
at you're s what if I jumped off you're
insane oh my God I don't like the way
that lady asked us can I help you am I
the I am the king of Michael's
CS you're going to get kicked out
here
hello okay like you're really intense
with this you know what the Big D's for
right no he doesn't know what the Big
D's for what is it f are you serious the
big de is for delightful delightful oh I
keep getting emails that people are like
trying to they keep venmoing me money
and read these like I'm not even joking
read these out loud that's serious wait
can I get a drink literally take any
precaution you need to know this is
legit to prove I'm not trying to scam
you and that I will never leak any feet
picks I just buy you're genuinely just
one of my favorite people ever so they
want your feet yeah they've been like
begging me to send feet picks and
they're they like saying they'll V me
$1,000 that's crazy like what are you
I'm say money up front money up front
send me I'm so dead ass about spending
1K for feat vids I'll literally send you
$100 up front for just a pick to start
off hit me up on snap and we'll start
talking
details I like it I like they're like
they're like they they're moving a
progression I feel like I'm not doing
that sick [ __ ] all right guys it's the
season of holiday spirit and we want to
really really make personal I gifts for
some random fans so what we did was buy
20 cards on Amazon that you can record
the messages on the inside for example
yo what's up it's Nick I hope you enjoy
this merch Matt's also
here I'm really craving pasta tonight so
basically we're going to record we're
going to record messages for 20 special
fans that are going to get a random card
in our Black Friday merch orders yeah
we're going to use the stickers that we
got at Michael and we're going to
customize some cards for you
guys oh yo it's Chris if you got this
card that that means you're the lucky
winner prepare for Max feet pick Chris
I'm not sending anybody feet picks
bro okay so
now yo it's Chris if you got this card
then that means you're the lucky winner
prepare for M
Fe I'm not sending anybody feix yo it's
your boy boy Chris I hope you enjoyed
your merch when you put that [ __ ] on
you're going to look out of this
world y it's your boy Chris I hope you
enjoy your merch when you put that [ __ ]
on you're going to look out of
[Applause]
this W that's good I hope they like this
card I think they're going to love it
Chris all right check this out I
finished the first card hope you love
the merch and then I'm going to let it
play so they ignore it yo it's your boy
Chris I hope you enjoy the rch when you
put that [ __ ] on you're going out of
this hor
it's going to make you look out of this
world from Chris hope you have a good
day and it's like so staring I love
that's a good all let me
sign card number one one out of 20
amazing here 1 2 3 squirrel
horde oh my God okay I hope this card
makes you go nuts 1 2 3
[Music]
squ perfect perfect it couldn't have
gone any better that's kind of
terrifying awesome card number two
squirrel horde is the craziest thing
ever we made this card because one of
our videos is like a
farm my card says we couldn't fit 7
million horses in an
[Applause]
[Laughter]
envelope so instead we got you this card
have a good
night are we leaving it it's
just yeah it sounds like a Clash of
Clans warrior we did a YouTube video
where we turned our house into a
barn LOL we had a lot of fun hope you
like that
video we made this card because one of
our videos is like a so
true wow Chris CHR Matt and I love it
nice okay mine says hope you have an
absolutely rocking
[Applause]
day rocking that's awesome I love it all
right we made three more cards we're
going to reveal them to each other right
now go Chris okay this is card number
six I know that this is a donkey but you
the goat all right I love you the goat
stay humble stay humble I love that
always believe in yourself another one
follow your dreams you the
goat we got you this card because you
are Delight I [ __ ] with with a big D in
it there we go you're delightful big I
got it it's
on you are delightful with a capital
D yeah I don't know I don't even I don't
know should you try again it feels like
aliens invaded our card
I think [ __ ] you so fly yeah keep
soaring oh I [ __ ] with that I love it
I'm afraid of
birds so true isn't it so crazy that you
can hear what I said right now when you
open this card but then I said but now
that you have L STP marks nobody should
be afraid of you okay that's kind of ass
kind of mid really mid it's true I hate
to get that card the fact that you enjoy
the new merch
is music to my
ears okay that was a good one way better
than Nick mine's kind of good Lions
Tigers and B you should let me love you
okay I'm not adding to that get out of
here okay lions tigers and bears and you
the king of the jungle you
no so good you need a
comma okay I feel like we should have
utilize that this can like capture our
voice and not just like yell every
[Applause]
time yeah I said you know what they say
about 30th
birthdays they only come once and it's
when you turn
I love it thank you happy
birthday to you we don't know when it's
going to be but I hope that 30th is
special for real what did the pig say
about your new merch H oink oink [ __ ]
yeah
yeah if you are having a bad
day hang in
there you just hand in there hand in
there oh my God I don't I'm dyslexic I'm
dyslexic that's really good you just got
an exclusive gift from the stera
triplets hope you like it that's really
good I'm
C hang in there wow
[Applause]
actually it kind of sounds just like a
monkey I said there are plenty of fish
in the sea but only you got this card
and there's oh Nick that's a good idea I
don't really have any idea of what to
put on this
card but this reminds me of the Gatorade
logo oh like you're insane yeah I'm sure
it does it looks just like it life moves
fast life moves fast take it one day at
a time what's the rush and it's a
turtle wow
man the last three cards you ready to
read a card full of penguin facts and
let's trip merch
penguins are flightless birds penguins
eat Krill squids and fish penguins are
carnivores Penguins can poop up to 145
times a day my God penguins cannot watch
the Ser trip that is the best card ever
like so sad what how cool you get like
let's trip merch and penguin facts if
time if time gets hard just stand tall
you can do it do it oh wow that's
awesome he loves these motivational
that's so good uhhuh all right I know
we're taking a guess happy
birthday I love the Simplicity of the
outside and then the shocking 16 yeah
like I don't know I don't really know it
could be that was really fun I don't
know if we're going to if it's like
their birthday but we're just taking a
guess all right guys we just made 20
cards for you guys um make sure you shop
our Black Friday merge with the first
link in the description down below so
that you can possibly get one of these
cards in your purchase I had so much fun
doing this and I think this is like a
really cool thing for us to do yeah
lucky people man they're all
personalized just for you and we had so
much fun doing it it's going to be
awesome they're all numbered 1 through
20 as well like I put yes one out of 20
2 out of 20 3 out of 20 all the way to
20 out of 20 if you get one post it and
tag us so we can find the people that
correct retrieve them
[Music]
w