[Applause]
Next up is a brand with a mission to
inspire cultural pride.
[Music]
Hi, my name is Sam Hyan. And I'm Adam
King. And we're two unapologetic
Asian-Americans from Boston. We're
seeking $100,000 for a
15.87% stake in our revolutionary
sneaker brand. Sharks. Did you know that
Asian-Americans are obsessed with
sneakers and are a huge factor in
driving sneaker culture and a
significant percentage of all sneaker
sales? I'm one of those guys. I live,
breathe, and sleep sneakers. I even
slept on the street overnight to cop a
pair. After working in the sneaker
industry for 20 years, I got so tired of
hearing that Asian-Americans are
follower consumers. And that is why we
started 1587 sneakers because 1587 is
actually the year that the first Asian
is documented to have set foot in what
is now known as North America. So when
people say you're new to this country,
you're a foreigner. Go back to your
country. What? We've been here 400
years. And so that's why we launched
with the Marorrow Bay. Not only is the
Maro Bay a throwback to 80s basketball
sneakers, Maro Bay is also the exact
landing spot for where that first Asian
step foot in this country. Next, we have
the AP87. This is a classic tennis
silhouette that looks great with any
occasion. All our sneakers are made with
the world's greatest leather and natural
rubber, so your sneakys will always look
like a fob. Fresh out the box.
So, Sharks, who's ready to walk with us
and change the sneaker game forever? All
right. Love it. Love it. Love it. So, in
front of you, we have customized
sneakers for each of you. You can smell
the leather, feel the quality, feel the
softness and the comfort. Are you guys
marketing towards Asians only, or is it
just for everyone? So, right now, we're
marketing towards Asians. One thing
we're super excited about, 30% of our
customers aren't Asian-American, so we
definitely think this has legs with
everyone. So, walk us through your
business model. You're selling direct to
consumer, correct? Where are you
sourcing the product from? It says Italy
in the tag, right? Italy. Yeah, it says
made in Italy. So up until now we did
all our stuff in Italy because they are
great for small batches and testing
concepts. This is my third sneaker
startup. So I understand the importance
of having good margin. What happened to
the other two? The first one I was just
employee number four. We went from
$800,000 to $8 million. Then you started
the next deal. So that brand was
marketed towards African-Americans and
that company was the first time for me
being in charge and we learned I learned
a lot on the woman. So it failed
miserably is what you're saying.
And why is this one going to work and
the other two didn't? Great question.
Cuz our messaging, walk me through that
process. I never heard of you. Snap my
fingers. I'm Asian now. How are you
going to communicate with me? One of our
greatest assets is Sam. So he's actively
involved in the Asian-American community
online everywhere. Sam, tell us about
you. What do you do? So I was actually
um born in just outside of Boston to a
single mom. Uh and she worked every job
under the sun trying to make things
work. And it was, you know, the American
dream tells you come here, you work
hard, you play by the rules that you can
achieve anything you want. But watching
her working so hard, working three jobs,
and becoming a small business owner, you
just realize that that reality wasn't
the case for everybody. Yeah. And so I
decided that I want to dedicate myself
to making sure that America lives up to
the promise that it said it would. And
so for 10 years, I spent my career in
both government and advocacy work. So
during the wake of anti-Asian hate and
the rise of violence, we spoke out a lot
and we made sure that people were
understanding what my community was
going through. So do you have a wide
following on social media right now?
About 250,000 followers. How many people
follow the company's Instagram account?
Roughly 7,000.
Right now your followers, your lifestyle
brand hasn't caught up to the
opportunity, but I'm still trying to
figure it out. All right. How much does
it cost you to make it and how much you
sell it for? When we built in Italy, um
the landed cost was 110, the retail was
2.88, but starting in 3 weeks, we
transferred 90% of our production to
Asia. So now the landed cost is $50.
We're going to retail at $175. We wanted
to make sure that we also understood our
worth as a luxury brand shoe and we
price it at that point, but also within
reach and accessible to as many people
as possible. When were you guys founded?
We've only been in operation for 10
months. And what are you projected to do
for revenue this year? We're projected
for 500,000 this year. In the last 10
months, we've done $240,000. So, have
you calculated your customer acquisition
cost? Our acquisition cost is $45 and
our average purchase is 170. You guys
have to really build the lifestyle part
of this and that's also going to help
you get your customer acquisition cost
down because right now it's too big of a
percentage of your profit margins. Well,
what do you need? What do you need?
Well, we definitely have to scale. So,
that's cash. Yep. And be able to get
into retail spaces. So, we've already
started. But are you really designed for
retail? Because I mean that's hard to
sell in retail, you know, and you don't
get your mission statement out. Listen,
I don't think this is the right business
for me. I'm really not a very good
senior person. I mean, I, you know, to
get on the treadmill that that's like it
for me. Not the right deal though today.
I'm sorry I'm out. Thank you so much. We
appreciate that. So guys, the shoe
space, which is 80% of your sales, is
incredibly competitive. The idea of
going into retail, to me, that's sheer
insanity. This isn't for me. I'm out.
Listen, in my world, I look at how many
points of failure are there between now
and where this business needs to get to.
And the ones that have like three to
seven points of failure that we can
identify and mitigate and structure
around, I'm excited about those. And for
you guys, they're like 25 things that
need to go right. But the most important
thing for me is the lack of traction. If
you had a bigger community, if you were
viral like how he is personally and you
can sell them anything, then I can see
this as a lifestyle brand and I would be
more excited. But because it's not, I
I'm out. Here's where I I have a bit of
a challenge with it. I've been in this
business and when I did buy the company
Eonic, I realized so much that goes into
these this this footwear and I don't
know if I want to take that part of the
journey with you. Especially if you're
going into retail where you'll sell out
of all your 9 and 1 halfs and 10 and
then you have a massive amount of
inventory sitting there. It's just going
to deplete your bottom line and those
are the things that you're going to have
to learn before I would be ready to
invest in you. So, good luck. Powerful
idea. Uh I'm out. But I love these
sneakers. Yeah, guys, I disagree with
Rashad. You don't have 25 points of of
failure or problems. You just have to
find your right path and you want to be
bigger bigger bigger because you want to
go into retail because you think that's
where you're going to scale. So you
think we should focus on TOC? Yes, 100%.
Because you have no margin in this
thing. You'll kill it. Bam, bam, bam.
You get to control your own destiny. You
need to reel it in and just follow the
course that is is organic for you. So
for those reasons, I'm out. Awesome.
Thank you. Good luck, guys. Thank you,
guys.