that's honestly pretty good me and Chris
look like big balls of of white fun yeah
Big Balls of Fun well it's like really
white and bright and both black you
don't know [ __ ] about Big Balls of
Fun welcome back to The stery All Out
triplet YouTube channel that's a new one
yeah it is happy Friday this is our
first car video when mat just did that I
got flashbacks to tour cuz whenever we
were in Texas that's like the only voice
Matt used like the entire time we were
in Texas like ially filmed together in a
car in over a month and a half that's
what I was getting we haven't fil
basically we are going to just do a
storytime car video telling each other
stories about things that happened or
things that we witnessed and I have such
a story for you guys who wants to start
with something I'm sweating with is this
a new shirt Nick it's not I like how
it's kind of like a there's no sleeve
it's kind of just like all built into
one I wish I had tattoos on this arm cuz
I always sit left facing in the car get
them I should it's I really am warm are
you not warm who wants to go first I go
first hey guys I'm interrupting today's
video really quick to tell you about
Opera Opera is one of the safest and
most secure internet browsers because
our job is social media we want an
internet browser that's trusty and easy
to use and that's why we use Opera we
also use Opera because it includes many
helpful features Opera has a built-in
VPN which is awesome because it can
protect your privacy while using the web
it also has a built-in ad blocker which
makes browsing and searching easy it
also has a built-in AI called Arya that
can easily help us find video topics or
answer the ridiculous questions we get
during car videos with Opera you can
also sort your tabs into Islands so that
your searching can be super organized
and you don't get confused by having way
too many tabs open for example we have
our tab sorted by entertainment shopping
and travel if you want to use a web
browser that's more safe and secure then
download Opera with the link in the
description down below and a big shout
out to Opera for sponsoring today's
video I'm going to share my story first
yes sir go for it all right Chris
already knows this story so it's only
Nick that's going to be surprised the
other day I went to the store yep right
and at the stores you know how sometimes
at like the grocery store that we go to
how there's like cops and stuff
sometimes or like but like you know how
like sometimes locations have like the
Renta cop where it's like the security
dude but he's not actually like police
officer yeah like he's just like I'm
here for work yeah I went to the store
the other day and I go in come out as
I'm coming out proud of
you for coming out
it's not funny bad joke the dude saw
which car I got out of and as he's as
water yes kind up yes whose water would
that be if it wasn't mine so I go in the
store i' come out and the guy saw what
car I drove there yep and as I'm walking
out he goes tin's a little dark
buddy I look over my shoulder and I said
yeah it's a little dark and I kept
walking as anyone would do walk back
over get in my car you want to know what
I hear when I get in my car and turn it
on let's do a demonstration I hear a
little from that window so I go
okay go the window down what's up we
what's what's going on he goes you you
don't have an answer for me on why that
tint so dark you were probably so scared
anxiety written to the core I would have
[ __ ] my pant he goes he goes you don't
have an answer for me on why that tint
is so dark I
go no not really and he goes so so are
you a
cc in my head I'm like I don't know what
that means they're like no I'm
AC that was a bad joke I said I said I
have no idea what that means I don't
know and he goes are you CC and I said
no I don't I don't think so I don't know
what that is and he goes concealed carry
oh I like if someone doesn't know what
cc means when you ask there's no way
they done and I go and I go no sir don't
I don't have a gun in here and he goes
do you have any outstanding warrant
and I sound like an [ __ ] when I say
stuff back but I like I don't mean it in
a harm harmful way but I guess like I do
sometimes give attitude by accident yeah
mattitude yeah but I said if I have any
warrants they're not outstanding you
said that yeah Matt which was probably
not the best thing for me to say what's
an outstanding warrant like you did a
good job at the crme no no no like it's
it's active outstanding warant like it's
active like it's like like he could like
you that he asked me that I was like
holy [ __ ] I started shaking I was like
I'm going to be put in handcuffs I was
like like for sure what is going on you
know what I mean so then I said buddy do
you have a family at home so then I do
you have business to mind he goes he
goes we'll see about that huh and starts
and I go do we have I said do we have a
problem I said is there something I need
to be concerned about and he goes we'll
just see about that and walks away I'd
leave so I I put my window up and I
start driving away like anyone would I
see the security car that he was
standing next to start following me out
of the parking lot and I'm like you're
kidding and I go oh my God I'm like I
don't know what's I don't know what's
going on and like for some reason it was
like a it wasn't a cop like it was not a
cop at all like he had like a polo shirt
on for like the store that I was at so I
was like this dude is has no Authority
over me yeah he can't do anything
nothing so I start leaving the fact that
he already talked to you this much is
not allow so I start leaving and he's
like doing something in the car
following me he's playing Club Penguin
on his side I take a right I take
another right and he follows me again
and then I go to take a third right and
he goes straight never saw him again but
I was [ __ ] my draw what a scary man
he must just been angry and you want to
know you want to know what he looked
like I already told Chris he looked like
the um what do you have a photo of him
nope I have a photo reference of what he
looked like he looked like the time
traveler from Gravity Falls oh this is
what he looked like hideous that's what
he looked like chat but yeah that was my
story of how that's insane I almost had
a heart attack the other night I would
have [ __ ] my pants I was I was nervous I
was shaking to thee shaking to the I
would have [ __ ] my pants yeah next like
I would leave instantly next time I
didn't I thought like well or just at
least be like you like I'd be like are
you police officer he'd be like no i' be
like okay am I detained no that's why I
said do do we have a problem and he was
like we'll see about that and like walks
away it's like you don't you can't even
check for warrants I literally like I
want to go back to the store I want to
go back to the store I want to like file
a complaint we don't have to do all that
I think we should I absolutely think we
should be like you harassed me for no
reason correct I I don't want to do that
do you know the show Court cam it's
basically like live feeds from
courtrooms and it shows no it's not
Judge Judy is it the one where the guy
Dove over and he like attacks yes that
that that thing is on court cam but
basically it's a bunch of like footage
of like inside of courtrooms and just
videos of people talking and whatever
happens in isn't that illegal no it's a
show it's a whole show about it oh but I
was watching an episode the other day
and this guy was suing his roommate
me because he he one of the guys took
his testicles off and put them in a jar
and was and was securing them in their
refrigerator and the other room free
that's got to be a freezer thing yeah
and the other roommate was disturbed by
it and accidentally threw it away but
the other roommate was like he did it on
purpose and that's my property and I can
never get my testicles
back I wish I worked in like a lab with
like all like the fun little glasses and
like I could like work with Matt and
then like I'll look and be like Matt I
need this and like we're looking through
like the beaker at each other and his
face is like big and mine's like
triangular do you know what I'm talking
about yeah that's a good moment funny
and you have to like peek over the
little nut sack rolling around in the
jar to see him this might turn into what
sounds like an infomercial have you ever
been sitting at home bored and want
something to do with friends this does
sound like an info mercial just like it
have you ever wanted to go out but have
nothing to do yeah Chris has the
solution oh God
I want to invent a game and this might
literally get cut out cuz I might
actually do it do you know Pokémon go
how you have to go to certain places in
real life and catch Pokemon or scan Poké
stops very familiar love it I want it to
be based on cities and then you can
select your teammates and then you can
work together to complete local missions
so that way say we're back home we could
say we are going to be in Boston we have
a team of me Matt Nick Justin and Nathan
and we're going to be here from like
September 1st to September 30th we need
missions to do right and then we all get
on our server and we all meet up
together and then it says like go to
like blanket like the Chipotle on this
street and you have to go there and
solve your first virtual Mission and
then it tells you like a next step and
it's like an IRL Capture the Flag game
but all virtual that you can play with
friends and you can get like awarded
ranks and like how many missions you
complete and you
canel I delete the app in an hour what
it' tell me it' be like go here no but
it can it it would get so viral that
people are like competing to like do
like specific challenges you can travel
like oh my God we should do like a
national park it's going to get taken
too far I think it's not I think that
you need to going be or something people
are going you need to work on you need
to work on what your missions are and
then I can see this getting something
but the fact that you're like in this
blind right now I don't really like if
some if that game gets created and sold
for millions of dollars what is it that
you predicted in our podcast what was
that that was crazy I forget I was
talking about how there should be like a
like a portal in Time Square or
something and then it happened yeah
helling you I got some good
ideas you're just s if there is a if
there is a a capture the flag teammate
game that you can do in your local city
with your friends are you capturing
Flags it it's like it's more of treasure
hunt it's like Outer Banks how how many
times do you watch Outer Banks or
Adventure kid movies like and you want
to be them this is your chance you can
make a little Avatar that's the app
description you going to be like little
like maybe like brand Integrations like
oh you have to go get a Sprite for one
of the missions and it's like an
advertisement paid by Sprite so there's
money in the game and then you can do
cash rewards and like the top of the
world can get paid to like like I'm it's
a whole thing yeah you're cooking it's a
whole thing how good of an idea is that
maybe an app developer will watch this
and he'll created it I need my cut or
she I need my cut I feel like I am
literally one of the only people that
genuinely count sheep to fall asleep no
you don't I swear to God are they
hopping over a fence or I was laying
down listen can you finish can you stop
I mean and I literally virtually
pictured a little sheep going like this
like one not virtual or mentally one and
do you know what it looked like do you
know that mattress that literally has
that like one sheep Serta and it's
should like that's what I picture and I
literally go one two and it helps me
fall asleep and what it made me think
and what it made me think what it made
me think is oh my God if other people
count sheep to go to bed when do you
feel the most scared and vulnerable at
night or when do you feel the most
scared and vulner when do you feel the
most scared and vulnerable in your life
at night right right before you're going
to fall asleep I figured that's the
answer new idea I'm creating the
counting sheep horror movie and it's
basically going to be something so scary
and like paralyzing you with fear but
during the movie there's going to be
like little sheep hopping over the fence
or something I haven't got the concept
down yet but basically what basically
what's going to happen is it's going to
be some intense crazy horror movie and
every time you go to sleep and you try
to count sheep you're going to think of
it and it's going to give you nightmares
and that's going to be the most
successful most scary horror movie of
them all cuz it going of literally how
many sheep how many sheep did you get to
the other night I stop at around like 30
every night probably 30 and you're sleep
already well no it just takes my mind
off what I'm thinking and then it helps
me just rest and go to sleep oh so it's
not like a it's not like I'm counting
till I doze off no it's like I'm
counting to distract my mind okay I have
think I have the idea of like the
opening scene is the sheet
like well of course of course and then
the closing scene in addition is the so
it's like you're just always like feel
like the she I have the bread I need we
need the lettuce the Tomato the B
exactly have to bear with me cuz it
starts slow okay is it recording yes
okay so I've never in my life ever in my
life ever in my life done room service
cuz I think that like the way we grew up
and like what we're doing we're kind of
like not in like hotels that even
offered it mhhm so when we I was just
around the world as everybody knows and
I was in one of the hotels in Australia
toward the end of the trip we get to the
hotel super late it's like 11 11:00 and
I checked the in room service menu and
it says the room Ser I haven't eaten
today okay busy day get home at 11: at
night and you haven't eaten once no well
like I ate I dabbled and but I haven't
had dinner okay starving like there's a
daytime menu from whatever breakfast
6:00 to 5: or something and then 5 to
11:30 is dinner okay I'm like okay guys
this is my [ __ ] time I must call now
cuz I if I don't get this I'm going to
bit hungry I'm going to wake up hungry
and I don't know what I'm going to eat
in the morning have to capitalize on
this moment I can eat the menu ends at
1130 11:30 I got it and what time is it
for you 11:00 so I'm like these are the
options I can choose from roasted
butternut pumpkin Caesar salad re egg
omelette club sandwich Crispy Chicken
Wrap all these things right I go I look
at the menu and it says beef burger
brisket Patty aged cheddar Smoky tomato
relish pickle and tomato with fries
great I love cheeseburgers but I am a
21-year-old baby so I like my burgers
with just meat and cheese in a bun cuz
I'm a simple man plain as can be plain
plain burger that's all I [ __ ] want
and dream of I'm starving so I pick up
the phone and I'm you guys know I'm if
I'm if I'm patient the person I'm most
patient with on Earth is a customer
service worker I will work through this
with you I will speak to you for 20
minutes I will encourage you you have my
time yeah no worries no worries at all
can I get a cheeseburger to my room and
he goes I'm sorry at this time we don't
have cheeseburgers available and I'm
starving so I'm like I H I usually be
like oh okay and just hang up but I'm
like I need to eat so I instantly tell
this guy I'm like oh like I checked the
menu and there like the the the Burger
on the menu and that's like what I want
to eat he goes oh yeah we don't have a
cheeseburger but we have the beef
burger and I said
okay I'll get that but take everything
off but the cheese he goes let me check
with the chef please if we can do this
I'm like okay he goes I'll call you back
I hang up I sit literally like this not
moving for 5 minutes at the edge of my
bed waiting for the phone to ring phone
rings ring ring ring ring R ring I
answer the phone yeah so I spoke to the
chef and it at these hours of the night
because we're down to the nighttime menu
we can only do the beef burger and I
said no totally fine completely
understand I'll do the beef burger I
don't need a cheeseburger I'll do the
beef burger but I'll just take
everything off it but the cheese yeah
and he's like yes so sir we can't add
cheese to the Burger we can't do a
cheese burger and I said sir the beef
burger comes with cheese yes I'm not
asking for something you don't have I'm
asking for a [ __ ] beef burger keep
the cheese on it I'm making your life
easier you don't have to get the [ __ ]
pickles out and the tomato and the jelly
and all this [ __ ] all I want is cheese
okay so I ask again I say I'm like yes
sir the the beef burger is to I
literally was being so nice I was like
the beef I understand like I understand
the beef burger is totally fine like
don't worry about it like I don't I feel
bad like I don't want you to stress out
like the beef burger is fine I just only
want cheese on it and he goes give me a
second hangs up on me again I sit down I
wait for a call back the manager calls
me and she's like hi um so I I hear you
on a
cheeseburger no the beef burger I'm like
yes if you can do that she goes yes so
we can't do a cheeseburger because it's
not on the menu right now but we can do
the beef
burger and this goes on for like 30
minutes I literally dropped to my knees
alone in my room I literally was sitting
there and I dropped to my knees in shock
I'm like I understand that I can only
get the beef burger but the beef burger
comes with cheese on it so just leave
the cheese on the beef burger what's the
difference between cheeseburger and beef
burger nothing Wait nothing and
meanwhile meanwhile no no meanwhile the
day prior during the day I ordered hey
can I get a beef burger with just the
cheese on it and they're like yeah of
course and they sent it to my room so
I'm like what is the issue now okay but
listen isn't a beef
burger like the American hamburger so
it's like cheeseburger yeah I'll take
the beef burger with just cheese on it
yeah but that's not but Chris the beef
burger comes with cheese show you on the
menu it says beef burger brisket Patty
aged cheddar yes got it so I'm like oh
maybe they're getting confused with the
cheese and the cheddar yes even though
cheddar cheese is [ __ ] cheese I'm
like I'm so sorry for the confusion I
hate I I like hate being this guy yeah
it's totally fine I just want a beef
burger with cheese and the lady goes
okay okay we can we we understand you
want so you want the beef burger and you
want everything on it but Che
cheese I said no reverse that keep the
cheese and remove everything else yes
she goes okay so a beef burger with just
cheese anything else and I'm like a
Pepsi yeah she's like okay and for the
troubles that like All the Troubles will
take off the Pepsi charge I'm like no
you guys can charge me for the Pepsi you
can charge me at 10 million more dollars
just bring me the cheeseburger just
bring me the cheeseburger okay and they
finally they finally bring me my
burger and I eat
it and it was a [ __ ] beef burger with
cheese that's it and a side of fries and
a Pepsi and I had dinner wow but I'm
like the fact that I had to have this
conversation 35 times that's insane blew
my mind blew my mind when I said can I
get the beef burger with nothing on it
but cheese and they were like we can't
do the beef burger no we can't we can't
do a cheeseburger we can do the beef
burger because I said the beef burger is
fine so what is the cheeseburger there
the che the cheeseburger is the same
[ __ ] thing so they have a
cheeseburger and a beef burger on the
men there's no cheeseburger on the menu
if you at all if you ask you ask for a
cheeseburger they just don't understand
what's going on you need to ask for the
beef
burger a che a beef burger is a
cheeseburger if you if I called and said
hey can I get a beef burger I would have
got exactly what I at think of is Burger
bot right now and that's it who's the
burger bot remember when Matt was the
burger bot I would just like to share
that if you guys ever bought something
for me super expensive as like a
surprise and I had zero say I'd actually
be a little upset why share an income no
just like let me get my say like I would
hate to be surprised with like a brand
new car or something and it's like I had
zero say in like anything and now it's
like my car for the next
like her mom surprised her like a Tesla
she's like I don't want this [ __ ] yeah
that's insane but it's like I'm saying
like if I'm going to like if you guys
were ever like buy something super Niche
for me like that's expensive I don't
know what like all I can think of is a
car right now but I would be like kind
of like damn I couldn't say anything
about
it no that's valid that's a valid
feeling and I'm just saying it to you
guys so like don't do it you know I was
never going to also you can I I know I'm
not planning on driving at all but I was
thinking like damn I kind of want to get
Matt a nice car but I want have a say in
it the other day I felt like I was
literally getting
pranked I put a whole outfit on right an
outfit you're not funny at all and well
I I didn't leave the house yet so I
didn't have my shoes on but I put a pair
of pants on I put a t-shirt on and I put
a hat on okay and I've owned all of them
for like probably over a month okay
right and I go in the mirror and I look
and I have like a little like medium
sticker
and I go oh take it off and then my
pants had like the 32 waist thing I go
oh ripped it off and then I went like
this and I scratch my head and I look at
my hat and it has like the oh my God and
I was like I was like oh my God I'm like
my I was like I thought someone was like
trolling me like I thought it was like a
fib and then I put my shoes on oh my God
what remember the game fiber and then I
put my shoes on and it had the little
cushiony thing and remember swear on
everything you just reminded me when you
said this you remember the game fiber
yes yeah you extend your nose haha super
cool like Pinocchio you just reminded me
when you said you thought someone was
trolling you you guys aren't going to
believe me today oh God I like think I
have like a third sense or like a
paranormal like five or something like I
supposed to have like five senses no
like like a six sense I mean there it is
I say triple it double I literally was
on the ladder I have a little step
ladder in my B in my in my in my closet
cuz I can't see the top of my clothes if
I don't step up okay and I step onto the
second level of the ladder and I'm
sorting through my shorts to grab the
shorts that I'm putting on and I hear
like like literally like that was three
steps and a shuffle back and I thought
that Matt was going to like pull like
something out from behind me and I
turned and I was like Matt no one was
there and I was like what like it was
literally that like that like gives me
chill
I felt I'm not kidding I felt the ladder
shake and I felt like a like a pull like
I thought there was like a shirt under
in my brain genuinely my pure actual
honest thought was that there was a
shirt under one of the legs of the
ladder that I was standing on and Matt
followed me to my room and pulled it out
what is that M literally I'm dead
serious I genuinely thought that like I
turned around and went to say something
to Matt and it was the fastest I turned
around ever in my life like as if like
like it was a genuine reaction like I
turned Nick it was like how do you not
and I forgot about it until you just
said that the other day you thought
someone was pranking you wow when you
were had all the clothes I was like
today I thought I was being pranked and
it was a ghost no I do that all the time
like I was laying in my room the other
day and I was taking a nap so I was like
partially kind of like opening my eyes
here and there but not really and my
room was like that weird like dark
because the curtains are drawn and the
lights are off but but light enough for
me to see everything cuz the Sun is up
you know what I mean and I'm I always
think I'm like what if someone was just
standing in like the corner of my room I
Look to check which is a bad habit but
I'm like if I don't look I'm going to
[ __ ] if I don't look I'm going to not
be able to sleep like last night I was
going to bed and I was like oh there's
probably someone hovering over behind me
on the other side of like no I have to
look now and I go and I turn and I look
and I'm like imagine if I look and
someone's actually there yeah but I also
like I also just like am okay with it
like I'll look over at my towel like
hanging from my shower like is that a
person that was freaking me out when I
was sleeping in your room while you were
gone it's scary it's really scary I feel
like Morse code should be more like in
your face kind of it's when are you
going to communicate with Morse code
well like for the people that need it
they can't really
see isn't oh I'm thinking of Braille
sorry if you think about it and I'll
actually say this is like sheer honesty
every movie ever is like inaccurate to
real
life like every movie ever cuz when I'm
watching a movie I'm just like oh you
kind of like understand like there's
like the tropes to the movies and stuff
but I'm like when are we going to just
like make a movie where like people are
in like a life or death situation and
they don't survive because they
obviously wouldn't know how to [ __ ]
get out of this it's like in the life or
death situation it's like someone's like
oh I know how to [ __ ] pick a lock and
backflip it's like no you don't yeah
like stop joking every movie ever is
unrealistic and yes I understand that
movies wouldn't exist if they weren't
unrealistic think of that my favorite
Instagram real the other day where it's
like this this is how
Instagram real yes I do all right guys
that has been this week's Friday video
we see you guys golden Raising Canes in
Boston golden it's gold wooo
[Music]