so I grew up in a lower middle class
family almost a third tier town in India
in my town at that time there was only
one person with the car I really loved
math I was very good at it I just wanted
to learn more math someone told my dad
you should put your son in computer
science because that's the the next big
thing and that's what probably got me
into one of the top colleges in India
called I quite lucky to get to Google in
early days I ran couple of things at
Google Google's mobile advertising which
actually I happen to Drew that to $50
billion in Revenue before joining
company called flip cart in India where
I was Chief product officer second time
I joined Google I walked on Google's
product search uh most recently I was
Chief product officer at coinbase and
helped coinbase through their
IPO I am surit chatur I'm founder and
CEO of Emma the full name of the
company's Enterprise machine assistant
EMA we built Emma as what we call a
universal AI employee so the idea is
Emma can collaborate with human
employees and take a lot of the
repetitive tedious task that humans do
today in
Enterprise so I grew up in in India I
went to one of the top technical
institutes in India called IIT I was an
engineer in early years of my my journey
uh got a business degree from MIT I was
confused that oh should I be a
consultant investment banker and it took
me a little bit of time to realize no
I'm a technologist at heart I need to go
back and just focus more on technology
quite lucky to get to Google in early
days I had no idea what product
management was before joining go to be
honest and I was an engineer I had a
business degree I interviewed with
Google and they said you can be a
product manager and had me they told me
oh your first job will be in actually
payments and billing and fixing their
Google's payments product I have no idea
what it is I like yeah that's fine just
go learn and figure it out that was
really interesting for me that kind of
uh culture where we hire really good
people really smart people and we
believe they can figure out anything I
was very lucky to I had the opportunity
to actually co-found Google's mobile ads
team so another engineer in myself we
started very modest team working on
mobile advertising at Google crew that
that business from 0 to $50 billion in
Revenue see at Google I built stuff that
were many times incredibly hard to build
many people told me they were impossible
to build this happens all the time in in
larger companies because people someone
will try the product that you are trying
to build before and they might have
failed they'll tell you oh no no don't
try it it already failed so far my
biggest learning was you know how to
take on very ambitious idea uh believe
in my conviction believe in my gut on
those ideas and really risk it all I
would always go to work I would tell my
team you know I'm ready to be fired
today but not doing anything unethical
or illegal but pursuing my idea when I
was running mobile ads so I came up with
the idea of click to call ADS there's a
button to call you can call the
advertiser directly that now it's a
multi-billion Dollar business for Google
you would think it's the most obvious
idea today but for some reason there's
tremendous resistance internally we
wanted to go and experiment in Google
you experiment everything and Google had
this massive experimentation framework
to launch anything you need to get like
significant volume like you need to show
a statistical significance of your
feature and at that time on mobile uh
the number of users were really low so
if we just follow the Norms of Google at
that time which is a large desktop
business the mobile features will take
at least 9 months or a year each to
gather enough data to launch that just
seems like too long and the the mobile
industry is moving really fast we can't
wait that long let's make a mistake and
turn this feature on for 50% of the
users and how long would it take like
like okay only just a few weeks if
somebody finds out of of course they
will find out I'll take the blame and
what are they going to do fire Me Maybe
that's that's fine so we made a mistake
and launched that feature 50% of course
I had to go and explain what happened
but then actually it is working really
well let's not unlaunch it and lot of
things we had to do in early days was
breaking the Norms when you build a lot
of success you create some norms for
that success and that becomes an
innovator for the next success because
those Norms is actually stopping you
from innovating so everything I did on
mobile I had to break a lot of norms
there are many many projects I did this
enormous internal resistance Google has
really smart people right if bunch of
smart people are vly against my idea I
think there is something good in it that
actually gets me fired up to pursue that
idea I think the the conviction on your
ideas is very important attribute of a
product manager of of any leader right
of course not stupid conviction but
conviction to the extent that you want
to take it all the way and test it out
that's how I have lived my career trying
out things that often seemed
contradictory and often seemed out there
a little
bit I was try running mobile ads at
Google doing extremely well I got
promoted many times it was the fastest
growing and largest business at Google
at that time you would think there is no
reason to leave back of my mind I was
getting a little worried that I will
never leave it's kind of so comfortable
in some way I've done well and that was
kind of worrying me a little bit that oh
I may become like a lifer and I I just
want to learn always learn more but the
flip cart thing was completely said
indeas I was visiting bunch of customers
in India what was curious was Indian
customers like flip cart and others at
that time had already made the leap to
Mobile so the India was a mobile first
company they skipped the desktop
generation so lot of the e-commerce was
90% of the gmv or the net the net
revenue was from mobile which is very
different from developed markets where
at that time it was still 90% was on
desktop or maybe 80% was on desktop it
was great to see that I was very curious
about that going back to India and
meeting lot of these customers I thought
uh this is the kind of EX completely
different thing thing that I could do
from Google it's a different country
very different business I would just
learn a
lot India was the last place where
e-commerce should have gone in the those
times so if you think about it the three
ingredients for e-commerce internet
electronic payments and Logistics at
that time very few Indians had credit
cards or debit cards the road
infrastructure was very poor so flip
cart a as a company had to take on this
enormous challenge of the infrastructure
of the country to build Ecommerce for a
billion people so how do get a product
like a village in India the second tier
30er town in India we had to design
special trucks that were thin that could
go through small lanes and alleys so we
had to solve a lot of the technical
challenges logistical challenges that
was really amazing learning for me so
flip cart actually got into an agreement
to uh get bought over by Walmart that
was kind of the motivation for me to
come back and rejoin
Google running a company is different
from popularity contest you cannot
please everyone and whenever if you try
to please everyone as you grow your
company then you will definitely
degenerate your culture the next 3 years
at Google when I ran shopping Google was
becoming a place which was not very
enjoyable to work anymore Google had
actually as a company changed
dramatically from cultural perspective
some of the things that were very
positive about Google had degenerated
into being very negative so Google was a
place where people would always express
their opinion very freely people could
discuss anything but you can can take
that to an extreme and then discuss
anything and everything that is outside
the scope of Google's main mission of
the business and there's everybody is
distracted so I felt actually very
fortunate to leave Google have done
something else have seen something
different at every stage of growth there
is a risk that your culture will
degenerate because you are hiring new
people you have to learn how to work in
a in a different setting and so on so we
have to be very aware and very
deliberate very intentional to maintain
culture in fact you have to take a
stance that this is our culture if you
as an individual don't align with our
culture there are other opportunities
out there other options out there yes
it's possible to maintain the culture
but you have to be ready to be unpopular
make hard calls and be very intentional
about maintaining the
culture look I have run very large teams
grown teams in in companies like Google
coinbase flip cart some of the best
companies in the world and one thing
that always bothered me we had really
talented people but then a large
percentage of their time was still spent
in repetitive work so the idea behind
Emma is can we automate most of the
mundane tasks people have to do in
Enterprises and and free them up to do
more value added more creative tasks in
our journey first thing is we walked
very closely with customers very very
early on we build the product actually
working with multiple customers as
design Partners so from the get go we
knew there is there is a need we knew if
you build it at least there are a few
customers and I think the trick is to
figure out okay are this the only
customers who will use it or there is a
broader demand so you have to talk to
enough customers to recognize patterns
and make sure okay whatever you are
building is not too custom for this
given customer you may have to do some
custom work for your early customer but
you have to be very clear ey on which
part of your product is a platform that
can be used and which part is maybe you
are customizing a little bit for some of
your early customers the other advice
I'll give to any startup founder or
particularly AI founder focus on
building nothing matters we kept the
company in stealth for a year uh we did
not announce our fundraise we didn't
announce even incorporation so funny
story some of our employees in in India
will complain that what do I tell my
parents where do I work
work it just say Ste and there is no
ifite we kept it under radar uh and Ste
just so we can focus and not get
distracted by by everything that
happening you know there's too much
noise out there you can spend your
entire day on Twitter and talking to
many people and getting too much wisdom
you of course want to absorb that and
and look at what's happening in the
world but you have to have your own
conviction and you have to block it out
and focus that's so important because
when you build a great product
everything else will fall into place see
our long-term vision is uh will be a
conversational operating system for
every Enterprise out there I think there
will be a future where in every company
team of human employees will work with a
team of AI employees that's the world we
envision where uh companies with very
few people actually being able to create
enormous impact 100 people company
making a billion dollar Revenue how
about a 10 people company making a
billion dollar revenue or even a one
person company making a billion dollars
in revenue or more I think we will be
able to enable that in the future where
a few a human employees will work with a
a group of AI agents and and AI
employees like Emma to build really
large companies