First in the tank is a healthier version
of a popular indulgence.
[Music]
Hi Sharks. My name is Marvin and I'm
Aaliyah. We're from Baltimore, Maryland,
and we're seeking 150,000 for 7 and a
half% of our business. Sharks, as a
husband and wife team, I can tell you
there's always two sides to every story.
Oh, Marvin, don't even get me started
with that one. Take bacon for instance.
It's so good and it pairs with
everything. Yeah, like high blood
pressure and heart disease, but it's
crispy and smoky. Full of saturated fat
and cholesterol, but it melts in your
mouth. It's so delicious. Marvin, all
those nitrates and preservatives. Come
on, babe. Okay, my wife is correct as
usual. But that's why we created a
better for you bacon. And we like to
say, if it looks like bacon, smells like
bacon, and tastes like bacon, it must be
mushrooms.
Introducing Shrew Min, a plant-based
bacon made of sliced mushroom. Shroom
has only five clean label ingredients,
and soy ain't one. And the taste better
than pork bacon on a BLT, on a juicy
burger, on a salad. Just the thought of
it has me hungry. One bite of shama and
you won't believe you're eating sliced
mushrooms. In fact, that's what makes it
so special. It's not highly processed
and it's not made in a mold. Sharks, let
me show you how we slice our mushrooms.
Hit it. Samurai guy. Samurai guy. Slice.
Slice. Slice. Slice. Slice. Slice.
Slice.
Marvin. Marvin. Wait a minute. Wait a
minute. This is not how we slice our
mushrooms. Uh, you're right. But a guy
can drink, I guess. So, so Sharks, who's
ready to swap out the swine and start
shrew making the world happy with Meet
the Mushroom? Oh, boy. Now, this is it
in front of us. It is. Bye-bye. Meet the
mushroom. So, in front of you, you have
juicy BLTs and you also have some slices
of uh shama. It's actually really good.
No fat, clearly. Yes. Very lean. Yes.
Nothing squishes.
Nice and crispy. Crispy. It's smoky.
Again, only five ingredients. Non-GMO.
You can cook it in the air fryer. You
can cook it in the skillet. If you don't
want to use any oil, you can cook it in
the oven. In Shark Tank, we've had so
many plant-based products. They all
taste like crap. No, they do not.
This is good. Oh, yeah. This is good. I
like it. What kind of a mushroom is
that? That's a king oyster mushroom.
That's a king oyster mushroom. Yes.
Those are expensive. What are your cost
of goods on this? Uh the pack that
you're holding currently cost $29 to
make. However, we know for a fact we can
get that down to
$1.75. We sell it retail $8.99. Wa. And
then uh to our distributor, we sell it
for $4.40. Tell us a little bit about
your background. So my background is as
a Facebook ads manager. Um my first
business was cars. Um I was wholesaling
cars. My next business was a mover and
that's how I actually me and my wife met
out was our mover, you know. Um, there
you go. Okay. A mover. He moved right
in. Yep. Yep. But, um, I had a heart
condition and, uh, the doctor said I
wouldn't I would have my whole for for
the rest of my life. I had, um, enlarged
heart muscle. So, I went vegan. I went
back to the doctors a year later and my
heart disease was gone. I had asthma
since I was eight. That totally
disappeared. Once I was healed, I saw
the powers of a vegan diet and I wanted
to open a restaurant in my neighborhood.
In the black community specifically, is
a lot of food um related illnesses in
the black community with heart disease
and uh diabetes. But while I was making
these items for the menu and I saw they
could not only just help my community,
but they could help the world. So, we
transitioned the idea into um a product
based business instead of a restaurant.
So, what do you do today for a living?
Is this the only job? The only thing we
do. So tell us about your sales. Does
that matter? Sales. So May of 2021 until
December of 2021, we did $38,000 in
sales. Um then for all of 2022, we went
up to $86,000 in sales. And then to
date, we have in over
$238,000 of in sales, making our
lifetime sales over
360,000. We're selling primarily 93%
direct to customer. We've only now
started to get into grocery stores and
so we are just getting started. But
you're a couple. You're both in this
business full time. Full time. How How
are you getting by to pay your bills?
Yeah. So, we actually have gone out all
in. We sold a car. We moved in with my
mother-in-law. Um, we are really scrappy
with this. Okay. We are all 100% in. We
have a daughter. There she is. And her
name is Nora. Um, Nora has Down syndrome
and so, you know, she is really our
inspiration. She's phenomenal.
Look, I'm really intrigued because it's
so good, but valuation is insane.
However,
because I am a chef and because I'm Mr.
Wonderful, okay, the way I see this
deal, I'll give you
$150,000. I want to be the third
partner, 33 and a3%. Okay. I have zero
flexibility. That's a fantastic. How
much flexibility do you have on this?
Oh, I have zero flexibility. Okay. I
just want to I'll clear the deck. I have
a deal with Unreal Deli, which is a
plant-based meat product. We're getting
into the same space. So, that's going to
be a conflict. So, for those reasons,
I'm out. But congrats on what you've
done. It really was good. Thank you. I
feel that the passion that you have and
congratulations and what you're creating
is amazing. And I think the path to
success will be challenging for a couple
of reasons. Because what you're doing
now is you're going to be instead of one
step away from the money, you're four
steps away because now you have to make
it and be an expert in manufacturing,
then you have to get the store to buy
it, get them to list it, and then get a
customer to buy it all at a onethird of
what you would have been. Guys, this is
all great chatter, but you know, you do
have an offer on the table. Let me tell
you where I see some of the bigger
challenges you may have. And for that
reason, I'm out. Thank you. Can I ask
you a few questions? Sure. So, just let
me add a little little spice to the
offer. Okay. I offered you 150,000 for
33 and a third. They were so excited
about going to go ju it's going to grow
like a mushroom a little bit because I'm
not feeling the love. Okay. I'm going to
go to 150,000 for 33 and 2/3%.
Okay. So, the good thing is I really
liked it and I'm your customer, right?
The bad thing is is I wanted more. So,
it's like normal bacon this long. Yeah.
Yours is this long. Your only thing,
Lori, is that it should be a longer
mushroom. Um, it's not always about the
size, man. That's right. It's not always
about the size. That's what she say. But
that's what she say. I want a bigger
mushroom. And Lori to speak to that as
well, you know, think varying slices.
Yes. Because the mushrooms are very the
same thing. Um mushrooms. I feel so
unloved. And now unfortunately I'm 33
and 3/3 better known as 34%.
Hey, we do love you, Mr. Growing like a
mushroom.
Listen, Marvin Alia, you're very
inspiring to me. Thank you. Um honestly,
this is my fifth season. I've never seen
Mr. wonderful. Give a fair offer. And
this one is a fair offer. Okay. Given
where you're at, I was actually very
impressed with his offer. I don't think
I could give you that offer. Okay. And
so for those reasons, I'm out. Okay.
Thank you. And I and I think you should
seriously consider his offer. Thank you.
One thing that I also want to speak to
that Damon said that I think should be
addressed. I think you should talk to
Lori because she's listen torn. There's
like there's like a little voice on my
left that's saying horrible valuation.
little voice to my right that's saying
but they're amazing and it's amazing so
I'm torn you
know I will give you an offer for 33 and
the third oh
undercut Kevin would you would either of
you consider
uh cuz that's a lot more equity than we
were thinking of that we wanted it's
fair for you to say that but remember
the environment we're in the Fed has
raised rates at an unprecedented speed
capital is not cheap anymore venture
capital's dried And so the reality out
there is this offer is more than fair.
More than fair because we're in we're
back at where we were when we started
Shark Tank 2008. No money out there. And
here we are making you offers. I will
make you an offer that might sweeten the
deal. Okay. R.
What if Kevin and I went in together?
Then you get two sharks.
What do you think, Devin? Would you
consider going in together
for 25%.
Look, I'll do that deal with Lori at 33
and a third and start you on your
journey. You're great people. Okay. Oh,
thank you. Thank you. Thank you. But
it's 33 and a3%.
This is the thing. I'm I'm going to keep
it real. 33% is too much for us right
now. Um, you know, we're going to have
to raise more money. Yeah, we're going
to have to raise more money. I know
money is drying up, but it is money out
there. And I think our product is going
to get some of that money. It's not
enough equity to We got to get up in the
morning and we got to smell the bacon.
Okay. It's a lot of work.
Would you consider 200,000 for the 33
and a 30% with both of you in and help
with POS? I'm not there.
I'm not there. Sorry. What about your
34%. No, not there. You're over
negotiating. Guys, you have to make a
decision.
33%.
Yeah. All right. Go ahead. Do it. You
have a deal. Y. Congrats.
[Music]
Congratulations.
Thank you. Thank you. Making bacon.
Guys, well done, man. Good job. Thank
you.
You got the Got to do.
I'm not going to lie. It was very
painful to have to give up that much
equity, but we know that having two
Sharks on board, we're going to be able
to take our business to the next level
and really create a legacy for our
daughter, Nora. I can't believe we did
it.
Yay.