Next into the tank is a solution to an
age-old problem.
[Music]
Hi Sharks. I'm William Mias. I'm Michael
Curry. And I'm Tony La Hood. We're from
Cleveland, Ohio. And we're the founders
of Sauce Moto. Today we're here to offer
you a 15% stake in our company for
$45,000.
Since the advent of the drive-thru,
we've all been faced with a horrible
decision when eating in our cars. What's
that, Mike? Risk fumbling, making a mess
with your dipping sauce, or heaven
forbid, having to eat a ketchupless fry.
That's disgusting. And we could not
stand for this any longer. That's why we
took fate into our own hands and molded
from the clay of the earth the Saus Moto
dip clip. A condiment holder designed
specifically for your car. Sauce Moto
isn't just a cup holder for your sauce.
No, it's a purveyor of freedom. It's
universal clip attaches to just about
any vehicle's air vent. And its unique
5in-1 aperture holds sauce from just
about all fast food restaurants. Bravo.
Bravo. Oh. Through extensive field
testing and countless nights of grueling
fast food research, we developed Sausoto
to hold up to just about any road
condition. Sharks, don't try this at
home. You want to go for a ride? Yes,
I'm starving. Let's say you're enjoying
your nuggets when the driver suddenly
turns onto a cobblestone path. Oh, and
suddenly a strong gust of wind comes
from the east. It's hardly ideal dipping
conditions, but not with Sauce
Moto. That's right. Any sauce, any
climate, Sauce Moto has your nuggets
covered. Together, we can make the
ketchupless fry a thing of the past.
It's time to practice safe sauce. So,
Sharks, who wants to dip into this
investment and make sure no one has to
endure a sauceless nugget again.
Who's hungry? Oh, yeah.
And a bent, too. Yes. Oh, thank you.
More food. Just what I need. See that?
These nuggets are great. Yeah, these
nuggets are really great. So, how did
you come up with this? About 10 years
ago, we were on a road trip, got hungry,
decided to get some nuggets and fries,
and the inevitable happened, and I
spilled some sauce in Tony's brand new
car, and that's when we just started
brainstorming. Okay, how how could we
keep them secure? Uh, you know, in the
car. You really thought this was a big
problem? It really is. It really is a
problem. It is catch. How many of these
have you sold? Uh, we've done 12,000
units for about $77,000 in sales. Wow.
I'm just curious. Are you excited to be
here? I'm not sure I'm feeling any
pulse. No, I really am excited to be
here. I mean, I we work really hard on
this. This is Tony's natural voice.
What is your role in this business? Each
of our roles. Okay. So, yeah, I'm the
engineer. I designed most of it here.
Um, testing and your design, your
marketing. Uh Tony and I well I kind of
span between both. I'll I'll from from
design and creative. Uh I'll do any the
graphic design. We do everything in
house. Most of the product testing too,
right? And who? Oh yeah. And who
designed this package? I did. Fabulous
design. It tells you everything you want
to see. Doesn't take up any space. I
even want to have one. I don't even eat
fast food. That's the reaction we
usually get is when people see it,
they're just like take my money. So what
does it cost? What did you sell them
for? We're selling them for about 5.75
on, you know, our website and online. Uh
it cost us about 80 cents to make.
What's your background? I'm a sales
engineer in the tire industry. I'm a
mechanical engineer doing product
development for a wood tool company. I I
own a couple of bars. Oh, you do? Good
for you. In Cleveland? Yeah, I've
probably been there. My people are going
to find you. We knew that nugget culture
is actually really real. Nugget culture.
Absolutely. We built this for verality.
We did the amazing videos and those just
went viral. We had 44 million
views over Facebook. Do you guys really
expect to sell like millions of these?
Stanford study concluded that there's
20% of American meals are actually
consumed in automobiles. Wow. I eat
probably 30% of mine. And there's a lot
of Yeah, there's a lot of people who
just don't have time like to go home and
sit down and have a lunch. So, one of
the biggest things that we've realized
with Sausoto is it's an extremely good
promotional tool for companies. So, if
we approached a fast food chain, rental
car companies, um we were actually in
talks with two major sauce manufacturers
right now um for promotional product. I
think you guys are taking this the wrong
direction. It's not nuggets. It's all
about the fries. Everybody eats fries. I
like the deal cuz I can see taking it
public on the NYC. You'll be ringing the
bell with me. I think this is huge. But
wait a sec. Maybe there's a smoking hot
offer coming here. I do see the use of
it. I mean, I eat fries in the car and I
like to dip my fries and it's an issue.
But you know, I've got to wet my beak. I
got to wet my beak. You want a lot of
money here. This is $45,000. We're not
messing around. 15%. This imputes a
crazy valuation. You know that. But I'm
willing to go, but I want a little bit
more equity. I'll do it for 50%. Oh,
thank you, Kevin. Thank you. Appreciate
that offer. You want to be at the drive
up window and they say, "Look, for an
extra whatever, you can get the sauce
moto. This is really cool." You clip
your sauce into it. That's where you
want to be. That's complicated deal.
That's a complicated deal to cut. They
give it away as a promotion. Thank
goodness you went cuz that's the kind of
deal I like to take on as a challenge.
Look, I think it's a great product, but
like you've already found out, you're
going to have to hustle for big sales
across, you know, promotional
opportunities.
that that's just a lot of time and it
just doesn't get me all sauced up. And
so for those reasons, I'm out.
It's such a little product. It's such a
small price. Don't let these sharks drop
out. No. No. And this my price is going
way up. If these guys drop out, shut up
a minute. It's going way up to the door.
Three grown men sharing the potential
profit of this tiny little product. This
isn't my kind of business. I'm sorry.
I'm out.
I have one final question. Who created
the videos that saw 44 million hits? We
wrote the scripts and we hired a crew to
film them. How much did it cost you to
make however many videos you made for 44
million views? $4,000. $4,000. Wow. You
got to be kidding me. We
$4,000. You are in the wrong business.
Am I getting all the products you guys
create going forward? Going forward.
Absolutely. Yes. I get the dream team.
Yes, of course you'd complete the dream
team. Okay, guys, I'm going to help you
out here, okay? Cuz that's the kind of
guy I am. I'll give you 45,000 for
40%. I got to tell you, it's the team.
Maybe it works, maybe it doesn't. I love
the three of you. You guys are an
ability to create the videos and the
marketing. I actually think there's a
great product within you. This may or
may not be it, but I'll go along for the
ride.
So, I'll tell you what I'm willing to
do. You basically got a third, a third,
a third. If I come in as a partner, a
very important one that's willing to
work hard on this, I'll do it if I get
25% so that we're all
equal. Stop thinking about it because
the clock is ticking and I want you out
of here with me as well. You actually
would not be a bad partner for you. And
you knew you would get you were going to
have to give up 25%. Yes or no?
Guys, we got a deal. We got a deal. Oh
yeah. Wow. We are going to take over the
world with this, guys. Thank you, man.
Hug it out. Hug it out. We're talking
the ketchup. We got all the sauces.
Mustard. You're the man. Thank you very
much. Now, let's go make hundreds of
dollars. All right.
Good luck. Congratulations, guys. See
you guys.
Sauce Moto is going to take up from
here. That's we know. Kevin's going to
open some doors for us. Now, everyone
can practice safe sauce. That's right.