chair up all right it's already
recording M if you want to go check it
really fast oh Nick that's good to get a
gator Gatorade if you're feeling down
yeah thanks yeah it's like electrolytes
that's good for you for
[Music]
sure hey guys like that big yellow troll
that Dora fight that Liv under the
bridge you know talking with a big
orange beard yeah yeah he looks like
Jason Mamoa I feel like he does just
like you're wrong like a little smaller
I wouldn't keep talking if I was this
wrong I don't know what this
[ __ ] looks like what are you
talking about Nick the troll from the
troll from Dora Matt you know exactly
who it is he got the big long orange
beard he's a big yellow Beast mhm troll
from Dora oh his name is literally
grumpy old troll like look up troll from
Dora his n's Google name oh he got TN is
grumpy old troll oh my God I love
him that's you Nick okay that's
literally you he's super cute looks like
that doesn't look looks like a prison
fit
oh going on here the fact that his name
is grumpy old troll is so funny we
missed a couple episodes here we missed
the party Jesus maybe her
ketta
maybe oh my
God the maps if you think about it like
inde depth like you put a lot of thought
to it there's really not much of a
difference between Dora and
Candyland what think about it there's
really not much of a difference between
Dora and Candyland she's just exploring
well you're just saying that cuz of
colorful paths you could say the same
thing about The Wizard of
Oz the wizard of has one colorful path
and you know it's the one you got to go
down the entire time yeah I don't know I
feel about what you just said all right
guys welcome back to another stero
triplets Friday content car
video dude save some for the fish
Jesus the fish I hate when [ __ ]
said that while I was drinking water at
school out of a water fountain yeah it's
school it's like there's never going to
be can I tell you something gross can I
have a gross confession you just put
your mouth over it every day yeah e in
first grade I used to put my mouth over
one of the water fountains because I
used to claim that it was just like like
I claimed in my own head and didn't tell
anybody that it was mine Nick don't say
[ __ ] I was like this is mine and I don't
care like anyone else who used this like
this is mine Nick keep that in your head
bro don't tell people that for like
months in a row don't tell people that
you would do this some [ __ ] like that
you also like used to like brush your
teeth and then like literally suck the
water out of the sink right there still
do that to this day yeah but you put
your mouth like all up on it like it's
the best way to get water straight from
no it's not you can get it while it's
dripping down for sure my allergies are
so bad I must State this first because
everyone's like why do you sound
different his voice is so different it's
cuz I'm I I have the worst allergies of
ever of my [ __ ] life I want to just
like if I could rip my head off and
shake it and put it back on I would
everything
out I just feel disgusting
and how do you keep the straight face
doing [ __ ] like that D I don't know it
was inside I feel disgusting and I'm
prefacing that now you want know what I
feel like right now what do you I feel
like bionic right now I don't know why
you don't even know what that word means
yeah like half robot like in with powers
half robot with powers yeah what what's
making you feel this way I don't know
like I just woke up from a nap and I
feel like I had to like re-calibrate and
I feel like my mind is somewhere else
than other than here I hate getting like
a salt packet just season it they do
it's just like if you want more salt
yeah but I get it I hate like the little
salt package it's almost like pity I I
disagree with your take on salt but I've
always said that parmesan cheese is a
personal thing yeah you're also like a
big sodium guy I feel like okay yeah you
are Nick call me King cholesterol too no
you like sodium a lot like salt I know
that about you like Nick always said
growing up like the perfect amount of
salt is right when you think you're done
doing a little
more you you have said that Nick you
have said that that's a quote from you
okay you said when you think there
enough salt two more shakes exactly okay
really
I I really want to see a redw a red
what's it called a redwood tree yes I
did a project on a redwood forest when I
was in fourth grade and I feel like now
that we live in California part of me is
just screaming go find the Redwoods I've
never met someone in my entire life that
refers so much to like school projects
outside of
school every like oh like we'll be
talking about a normal conversation oh
and second grade I did a project on this
or like like like anything well I just
think I was a very Hands-On learner so a
project is where I soaked in most of my
information we posted we posted an
Instagram story that said if you had to
pick between blank or blank sorry sorry
I'm so sorry
Mt I you never burp in the house well no
it's cuz I fuel up for the videos so I
dra a lot of Beverage we don't care
water water makes you burp if I drink a
whole thing in the second yeah we posted
an Instagram story that said if you had
to pick between blank or blank what
would you choose so
basically we give two examples music or
movies and you have to pick between
let's do it let's do it man uh music or
movies had to get if you pick one the
other one is gone forever I think that
music makes movies better when they have
like songs in movies yeah I was going to
say keep movies just because you can
like play a movie that has a good
soundtrack and like hear the songs in
the movie uh the I was going to say
songs are gone oh yeah I was going to
say it the total opposite way songs are
gone I was going to say if if I think
that there's some movies that songs make
the movie better then I think songs are
just more important of like a thing the
audio pack yeah the tech file Nick no
only with friends and I can't pick I
don't want to pick Nick you have to pick
I'm not going to pick Nick I love movies
but I also love music but here's a
really hot take that's my version of
M&M's music and
movies like never I can't even say what
does that like what does that even mean
bro like what are you been saying go
ahead also [ __ ] their Dum [ __ ] their
dumb melts in your mouth and not in your
hand had M&M's in the summer in New
England those [ __ ] melting on
everything I have Rainbow on my [ __ ]
hand go wash off M&M's also don't stand
for two who's had M&M who had M&M's melt
in their hand show of hands I am [ __ ]
ridiculous change your slogan it's the
old slogan to be fair they're not
throwing that around product got worse
no they're just not throwing that like
their new slogan is probably like like
nutty and chocolate fun like I don't
think it's like mov on moving on I don't
think it's like that slogan still Nut
Chocolate funf it's way better there's
no nuts in them Peanut M&M's Matt yeah
we're talking about original M&M's e
those are gross oh I don't want to say
that cuz of brand deal purposes what if&
have a br de here's a billion dollars
promote my little product
okay well what I was going to say is
M&M's don't stand I'm not doing sorry
I'm not doing a brand de with Eminem
unless they have one of the M&M's come
to my front door what I tell people
about us I want it to be one of the
M&M's or someone in know M&M costume
yeah no Matt go ahead what I was going
to say is M&M's don't stand for two
words that start with m&m yeah they do
no they don't yes they do two words I'll
goog movies that's your version nose
blowing break sorry guys blow that horn
you little
elephant that's insane I feel like Nick
is really like embodies like a baby
elephant that's a good he's going to
love that I think he will do you know a
baby elephant doesn't have full control
of his trunk so it kind of just like
lobs around and he doesn't know what to
do with it what are you talking about
right now I'm being honest what am I
doind you open how do you how do you say
I remind you of a baby Eminem and then
saying a baby Eminem has no control
over that baby elephant has no control
over his trunk it doesn't yeah that's
good well no they're just cute and like
clumsy and like w they got big years no
they're not gigantic not saying that I'm
to say is when we were picking between
music or movies I love music and I love
movies I really hate
musicals you hate the combination of it
yeah I don't like the the in the in
between so what would you pick I already
answered I was just like that's a good
point that's a good pointed me I was you
hate the big blend of it all if I want
keep them separate sure you want to see
Paradise willly Wonka's a musical that's
good I the new one no the old one I
think about it when Vera salt she was in
the room she's like I want the world
don't you have a funny video I was seen
that the other day I watched really long
in my room and I just couldn't get the
veroa salt song out of my head do you
want to see it
[Music]
okay my [ __ ] ass no you can't put that
in we could yeah but I've been going for
like don't put that in the video why
lose all of your memories or not be able
to create new ones lose all of them I
already do I forget
everything no I actually would hate to
have all that on yeah that's what I'm
saying that's like a die or live type of
one Tootsie Pop or Blow Pop Tootsie blow
oh we have a duel you guys should fist
fight there's no fist fighting a
lollipop suck off okay
that's good I'd be down for what the
lollipop suck off no more ninjas or no
more Pirates no more Pirates what get
out of the sea I love a ninja like a spy
like a like a pirates are way cooler
than ninja I strongly disagree I feel
more influenced by Pirates every day
than I ever have ninjas I agree because
ninjas are be being too stealthy to have
an a um uh effect on you that's why I'm
saying we don't need them if they're so
stealthy and they're like they only move
through Darkness it's like what do we
really need them for the Pirates have a
much more fun story but what are pirates
going to do
nowadays I have any if we already at
ninjas would we still have Batman yeah I
feel like he's a ninja no he's more of
um um he's more of a um what's the word
visual anti okay dude literally just qu
they're quoting the movie visual an is
like a it's like a
um I'm not wearing hocky pant I love the
[ __ ] dark night it's such a good
intro would you rather meet your
soulmate or meet Abraham Lincoln Abraham
Lincoln is my soulmate check check Nick
you're weird we're killing two birds
with one stone would you kiss Abe
absolutely on the forehead and be like
I'm so proud of you Abe he's just an
amazing
man I feel like Abe would tap dance like
I feel like there's there times in the
white house where he got loose like he
just like tapped his way to like a song
OG fortnite or OG Pokemon go OG for [ __ ]
Pokémon go Pokémon go got me out of the
house in the OG days and I would like
run around with friends and have fun and
get exercise so this is actually valid
duel I would say I think fortnite had a
bigger impact on my life yeah quite
clearly it's very evident to everybody
Nick shut up paper cutter Splinter I'd
rather get a splinter yeah see I think
taking a splinter out is so satisfying
like just removing that little piece of
wood from your skin okay it's way better
than getting oh my God I have [ __ ] ah
my hands are are so strange I'm going to
throw of paper at you Nick one by one
slide them by your body go ahead mat oh
my God that was little done talking
gazebo or Fortress we what Chris what
we're doing the pick one eliminate one
for
Fortress take a guess what do you
envision in your head that's exactly
what it is I vintage I vintage I en
Vision like a [ __ ] like a medieval
castle okay so would you rather have
that or a gazebo gazebos I've never been
in a medieval Castle I would clearly
pick a fortress I feel like that's a
such an obvious one Fortress like what
is happening Nick a fortress or gazebo
Reese pups or Cocoa Pebbles Reese's
Puffs are Cocoa Pebbles Reese's Puffs
have like that weird like paste almost
to them yeah Cocoa Pebbles Puffs Coco
Puffs Puffs pebbl it's Pebbles n [ __ ]
the Pebbles that's what I'm saying oh
Coco Pebbles are [ __ ] I think you said
Puffs I said Pebbles I think he said
Puffs did he say puff say Pebbles Cocoa
Puff
Pebbles what did he say he said Pebbles
pebbles no it's Reese's pups are better
than pebbles for sure [ __ ] yeah yeah
yeah I agree have like a glaz no wait
Reese you're talking the chocolate Cocoa
Puffs cuckoo for Cocoa Puff no I'm
talking Cocoa Pebbles the the the Flint
Stones yes I don't like that [ __ ] Cocoa
Pebbles are actually dog cocoa pffs are
fire I'm not asking you about Cocoa
Puffs I don't care about Cocoa Puffs I
said one thing and you're talking all
this [ __ ] about Coco Puff Coco C Puffs
goo Puffs okay
dude what are you doing nothing that
just funny okay I love the orange bird
like the Cocoa Puff mascot wrong isn't
it a
monkey it's a bir am I tripping that
hard it's not like a you're thinking no
no what are you thinking of a a [ __ ]
monkey right it's clear as day it's he's
orange and he has a big yellow beak and
he always goes cuckoo yeah he's so cool
yeah he's the lest I love him I like his
haircut he needs help um would you
rather go cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs or tell
the rabbit that tricks are for
kids um I'd probably rather tell the
rabbit tricker for kids cuz usually it's
like three kids saying it in unison I
just want to be a part of the group you
know what I mean silly rabbit like we
can all be tricker for kids we said it
together I feel like we should do that
as a video is like stand at the grocery
store and anyone who's not a kid who
tries to get we're not doing that anyone
who tries to get um we're not kicked out
of a grocery store in like 30 seconds
what is it called shower or brush your
teeth you can you can never do one of
them again
shower never brush again obviously feel
s brush again I need both I need both
never brush again I love brushing my
teeth the other day I brushed my teeth
four times in one in like an hour rocker
Pebble rocker Pebble that sounds like a
band tonight The Rocker pebble is going
to be and they go crazy for The Rocker
pebble
okay um New Hampshire or Vermont they're
the like potato potato it's like gutter
that's how I
feel's Gutter and what I was going to
you going to say rain drain is yes rain
the rain
drain oh my God I went into that show on
Nickelodeon brain surge what was what
the oh my God I can't no I could I can't
think about that cuz I get so mad every
single time I see one of those
[ __ ] on the on the memory walk
thing where it like plays oh my God it's
like a straight line they're like
jumping left and right and it's like you
had one [ __ ] job you go straight all
the way across and you win like [ __ ]
whatever the [ __ ] the electric scooter
the microwave coing and the trip to the
[ __ ] Fiji islands and all you have to
do is jump to the left instead of right
you've seen the path six different times
and you're jumping to the right at the
end you want know who would be really
bad at that who you yeah I know you're
you'd be one of the people that watch on
TV and I'd be like look at this this
[ __ ] idiot I just forget so fast they
probably on purposely got people like
you
cuz those [ __ ] idiots are going to
just jump around and there my shortterm
memory is just really bad I don't know
what it is I need to get like I need to
go learn about it time's up do you guys
remember was Danielle bergoli the host
of that show Trina Vega the brain surch
Danielle bergoli is catch me
outside that's bad baby that's not Trina
Vega no she's what's her name Danielle
boli no that's that's a bad baby that's
that's that's the [ __ ] d yellow Bol
is the girl with Gucci flip-flop yeah
that is not Trina Vega oh what's her
name you're thinking of her sister no
Monae Daniel Monet yeah not Danielle
boli different person that's so funny
different imagine Danielle boli hosting
brain surge oh my God she didn't host
that show she hosted the par she hosted
Paradise run Nick yeah oh I just got
chills on
hold on hold on guys hold on do they
exit or did they arrive in a slide I
forget exit exit into the Slime yep okay
well the whole slide was filled with
like soap and goop like
gush thick crust guy or thin crusty thin
crust thin crust till I die unless it's
poofy and doughy like it has the like
little like CR well you're contradicting
yourself actively no thick crust that's
like chunky is gross but like thick
crust with like the Airy inside and the
nice texture is nice I'm more like M
this is hard dude I'm not going to beat
you up over it I want you to beat me up
over it okay dude say pick one then it
crust oh oh oh y don't actually HT
you're so weird Nick got some thin crust
never talk about my crust
again if you were all something from a
pizza joint what would you be uh I call
Di on being a Garlic Knot I'd be black
olives never you can never have
breakfast again Chris you could have
breakfast food just not breast WAFF I
think breakfast isn't categorized as a
food it's car categorized as let me ask
this question again breakfast food or
dinner food rest of your life which one
dinner dinner food all breakfast food is
gone absolutely it's not an argument
French toast waffles think about the
amount of different things you can have
for dinner Matt think about the amount
of different things you can have for
dinner no yeah you you just listed off
breakfast food because there's so few
that you can just do right in one little
count what do eggs count as breakfast
food yes everyone pray for Nick he has a
stuffy nose pray for Nick has a stuffy
nose I think I'll make it the [ __ ] pray
for neck what I'm totally
fine everybody Nick has
allergies report to the media we need
you all to reach out Nick has allergies
report to all the tissue Brands make
good guys I'm going to do one full day
of updating the people on Nick every
move Nick just grabbed a drink from the
fridge Chris I think I'd actually cut
your arm off Nick why would you do that
so you can stop touching your phone if
you did that that's sayte Nick just woke
up in like a photo Nick's allergies are
not getting better and I'm going to post
it well guys sorry I was clearly sick in
this video I don't feel good but it's
okay The Show Must Go
On okay the greatest show got David bla
the next thing you're going to see is a
tiger jump through a hoop like what are
you talking
about going do the tight rope trapas
artists are next right after
this can get some cotton candy while
you're
waiting you're a [ __ ] oh that's a
good one all right guys make sure you're
shopping our merch from the link down
below we're super close to 6 million
subscribers yes so the next merch drop
is going to be our six mil merch yeah
yeah also shop space camp wellness.com
yes yes wait wait staring contest with
the viewers go no I'm not doing this why
I can't [ __ ]
[Music]
blink