it smells like legit pu outside Fu reeks
pu is crazy no it smells like pu I'm
going to get the the the clothes pin and
pinch my nose yeah you're
funny [ __ ]
whoa neither of you have anything
Christmas at all that was insane that's
the whole point of
this wait I'm really Blown Away where's
your guys like Christmas like headband
or lights or something here you go wait
hold on are you guys pranking me and you
like have stuff no Nick we have nothing
you [ __ ] idiot what's the point of
the Christmas
special what is the actual [ __ ] point
of the whole thing I wore Reb that is
not I would say this is a Christmas
themed sweater that's better I'm like
actually thrown by the fact that you
guys don't what are we going to do Nick
I'm thrown are we all going to die I'm
shocked shocked yeah I'm allowed to be
shocked this is surprising it's the
Christmas special and you guys have
nothing [ __ ] Christmas related to you
at all you're sitting here eating
pizza yeah what about what did my pizza
have to do with your [ __ ] annoying
ass I'm just blown away all right let's
get into the topic on today's video
today's video I like to I've never
really seen you like intro let him do
it it makes me happy I like it cuz I get
interrupted so for this week's video
Nick made a little poll thing and he
said if you give us something you did
that's nice and give us something you
did that's naughty and we're going to
see what out
shame and we're going to see what
outweighs the other and decide whether
you're on the naughty list this year or
the nice list this
year I don't like naughty can we do like
good or bad list na it's naughty or nice
it's been naughty nice like why do we
have to be naughty that's good OG Santa
it's fine yeah of course you guys want
to be naughty Matt's naughty Matt would
totally be on the naughty list dude I
kind of hacked into my own phone I'm 16
and when I got got my first phone my mom
installed this app to lock app to lock
my phone at a certain bedtime she said
she would you're 16 years old she said
she would take it off when I turned 13 3
years later my phone still locks at 9:30
at night I figured out the passcode to
unlock it at night so now I can I could
have my phone after 9:30 she still
doesn't know I unlock my phone good
thank God keep it that way [ __ ] freom
that was her naughty thing here's her
nice thing I got my job I got my first
job and saved enough money to buy to get
everyone Christmas presents this year
get nothing for your mom she doesn't
deserve it she's being relentless 9:30
bedtime is crazy you're what 16 uh she's
on the nice list
definitely wa yeah like her naughty
thing that she did I would have done
correct I agree and it's like anyone
with the sane mind would have done your
mom should make the naughty list for
being an annoying parent period just
saying IED peppers you got a full salad
well so there was a situation he wanted
oh God yeah cheated on my essay by
stealing by sneaking in notes I still
think about it to this day and I feel
guilty no one don't worry about it uh
the nice thing made the new girl at the
school feel welcome and became friends
with her you're amazing you're on the
nice list you're on the [ __ ] nice
list for sure one time I cheated on an
exam I wrote the whole quiz down on the
back of my leg you're not
cheating know what's more hey to cheat
in school did I give you napkins a
minute ago no to cheat in school you
want to know what that means you're
doing trying putting in effort M so you
get an A all around yep well also what's
more important than doing well in school
classes and courses and grades is making
sure that all the students have a sense
of community oh Nick wow I hate the
community okay I accidentally got the
cops called on my best friend and then I
lied about it but my what but my
intentions were good I swear um that's
all she said I'm confused I don't buy it
so far we're gonna need we're going to
need a good nice to keep to keep off the
correct the whole car is shaking Nick
yeah for Thanksgiving I put together
food and a backpack of Essentials for
homeless guy that lives in my city she
had the most nice thing but the most ner
naughty naughty in the middle naughty
naughty I'd love to know what your
intentions were cuz you're swearing that
they're
good yeah how do you acally call the
cops and your best friend maybe her best
friend was like doing something bad and
she needed the cops called on her and
she like didn't want to do it but she
had it was the right thing to do no I
don't think she called the cops I think
she told their
mom what where what you oh she's not
doing like something good and the mom's
oh so you think she snitched I
accidentally got the cops called on my
best friend and then lied about it but
my intentions were good I like I think
she was fearful something bad she was
like talking to like a parent or other
friends and they called the police
you're totally just guessing in the
scenario aren't
you this sounds not good this is a
really long one so strap in are we ready
don't you don't have to actually put
your seat belt on the
joke okay they said naughty crazy word
word use I know she agreeing with you
she doesn't like the word naughty yeah
but typing out's weird like her that was
you vocalized the exact same thought
different than what I did publicly
shamed someone AC after she had she had
wrongly accused me of something and made
her cry and beg for forgiveness in front
of the entire school oh my God beg for
forgiveness what are you to be head her
at the end of The
Classy thing like the [ __ ] Game of
Thrones wait I need you to read it again
um this girl tormented me and publicly
shamed someone after she had wrongly
accused me of something the wording is
insane made her cry and beg for
forgiveness in front of the entire
school that was a passage that was
literally a passage that wasn't even
like a text like the intro to a
character in a show yes literally here's
ni I was wrongfully done so I made her
beg for mercy in the schoolyard made
sure I was I was not going anywhere made
sure I was a safe space for All My
Friends by walking through some of their
hardest moments with them keeping their
secrets giving them advice and making
sure they felt listened to oh so you did
the bare minimum as a friend you're on
the naughty list dummy you just sound
corny correct she said even though no
one has done something like that for me
even though I oh and you're crying even
though I struggle with my feelings of
even though no one did it for me listen
know what she's about to say I put a
brave face on every day so that I can be
their strength first okay that's all
love you guys blah corre blah blah blah
blah blah blah how about someone who's
so like oh you need someone there for
you you're publicly shaming somebody
correct you're on the naughty list
without a doubt like you're you're
naughty list you might be on the naught
predicts what your nice thing is yeah
you may listen to your friends but
someone has to be your friend for to
them not be publicly ridiculed are you
sick correct let's go back to the
naughty one more time publicly shamed
someone after she had wrongly accused me
of something and made her cry and beg
for forgiveness you talk like you're
writing a book and that I don't like
yeah I can just tell she makes
everything a big deal like everything's
a big deal okay
oh what happened did you see that
no go ahead Matt sorry sorry I know you
hate when I burp I know you don't have
to do the [ __ ] of the CR sign of the
cross just I'm sorry I'm sorry just
never do it again that's worse than
burping whatever you just
did that was so rude for context I'm 6
feet tall and my brother and I are only
15 months fls right away though we are
close in age my brother is still
significantly shorter and smaller than I
am which is often something I forget one
time we were joke fighting and he
accidentally scratched and jammed my
nose into my face which obvious viously
made my whole face jolt in my eyes water
and it legit filled me with so much
anger and rage I full on five starred
him in the back and no joke the slap
echoed through my house and it sounded
like a gunshot or something similar I
don't think it matters that much because
he hit you first he hit you first you
guys are also siblings siblings are
going to have moments correct he hit you
first but also like I don't think the 64
thing the six foot thing was necessary
at all I agree I think she just wanted
to tell us that she was tall 64 and he's
shorter than me which I often forget
what you what do you remember when you
walk next to this is her nice thing is
nice but Nick's going to freak out
Nick's going to actually freak out
unplug those ears big boy I recently got
elected to be a American Red Cross Blood
conductor where
ictor where I where I run and host blood
drives through my city ew I've run up to
nine drives a year and so far I've
collected no no 300 p no no no okay good
thing but thanks a lot never tell me
again correct someone has to do someone
has to do it though and she's doing good
so I put her on the nice list she
retaliated which like okay you shouldn't
have hit him back but it's okay he
didn't he probably whatever you guys
made up I think you're on the nice list
you're doing something very nice nice
list Nice List get out I threw a
basketball on my brother's face and his
nose started bleeding but then I gave
him a piece of salad to cheer him
okay that's it nice a piece of salad
would not Tri I was about to say a piece
of salad you punched me in the face and
my nose started bleeding you gave me a
piece of salad I would drag your face on
cement ever correct it doesn't make any
[ __ ] sense oh sorry oh
sorry sorry that relax something nice I
did was I helped my best friend who I've
known since s kindergarten go through a
difficult breakup something bad I did
this year was lie to my my mom saying I
actually did something when I knew I
didn't BL blah blah blah you Mak no
[ __ ] sense I don't know I don't got
enough boring boring I told my mom
something I did I didn't do and my best
friend broke up helped her I bought a
varsity jacket at the Rose Bowl this
year and it had the name of a high
school on it and the student it belonged
to I then proceeded to find the former
owner on Instagram just out of curiosity
and ended up reaching out to her she
said she would pay me for the varsity
jacket so I sent it back to her a couple
months later I got a letter from her dad
saying their house had been robbed from
her childhood was taken including old
photos of her with her mom who died when
she was young but she was happy that she
could at least get this back my mom was
mad at me for getting rid of the varsity
jacket but I think I did the right thing
[ __ ] your mother
thoughts million per did the right thing
what is your mom needs to stop talking
indefinitely
forever what Mom isn't proud of someone
doing the right thing that's like when
you're like a kid at the store and
there's like the last of something
whatever and you like let the other kid
buy it or something like that the mom is
always like oh be the bigger person be
kind to others your mom's teaching you
the opposite things of cor your mom's
doing the negative thing like are you
[ __ ] crazy correct Nice List like
literally went out of your way to reach
out and find the owner who had such a
Sentimental story and you shipped it
back and gave it to her and now your
mom's mad re-evaluate sister
I hate your mother correct holy [ __ ] you
can buy another varsity
jacket no it was that was it thoughts it
depends how rude the person on Instagram
was if she was like oh yeah that's mine
give it back yeah or if she was like oh
my God my house like burn well also we
don't need a Saab story for no
reason like that like like all the
information you get like oh this is so
crazy I bought your jacket at the Rose
Ball oh my house was Burg yeah just have
it back shut up holy [ __ ] you're saying
so much I don't care she got the letter
lathered though if I heard that
much I would have been like holy [ __ ]
I'm dizzy trying to fall along stop
talking correct take your jacket I'm
literally giving it back to you sh shut
up
here
[Music]
oh [ __ ] cartoon ass motorcyc cartoon
motorcycle you know you're not allowed
to trespass in Pokémon go
yeah we're
all you're not allowed to trespass
anywhere in real life Matt
you the Cho salad no I just spilled this
all over my feet like my feet Matt how M
are you this whole car was nice and
clean oh yeah it's a little wet down
there ew Nick put your yesterday my
neighbor was putting up Christmas lights
outside their house at the same time
they were doing this I was taking my dog
out my neighbor then asked me to put the
ladder away while he was on his roof
roof so I didn't question anything and I
put the ladder on the side of their
house and went back inside I went back
outside 2 hours later to take my dog out
again but ended up also seeing my
neighbor stranded on his roof he didn't
tell me to put away the ladder he told
me to get away from the ladder because
he didn't want me to bump into it or my
dog to bump into it I couldn't fully
hear him when he was on the roof because
I had my airpods on that was her naughty
thing okay oh my God why would you take
the ladder away but my thought is I at
first I was going to be mad at the
neighbor like [ __ ] this guy why is he
asking you to move the ladder inantly
unless you're you're just saying hey
move I'm on a ladder you're probably the
most obnoxious person ever and love
getting in people's face cuz in order
for him to say something you need to be
right up next to that ladder and in
order for you to fully grab it and put
it away you're [ __ ] crazy correct and
he didn't want her to bump into it oh my
God he was looking out for you you're
just D your neighbor lawn get off his
lawn okay I just I just wouldn't
understand it like if I have my airpods
in and someone like murmured something
all I heard was a ladder how about what
excuse me how about what the [ __ ] did
you just I can hear you clearer so I
don't have to strand you your my problem
is she had to fully grab the ladder put
it down put it into his what was he
doing the whole time he should have been
going hey hey hey he's also bring the
ladder back everyone's an idiot for the
naughty I accidentally fed my grandma's
dog a piece of chocolate cake on
Thanksgiving because he was begging for
it I didn't know it would I didn't know
it would kill him you're begging for it
I didn't know it would kill him yeah
insane as for the nice thing I wrote my
grandma a very good apology card for
killing her dog bare minimum people need
to understand rebuttal your [ __ ] dumb
action is not nice a bare minimum to be
a good
person you [ __ ] idiot agreed also Dog
101 don't give them chocolate I agree
hello easiest thing ever easiest thing
ever oh he's Begg for he's begging for
it he's the [ __ ] dog dog's beg hello
let that click on your head dogs beg I
can have a [ __ ] bag of watermelon
seeds and the dog would beg I could be
walking through the room with bleach and
cleaning supplies the dog will beg you
rustle anything the dog's going to
[ __ ] beg it's dogs do use your head
so would you give him bleach if he
begged no cuz I have [ __ ] two brain
cells to rub together gra that's it just
two at least also go to one piece of
chocolate cake you're
weak no dog is proba last anyway one
piece of chocolate cake Trevor our dog
is eaten an entire PL brownies BR like
to go to One Piece of Cake you're ran
away with my ex-boyfriend we were
missing for 3 Days me and my family
decided to host a foreign exchange
student from Thailand that's their
positive and negative negative I don't
think your family should have the
allowance to host a foreign exchange
student if you're [ __ ] running away
for years I agree okay this is getting
personal really really fast you're
[ __ ] running away and then allowing
someone else into your home use your
head you're not
suitable I agree I once went on a an ice
skating Rank and I was bored so I
started tripping people on the ice for
fun F you're an idiot worst you that's
how you kill someone people die people
get sliced you're on blades I ended up
tripping this kid and breaking his arm
yeah [ __ ] you you're a der I skated away
and pretended I didn't do anything but
the child's mom caught me and apologized
with the family said they weren't going
to press charges because it was an
accident Fu it wasn't in parenthesis
you're an absolute douche I never went
to the ice skating rank again good good
there was basically a guy I liked in my
class but I didn't have the nerves to go
talk to him so me and my friend decided
that it would be funny to make a
Snapchat stock account weird you're
[ __ ] weird if anyone ever comment and
name it I see you oh I even added his
friends and every single day he would
walk let me get a napkin I just smack
that bug you see that you killed a bug
can you guys stop talking you go o that
one looks every single day after school
I would talk to his
friends after school and I would tell
him what he wore and what he did that
day you would think it was an obvious
joke but it was it was went on for so
long no you that's the that's the
problem that's the problem it isn't
obious
I see you you're a [ __ ] weiro the
last thing on earth I would think spit
every the last thing on earth I would
think that is it's a obvious joke I
would think it's someone coming after me
to kill me you're an obvious he ended up
telling the teachers the whole grade had
to meet up together and the teachers
told us the person could be in serious
trouble good if you're making a stock
account with your buddies for fun you're
a [ __ ] weirdo you know that that
happened to me once what not a stock
account but I remember when I was in um
like 7th and 8th grade these two people
that we are not friends with at all
anymore and I hate them both so much
with like every fiber in my [ __ ]
being made a like catfish Instagram
account dm' me on it and like asked me
for a Snapchat and sent me photos while
we were all hanging out together what
they were with us yeah we were all at
house and
[ __ ] made an account it was before I
had come out or anything so I think they
like knew that I was gay and like trying
to get to the bottom of it and I'm just
now remembering this and they basically
made an account using like catfish
profile photos and like DM me on
Instagram and like added me on Snapchat
and I literally found out in like under
3 hours on that day cuz they were like
saying [ __ ] that I was doing in that
moment and I was like what the [ __ ] look
at what this person's like Snapchatting
me or talking me about and they were
like oh it's us the internet's a scary
[ __ ] place I was like you guys are
the worst people ever yeah people that
do that [ __ ] are [ __ ] lame as [ __ ]
really weird I see you the name of the
account and then describing what they're
doing in the day you don't understand
how that's an issue I would literally
get driven insane genuinely fears me
that this person their takeaway was I
got in trouble for no reason there's
definitely a [ __ ] reason actually
psychotic
correct and crazy correct I'm honestly a
good person but the naughtiest thing I
did this year is absolutely diabolical
and I wish I could go back and change
this but my dad was having an affair
with some other woman so he was cheating
on my mom dude have to tell us
everything I know you know what I mean
we're just YouTubers yeah we don't need
to know this is for fun I found some
condoms in his lunch bag and I thought
why why would you need condoms in your
work lunch bag so I decided to poke some
holes in them and H put jalapeno sauce
to see if he would you know this is fake
it's fake it's fake fake it's fake so he
did that N9 months ago guess what who
has a babysit lie lie lie Li saying she
has a baby sister PS the baby sisters
with the lady was affair with
the you're weird you're
weird is also a blind man walked into me
from behind and I felt so guilty but I
didn't see him he kept apologizing and I
kept telling him I'm sorry and said it
was okay then he proceeded to walk into
a table who walked this isn't a naught
nothing na or nice get out of the Blind
Man's way yeah you couldn't see him he
couldn't see you for sure so get out of
the way Matt no need to hate on the
blind I'm not no that's a point it's
like how are you going to get bumped
into by a blind man and have your excuse
me I couldn't see him he's blind he
definitely can see I can see a blind man
coming from an hour away and get out of
the way it's not it's like a mile away
that's an hour but also it's like blind
people usually move with some like like
caution they can't see so you you have
to be in the way like first a lot of
blind people I feel like are fearless
like I see someone just moving around oh
this has to be a fake story I and I
liked it
what after I attended his funeral and I
and now I can't stop thinking about him
either I volunteered in a dog shelter
and I donated to poor people and babies
they're
good like I don't know what that even is
at work I told a customer to go [ __ ]
themselves but I was nice to most of the
other
customers love that I don't know I feel
like a lot of people's naughty this year
are a little too naughty go do something
kind we want to see everybody on the Nic
list next year well happy Friday and
welcome to aern little Christmas we will
see you guys on Wednesday's Mondays and
Fridays with a bunch of content lined up
for you
guys and then what you saying how you
miss me yeah you miss me and all the
things that we did we said we going to
travel from the is to Madrid we had a
lot of plans but
they why because of someid but it's okay
cuz I'm moving different don't be saying
nothing when I PST up with other [ __ ]
P for my brothers