there was a lot of fight within the
company out of 100 projects which one do
we keep it alive we should actually keep
some of it instead of dropping rest of
the 99 problems but I said no we have to
be the master of a one single product
and one single problem we don't have
resources to dilute our Focus I think I
made the right call those 99 Problems 99
products didn't matter if you have one
single killer item that's going to carry
all the way through
[Music]
hello my name is hin Lee I'm the captain
of Soul robotics Soul robotics is a B2B
autonomous driving company so when you
think about autonomous driving there's
company like Tesla and way while they
provide robotaxi services or a
autonomous driving service that you can
use on the public road we to be
autonomous driving is not like that we
provide autonomous driving Services
where there's a lot of driver shortage
we are currently focusing on two major
areas first is finished vehicle
Logistics when the car is manufactured
somebody has to drive these cars to the
ship or train or truck this requires 200
people perfect relocation for the car
makers currently simply there's not
enough drivers out out there who's
providing this type of Labor forces so
we are providing autonomous driving
system to move these cars autonomously
so that the the car can be transported
safely to your doorstep the Second Use
case we're focusing on as a B2B
autonomous driving company is that we
are focusing on the logistics centers
when you order a product that product
has to go through a large logistic
centers within this logistic centers
there is lot of manual driving needs to
be done somebody needs to move the car
to be charged to be cleaned to move to
the third floor or second floor we have
13 different nationality and now we've
been focusing on the B2B autonomous
driving for the last 3 4
years I went to us when I was 12 Junior
High small boarding school that's where
I spent my youth and then I went to Penn
State I guess that was my youth but
actually I want to rewind my clock L
back before I went to us until 12 I was
in Korea but my parents thought man the
robotics is going to be future well this
is early 2000 and when I went to Penn
State I studied mechanical engineering
thinking that well if I want to do
robotics I got to be able to build the
robots but I realized as I was studying
mechanical engineering the robotics is
not a hardware problem it is so much a
software problem that's where I as soon
as I graduated I started to study
software by myself but and then I came
back to Korea I went to Korean army cuz
I'm Korean citizen so I spent 2 years in
the Army as a tank mechanic so that was
pretty fun right after finishing my duty
as a tank tank mechanic in the Korean
army I started looking into studying Ai
and self-driving with groups of people
in 2016 I thought while the industry is
new They Don't Really teach Ai and
self-driving in the school yet and this
autonomous driving Market is just going
to be massive so why don't we start a
company to see how it can go so 2017
August with four of the co-founders I
started so robotics really not knowing
exactly what Market we're going to go
after our company started with the study
group that studied Ai and self-driving
and there was a competition the study
group attended the competition and the
competition member became the foundation
of s Robotics and I was the captain of
that study group and that title still
stuck with me so still today after 8
years my title is still Captain that's a
founding chapter of s
robotics so our our first business model
which was again this Sol robotics was my
first kick it still is we didn't a whole
lot we knew our computer vision
technology was pretty good so our first
approach was going after the oems so
first couple years we really chased
after that the amount of the capital
resource that we had we couldn't go
after kind of full autonomous driving
system and have a business model that
generates Revenue at the same time it
was going to be a very long-term just
purely R&D focused effort it turns out
that first of all the car makers
themselves moves extremely slowly and
they're very conservative and we
realized that man this trying to sell
our system to OEM is just not going to
work without then what else what else
can we do since then we did bunch of
different autonomous driving projects
there's about 100 different project that
we worked on sometimes we add a little
bit of systems Control Systems maybe
camera systems we are working as an
Outsourcing company but a lot of this
project just weren't scaling I got to
feel that man this is going to be tough
to commercialize there is simply not
enough forerunners who have shown that
using this kind of system redu ES cost
or improves efficiency by significant
amount to really widely adopt this type
of technology for their B2B use cases
the first major client was BMW so they
had a very interesting problem problem
so significant that all the way to the
sea level they wanted to solve this
problem and the problem was when they
make the car somebody has to pick up
this car manually and drive them into
the train station and this drive was
anywhere 1 km 2 km or 3 km you need to
have three four shifts of workers
driving these cars and it's a large
Factory you need a lot of people to do
this in the automotive history this has
been never been automated so it has been
always driven by humans and that's the
problem they want to solve because
simply they couldn't find enough people
to drive these cars and so this was one
of our 100 project 99 failed and this
project succeeded that's how we had a
first glimpse of B2B aut autonomous
[Music]
driving if I were to kind of explain
what B2B autonomous driving is Tesla is
not going to provide autonomous driving
for every industry segment you can use
Uber app you can use Facebook app but
these are running on backend system of
AWS and AWS makes a whole lot of money
from all these companies AWS is a B2B
cloud system you guys might know company
like Oracle database related company or
Salesforce who maintains the database of
clients for companies and these are
purely a B2B driven backend server so to
say companies and B2B autonomous driving
is like that we are a specific domain
autonomous Driving Systems so that the
societies can operate we're the backbone
we the backend autonomous driving system
for the society that's how I like to
think of what we
do the difference between average and
the best maybe 100 to one yeah so our
technology is quite unique it's very
different from weo and Tesla first of
all we are still predominantly using lar
second of all these Lars are not on the
cars themselves these Lars are installed
around the infrastructures you'll be
able to see there's a poles and then
there's camera and the lighters
installed around the facility we have
embedded our robotic system into the
factory ground or into the building
itself what we have essentially done is
is along the path of this car has to
drive we have installed these poles
these sensors and then these cars will
be guided from this infrastructure
system the software is identical to the
standard self-driving which it goes into
the car we just have expanded on that
idea to turn the infrastructure itself
into a self-driving machine now when you
do that you can solve a lot of critical
issues that cannot be solved by a
conventional method first of all you
don't have to install hundreds and
thousands of dollars of sensors per car
you just need to install handful of
sensors around the infrastructure second
of all the issue with current
self-driving is that it cannot handle
heavy weather scenarios because when it
rains when it snows the sensors are are
blocked by precipitation but when you're
using infrastructure first of all you're
bypassing that limitation because the
sensors are installed lot closer to each
other so that firstable you can mitigate
just for the shortage of sensors cuz you
have just a lot more of them so kind of
brute forcing this Problem by just
putting more infrastructure system into
it but obviously second of all it's not
about the hardware it's about learning
how to fuse those immense amount of
sensor data processing them with the
data that you have collected for last 6
years to AI to figure out what is rain
what is snow what is noise and filter
all those out to exactly identify where
my fleet of cars are now this technology
which we call autonomy 3 infrastructure
gets to solve a very almost is ur
byproduct by doing so this was going to
be solving one of the critical issue for
the specially B2B use cases because the
cars needed to move in Fleet groups of
five groups of 10 groups of 50 groups of
100 cars and the current technology of
autonomous risings wasn't going to solve
that but if you're having infrastructure
system orchestrates fleets of car
simultaneously all of a sudden you can
move the fleets of cars safely we didn't
take the path of the least resistance we
just took the path of what kind of makes
sense to solve this problem at step by
step and it turns out that our system is
actually extremely cheap to deploy
because conventional method you need to
install systems for 100 cars for us it's
a small parking lot handful of sensors
then you can move hundreds of cars
simultaneously so CES and especially
Nvidia is they're looking into 10 15 20
years in the future now they're painting
a picture of what in is to be and they I
think they coined the term Fiscal AI
most breakthrough application is going
to be Robotics and fiscal AI is simply
AI agent going all the way to actuating
robotic arms and what's the difference
between robotic arms and engine of the
car it's the same it's a self-driving
system or you could call it humanoid
robotics etc etc etc and it is still few
more years away from commercialization
but it's slowly getting there and
physical AI as well eventually it's
going to get there what I admire about
Tesla and wayo is that they stuck to the
problem with the original design for
actually longer than anybody else with
extremely Talent groups of Engineers
this physical AI I think it just means
that there's more degree of Freedom
robotics being rolled out for many
different application human a robot
being kind of the epitome of that
application use cases but I think if
robotex and human is kind of similar as
it's like a b2c application get be
widely used for everybody else I think
it's going to be the same there's going
to be a lot of sectors actually that you
need to provide product for B2B use
cases for tunnel driving and there's
going to be a lot of Robotics for B2B
use cases as well that might not look
like Humanity robotics maybe somewhere
in between of those large industrial
robotics that you see in the car
factories and the human robotics a lot
of Robotics that goes into B2B sector is
somewhere in between it is going to be
the future it is
fixed thing that's always a big mistake
is going after a giant market on on day
one
I think one of the thing was a pivot
again we pivoted several times until we
kind of settle down on this B2B
autonomous driving and there was a lot
of fight within the company out of 100
projects which one do we keep it alive
we should actually keep some of it
instead of dropping rest of the 99
problems but I said no we have to be the
master of a one single product and one
single problem we don't have resources
to dilute our Focus I think I made the
right call those 9 99 Problems 99
products didn't matter if you have one
single killer item that's going to carry
all the way through I don't want to use
Samsung as a bad example but you know
Samsung and tsmc tsmc just focus on the
single fling you know Apple and Samsung
Apple focuses on a very handful of
products Samsung does a lot of things if
you look at the pure evaluation how the
market perceives those two three
companies tsmc and Apple has an higher
evaluation than Samsung I think that
makes sense one risk that has massive
upside that if I failed in this it's
okay because that was a massive upside
instead of the mediocre Market
distribute our focus on different
autonomous driving projects that was
just going to be mediocre all all around
and that's the risk of starting a
company if you fail we fail but if you
succeed in this one market segment that
is going to be so massive that just it
wouldn't be matter and that kind of
thing as the company grew people had a
different opinions about what kind of
product to build what kind of focus we
need to have multi-product strategy
multiple a strategy etc etc etc I didn't
like that I think those were some of the
kind of
learnings let's take for example Tesla
they started with focusing on the
electric motor itself they actually
could build a pretty good powerful
Efficient Electric Motor so they start
building that only and west of the car
component they just kind of Outsource it
battery car body or whatever the next
thing was the battery Focus on the
better technology was going to be very
important for Tesla's future and then
after that they were trying to sell the
car using the body of somebody else's
and they learned that okay you actually
got to build the body frame around your
core technology to build a solid product
that you can sell and Tesla actually
worked on Outsourcing some of their
Battery Technology and the power train
technology in the early days so they
were doing some of the Outsourcing
before they built their first product of
the model S but that is building one
success on top of each other to build
vertical Iz ation of Technology into a
singular solid product that outperforms
everybody else's so is we kind of took
the similar approach when it comes to
tunel driving perception was the most
important thing so we really delve
deeply into solving the computer vision
problem on top of that we were medling
around many different applications but
we found that in order to serve the B2B
autonomous driving problems we got to
build the entire product not just the
perception side we got to build the
planning and we got to build control we
got to build a system around that to
make our product work so that kind of
verticalization was extremely important
in order for that to work you still
actually got to own that core
differentiation technology for yourself
you can Outsource that and I think
that's one of the problem that a lot of
existing car makers are having cuz their
core technology is not batteries or
software or electrical motor it's
assembling parts so this core technology
differentiation is kind of showing the
impact
today we want to kind of Rebrand
ourselves and I thought te is just the
perfect domain for our website so
robotics. te sound perfect for our new
chapter that's why we chose Tech domain
if you're a hardcore tech company te
seems like the Just Right Choice like
hardcore robotics especially it's the
perfect domain autonomous driving that
we know is not just limited to robot
taxi there's just lot to do in the world
the driver shortage is severe in Korea
and Asia we need to provide robust
autonomous driving technology to the
backbone industry it's still in the
early days there's a lot to do right now
we are the only very few companies in
the world who's providing autonomous
driving technology to multiple car
makers and multiple logistics companies
I think we're going to be one of the
longlasting and very successful
autonomous driving company that solved
this severe societal problem we are
based in Korea if you want to solve
autonomous driving problems across the
different domains of Industry please
have a take a look at our website Sor
bar. Tech
[Music]
[Applause]