happy
Friday happy Friday to you I can't tell
if I have a pimple or a mosquito bite
what if it's a what if what if it's a
bobo bite a bobo bite I really don't
care stop I need the bug
sucker why do you you guys both have
like caps on like I feel like I'm with
like a um the cap God I feel like I'm
with like a spy they hate my haircut
[ __ ] them they can choke yeah I know
it's so inevitable to be to be judged to
be
crucified I me
criticized was like oh my goodness that
was like an extreme turn people are
filled I'm going to prank both of you
I'm going to put butter on the soles of
all your shoes and then you're going to
put your shoes on both you and you're
going to go it's going to look like
you're on ice not and I'm going to go
like this and that's all it's going to
take to knock you down that's it what I
was going to say is people are so quick
to judge others and everyone will call
you stop it people are so quick to judge
others and they're so quick to judge in
general when I think if you're going to
judge others and be a total dick bag
loser why don't you walk to the closest
[ __ ] mirror in your house which is
probably not many since you probably
hate seeing yourself and you look in
there can you stop and you judge
yourself if you're going to sit and
you're going to judge other people how
about you take a good long look in the
mirror and tell me if you like what you
see
cuz I know when I see a mirror I don't
hate what I see at all because I'm not a
judgmental horrible person I really
think that that you live by the Golden
Rule and that is treat others how you
want to be treated I do I'm a really
like as much as I say things that are
just crazy I am a very I do I definitely
do I definitely live by the gold my
whole thing I'm genuinely there's not
one person that I've met that would say
I'm a bad person
unless they're unless they're a [ __ ]
idiot sure which is a few maybe like
three there probably three people who
don't like like me at all okay and that
is because they are wrong uh I could get
the double digits no that don't like me
name
them [ __ ] idiot
obnoxious
who would never say that she would never
say really you don't think so never say
that okay um
was a loser and if that's eight people
who don't like me and I've been alive
for 21 years that's not that many if
you're honest and true to yourself
you're destined to have someone not like
you and that's a fact that's what I I'd
rather have hundreds of people not like
me for being Who I Am A Friend Of All is
a friend to none correct I'd rather have
many people dislike me for being who I
am rather than try and fit the mold you
guys try and box me into who's you guys
them who's them they know okay that's
good you guys are going to make make fun
of me when I say this probably it is so
unbelievable to me how dependent we are
on water as people and it's also so
crazy how like water is genuinely
magic you may say you're so [ __ ] you
are ridiculous and you have lost your
mind but when you think of it on a
deeper level if you did not have water
you would die so in the grand scheme of
things water if you don't have water
you'll die so in the grand scheme of
things as human beings who drink water
who need it to live we're essentially
like drinking our youth euthanized
euthanizing youth youth bringing serum
Elixir like water AR water doesn't make
you young it just keeps you why aren't
we but it's like an Elixir it's
literally it's literally like a magical
Elixir and it's why we are all still
here today and that's if it's crazy to
think that when I go to the to the
airport when I go to Disneyland when I
go to super public settings I can look
around and guarantee you these people
are all drinking water I can go anywhere
and almost guarantee someone here has
had water today for sure and it's like
it's so crazy almost every single person
you ask unless they're crazy asking
people for youth serum instead if we go
to a restaurant what do you guys want to
I'll just take some youth serum you or
you is better you should just start
going up to people be like did you drink
water today I love pool Flags what's a
pool flag like the rainbow array of
flags crossing the pool no oh they're
like oh multicolor they're like the
triangles love those they're such a Vibe
catcher they're just like wow at a pool
but now put on the screen now we're at
The Vibes at a picnic table in a hot dog
friends yeah cuz those also those kind
of just pranking
people I feel like we need to start like
more mystery liquid at at the Super
Bowl what myy
at the next Super Bowl you will go to
the you go to the hey can I
get shots one of these is anti not for
purchase not for purchase when they
celebrate and they dump the Gatorade
yeah I want the BET line to be
ridiculous I think the Gatorade is going
to be red I think it's going to be blue
I I want to bet if it's olive
oil do you I want to
bet negative blood now now now what was
that whole thing about molasses not that
long ago that we talked about the big
Molasses Flood do you remember that that
was crazy that was a big story no that
hit the headline why the big Molasses
Flood I want the next Super Bowl dump
molasses on that
[ __ ] where's the syrup and
what's the difference between molasses
and syrup let's see it today Google it
Matt do you when was the big old molass
saying slow as molasses came by an old
story kind of like Paul Riv but less
historical [ __ ] Paul R I was talking
about Paul R today they had a big jug of
molasses
and when did molass it was like a slow
tsunami hitting the city when did
Molasses Flood the
city and everyone was like
no on January 15th 1999 a steel tank
holding molasses ruptured sending a 2.3
million gallon 26 million pound wave of
the dark sticky syrup surging through
the North End Neighborhood streets of
Boston Massachusetts that happened that
happened here [ __ ] yeah
baby this is my [ __ ] City yes we
survived we got we got part we got
chowder oh te the lobster we got
molasses at it to the
wi we have family Franks dude it was
actually a really devast event
no like this is kind of terrible oh my
goodness oh 50 people died when did wait
we got Paul Riv we we can't celebrate it
it was a tragedy the how many people
died Tom true 21 people died in the
syrup it's like crazy cuz like is it
crazy that I feel like that's how I need
to go just B don't even say that like
that's just such nixo L don't even say
that what happened he was
so Nick we can't talk about wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait why was there a giant
vast of molasses in Boston the Molasses
Factory I assume but like why was it so
high up that it was like pouring
out no more question syrup and molasses
can differ in their production taste
texture and nutritional content so
everything they're different I want
molasses I want to give it a shot syrup
and I think it can be compared similarly
to
honey the poo I hate the [ __ ] bees
and they're pollinating all over the
[ __ ] don't hate on poo [ __ ] poo poo did
nothing to you [ __ ] poo do you think his
homies called a pooy or no he call him
Poo
Bear I [ __ ] hate that big of honey I
hate honey that to my least favorite
things chocy are honey and butter I hate
a bunch of butter and I hate honey don't
worry about butter is going to all be at
the bottom of your shoes you're so
weird when you when you wake up and slip
to butter shoes just know that I was
when I wake up and slip when you get up
and you put your shoes on and you're
getting ready to leave for the day and
there's butter and you're you start
slipping and I blow you down a flight of
stairs whoo whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa he
did it he buttered my shoes that's going
to be your exact words how about how
about today when we go to the movie
theater and we see the the trailer for
afraid AI
AFR
AI
D not the AI horror movie AI horror
movie before GTA 6 is crazy stop the
world end the
madness I hate when I go to text someone
on every platform now and it happens to
be a robot by accident I'll go to
Snapchat Instagram I'm talking to Stuart
in in AI you named your Snapchat AI
Stewart I did why cuz one night I was
texting him and I felt weird texting AI
so I gave him a human name so little bit
moreing that's more weird Chris why
Stuart I had a friend
in Stuart I haven't thought of
Stuart friend Stuart and he was a
great no do not do not put that in a
video seriously
that's dude remember when Stuart used to
just do cartwheels at The Landing at
every step he I remember he was so nice
I loved kids at school that were just
flipping around like when I left when I
yeah we're going to English class but
also you are doing a
bad we are we are going to math but yeah
you're doing a 50 TR I just going to
flip I just saw a [ __ ] incredible
performance by multiple [ __ ] weird
kids weirdos on my way to class and I L
every moment you just literally pull
vaulted through the library and I
enjoyed watching I did those kids get
[ __ ] on oh the weirdos that run from
class to class no they are entertaining
they are our superheroes they are
entertaining us what we going to do if
everyone went to their class at a normal
Pace God we needed some boring flips we
needed some Sprints oh my God L it he
would walk into every single class and
go steuart's
here what I remember who [ __ ] yes he
would always go you would always be like
sup it's Stuart like if you I am Stuart
and I am here I will the energy that was
he was he was on I'm going to start
walking into places Chris is here that's
what he I am no cuz now you're just
stealing steuart's whole thing no yeah
he did kind of start but how amazing to
just be so confident in yourself get the
[ __ ] out of here if you like grapefruits
more than
oranges my newest pet peeve and I've
developed this
recently when people lose their [ __ ]
mind that someone is leaving the theater
before like the post-end credit scene
rat look at it oh my God oh my God
oh I don't it's not I still see him he'd
be more scared of you if you're
meowing are you all right no but my my
newest biggest pet peeve is when people
post on they'll post like a what was
that the giraffe cover the elep when
people I hate when people post on Tik
Tok like videos of people like leaving
the movie theater before the end credits
and they were like they're clearly not a
true fan or I was raised by Mar so I
know that I have to stay to see the post
end it's like this post end credit scene
that's [ __ ] 15 seconds long has been
blasted all over the Internet and I came
to see this movie because I possibly saw
one of those clips so when you think
you're so tough judging someone cuz
they're getting up and leaving the
theater after the [ __ ] movie comes to
completion and you're like but you
didn't stay till the post end credit
scene I've seen it a million times I'm
going to go home I'm going to see it 20
more times and it's never that big of a
[ __ ] deal oh it has to do with the
next movie it's a teases to the next
movie I'll see it when I can see the
whole [ __ ] hour and a half to two
hour long goddamn Phil film that they're
producing from that little teaser have
you lost it and they're judging people
oh my God this it's like cuz that's what
I need in my life I need to feel judged
for leaving the [ __ ] movie theater
when the [ __ ] credits roll that's
what I
yes judge me because I don't want to sit
there for three godamn minutes of a
joyful little beat after inside out two
to see [ __ ] Joy go oh that's the big
secret and then the big secret comes out
and it's too shy to [ __ ] share and I
seen it on Tik to already and that clip
was 2 minutes long and now it's delaying
my night cuz I'm going to look like the
[ __ ] fool I'm going to look like the
I'm going to look like a silly
[ __ ] if I
leave what the deep dark secret was a
hole in the rug and now you know and you
just saved yourself 10 minutes am I
right I it's just crazy when the end
credit what was the deep dark secret
some stupid [ __ ] a hole in the rug I
don't care the end the end credit scene
is always posted on the Internet it's
like I don't need to see what I've seen
already here I get it if you're posting
and you're like oh there's an end credit
scene stay to watch it but it's like the
[ __ ] that are like posting the
end credit scene and be like people
walked out before this played it's like
yeah cuz idiots like you are putting it
everywhere I seen in my dreams at night
cuz we were at the movies the other day
obviously that's why I'm going to this R
and I'm leaving during the end credit
scene and I see like a glare of like oh
he's leaving and like the end credit
scene's happening it's like yes cuz I've
seen it what am I going to sit here
forever for for what
what and then and then and then I love
the movies when they're like they know
to just be like let's fake let's fake
let's pump fake the credits right let's
throw like the director the actors and
then give him the end credit scene we
have the [ __ ] 20 second person to
touch a light for scene number 745 every
[ __ ] goddamn person is credited who's
ever touched a film ever and then we get
to see the goofy little 20 second
monologue at the end thank you my pride
and joy I'm so happy I sat on my [ __ ]
thumb in this theater and waited for an
extra five goddamn minutes to experience
the same thing I would have already
before you're crazy I
think I
agree this helps me a lot deal with the
actual issues in my life freaking out
about literally nothing you're crazy so
cuz I no hold on that's the most passion
you've talked about any
I just had so much to say my favorite
thing about Nick is he'll do that he'll
do that right and that's been what five
six minutes at the end of the day he
doesn't really care I don't at all he
doesn't cuz that just walk out anyway I
don't care if you're like and you want
the fun the even funnier part about
it sometimes you stay for the end credit
scene I do you know what I mean like
yeah like that's why we can't take what
I say too seriously here cuz I'm not
only a hypocrite but I'm careless and I
don't actually give a [ __ ] about what I
just went on a five minute Rampage about
but it's fun but that's what makes you
you Nick yeah let's see if there's
anything else I want to talk about oh
this was another thing that blew my mind
today I post the photo dump I posted on
Instagram onto Tik Tok and I'm like Oh
my new Instagram post to try and get
some people from Tik Tok over to my
Instagram comment oh God this is not
going to end good me me when I don't
have Instagram or like thanks so much
for posting this here I don't have
Instagram or like H uh like frowns with
no Instagram how are there parents in
this world that are allowing their kids
to go on Tik Tock but not Instagram
Instagram to me is like a social app
where you can chit and chat and see fun
photos of people you know in real life
or follow like celebrities or micro
celebrities that like you just want to
see some funny content from and there's
not really something bad on Instagram
true Tik Tok is an abyss of hate and
vile
Behavior why do you have Tik Tok and not
Instagram you're going to go on
Instagram and see a pretty sunset you're
going to go on Tik Tok and see a crazy
[ __ ] you're you're going to go
on well Instagram my kids are going to
bang rocks together till they see Sparks
for entertainment my kids are going to
play Uno and [ __ ] wrestle yes K's
favorite activity is going to be
braiding Blades of grass together
they're going to love doing that I just
I think genuinely that who's going to
have an iPad kit out of the three of us
not me whoever gets tired first give the
kid a screen no it's so crazy how
entertains kids can be with an iPad cuz
the kids are all small so like an iPad
to them is like a [ __ ] you're
bringing a movie theater you're bring
them the it's a [ __ ] imatch Dome
Theater remember those ones yes that's
they [ __ ] bring the iPad with them to
dinner and then I just see the kid
rotting away with their nothing nothing
nothing nothing beat when we went to
that that bar that one time and we were
sitting and
eating and that lady's kid there's this
sweet lady she's like 80 years old like
allergies you have to understand when
you don't have a lot of time left with a
person and this lady's like 80 years old
and she has she has like her
granddaughter with her and she's like on
her iPad can we end the Kitty headphones
Kitty head phones and it's like dude
that's your [ __ ] grandma be happy and
spend time with her cuz she's not going
to be there forever and the little kid
was like seven yeah but it's like dude
like you're with grandma get your get
the [ __ ] off your iPad go [ __ ] I hate
that's actually my least favorite thing
is ungrateful ass [ __ ] if I do
something seven-year-old no this is my
least favorite thing if someone got me a
shirt a size too big and a shitty design
I don't like I'd say thank you for
getting me a shirt correct and I
wouldn't critique it if I was like oh
this design I don't like and it's not my
style and and you got the wrong size
shut the [ __ ] up you just got a gift you
deserve a smack on the face you monster
this guy's swinging a nice bag I just
think laugh this guy's literally like
what do you mean by that no like he's
swinging a bag yeah that guy's swinging
a good bag no but this guy's like the
definition of like moseying around right
now like uh so chill oh my God he just
looked he just looked at that car just
looked looked at that car up and down
and he went yeah I we all can't be
caught looking that's why I'm looking
this way dude what I'm kind of
scared what are you checking out every
car for oh this makes me sad what he's
at the bus
stop after looking at all the
cars that's why he was checking up the
cars I'm so grateful that we have a car
and I'm so grateful that Matt can
drive I feel like I get so
devastated at least once a day today
today we were driving by and I saw this
guy who looked like he had like a long
day like he was like stressed out and he
like was driving on the and he had his
hands on the steering wheel
and he had a cigarette and like his
hands were covered like in paint and I'm
like this dude worked so hard today for
his family like he was like painting
houses and painting walls I can't get
into this bro and and now he's just on
the way home like enjoying like a
cigarette and a nice ride and probably
has an ungrateful iPad kid at home and
it that just it makes me really like it
moments like that I I'll be in shambles
it's just so sad cuz like we are so
fortunate and blessed and thank you you
God but it's like why do I deserve to be
in the position I'm in that's what I
think of all the time when I see other
people I'm like why do I deserve to be
in the position I'm in I feel like
sweat when I'm I'm obviously talking
from experience right now cuz I'm
sweating I'm gross and I'm so mad I'm
wearing a white T-shirt I like it I I
think
sweat okay that's weird I think sweat
instead of being like clear like you
never see sweat don't say it should be a
color I feel like it should look like
frosted Gatorade like white like that
white Cherry one imagine being a sports
player and they're like an athlete
whatever and having like a designated
like correct himself sport player to
athlete I don't know I felt like I was
going to be made fun of no you weren't I
you made imagine having like a Gatorade
flavor like i r blue like I'm a blue oh
I can't say that
what were you going to say like like oh
like I W like this color Gatorade that
they just have like a Gatorade they like
[ __ ] with the most you know what I mean
it blows my mind that when you like go
to a hotel you could get off the
elevator like the second floor and then
go up to the third floor and it looks
like you're in the exact same place yeah
that's not that M like your that's crazy
you're talking like that's like a
[ __ ] very impressive thing just like
pick a build and they're like all right
that 300 times yeah if you think about
it every room in a hotel is probably
mirroring the exact square footage of
each other and like layout sorry I
didn't know I was with the [ __ ]
Property Brothers you're not you're at
the carpentry God forbid it's not you
are with the carpentry Bros bro felt
like he was with Mario and Luigi oh
they're plumbers bad joke [ __ ] the price
to pay for it's like horrible joke give
me your voice box little boy what
who am I
with who the [ __ ] are you what Disney
film is
this that was like a cross between like
Captain Hook and Ursula in like one Vibe
y me then you're
[ __ ]
mother I hate a push to start car and
that's like a flex for some people oh
like my car is a push to start like
you're
tough nothing tough nothing means more
to me than turning that [ __ ] on
with keys it's like an action it's
like I don't want to hit the button and
be like Oh my car's on what am I playing
Pac-Man let me ask gag let me ask you
something let me ask you something let
me ask you something shut up let me ask
you something let me ask you something
let me ask you something I think he
wants to ask me
let me ask you give me one second than
yeah he's going to ask me question let
me ask you something ready wait yeah
what do you know about
either want to know what I know about
either Matt what do you know about
either one I am the [ __ ] bumper cart
Pro you ever never stick key never put a
key that's on switch from a lady 20 ft
away and every time I'm in it I said I
wish I was starting this [ __ ]
with keys you're in think you bump
harder I think I think I drive through
the [ __ ] wall I think I drive home in
that
[ __ ] I think that we should have
a big glass screen oh God somewhere in
our next video like breakaway glass or
even if we ever go on tour again and I
want Nick to enter through it every time
I want you to Barrel through that's a
really good thing that's a good that's a
good liability if you think for a split
second more than someone some else
you're outdoing them you're working
harder you're being more yourself okay
Gary no that's how I feel that's how I
feel app that's why I never like I go to
bed and I struggle to stop thinking same
because I'm too busy so would you say
yes you are the Thinker I think I'm the
Thinker I just think I I I just walk
into I walk into a room and I I say I'm
outthinking everyone in here I I never
think about that I um I I have to
confess this for a very long time I've
been confused about the difference
between Chicken Little and Stewart
Little and one is a chicken and one is a
rat and they're both little there's no
they are not the same and I've just
figured this out cuz Stuart Little has
those big ugly red [ __ ] shoes
on and Chicken Little got that crazy
looking friend that girl but what's the
point of both of those I need to I need
to up my knowledge on the littles I am
unfamiliar Litt do you think oh my God
shout out cement new doing your thing
new conspiracy theory chicken and Stuart
Little are long lost Brothers oh and
they are both little and they need to
find each other to stop the sky from
falling I'm going on I think that that's
it are we talking about steuart from
earlier no no that Stuart about Stuart
Little wow it's crazy that Stuart came
up twice in this video by accident
insane if you think actually crazy you
had a conf that's like a parallel
universe cuz if Matt never brought up
the pr what if we get a three fur collab
Chicken Little Stuart Little and Stuart
from middle school and they get together
and they [ __ ] make a movie and they
make a [ __ ] diss track I just can't
believe anything right now I need to
play a carnival game soon like I'm going
to bed I can't wait to win a big stuffed
animal one day Nick let's do I never
want one I never want a big one I don't
want that why too big too much space
you're taking up I'm good with my
miniature prize no I'm not a greedy
[ __ ] no you have to have you
seen the video on Tik Tok and the guy
goes and he like is determined to get
his girlfriend a [ __ ] big prize and
he goes and he brings the he buys the
supplies at like a store goes home
builds the game practices it with the
exact same rules learns how to does it
when learn how to does learns how to
does it how mad would you be on a scale
of 1 to 10 if someone threw a bowl of
soup at you right now
[Music]