What is up everybody and welcome back to
another Sterno triplets Friday video.
Woo!
All right guys, as you know Nick is gay.
Nick is not only just gay, he's also
onethird of the Sterno triplets and our
leader. Yeah, leader. Yes, I hardly know
her. Anyway, because Nick is gay for
Pride Month, me and Matt are only
allowed to say yes to any question Nick
asks us. And we can we basically have to
We basically have to do everything Nick
says for the entire month of June. Hey,
Nick. Hi, Matt. Happy Pride, bud.
All right, Nick. Do you want your little
Pride Month gift or what? Pride month
gift. Of course, it's the month to
celebrate our gay brother. We're reusing
this basket. Not the panty basket again.
The picnic basket. What's in here? Is it
going to bite me? No. Oh my god.
Gamer. Gamer.
gamer shirt. Matt, isn't that cool? Oh
my god. Is that not so cool? It's
definitely not. Go ahead. Next one. I'm
so scared. Look.
Sorry, girls. I like bananas. Oh my god.
Is it not perfect?
I don't think. Put it on. No. Absolutely
not. No, I'm not wearing that. Smells
like some high-end gays live here. Does
it smell good? I don't know. I haven't
sniffed it.
No. Rupaul Mad Libs. Mhm. Last thing.
Brokeback Mountain
little book. This is so cool. Matt,
right? What is this? I don't know. I saw
it. I love it. Wait, can I tell them
about today's sponsor of the video?
Sure. Are you like me, Matt, and Chris,
needing to get out of the house, wanting
something to do, or just wanting to buy
a gift for a friend? That's why we
wanted to give the sponsors of today's
video, SeatGeek, a massive shout out.
With over 28 million downloads, SeatGeek
is the number one rated ticketing app.
There are more than 70,000 events listed
on Segeek, like concerts, festivals, and
sports games. Right now, you can get
tickets to Kendrick Lamar and Siza, Tate
McCrae, Katy Perry, Lady Gaga, and so
many more. Segeek has your back. Each
ticket is rated from 1 to 10, so you
know that you're getting a good deal.
Green means good and red means bad.
Plus, every ticket is backed by their
buyer guarantee. And you know it came
through for you guys. So you can use
code Sternolo 10 for 10% off your next
set of tickets with SeatGeek. That's 10%
off your next set of tickets with code
Sternolo 10. Make sure you click the
link in the description to download the
app and have the code automatically
added to your SeatGeek account. Thank
you Segeek for sponsoring today's video.
All right, Nick. What is the first thing
that First thing we're doing? I want new
shoes and I want them today and now. So
if they have my size, we're going to buy
them from where we're going to take you
to pay less. We're not going to buy
them. You guys are gonna love them. I
forgot. I slipped my mind. Like they're
very similar to these boots I have on,
but they're like slightly different and
I want them. So, we're going to go buy
you boots that are slightly different
from a $2,000 pair of boots that you
already own and just use mine and hers
as mine. Wow. You pieced it together
quick.
We all saw this coming, didn't we? Like
a moth to a flame. Salt. Yeah.
We all knew he was going to stop, right?
[Music]
Should I do the worm? Yeah. I almost
broke my wrist. Nick, what are you
doing? Look, I got my There's a full
watch indent on my wrist. What are you
doing? I almost just broke my wrist.
You're going to start Now there's a car
coming. I'm going to kill myself. You're
going to start getting Nick can't even
film. What? That guy was hot. Hi. Nick
can't even film a sick montage cuz he's
too busy being a living. No, I can't do
it. Well, show them off. Show them off.
And they got like the big new buckles.
No, they're fire. Can we watch Brokeback
Mountain or No.
I'm down.
I really love this movie. It's a really
heartbreaking gay story, but it's like
it's an important piece of gay history.
I just can't imagine that people are
homophobic. Like I think homophobia and
like worrying about people being gay is
like really [ __ ] gay. It's crazy cuz
sometimes homophobic people get like
they get super worked up and angry when
no one even said some gay [ __ ] Like
sorry you're thinking about
and that's why you're like spiraling out
of control. You know what I mean?
Popcorn ain't going to last.
[Music]
Up again. The most painful story.
You're going to broke back mountain.
Even if you're going to Big Back
Mountain, huh? Know that's all right.
Watch yourself, brother. Your wife's
right there.
[Music]
He was only 39 years old.
Hello.
Aren't you so happy to have a gay
brother?
Mhm. That movie's so good. I feel like
every single time I watch it, I might as
well just stab myself in the face. Yeah.
It's like an equivalent feeling. It's
really, really sad. Equivalent. You mean
equivalent, right? Like after all the
gay people go through, you want to
correct how I say a word, after all the
things I experienced emotionally in my
life. You should pin that back of your
hair down. It looks a little silly. It
is crazy like what people had to go
through. It's so sad. It is. It's
devastating. All right, that was movie
night for Nick's Yes Day. I don't know
why I just decided to torture us. That
was a really good movie. It's a great
movie, but it's like emotional torture.
I can't believe I've never seen it. I'm
happy I watched it. So good.
Lamar Jackson, get ready. Receiving the
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. I'll
let you know if I have any more
questions. I appreciate you. This This
kid hates AI, by the way. I do.
No worries at all. I'm I'm always happy
to help, whether you love AI or not. Oh
my Whoa. You're paying a little bit too
close of attention. That kind of scared
you that you heard him.
Oh, I'm sorry if that caught you off
guard. I just tried to be attentive. All
right, I'm going to listen to music.
Talk to you later.
There's a prize for judgment. All right,
I have an idea.
We're going to go watch the sunset at
the beach and we're also going to do
yoga cuz I want to be more tranquil
tranquil and peaceful. So, I think we
should do a yoga class.
You can hear the waves crashing already.
Ah, it might rain. Rain, rain, go away.
Dude, you're weird. Imagine living on
like a beachfront. Gorgeous. Sorry, I'll
take a walk.
Imagine living on a beachfront gorgeous
home and it's the ugliest one in the
vlog.
Watch out.
The Green Brothers are back. The boys
are back. It doesn't even look like
you're wearing green. It looks like
brown. Bro, people see this hoodie and
they're always like, "Chris loves that
hoodie." And they think it's like my
gray one that I wear. I think whenever
someone talks about the quantity of
which someone's wearing something, they
need to stop talking. Okay. Well, it's
like I'm wearing it. Like I'm I'm I wear
the [ __ ] out of my clothes. Like if I
like it, I'm going to wear the [ __ ] out
of it cuz I like it. I thought for some
reason the sand was going to be freezing
cold, but it's kind of not. Is it not?
It's not at all. I don't know why you're
wearing Timberland boots. I don't like
touching I don't like sand touching my
skin. I like get freaked out by it. We
should have brought chips. We should
have brought Lays chips. [ __ ] Dude, we
should have stopped at Jersey Mike and
got BLTs. Let Mike have his way with our
sandwiches. Let Mike [ __ ] it. Let Mike
do his thing.
I don't know. I think we should just
like enjoy the moment. I'm down to enjoy
the moment. Let's do something fun. I
agree. What? You're going to get sand on
you. Are you serious? Yes.
Oh my god.
Again. How the [ __ ] did you do that
again? Come here. No. Yes. Dude, that
like hurt my hand. Come here. You have
my balls. No, I didn't. I know where
your balls are.
That was so fun.
All right, so Matt's turn. Matt, your
turn. No hands, though. No hands. I
don't think we can do it just like No,
we can try it.
Yo, Matt, that's kind of impressive.
Really? It's all Nick, you should flip
them like in circles. No. Should I back
flip right now? What?
Yo, there's sand in my shirt up here.
Do that. Obviously, bro.
What's other fun yoga moves you could
try? Downward dog and [ __ ] like this.
Yeah, do that next to him. Matt, do it.
Do it. No, you do it. What's the word?
What's a good like yoga move? I don't
know. They're standing in my mouth, on
my face, and in my butt when I have
moisturizer on. So it's like kind of
like primer like like sticking to my
face. Okay. What do you want to do? I
like shit's sticking to All right. I
know.
Stop. Do you think there's a life guard
on the lifeguard tower or a life guard
in the life guard tower? Do you think
there's one? I don't know. I really
like God. You guys should have like
definitely got me a date for this video.
You should have asked. You didn't ask.
Yeah. You wouldn't have found anyone
anyway. Yeah. It's hard. It's an
impossible task. Find Nick a date.
World's not true. I have to I need more
than a month. Search high and dry. Oh my
god, guys.
I'm not that good.
Stop laughing at me. Good. Stop. Okay,
dude. I just got flashbacks to when we
were like 11 years old. Dude, what is
this? What is this?
I was going to pull your pants down. Yo,
what the [ __ ] was that? Nick.
Holy [ __ ] Nick. No. No.
Get away. Nick, stop. I'll smack the
[ __ ] out of you. No. Dude, beach patrol
is going to come over. The beach patrol.
Nick, it is really freaking me out that
you're like moving your feet around like
that. Look at him. Like it just freaks
me out cuz I wait Nick. Oh my god.
My I was like I got taken a back cuz I
saw his penis on the ground. You want to
know what I realized? You almost got hit
by a bike earlier. These are only for
bikes and people are supposed to walk up
there. So we're like rollerblades.
She's good. Let's go. Come on. Yeah. She
would have smoked.
It happened to me once. I got hit by a
bike except I was walking in a straight
line for 30 minutes and then he hit me.
Like what the [ __ ] I'm literally tired
like in my back.
Really? Yes. It's our ball. It's our
ball. Z carry me. Yes. Wait, I forgot
you guys have to say yes. Just try.
Okay.
Okay. I don't think this has ever
happened in my life. My butt cracks kind
of out.
Hello. Sorry. Get back. Get back cuz
you're leaning back. I'm going to drop
you. Hot. Hot guy.
We're going to get chips. We're going to
get chips. Let's go get chips. Fix your
hair and resay that.
Oh. Oh my god. I almost got our car door
taken out. Seven more cars. Go chips.
Chips. Nick. Nick, there's more cars
coming. I want chips. I'll tell you when
you can open the door.
He just doesn't. Oh my god. Hey guys,
what's up? You know where it's Nick's
guess what month? Two weeks. How long
has it been? It's a month, Matt. Pride
month. Sorry, forgot. Um,
we're going to get him a cake because
he's out with friends right now. And
we're going to surprise him with a
little sweet treat when he gets home cuz
we know he'll love it. I'm not baking
him a cake. You're not? No. Like, I'll
buy him a storebought one, but I'm not
baking him. I thought the whole point
was like to bake a cake. We can frost
it. I'm not baking it. Okay. I feel like
let's try to bake him a cake and then we
can use like something like this like
and he'll No, no, no, no, no. Oh, Matt,
what? Oh my god. Oh my god. No way.
Wait, this just made our life so much
easier. That was easy as [ __ ] And he
doesn't he like chocolate cake? I don't
know. I think he does. Where's like a
chocolate cake? I feel like he likes all
types of cake. Should I get him like
this? That's That's giving like gay,
right? Yeah. And we can like type on it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I think we can go to
the aisle instead of like a little end
cap over here. This is per What's the
difference? Are you judging it based on
where it was found? No. I just think of
fruit. I think we can find more options.
I think we go Chris. We can find better
options. We don't need better. But we
can get like a Chris. That's the worst
thing. Eating icing pink tastes
delicious. That's the worst thing. We
don't need pink. What is it? Is he
having a girl? Like let's not No, he
just loves this. Okay. No, I think we
find like an actual good color. You're
saying this is a bad color? No, I'm not
saying it's a bad color. I'm saying that
we can do better than this. You just
like don't even want to put effort. I'm
buying this. Chris, let's go. Chris,
let's probably get him a hat, right?
We're here for a cake. We're not going
to He'll love that.
Should we get him the hat? I don't think
we need to get him a sun hat. All right,
let's keep going. What about flowers?
No. No. No. You don't think he'll love
flowers? No. You know, men only get
flowers at their funeral. Damn, that's
deep. Come on. Wow, that's actually
really deep. I've heard seen that like a
million times. I feel like you can get
deeper there.
[Music]
Matt, I'm fine with this one. No. Why?
Cuz like, dude, you want to bake them a
cake? No, we could do Look at Look at
all the other options. You can just get
this better and you just don't get that
but smaller decorating gel.
See, but now we can get like the letters
like we can spell like easier to type
with.
You think that's easier to type with?
100%. Oh my god. Let's get him a party
popper candle, Chris. Yeah. Yeah. That's
the type of [ __ ] I'm on. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Do you want to carry something?
Yeah, I do. But I'm also recording.
Get that. Okay. What is that? The thing
with a million wicks in it. Grab it,
Matt. Okay.
What is that? Yeah. Incredible candle.
Oh, it opens. Yeah, but it says happy
birthday on the inside. That's fine. No,
he'll love the idea.
Oh, wait. Chris, he'll love this. What's
that? A n like nautical theme. I don't
know what that has to do with pride, but
let's just make it like like the crab
looks cute. We should make them [ __ ]
like we'll make that crab [ __ ] the other
crab. Chris, I don't even like hearing
that. I feel like we can ditch the
single slice cake. I kind of agree.
Yeah. Can you go put it back? I will put
it back, but let's figure out what else
we need. I just looked at this decorate.
One.
Matt just looked at this sheet of A
through Z letters and goes, "Will this
spell pride?" And he's like trying to
find all the letters. It's al it's an
alphabet. Okay, let's just get a bunch
of rainbow sprinkles to like top it off
and then we'll be done. Okay, bye.
Are you home yet?
Am I home yet? Yes. I think that's the
question for you.
Yes, I'm in the living room. Where are
you? You You need to go upstairs.
Where? To my room.
Yes. What's going on? Me and Matt just
got home, but we have a surprise for
you. But we have to prepare. So you we
didn't know you got home. You need to go
upstairs. Okay. Okay. Okay. You do you
understand me? Cuz I you're speaking
English.
All right. Get away
and I'll tell you and you can return.
You hear me?
What?
I'm about to make a masterpiece.
I have no idea. So, I think that the
goal is this is Mr. and Mr. Crab and
they're and they're married and that's
the vibe that we're getting. Okay. Okay.
What? Can you eat these? No. No.
No.
What are you doing? You know, I thought
you eat them. I promise you. I promise
you this is the vibe. I promise you this
is the vibe. That's the vibe. Chris, do
we put Just married right here?
I don't know. I think we should. Should
we put like gay with an arrow? No. No.
No. No. No. No. Like it's obvious that
they're both male crabs. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. No. Don't Don't ruin it now.
It's the vibe. Okay. When did you so get
get so good with the gel pen? When did
you get so bad? The birthday candles are
really hot. This is for celebration.
What?
Come downstairs.
Okay.
Hey.
Wow.
Just married. Yeah. The two gay crabs.
Oh my god. They're really cute. Chris,
they're really cute.
What is that? A bomb.
They're really cute. Chris, you did a
good job. You did really good. Who's
saying this is Chris? Oh, did you do Oh
my god. Watch out. Oh my god. Oh my god.
It's not my birthday. It's for fun. It's
singing happy birthday. I know. Blow it
out. Oh, wait till it sings the song,
right?
Happy birthday. Smoke alarm. Nick, blow
it up. Nick smoke. Shh. Shh. I'm going
to blow it out when it says when it's
done. I'm getting nervous. I'm getting
nervous. Don't be nervous. I'm getting
nervous. Don't be nervous.
It's almost over. Blow it out there. Oh,
I didn't even say that. See this blow.
Blow it out.
Pan it. Pan it. Pan it. Get it. Get the
thing.
So terrified.
So much. So much. Turn the bed. Open the
window. Open the window. Open the
window.
The vent's on. The vent's on. Wait,
Matt. Open that window. Okay. Okay.
Chris, run it under water.
Take the
Can it stop? Stop singing.
Stop, Nick.
I knew that was a bad idea.
We have to go bury that somewhere. Run
it under water. No, that's going to
electrocute me. Happy Pride. The This is
so cute. Like you did you do this?
You'll have to watch when you edit. This
is super cute. Okay, I think I'm
obsessed.
Yeah, it just married crabs. So cute.
Chris is out of breath. We're good now.
We were safe. I think we were safe the
whole time. No, we weren't.
Oh my god, dude. You're scaring me.
All right, guys. Thank you so much for
watching me and Matt do anything Nick
wanted for a whole month for all of
Pride Month. We hope you enjoyed the
back half of June. The back half. No, it
was all month and like four tasks. No,
we started in like the 15th. Yeah, but
Nick, you whatever. If Nick, your ears
are just like Sorry.
Stop being rude to him. It's not you,
it's the headband just taking away your
aura. It's not you, it's me. What are
your ears are like soft like they're
really soft. Thank you guys so much for
watching this Friday video. We will see
you guys next time we post.
[Music]
Hey,