ever think of how bizarre it is that I
can't see either of you like the whole
time no I'm always looking at you I
always always I'm always looking at both
of you what's up little monsters welcome
back to another Friday video we have
finally finally upgraded our car video
camera but we can always go back to the
other one just let us know it like right
away just you know Stern Yow team draw
this up put the poll in the comments
what camera do we use this one or the
other one let us know we don't have to
the only no the only um the only flaw
what did you just throw my eye it was a
plastic thing I was chewing on and what
if it went through my eye and killed me
and I was blind and I never first never
killed you death of the STA triplets I
wouldn't be able to edit a video ever
again you just threw something out my
eye these are like some of the most
valuable parts of my face never throw
[ __ ] at me again yeah you can't even use
them watching planted the Apes yet last
night you you the most valuable part of
my face was crawling toward the screen
with his knuckles down like this looking
at the screen and see squinting you look
like Caesar you want most valuable part
of my face
what all of it the whole thing the whole
the whole kitten Kaboodle speaking of
plan you have like an obnoxious hair in
your face and it's driving me nuts get
it no it's like attached to your head I
think pull it out ridiculous I think I
got it we were watching Planet of the
Apes last night and we were like like I
was getting drinks from the bottom shelf
of a fridge and I felt like one of the
Apes because I was like I didn't bend my
knees at all but I put my entire like
hips and up bent over like but my legs
were perfectly straight like I've never
been able to touch my feet standing up
straight but I think I did it I think I
did it getting food last night last
night I had Nick text me this cuz I was
like no way you just said this this is a
quote from Nick the second he laid down
in bed next to me last night after all
those eight movies I just want to drag
my Knuckles on the ground do you know
what I mean though I do like I'm like
they're going through rough terrain
constantly with their bare knuckles in
the ground like I don't feel like I'm
getting somewhere unless I feel the
gravel on my Knuckles like that's how I
know I'm I want to like I want to just
climb a mountain going to start going
somewhere he's going to get there and
he's going to go I I just want to like
drag my fist on okay this is what I I
watched the movie and then I thought
this to myself and I was like you know
what we have to film a car video soon
I'll save it I wrote down and it's a
full paragraph after watching Planet of
the Apes and seeing the monkeys drag
their Knuckles on the ground and how
they don't speak unless super provoked
to speak you know what I mean I think we
should speak to each other and
communicate via like a side eye or a
nudge but only yell or speak in like
demanding words or phrases like if we
limited our speech in a day to like if I
needed something I was just like Matt
like or like like side eyes and like
phrases and stuff and then like after
like three hours not talking I was like
you did that I was like no snacks I fear
dinner like just random like aggressive
words I fear that's how I live my life
yeah it is that does do that he only
speaks if like super provoke especially
first thing in the morning when we're
getting ready to go somewhere you're
very limited on words I get like matter
you getting up
shower Matt what are you doing bathroom
shower bathroom no I think I got can we
go drive I think I have a total of car I
think okay this is probably why as well
you know what I mean interrup
I think I all right are we
done that was really good that I think
we have a to I have a total of like 15
words Max before my feet are outside for
the day oh I complet kind of crazy
sometimes I don't even talk to Matt we
get to the car and we're already going
somewhere I'm like Hello nice to see you
um speaking of me not being able to see
the TV I genuinely believe if I went to
the eye doctors today and they said like
if I went to the eye doctors today
they'd prescribe me contacts for daily
use you said this like probably I can't
read anything that's why go can you go
and get the things I have to I'll be
drive if I drove down a street and the
sign was like like you know how signs
usually like the the color matches the
vibe like yield is definitely yellow
stop is definitely like red like hold
off what yield signs are not yellow what
they definitely are Google definitely
are they definitely are Mr driver take a
Google search no it's a it's a red
outline with a white triangle that says
yield in Black East Coast yield sign no
but anyways no what I was saying is like
there could be a sign that says like
extreme danger do not enter and I'd have
to like get really close to it to see
like I'd be in danger by the time I read
the sign which is oh yeah when I'm
driving by the danger low clearance and
you only read danger the other day oh my
God we were on the way there was a
tunnel and like it's a it said
like the direction M was going it's a
danger so I looked I looked up and I
said danger he was like shut up I'm
giving them perspective you know how
when you drive through a drive-thru and
it's or like yeah a drivethru is the
perfect example and above it says like
clearance 9 ft like can't take a semiu
correct there's one of those under a
tunnel because the tunnel we headed into
Boston and it was a sign that literally
said d
clear I danger was more bold on the
thing danger and I thought mat was going
on the offramp of a highway yeah and he
started freaking out back there and he's
like Matt you're driving into danger
stop stop and we're like all like yeah
but then Chris tried to Gaslight me
Chris did gas he goes he read just the
low clearance and he goes Nick the sign
doesn't even say danger I didn't read
anything I just new with my head I see a
big pole I'm like assuming it's a
clearance thing yeah but he goes Nick it
didn't even say Danger did say danger in
my professional driver opinion oh I
think you should we [ __ ] Louis
Hamilton with us in my Professional
Driving Experience y I think both of you
should just shut your
mouth in my opinion that's fine what
about when I saved you from murdering a
bicyclist the other day then you can
open your mouth there we go that's H
pedestrian if it's not important first
of all it was the Biker's fault no not
no it was not cuz you almost hit him
Chris stopped you and then you claimed
to not be able to
the hold on hold on hold on if I have
one question and I only need one answer
if he were to hit or if we were to have
hit each other where would his bicycle
have hit my car you would have no no
your your where would my bicycle hit his
car the front the front left portion of
the front of the car so the side you
would
have side of the front not really kind
of you would have hit his front tire
with the front of your car yeah I think
correct I've never been in an in my life
except for when I got rear ended my
[ __ ] Mick I can't believe we use that
as a joke to this day like we memorize
the girl that rear ended us and we
memorize her name because of her ID and
we like use her name on a regular we use
her name as a [ __ ] adjective or a
verb what what is it I think it's an
adjective it's an adjective we like oh
we're going to get if this car keeps
speeding up you can't name drop I keep
forgetting I just forget it's like a
real person
to me it's like a just like a
joke give her give her a fake name
[ __ ] like if her name was like I have
her ID picture Matt if her name if her
name was like bad driver it would be
like oh we're about to get bad drivered
by it's so much more funny because it's
just like a generic yeah I
have a good
question okay okay the other day we get
in the car I've never been that
passionate to say something the other
day we get no for real it's so good the
other day we get in the car and it was
me Nick and Mom I forget where you were
I don't know actually you might have
been in the car I forget but we were
driving and it was me Nick and Mom and I
was talking to Mom and I go yeah we oh
no it was like about our permit or
something I was like yeah me and Nick
definitely need to get our licenses soon
and I said licenses plural I licenses
and Nick goes that was so gay like the
way I said it it was like I was there
and driving the car I'm like how was I
supposed to say licenses plural and not
sound gay in Nick's professional opinion
I'm just laughing at the fact that you
were in the car and he hasn't even just
driving you no you weren't operating the
mom speaking of licenses I was driving
was Mom with us yes I'm going to get
blacked out before I can drive a car
you're not going to get blacked out I
I'm just going to end our sobriety on
our 21st birthday okay no did you see
it's our
sobriety did you guys see the Battleship
game that I sent you today oh I didn't
send it to you guys hold on hold
on no clue I sent it to someone else
hold on dude I think there's so many
people drinking game yes there's so many
people that want us to drink on our 21st
birthday goodbye beer pong welcome
battle shots that's actually do that
with no the reasons I don't drink the
reasons I don't drink is because I can't
even stop having one Pepsi a day so I
only imagine if I had if I had a spiked
lemon if I had any sort of fruity
lemonade iced tea how addicted am iced
tea I'd be C if I had IC tea that
altered my feelings and made me drunk
and just upsets
meol it upsets me so much cuz I knew
that if if I knew that I wouldn't be an
alcoholic I'd be such a fun casual drunk
but I can't do it cuz I'd become an
alcoholic in one second okay for our
fans that are 21 plus and drink based
off of the videos that you've seen of us
and like the who who you know of us on
the internet comment what would be our
favorite drink you're weird where would
be your nightmare place to get blacked
out drunk for the first time like your
nightmare scenario mine would be a meet
and mine would be a meet and great
imagine me being blacked out and like
people want to meet me I'd be like
hi let's take a photo and the Flash
would go off and I'd pass out do you
think when people say wait hold on do
you think people that drive by like I
always do they gota like they got to
look over and be like why
that whole car fully illuminated yeah in
the camera they got to know what we're
doing though right filming a por do you
think when a [ __ ] says that we
like look alike they think they're like
the first person to do it 100% like when
someone comments they're like Nick looks
like Matt Matt looks like
Nick well yeah I do I think like the
people I think people make triplet jokes
and they think that they're so original
but they don't realize I've Pro I
probably heard that for the first time
when I was six there's a [ __ ] rat
right there look at it I think Tik talk
just the app and being chronically
internet has ruined normal
moments for people I said like why am I
seeing at least two people dead and two
babies delivered every time I open my
phone yeah it's a little crazy Nick what
it's crazy it's like Tik Tok has like
depersonalized so many things on the
planet it like blows my mind cuz tell me
open my for page and it'll be like your
outfit if your birthday is this month
and then I'll Swip and it'll be like a
woman birthing a child and I'll be like
and then I'll swipe again and it'll be
like a guy dying in a car it be like
you're AI animal and I swipe and then I
swipe again and it's like and it's
someone getting literally hit by a train
and I'm like what I like I'm being hit
by a
train the Peaks and valleys I just
[ __ ] Triumph through is unbelievable
I've been on my phone for 45 seconds
I've seen a life taken a life gained and
I've seen a meal eaten and I know what
[ __ ] AI little baby creature I'd be
what great facts I just inok for 60
seconds of my life and that's why it's
like I wake up and I look at Tik Tok and
I'm like do I want to open you am I
prepared for this today what am I going
to get it's like a random
shuffle Shuffle birth car accident a
good meal maybe a suggestion for date
night or a play date I think people used
to have to like go up to girls they
liked or like whatever and be like oh
hey my name's Chris whatever blah blah
blah whatever and actually introduce
themselves but every single generation
from after ours is going to be like oh I
like slid in your mom's
DMS literally like imagine you think
about you know what I mean like there's
going to be no really dizzy like almost
passed out
dizzy there's going to be like no more
like love stories like oh I met your mom
like this and I think of like also like
I refuseed to I care listen listen
listen I also think of like people but
you can lie you can lie to little kids I
know you can if I meet like my future
husband on the internet and be like yeah
he's like a massive baseball player like
one of the best in the league and I was
in the stands and he hit a home run and
I caught it and we just fell in love I
think a lot of like texts I have or
conversations I have always like confuse
me and I'm like I need to stop texting
or Snapchatting because then I just in
my head I'm like confusing myself and
I'm like like I feel like text
conversation is so easy to like mix up
cuz like I'm a very like sry what are
you
saying let me talk let me talk let me
talk let me checked out checked out let
me talk this is actually like more than
just a car video funny this is like life
for me I'm dead serious listen it's like
I think the text just gets so confusing
and I'm like sometimes I need just pick
up the phone and talk to this person
right cuz I'm like I just need to talk
and get my point across right and then
like the other I'm like I hate Snapchat
and Tik Tok and all these apps I'm going
to delete them all but I don't want to
be the only one you know what I mean
like if I delete all these apps and I
start like just calling people when I
need them and not like texting or
they're not like why not texting then
I'm like then I'm I'm the odd one out
now you know what I mean and everyone
else is normal pave your own path thank
you Nick I'll start calling you you I I
don't think I gave them enough to edit
today oh my God I actually was thinking
of this Matt know what I think we all
name a song that we want to get edited
to this is the most chronically internet
thing this is bad this is bad and then
we each get like 10 seconds to pose and
like do your one like big one like for
the clip like if I went like this
like I say my song like I say my song
I'm like okay Airbnb by Ian right now
now you say a song and then you say his
song and then whoever gets the hardest
edit after this video wins I think I'd
rather shoot myself in the face
know what I
mean I think I'd rather just like I
think it's like crazy to turn it into
like a CL you've said like an like oh
edit me to that song before you've said
that for sure cuz it's funny dude you
don't you don't like all right all right
let's all right let's each pick a song
for this video who was I with one time
I'm giving who was I with one time and I
had this Skittles Littles thing and I
went like this and they and they like
had like a flashback do you remember
that who was I with you guys no idea I
was with a friend I I'm like totally
forgetting who it was right now and I
really wish I remembered but I was with
a friend and I went like this and they
were like oh my God and I was like what
and like that exact noise is like the
scariest point in like a horror movie
that they had like recently seen and
they were like don't do it again my
favorite thing ever to do is Express
like an extreme amount of emotion or
aggression toward one topic and then
when someone like confronts me about it
being like I don't really care yeah I
agree like I love doing that like is
being like super strongly speaking about
something I really don't I don't care
yeah I don't care yeah what's the time
where you are Troy ofan why would I say
a song that I want them to edit me to I
think he just showed them he just showed
them you would never say like for
example like you'd never say like [ __ ]
Power by like future yeah it's terrible
G I took a good guess that like go of
the raapers you know Nick would we be
friends if I wasn't your brother [ __ ] no
why no hate
dude what's up am I Mr hair what's going
on I think it was the same one ni just
like moveed it if I had a hair on me
that whole time and you altered it in
the beginning I'm going to shoot you oh
I did I did nothing but a favor for you
so maybe you can [ __ ] off and complain
about something else that that stray
hair is a new addition I hope you know
this girl is on Tik Tok and and she I
just found her she does the videos like
ideas for the stola triplets you know
what I'm talking about you just found
how would I know what you're talking
about you might know already I don't
know if you've seen it I've seen I've
seen nothing on the Internet it's so
funny though but okay so listen we just
I just want to clar I want to clarify
this and this this alone quickly a lot
of people whenever we post like the
stories on Instagram like oh help us
with video ideas that's something we've
been doing since the start of our career
and when we had no fans way at the
beginning and only like 30 people were
responding they were coming up like with
insanely creative ideas so it was always
something we continued to do was ask
fans for um advice on content or what
they want to see us talk about or ideas
but it's gotten to the point of
popularity of us on the internet where a
good majority of the responses are good
but a vast majority of them are like um
hi who's going to sleep with me um I
love you guys so much can you come to my
graduation party my mom and dad are
getting a divorce blah blah blah all
this all this crazy [ __ ] so there's just
like not a lot that we can talk about
but when people post videos of
themselves giving us video ideas or
topics they're not going to post
themselves saying crazy [ __ ] so they're
usually way better which leads me to
this fan had questions for us and we're
going to answer them and if you guys
post good questions on Tik Tok we may
possibly respond to them in a video one
day in the future I'm so curious for her
question they're really good Nick was
show me the other day okay if there was
a ster University what would the mascot
in colors be and what classes would be
taught there ooh that's a really good I
do kind of feel like we should wait I do
feel like we should kind of wait till
next video yeah cuz then we could maybe
see other people's responses are and I
feel like I could go on like longer
tangents we've already filmed for so
long well shout out her that was a good
question okay yeah we'll we'll answer
that next video yeah we're going to
answer that and do other stuff next me
alive hate to say it again bring it up
again but if we do cut out Wednesday
videos and I know we bring that up every
video no I know we bring it up every
video to the point where it's like
annoying now but it's like we've
seriously been contemplating this and
the reason we bring it up so much is
it's been a year of our or two years of
our life where we've been posting two
videos a week I just want to make it
clear to everyone that it wouldn't be
like eliminating car videos or
eliminating Vlogs it would simply be
like it would just be like random and
who knows what we're going to do you
guys always bring up um pretty good
points and I do think that I wouldn't be
opposed to a break as opposed to cutting
them out so we'll just see what happens
no my thing is we're never going to not
be on the internet and sharing content
to yeah a lot of people constantly talk
about like us quitting which is never
going to happen cuz the internet is our
just more of like it's just more of like
we kind of hit a wall where it's like if
we're if I'm sleeping until 2: and then
doing nothing at home the Vlog is not
going to be interesting come Wednesday
because I sat at home on my [ __ ] ass
all day but it's not even that it's
about also like expanding our life
meeting new people seeing new ideas of
what we want to bring to you guys you
know what I mean we need our goal is to
lead a better more fun happy and healthy
life so that you guys can enjoy watching
a super fun happy and healthy group of
people on YouTube yeah and
holy [ __ ] my goal is I had a turtle in
my throat What's the phrase can I speak
it's like a my
goal no Matt you're just like you need
to talk with some compassion Matt I want
you to I want to hear it from your gut
second
there so talk Lou he like looks can't
even do
it oh no oh no can you get to the front
of the car go go say what you were going
to no Matt if you pour mat no don't B
don't Matt and my Snapple is
gone that Snapple had nothing to do s
got asay what the [ __ ] that Snapple just
got emptied from that Snapple has just
nothing to do what with what's happening
right now buy another
[Laughter]
one I didn't even [ __ ] want that that
bad a you didn't okay go ahead cuz
sipping it and making noise is a lot
more important than what
it am I
right am I right or am I
wrong am I right or am I wrong no that
was a good point that was a good point
okay go ahead you charge something no I
feel the
ogus now it's just weird cuz I was going
to like touch on the topic of like you
know touch all over it okay make the
topic your basically what I was trying
to say before I got very rudely
interrupted was my goal and Nick and
Chris's goal is obviously our whole
channel is meant for comedy funny and
escape from reality for some people and
just nice uplifting content and then
also just being our true authentic self
to the internet and that's kind of why
we are who we are today and why we got
to where we're at today so no matter
what we're going to keep doing that and
we appreciate you guys like being cool
with us growing and you guys growing as
well cuz everybody's human and and we
all live one life so I'm not going to
box myself into things that I think were
funny three years ago because that's not
my life anymore queen queen all right
guys thank you so much for watching once
again thanks for the little recap with
us at the end and we hope you enjoyed
the actual content funny part of the
video at the beginning um yeah I think
we touched on everything we wanted to
say recently so stay tuned have a blast
and don't let anybody D Your Shine oh
and one more thing we got back cool
merch designs that we're going to drop
soon but you guys haven't seen them yet
but I think that they are the best ones
that we've ever gotten back I'd argue
the same firly agree with you yes we
appreciate you guys thank you again and
that merch link is in our bio so you'll
see on our Instagrams and whatever the
[ __ ] that we did it it's not going to be
for a little bit but SK just wanted to
show do a double high
five oh my God that was good
[Music]