wait want to know what's funny though
our last Wednesday video was also a
tattoo yeah so for this little segment
of our video we're gonna me and Chris
have picked out tattoos that we're gonna
put on Nick without him seeing and just
you want to show them your owl while
you're at it oh yeah I just got this
oh there's a little blood on it but hey
don't mind the gas string from the other
room that's just Hogwarts Legacy
Maddie's playing okay this is what we're
thinking guys
upstairs that's Chris's and this one's
mine that was myself that was my second
option but I don't think I'm going with
it Nick said he wants more leg tattoos
so this one's actually like perfect for
on his mat why'd you pick the Trident
give us like um oh I shouldn't have said
that that loud he's upstairs that's fine
um he loves like
Percy Jackson uh Lightning Thief and
like those ones yeah and it's like he's
the the son of Poseidon and it's like
three like he always says he wants like
he's stabbing he just like loves he's
like he's
yeah you know he's just that type of kid
why'd you pick the I picked the disco
ball because he's like bro he likes all
that [ __ ] like the old retro [ __ ] like
the [ __ ]
does it ah
just so basically the reason why you
picked it I was thinking like you want a
little [ __ ] on him
just bold but I probably wouldn't [ __ ]
with it oh your bathroom door's open Hey
look it's on the other side anyway okay
hey guys here's the here's the victim
the victim's insane I'm so excited did
you wait up did you did you show the
camera then yeah yes obviously we showed
them like what she has on her iPad I
showed them
I showed them my owl do you stop I have
a banana you're like choking me out I
showed them my owl do you want to show
them uh what's his name
Carlos Carlos the magic magic bunny Sure
hold on okay
um you guys have to pick placement too
like if she's like oh good I can't see
y'all no yeah we know
this is so funny anywhere's Fine By the
way I just I just can't believe you're
letting us do this of course you're my
brothers right no I think so
Carlos Carlos the Magic Money he's a
rabbit man
come on
[Music]
I have like two blank spots on my arm I
don't know if Carlos took one of them
yeah
oh yeah like this back of my arm yeah I
like that too oh yeah that's perfect
I'm gonna say this okay I'm gonna stick
that one on okay and then we're gonna
stick the other one up and I think Hello
Kitty you might be able to take your
blindfold off true I can't really see
true oh yeah what's his name again Nick
Carlos the magic rabbit
it's so weird
so imagine grab it coming out of the top
hat wearing a top hat I feel like my
senses are so high like since I'm
blindfolded I feel like I can feel
everything else
you're so bizarre like the weirdest kid
Chris would say something like that I
definitely would yeah you guys are both
the weirdest people
you love us for who we are anyway
s
so weird I kind of love this because
sometimes like I'd want a tattoo but my
hardest decision is what it's gonna be
that shouldn't be the hardest decision
that should be like the most like
thought out decision but that's not for
me
Carlos the magic rabbit
[Laughter]
I would
I would honestly get Carlos the magic
rabbit I'm trying to see if I can feel
what this is it's [ __ ] a stencil bro
that's fun oh yeah yeah that's like turn
toward me Nick I don't know where you
are I'm behind you oh yeah that's lit
standing Matthew you like that yeah
which one go shirtless no
around it
yes
ankles are so sensitive like that's like
no that's like his weak spot no like you
know it's called an Achilles heel like
that's dead ass my Achilles heel and
whatever so like yeah yeah that's fine
Nick are you comfortable with that like
at the bottom
like it's just the back of your leg yeah
don't move because she's gonna shave
your hair off okay okay
the camera's right full vision I was
getting Carlos I felt like it was on my
elbow and it
now
no [ __ ] clue what anything is
okay let's go I'm excited I feel
different nothing's changed Nick how do
you feel that your Tattoo's in frame
right now
is it yeah
I don't know just don't look back there
behind your shoulder
I don't want to see them
this one's done I must have said it out
loud okay I was taking a photo Matt's
taking a photo because Nick still can't
see it because it's on the back of his
leg same with this one I refuse to look
at any of these well you couldn't even
see it if you tried I don't want to know
though okay well you won't unless you go
look in a mirror that's amazing
Nick for you I picked out it says hot
dogs Burgers cookouts America yes oh I
forgot I forgot I forgot football oh my
God
I feel dead
it's only my arm I'm like
Trace me right now
get the white chalk out yeah he's a
goner
okay show me the photos or am I looking
um photos
I'll fix that hair Jesus Christ I've
been lying down for like three hours
three hours is insane three hours yeah
the rabbit oh yeah that's right
yeah
I love this this is on my leg Yeah
Trident nice try it I love that Poseidon
I love exciting I know it's nice and
small too well it's not thin thin yeah
there's so much room for play down there
[Laughter]
man no you're just ridiculous wow I love
it I have the city this is an idea
that's awesome thank you Matt yep you
did good you listen
[Laughter]
[Music]
I was gonna do a disco ball but I was
like I feel like it seems complicated
but now I have it let's see I love them
both that one's bleeding and it fits
everything else that's there
they're both home you guys did really
good up top
me and Chris decided
it would be really really funny if we
ask you to spell certain words on camera
real funny
so we're just gonna ask you how to spell
some words that we picked out okay yeah
but every single word you get right will
give you ten dollars oh
a hundred dollars I'll give you a
hundred
that's a bold statement well Chris can I
do it because we're actually gonna I I
made the list of words because I also
want to ask Chris because I know that he
can't spell either so I'm gonna go back
and forth between you both and we'll pay
each of you we'll do we'll go we'll do
like thirty dollars thirty dollars each
one you get right I'm not gonna
I'm gonna go back and forth between you
and Chris
hey Mama
Matt I'm gonna go back and forth between
you and Chris do you want the first
question or do you want Chris to start I
don't care Chris can start okay Chris
first word accommodate oh
a com uh date a c o n
a c c nope you get the next word we're
already moving past it [ __ ] embarrass em
be wrong Chris you're not the one it's
right but you're not the one oh you're
wrong for going on
AR
e-s-s wrong Chris I don't know what is
it embarrassed
embarrassed embarrassed wait you're
getting a different word yeah [ __ ]
read it then you're looking like I just
don't even know how to read the word
either no awesome that's awesome we're
gonna skip Chris exaggerate
exaggerate e x
I love power this Wednesday I'm looking
out stupid b-x-a
G
hey Bro [ __ ] Matt nauseous
and oh it's like a u in it it's got a u
and an O It's like a n-a-u-s-e
nauseous
oh I don't know
and I didn't I don't know I can't even
like I don't even want to try Matt spell
it n-o-u-s something
keep going and ous is that for real yes
that's what you said now you started
with n a and you switched it to an o n a
o u s Wrong Chris
yeah
maneuver oh maneuver
m-a-n-u wrong
pneumonia pneumonia this is like life or
death doesn't pneumonia shorter than I
what
my turn to see oh damn my turn to give
away money whoever can chug a Pepsi
faster
wins a hundred dollars I see it's been
three days since Chris had soda and I
feel like that's gonna really
all right cheers okay wait you have to
slow
weight
oh dear God
this is her charity today
I can hear the bubbles
oh dear God
I wanna burn too bad I think I'll puke
[Laughter]
it smells like tacos
well I won good job
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things