is so
filthy what is that trash trash trash
trash trash go go go go go oh my
God guys fun fact on the cular trip
let's be foret to forget to put our
trash out every single day so hearing
the trash is like an
anomaly I don't [ __ ] with you one bit
actually I'm really mad n how about you
stop being Chris is Chris yells a mat
every single day you need to be you're
so negative oh you're so negative you're
the first [ __ ] to make a
terrible decision today and be rude name
it rude yelling at me for down the
recycle even though you spend hours upon
hours cutting up recycle boxes that they
all fit and I'm trying to quickly do it
before the [ __ ] trash people come
yeah and you're yelling at me for for
breaking down the box to fit it I don't
want to hear your solution I break boxes
when they won't fit inside the recycle
yours had plenty of room to go inside
the actual bin so it didn't matter if
you broke it down or not was already
inside the recycle bin and you freak out
dude what is going on he's just an idiot
what is going on I had time oh nobody
cares nobody right there cares I had
time nobody over there that cares Nick
Nick's angry I'm not you're just a
[ __ ] [ __ ] you need to be relaxed
you're about to get yeah tell me about
it he's the person who who ruined my I
had a good mojo today he didn't ruin no
moo today this you have the same mojo as
a [ __ ] zombie snail you're moving
slow you're you're literally dead well
I'm stressed out I didn't sleep cuz I
have to be [ __ ] put under an uh I
have to be drugged beyond belief and put
to
sleep right for the first time in my
life I don't want to do it so I have
zero [ __ ] sleep and in order for the
anesthesia to work you want to know what
you can't eat 12 hours before the
procedure I woke up at 4 [ __ ] p.m.
yesterday and I had to cut off my time
of eating at 1 p.m. do you know how much
I eat do you know how much I eat at
dusk I also yeah I also couldn't drink a
[ __ ] thing past 10 p.m. so you're
thirsty and hungry which is like it
makes sense yeah cuz the anesthesia has
to work but I'm [ __ ] starving I'm
thirsty all I wanted last night was a
[ __ ] lemonade and we have a fridge
full and I can't I can't have a [ __ ]
n want a lemonade so bad we have like a
ton of lyrical lemonade it's hilarious
[ __ ] pisses me off I just can't
believe this is happening to me here do
you want to know my process I've been
thinking about it a lot and I'm like wow
I'm so happy that it's Nick getting
sated and not me this morning so
basically what I was thinking is like
whenever I have like tried like like
horrible things that I have to do in the
near future or like something I don't
want to do I'm just going to pretend
that it's you or Matt that have to deal
with it and then just be totally
blindsided when it's me like be like
wait it's me that has to get sedated in
my Wiz te Bel so like if I were you I
would just pretend that it's actually me
and then it's not going to [ __ ] work
it would work flawlessly and then just
get there that seems like a horrible
idea how are you feeling upset and
annoyed
a last night I couldn't sleep at all cuz
of how nervous I was and literally just
thinking about getting like a needle in
my arm my whole arm has just been numb
for like 9 hours cuz I'm afraid and what
is this guy
doing oh my
God are you good yeah Helen Keller could
have drove better than him okay well you
have to just you have to not worry dude
thank you of course oh hello hi lady hi
sweet lady hi sweet
lady I'm so afraid and anything I Stay I
say when I'm on anesthesia like when I'm
first up the truth no I was actually
going to say just discredit it all look
at this dog oh my God hi buddy oh my
goodness he's so cute it's kind of ugly
ass dog yeah I was going to say that
like that I really do I just get songs
in my head and I have to release them
sing it again no come on no I'm
embarrassed now we missed it for the
Vlog I know I'm sorry sing your song
would you say fill me a me a butter cup
baby just something about Nick whether
or not let me down baby whether or not
he likes it or not if you tell him to
sing and then he says no if he starts
singing it I'll sing along he so th I'll
sing along every time yeah you will
let's go on a hike right after you get
te though I say let me go wherever I
want no dude just guys let me
go what are you talking about I can't
believe there's a possibility cuz I've
been watching Dr gab's Instagram and
stuff that I'm going to be taken out of
the dental facility in a wheelchair
today yeah you're going to I can't
believe that Nick you Nick you're going
to be there's no possibility you are
going to I want to walk you're going to
get put back into the car like an idiot
you're not going to remember being home
that's not true getting home you're
don't say that you're going to be like
wait wait what happened you're going to
wake up in your bed with no
teeth don't say that I really really
hope I get to keep my teeth Nick I told
you this already you're not going to be
able to keep your teeth cuz your teeth
are going to be literal Pebbles and dust
but how the [ __ ] is the Tooth Fairy
going to come I don't know it depends if
they smash your tooth or not I I think
when you have your wisdom teeth out they
give you four fake teeth to put under
for the tooth fairy but like the Tooth
Fairy knows the whole gist what yeah she
gets it cuz but she needs the real teeth
not
for no it's not not for wisdom teeth
wisdom teeth is like a okay that's like
the last time you're going to see the
tooth fairy so it's not now
no it is it is unless you lose a tooth
in your adult life it is the last time
the toothberry is going to come next so
I'm going to start so listen I'm going
to start pulling my teeth out so she
care she doesn't care to take the four
fake wisdom teeth that the dentist gives
you because of the fact that it's her
last time taking the teeth and it's like
it's like a thank you the Tooth Fairy
really grows up with you man yeah she
does that Mak sad nck you're not even
under anesthesia yet let's keep our
emotions together it's just actually so
sad think of little kids who get their
teeth taken out yeah or they lose their
teeth for the first time
yeah and now actually crying and now I
have no more teeth to give it's okay
Nick
sad no it's not sad it's a part of life
and you do have more teeth to give you
have four big ones to give them you're
doing a the tooth Fair a big favor Nick
you want to know what I
heard I heard I heard wisdom teeth are
20 bucks a
pop can't believe this don't be sad Nick
that's 80 bucks
tonight I'm so emotional recently what
is happening to me you might toss on the
extra 22 you might find a [ __ ]
Benjamin under your pillow tonight
Nick what are the odds man how crazy
would that be oh Nick you kill me I
haven't felt like this in so long what
do you feel like I can't believe this he
just feels
sad fill me up bu I'm so upset ni
I wouldn't have brought up the toothbr I
brought her
up I wouldn't have talked about it I
just can't believe
this it's not even this that's making me
so upset I just I can't believe
it what the Wiz the teeth are
gone oh my God it's so hot in here this
is going to be like the first wisdom
tooth video on the internet that that
way crazier before yeah that it's like
just as delusional before the teeth are
out as
well it's early for us guys that's why
I'm afraid that I'm about to be put
under anesthesia cuz this is how I am
natural but that makes it so much better
like people are going to people are
going to think that they like we put
them [ __ ] after the wisom teeth first
I know like you are so funny bro I just
can't believe
it I'm
dead I ate this F me
up just to let me
down Nick what's what music do you want
us to play when we're on the ride back
casha any final words before we get
closer to the
dentist no a State of Shock
I'm in a State of Shock I don't this
emotion is coming out of left field I
know what happen dude I don't is this
like about growing up what is this I
think
so oh my God ni me Chris got our our
wisdom teeth out years ago I know you'll
be fine I'm just shocked that I'm upset
because I genuinely like you've been
wait you've been waiting for this day no
I think here at like the stern triplets
we we hold in our emotions a lot and
especially like filming a lot of our
life we feel scared to like often just
Express like true like Express true
emotion you know what I mean so I feel
like it like for for me at least like
emotion builds up and then it just like
randomly
releases and I feel like that's what
you're
currently working with yeah what is up
with this I'm about to start crying cuz
of this traffic bricks and then I'm
thinking about it
wa what a [ __ ] loser literally I was
talking about the Tooth Fairy as a joke
but now I'm seriously thinking about
like every single
time choked up don't Nick
you're King me Nick I'm thinking of
every single time oh
wow like so upset
is going on I feel like I'm in a dream I
don't know I don't know I'm think of
every single time that one of us got our
teeth taken out as kids and every single
time any of our teeth fell out which is
so stupid and so I can't believe I'm
upset by it but it's just sad you guys
know I was the first one out of us three
to lose a
tooth yes that's what I'm thinking of
too and I had my little envelope yes oh
my God tooth very
came you were so cute and little and I
and I had no [ __ ] front teeth dude at
least I have front deep now they were
going to go back in and now they're in
and now you don't need
anymore I need to put the air
conditioning on like the last time the
Tooth Fairy will ever be in our houses
tonight can you [ __ ] off so let's really
soak it
in it's so hot in here as badly as I
don't want this to happen I'm very
excited with where I'm going to do it do
get my par or you sitting here and going
to touch yourself what's going what
what take a look at these guys look at
this this is a cool Vlog look at our new
updated camera scared don't be
scared how are you are
you hello I put a small I in could you
slowly falling asleep actually feels
nice it's a nice relaxing feeling okay
usually when you wake up you're already
like on your way out so you feel like 2
[Music]
seconds how's your health uh health
problems nothing notable no sounds good
needles are like my least favorite thing
ever IVs are like my least favorite
thing ever how many IVs have you gotten
very few and I'm not excited for another
one I'm proud of you too next I can't
believe this is [ __ ] happening to me
and I don't want it
to [ __ ]
thing I don't want this [ __ ] thing on
me I hate
this I'd rather actually think get shot
in the face than than an IV in my
[ __ ] arm yeah I kind of agree with
you but you're going to do it I'd rather
have my pinky toe amputated no but Nick
this is honestly good cuz this is like
for future reference any Hospital needs
you're going to be like I can do it now
I don't think that's going to happen
it's going to you're going to chill
you're going to be fine dude thing
freaking me
out it's your
heart don't say that it's it's how you
love yes you feel tired no you look
tired I got no sleep last night you're
going to get all the sleep you need
right
now you're going to wake up with all
your tee gone you can't wait for like a
from now
mhm what's going to happen in a month
from now I'm not going to be [ __ ]
here
yeah you're definitely feeling a little
bit I don't think I
am Nick yeah we have a password to test
your memory the password is
Apple yeah it's Granny Smith apple
[Music]
you tired you're yawning you're
tired you're not
tired you're wide awake
right yeah Nick what's the
password password
yeah all right that's okay um one of you
guys want to give him the next password
yeah you want password the next password
Nick is eyeball
okay you're doing good you don't need
the password you're all
[Music]
right you tired
buddy no you're
not I'm shocked you're not tired yet
you're doing so good you're Wide Awake
how are they going to take your teeth
out if you're so
[Music]
awake I don't think they're going to be
able to take him out if you don't go to
[Applause]
[Music]
bed
wow he's doing so
good he's out like a light ladies and
gentlemen Nick who do you like more me
or
[Music]
Matt don't don't make you
pick Nick you look good
today you want to take Instagram
pictures
today uh yeah we will I'll take them
with you
later leave that
there leave that right now you want to
take Instagram pictures right now I'll
take one of you next take one right
now wa cool sunglasses o those are cool
when you asked if you want to take
Instagram photos and he instantly just
gets up right now he starts getting up
how does this feel good I I really
wanted to be there for him I know bro is
stressing out but now he's not going to
remember the rest so the hard part's
over so we just saw his first two teeth
on the table which we're very excited
about cuz he wants to keep them so he's
going to be able to to keep them and put
them under his pillow for the Tooth
Fairy tonight so he's going to be very
excited I don't think we should tell him
until way later I think we should tell
him like oh they're gone they're gone
and then we'll like show him his little
jar how do you feel I feel good I'm
happy like just seeing the relief that
he's going to feel is worth it you know
what I mean he's been stressing like
headaches and all that type of stuff he
looks so
peaceful it's just it's just so like
it's so Nick you know what I mean the
funniest thing to me is he hates the
little thing on his finger no matter
what but it needs to stay on for his
blood pressure but he's like he keep
trying to take that one of the last
things said I hate this stupid [ __ ]
thing he's like hold this figure up um I
have a question so for his teeth I told
him that like I told him that for sure
that they're not going to be able to
keep his teeth and that they're going to
like cut them and that they're going to
be like a powder and it's like we have a
bunch of them yeah and I I told him like
for sure you're not going to get them
back so can I get the jar of his for and
then like show him like 3 hours be like
here's your teeth your good brother
he'll be so shocked cuz he'll think that
they're gone he's going to be crushed no
you can't have that that's
awesome I'm so
excited hi
buddy Hi how are
you good thumbs up
awesome
all
almost you're almost done buddy you're
doing so
good they're not all gone so cute now
like it's like the calest they'll ever
be it's so it's also so cute how he's
like talking to us cuz like this is this
is a side of him he feels but he'll
never show so it's like he's showing all
his little and stuff right now he's so
funny he's so funny I can't he goes
they're not all gone yet so he won't be
able to keep
them they're all gone yeah he he had to
grind them into a
powder but um we did our best
you did it
Nicholas did so good
nickis been it's been like a half hour
they're all gone a half hour yeah like
it was like 8 minutes each too they let
me they let me take one of them out yeah
Matt did one of them I did the bottom
left one yeah that like not lying oh I'm
not lying Nick I swear to God they let
him do it a liar I'm not a liar they
said we need a professional so they
called in Matt you're a
liar and chief
to and I don't believe you for a [ __ ]
second they almost called R Paul to do
it
[ __ ] oh my God is this goddamn IV oh my
[ __ ] god
no it's not not no it's not
yet yes you're done you're you're
slowly the not from last time song in
your mouth I I did it somewhere else and
IED putong in your
mouth okay let me
look your M right now so I just need
like an leave your tongue in your mouth
give them two right now sure give them
put your tongue in your mouth Nick stop
moving your no Casa in the car if you
don't keep your tongue in your
mouth keep that on am I already done
yeah you're already done okay that's it
yay so now there's some medicine in the
IV we're going to let him get all of
that before we let him go and then I'm
going to reel him to the car and that's
it okay cool was I asleep yeah you
weren't asleep you don't remember
anything I feel like I just I feel like
I was awake the whole time no you were
um you were definitely not awake the
whole time you could even remember one
word I said Nick what's the password
Nick yeah do you remember the password
we gave you no yeah no pass you don't
remember oh look it all right so here's
your goodie bag and what we have in the
goodie bag is you have these little
holes where the teeth used to be and
sometimes they fill with food so if you
want you take some warm water and you
can just shoot it out using this little
gun nice okay then we have some gauze if
is he all sutured up yes so there
shouldn't be a lot of bleeding but if
there's any bleeding you just put this
in the area that's bleeding and you bite
on it okay so you can just hold
it listening it you're taking it all in
you know what to do but you guys will
help right tell me what to do
instructions if you forget right there
perfect and some ice packs nice ice
packs that's nice Okay and like what I
did for my wisdom teeth when I had mine
taken out a lot of sleep and a lot of
you have to you have to leave that on
you're still at the dentist Nick you're
in the chat I know but I still you need
it on until until you get all your
medicine yeah thank you ni leave it on
leave it on okay Nick let's check your
memory okay you guys want to give him
another
password all right the new
password we're doing new password is
sunglasses I don't even know the first
that's okay that's fine that's okay okay
but you know the new one right what's
the new password sign this yeah good job
that was easy right uh like if I said
something like eyeball you would have
remembered
it like if I said like oh the new
password to eyeball yeah like yeah
pretty easy he looks crazy like I look
ridiculous like why would you forget one
word like eyeball you did like 10
minutes ago you had no idea I said the
word eyeball to
you I said I don't believe you I said
Nick the password's eyeball and I go
what is it you couldn't even get the
word eyeball out of your mouth cuz you
were out like a light did did they ask
me like open your mouth like again yeah
really yeah you did a good job you were
very easy to deal with I don't think I
did that no you
didck T
stop you're not going to want this in
the video what do you have to say to the
viewers look Nick what are you our
Vlog stop that you got to look good for
the
camera good job smile you want to put
the sunglasses down put the sunglasses
down no no no don't don't say so yes
good job who put this me for the for
your
eyes I
didn't keep them on I didn't know I had
you look good in them here you can keep
them up there you need to get some
rest Nick leave that
on Nick leave it on leave it on Nick
you're not allowed to take that off he
remembered right this time yeah yeah you
know the password
I no the new one what's the newest
password no IDE sunglasses you don't
remember listen to me new password okay
uh
eyebrow I yep okay now remember that's
the password to leave the dentist you
have to remember that password what's it
doing with the memory eyebrow not good
eyebrow
yeah all right now I'm not going to say
again and then I'm going to ask you in a
minute look here I'm going to ask you in
a minute what that password
is I hate this I know leave it on room
you are Nick I took out your bottom left
tooth why I'm not lying why they let me
take the bottom left one out why I was
standing here the whole time rubbing
your shoulder and then he said do you
want to like make sure you can how long
has it been it's been a half hour that's
it like 45 minutes and I'm done you're
fully done all res are out do you know
the password to leave the
dentist do you remember
it what did you just say what did I say
it is eyeball oh close it was eyebrow
I'll give you a new one okay new
password to lead the dentist is no no
why cuz you're bloody gross CER Nick
stop that on the camera you don't want
your tongue out no casesa no casesa
unless the tongue stays in your mouth
Nick okay you need a new password to
leave Hey listen to me Nick listen to me
mhm your new password to leave the
dentist is
skyscraper okay the I not yet you need
to stay still get it out me well Nick
that's the password to get the IV out
you have to remember the password okay
leave your tongue in your mouth the
password is
skyscraper remember
it now I'm going to ask you it in a
minute so that we can leave but you have
to remember the password
okay all
right pretty
smile
everyone say Nick say like And subscribe
so they do it like And subscribe ni all
right
nice you remember who you are that's
good I'm me
yeah I'm me
yeah who am I that's that yeah do you
have a favorite no no I love that I love
you too I love you so much I love you
too do
you don't move your finger you got to
stay still don't you can't move your
finger no no no leave it on leave it on
Nick I'm actually going to be mad at you
Nick stop it leave it
on Nick what's the password to leave no
no no no no you can't do that what's the
password to leave do you remember it
what is it let's hear it do you want
know
yeah doing good you finally remembered
it how many times did you ask me a
couple but no I switched it up a little
it wasn't skyscraper is there something
in my mou yeah Gau you're you were
bleeding you have to stay think I'm
choking on it no you're not choking on
it no close your yeah squeeze on it if
you were choking you would squeeze too
hard like don't squeeze just like leave
it there going to fall down my throat no
it's not do you want me to get Dr game
no leave it in Nick I'll be back Nick
it's going to fall down my throat okay
then yeah you can leave it out just be
careful with
it is that my tongue that this is the
gauze oh your tongue
see I know it's a little scary get it
away I'm going to put it back in uhuh
okay I'm going hey that beeping is a
dead giveaway that you're doing
something bad
no believe it this isn't funny I'm not
laughing W no
okay you look like the Joker with your
smile Nick I told him tongue yes that's
your tongue yes okay good job you're not
choking on anything I told them that
they wanted to keep your te you wanted
to keep your teeth but they can't cuz
they they drill ho in the middle to to
take the they like grinded them into
like they're like powder and dust so
they couldn't keep them no I know I know
you can only you only you can only keep
chea there's no one there keep teeth if
you take them out from a root canal or
something I can't believe how I'm way
yeah well you're you're good do you want
to hey Nick what's how long I sleep like
a half
hour was I like hey it's on it just said
it was
off on it's on you're being a bad boy I
have a cute little a on yeah you do
uhhuh Dr
G oh oh leave that in hey Nick is this
one tongue yeah that's your tongue take
this and put it somewhere he's confused
where his tongue is tongue is it exists
but you won't be able to feel it for
like two more hours yeah this is my
that's your lip that's your lip you're
touching the outside of your face okay
yeah your tongue's in your mouth very
ask yeah do you remember the password
from earlier skyscraper nice what was it
skyscraper skysc yeah that's a tough one
he remembered it too uhhuh that's the
secondes look nice up there
Nick mhm it looks pretty cool right I
can't believe I was asleep for 30
minutes yeah and bite
down oh got your lip you can't bite on
your lip don't do that try it one more
time there you're going to hurt yourself
and then what is that
[ __ ] that ship yeah he wants to know
what the ship is on the TV um I think
it's just a random Cruise ad or
something oh no it's um top older songs
and that's just the you're listening to
oldies during the whole surgery yeah he
loves old right Nick I do like that
Buttercup
song I love that song yeah can I get you
anything while you're sitting are you
good so the key here is don't bite your
tongue Nick you're biting your tongue
his arm is well rested but if you moves
it it'll stop doing this drip so the
medicine just goes slower yeah so as
long as you see this thing dripping that
means we're moving nice so you got to
stay still okay okay nice you're doing a
good job yeah you have an IV in still
I know that freaks you out just don't
look at it it's going in is the harder
part all they got to do is take out yeah
stop biting it just leave your mouth I
can't tell where it is it's right where
it should be in between your teeth like
in your mouth you just got to tell me if
I'm biting it I can't care I'll let you
know that's your finger you look like ET
when you do
that hey Nick Nick hey Nick need Nick
what what did he just say what did he
just say about the IV it goes faster if
your arms are still you have to stay
completely still like this like I
understand that I need some
slap okay yeah
thanks Nick Dr G Dr Gabe was nice enough
to give you extra gauze so there's like
aund [ __ ] Wes right here yeah there's
a bunch it's crazy my heart rate is way
slower yeah cuz you're calm
now your legs aren't shaking anymore are
being calm I I'm very happy to see you
Cal oh you're licking your lip keep fing
hey Nick oh yeah you need some of that
some space cam oh the easy twist tube
helps you out doesn't it so much it's so
much more convenient than the other one
I
agree yeah just nice oh
no you on your face buddy yeah you
missed a little you put it on your chin
here do you want it on your lip a little
bit a little bit Yeah I won't do that
much you
want I here I'll you need it go do a
kiss face Nick go M ni
good hey of course you got to stop doing
that Nick cuz you did that last time and
it messed up your gauze My Gauze is
already annoying yeah so leave it stop
making it more annoying stop rolling
your eyes stop doing that put that
finger down you're rude Nick you have to
keep your manners together we're in Dr
gab's
office stop stop it so I get
Mya they grinded them he broke one of
your teeth to get it out well [ __ ]
chill
I want the too fa oh they it's okay yeah
I want to talk to you do you have I'm
that sink is dripping what's dripping
the sink do you want me to shut it off
no it's okay okay you're should I tell
Dr
Gabe
no oh nice I have a question Nick you
look so cool Nick is there anywhere you
want to like travel soon
you look so cool bro this that chin yeah
yeah that's your chin is this a chin no
that's your lip Chris pause this or shut
it off I
can't do you want to take a selfie with
me let's do
it thumbnail thumbnail change pose ready
go like this like you're
shocked change no don't move don't to
show that all right put your arm
down change your pose dick ready one two
change your pose all right let's we got
it we got it nice let's take a
selfie the song Oh your hair your hair
yeah fix that it looks good do you want
to send a video to Nathan yeah let's go
hey Nathan I'm with Nick I love you Nick
loves you he just got his wisdom teeth
out right all four of them I think keep
them can't keep them they [ __ ] keep
them I can't [ __ ] keep
them what [ __ ]
ever like Dr Gabe and the surgeon said
that you were the easiest person to
remove their Wiz and teeth they've ever
had of course I one come on now you're
doing so good no leave that on remember
sorry sorry
sorry shut up
bch finger off give me a [ __ ]
second he keeps taking his finger thing
off no I don't fell off we're waiting
for the water to finish so maybe a
minute or two and then you can go home
yay yay ni how about you say hi to all
our 6 million
subscribers 6 million subscribers yeah
we have 6 million subscribers
yeah Matt you're about to get blood on
the
[ __ ] what do you mean blood that's
from in your mouth they cut your gums
and
stuff your teeth are gone not all of
them of course just your wizling teeth
do you want to what the [ __ ] is this
your lip that's Li it under that's your
bottom lip and that's your chin right
there take this Nick do you want to say
hi to anyone else you said hi to
want to say hi you said hi to with hell
okay all right what can I do to help
guys I think we're good all right so
we're going to uh take the IV out pretty
soon and I'm going to get you in a
wheelchair yeah all right today today
and tomorrow are Nicholas's days this is
like this is he gets his own separate
birthday where like if he wants to
change you know watch a show or if he
want a certain food give him everything
he wants okay of course everything I
want nice all right buddy
right how
long soon Nick almost done I need to sit
up don't don't sit up or you can but
just just wait we're about to leave in
like 2 minutes we already on a
wheelchair are you excited I can walk
you can't yes I can yes I absolutely
can Nick why not take the wheelchair out
though it's fun I'm not
handy you'll be it's fun though you get
pushed around by Dr Gabe it's so fun
stop off the camera [ __ ] you I [ __ ]
hate you who are you talking
about oh my God blow Nick Nick just said
the whole
name Nick okay Nick we're in public you
need to yes sh
you're doing good do you want me can't
just called out his Ops on the [ __ ]
Vlog Nick what about Sam McGrath do you
want to say anything to
Sam what do you want what do you want to
say to Sam hello is that good fire truck
there a fire truck Our Heroes right go
help them go help them go help them I'm
going to take these from you that's your
song
mix I can
seriously 100% walk you're not going to
walk Nick I could walk look at me you
can ask Dr gab you you get to ride out
on a wheelchair that's pretty cool Nick
stay looking over here cuz they're going
to take the ivoo and you're not going to
like it oh no no I know so just stay
looking over here we're going to get
through this together I think it was
going to hurt these cuz he has a lot of
hair so I think that's going to hurt oh
the sticker is going to hurt cuz you got
a hairy
arm you'll be all right
though Nick don't don't sit up yet just
wait
I [ __ ] thing is going death
me oh oh
yeah he hates that there you go cover up
we trying to make it a smooth this the
hard part's over you got your teeth out
you look like a mummy right
now I love you
Nick what' you say I love no you don't
do this is this to me is worse than the
the W
teeth I agree I'd agree you said that
you don't remember a thing from your
wisdom teeth Nick you're so
cool your mama is
insane is not yet the tap off so you're
not going to feel any tape they're going
to put the Nick you're literally a hop
skip for a jump and AEL wheelchair away
from being in the
car all right it's out Nick thank you
[ __ ] god stop swearing dude don't use
God you had a body M you're in public
too there's other people around you
can't just swear sorry yeah it's good he
said sorry
blocking oh
oh that's okay hey don't throw it Nick
someone has to grab that no leave it
leave it Nick Nick leave it stop Nick
there you go good job you feeling good
oh that's my zipper okay more
modest so we're going to put him in a
wheelchair now he's pretty much he
claims he can walk going to you pop the
wheelchair yeah you got to take the
wheelchair I could walk you're not going
to walk though we can do a lot of things
you could Skydive are you going
to exactly so we're going to take the
wheelchair listen add this this one's
just resting up ice cream you can have
soup you can have mashed potatoes
nothing spicy no granola kind of things
that can get stuck in those holes but I
did give you that little um that kit so
if something gets stuck and it's bugging
you you can flush it out yeah I love
your mouly oh good can I give you guys
some more you guys want to take home
some products n love it yeah okay good
it's all organic but it's strong right
uhhuh yeah I love it let me get your
gear off do you guys want to tell just
in case he's dripping yeah yeah I'll
take it Nick we're going to take that
home for you and your your your ride
is I'm gang affiliated no you're not
gang affiliated that's a good good
disclaimer let's get in the we're going
to get in the wheelchair not by yourself
you'll get help nice
Nick down okay guys some refills thank
you
mouthwash nice you got a tooth fac in
the B was oh tooth fac I love this [ __ ]
yeah he loves that [ __ ] to you guys let
me get this out of here all rest you can
have mashed potatoes that's a good sign
I know
right we bye
Nick you'll never have to worry about
those teeth
again the ice cream later okay I will no
problem I'm
sorry sorry
I'm dude don't say that Nick you want to
hit the elevator button
down there we
go is it not yes you keep asking your
lip isn't the same place it's feel like
a chin no lower this is all your like
care package stuff that's your lip dude
you got to make sure not to bite
anything this is not that's your chin
you keep touching right between your lip
and your chin and you can't feel that
yeah that's right between your lip and
your chin this is your lip I got to go
pay the parking and that's your chin
okay Chris yeah I'll take it matth has
to go pay the parking pass okay so it's
just me and you I'm going to get in the
car on the other side door so I put it
back in yeah you feel do you feel like
normal don't miss me too much all right
buddy I'll be right back I love you I
love you too well there's
Matt I'm going to hit him hey buddy
don't do that how you doing M what out
you say he's going to hit you what I was
just saying okay I'm I have a big job
for you I'm going to give you
this and then when we get over there and
we get to the machine you got to scan it
so we can leave okay so you can't lose
that here I was asleep hold on Nick wait
up I'll answer all your questions I have
to put the address in to go
home
sorry what the hell yeah you were pretty
much like you don't you're not you're
going to watch the footage and be like
amazed at how like out of it you are
you're fully like unres responsive at
one point oh no yeah I'm kidding did you
think I was ignoring you no you
literally waved at us when we left you
said bye when when me and Matt me and
Matt left the room for a little when you
got your teeth taken out I don't
remember that yeah I we know you
don't what you fling off the camera for
bud I'm fing off him who me what are
youting at he doesn't like why is he
pointing at me he just flipped me off
cuz he's he wouldn't care about the
lighting right Nick yeah it was lit Matt
talking how the [ __ ] did I get looped
into that that's the
light you got
it please SC your
ticket thank you for your get back in
get back in can you put your seat belt
on [ __ ] no can you fix your foot that
looks UNC comfy I'm putting your window
up you can get mashed potatoes you can
get ice cream did do I can eat or no he
said you can have like little [ __ ] like
like you can have soup you can have
Jello-O you can have mashed potatoes oh
what a [ __ ]
feish no you can have you just can't
have anything
spicy like you can't have like Takis
right now Nick Matt shut those worse
yeah way
worse you can't have Takis or anything
anything like that you can't have
anything like ridiculously hot stop
putting that on Nick you put on it
out and you can't have like granola or
anything that's going to like break up
like in your teeth F oh no
problem I'm not going to eat [ __ ]
granola are you [ __ ] me
he I told him how you eat granola every
morning
though you know better that you punk ass
don't call me a punk ass [ __ ] you said
you know better you pun
liola you know Matt took one of your
teeth out right is this [ __ ] for real
I took the bottom left one out he took
the bottom left one out he removed it
himself you're lying no swear to God do
you want to pull over and film a car
video car video a car video like a
YouTube video no Nick tongue in your
mouth Nick put your tongue in your
mouth God you're so
sloppy just gross take your glasses
off I have glasses on yeah take them
off I'm going to take them from
you looks good Swag yeah nice wipe your
teeth you have like blood on your
teeth Nick stop all right you're good
you're good wi your tee stop you're
freaking me
out are you [ __ ] kidding me what you
you want to do the lights red right you
dumb dumb stupid
[ __ ] [ __ ] beeping at what I can't
even drive and I know that you're a
[ __ ] [ __ ] you are selective with
your words
today wow that's the [ __ ] you
that's what I'm trying to figure out now
that light is as red as [ __ ] red
could be I
agree Nick should I get out and yell at
her
Nick Nick Nick
Nick I will dude what are you doing
not this sound cannot last the whole
ride
[Music]
we're back home Nick's fully currently
able ew dude why would you spit Your
bloody gauze on the
floor are you serious Nick you pick it
up Jesus you're a mess kid why is your
face wet I'm like stuck in the frown
[Laughter]
that's the worst place to be are you
tired mhm taking a nap today mhm I have
good news for
you do you want to know it mhm do you
know how Dr Gabe said they crushed up
your
teeth my teeth all this little
jar so we can put it under the pillow I
have wow look at those big guys oh my
God they're all out of your mouth
wow look at that monster of a tooth Nick
show them show them oh my God look at
how big that tooth is that was in your
mouth let me see no wonder you were
having headaches oh my
God are you happy you get to keep and
they look
Cut like they were
longer yeah I don't know what he did I
cannot wait for it te fairy to come I
can't believe all of these are just in
my
mouth take a photo of you with your big
tooth strictly blue bells from the tooth
Fair you know me um what's up guys it's
been a month since that happened that
was the craziest video I've ever had to
edit probably in my life cuz I remember
about it's so crazy looking back at it
the the point when I was in the office
and I like I don't know I just don't I
don't remember any of that anyway guys
let us know if you like the hour to 45
minute longer content videos we enjoy
filming and making them and we want to
come up with more creative ideas in the
future cuz I think it's [ __ ] awesome
to do that [ __ ] so yeah so we have the
45 5 minute or 40 to 45 minute plus
content which would eliminate that
week's Wednesday video but we have fun
doing that so if you guys enjoy it as
well that can be part of our regimen on
the stery triplet YouTube channel but
that with that being said we haven't
posted or we haven't dropped merch in
quite some time so keep a look out in
the link in the description the first
one is our merch website and it's always
our merch website so just make sure
you're keeping your eye out cuz we sell
out pretty quickly usually so you don't
want to not get it when the time comes
around and all merch updates and content
updates and every single update ever is
on our group Instagram so go follow that
as well also in the description below
peace out happy Friday see you on smile
big with those cute little teeth
[Music]