[Music]
When you get dressed, you should think a
little longer. Next, the gay son and
you're the daughter. When you get
dressed, you should think a little
longer. Put down all the soda. You
should go and drink a water. I'm the
favorite child. You can go and ask your
father. Me and Nico give you bars.
That's a guarantee. Competition for the
worst. Brother, you're the nominee. Now
you hit him up, but I don't even
disagree. Yeah, I had to tell him cuz he
want to be like me. Yeah, he want to be
just like me. Yeah, he want to be just
like me. Yeah, he want to be just like
me. Yeah, he want to be like me. Looking
at me thinking that's something I should
do. I'm the gay triplet, but I get more
girls than you. Me and Matt hold this
together. We the triplet glue.
Haven't thought of a good video since
the zoo. I'm the favorite child. You can
go and ask Mary Lou. Pepsi said no. You
should probably climb Mountain Dew.
After all these bars, I can't believe
you still don't have a clue. Can't get
back to the hook. Somebody's got to tell
you. Yeah. You want to be? Yeah. You
want to be Yeah. You want to be Yeah.
You want to be an army? Make a case on
it. You're the hot daughter. When you
get dressed, you should think a little
longer. Look at all the soda. You should
go and drink a water. I'm the favorite
child. You can go and ask your father.
Yeah. You want to be just like me? Yeah.
You want to be just like me? Yeah. You
want to be just like me? Yeah. You want
to be just
like me?