I am making it a goal of mine to sit
with perfect posture today.
Oh god, that's not happening. Edit
farming within a minute.
Do your legs get numb laying like while
we film?
No.
Like I look at you and I feel a sense of
Does your neck get numb sitting like
that every day?
I am sitting with perfect posture.
No, you're not.
All right. Can we start off today's
video by doing something I want to do?
Of course we can. We can start off his
video. He
does that. I hate when he does that.
Go, go, go, go. What do you want to Are
you sure we can do something to start
off today's video doing something that I
want to do? Yes, I'm sure. I bought a
diet Dr. Pepper case simply for like the
aesthetic of how cute the cans are. Like
the white on maroon is just so much more
appealing to me. Like and I eat with my
eyes first before I consume.
Oh my god.
It's true. I feel like I just look like
a little delicious berry dessert today.
I
purple purple sweats on. My shirt has a
pink logo. says Homo American.
All right, so we didn't start the video
how I wanted to.
That's because you didn't rip the floor
from beneath our feet and you have to.
I want to start it by each listing at
least
two to three things we don't like.
Two to three things or like things that
would bother you.
Has anyone ever seen a clip of me ever
complaining?
Like I don't really do that. So it's
like it's really hard for me to think of
something I don't like. I don't really
complain on this YouTube channel ever.
Um, so it's hard for not like a
negative, not a pessimistic person. How
about a positive? Trevor is here. Trevor
and Trevor and the rest of the family
are in Los Angeles, California. So
that's been a blast.
That's why I have dog fur all over me.
And Trevor was hanging with us on the
couch, but our my mom went to bed, so of
course he prioritizes her because she's
the lead of his pack. So when she goes
to bed, he must follow suit. You know
what I mean? As as someone who was once
a wild creature.
Yeah.
To warrant this angry behavior at this
grumpy's face.
Go see dad.
Um I have to wash my hair. I hate the
way my hair feels right now
and I need to shave. But I am like I
want
Is that your number one and number two
things of
those are my two things that are
bothering me is my hair and my like
facial hair. Facial hair.
Facial hair. One thing that's really
bothering me, or it's not happening
right this moment, but it does bother
me, is when my ear like pokes out, but
like and my hair like goes on either
side of my ear. You know what I mean?
You're serving us leprechaun.
When I have hair here and hair here, and
my ear is just like protruding out. If
you can visibly see my here here, what
is it? I just thought I got a
notification cuz my leg vibrated and my
phone is empty with notifications.
Second annoying thing I saw today is
this girl was cooking food on my for you
page. Like crazy good chef. Like you
could tell she knows what
crazy good chef.
Yeah. Like she got it.
A CGC.
Yeah.
Wow.
CGC stands for crazy good chef. For
those of you that
we picked up on that. Nick just invented
that by the way.
That's been a thing for a while.
No, it hasn't.
I've been texting. I'm like, "Oh,
there's like I love this restaurant.
There's a CGC." No, you
I swear to God. But you can keep going.
Never. Never in his life.
You're wrong. But this girl was cooking
at her house and she was grilling like a
piece of chicken and she was like about
to plate it like she was taking it off
and she dropped it in like the dirt.
Oh, I'd eat it anyway.
Oh my god. Like imagine.
I would eat most things if they fell in.
Just imagine like really slow roast
cooking something for like hours and
then you just drop it on the ground like
it's
I can't even imagine that cuz I'd never
do it. But yeah, it's terrible. Update.
We're back in LA from Japan. Japan was
great. We had a blast. What was your
favorite part?
My favorite part was winning Kirby and
bringing him home.
Okay.
And he's safe in he's safe in my bed,
which is amazing. Don't shake your
[ __ ] head like you're not the most
You're not allowed to say anything about
that, brother.
You want to know my favorite part of
Japan? or not my favorite part, but just
like my favorite thing to witness
sometimes.
What?
Nick, not knowingly. He walks very fast
and he knows that he walks very fast,
but there was a couple and I swear to
God it looked like Nick was trying to
scare them because he was walking so
fast. He was he was
where their couple or where their where
that couple's shadow was projecting,
Nick was stepping over. creeping behind
them. I literally swear if that's like
not the biggest hint to move faster, I
don't know what is. You know what I
mean? If I'm trailing behind you, move.
And especially that's my biggest that's
my biggest red flag of couples is they
get so comfortable in love that they
think the whole world has slowed down
that they can gallivant or hold hands
and peruse through the streets. You need
to still walk with urgency. I don't care
that you found the love of your life.
And you're you're trotting slowly cuz
nothing matters to you but the situation
you're in right now cuz what matters to
me is getting by you.
Wow.
And you are taking you much space. I can
cuz I'm not going to hurt him. My goal
isn't to big ass with the with the
changing. Nick was going to be like
right behind.
If you hear me right behind you, you're
moving too slow.
Yeah. Well, it's like the thing too is
also is I am good at bobbing and
weaving, believe it or not, because I'm
not an agile person.
What did you You did something in Japan.
You literally like like stomped on. Do
you remember? No, this was today.
What? Today me and Nick are walking down
the street and like
Oh my god,
no. I can tell the story.
I totally can.
No. We're walking across the street and
we're like diagonally crossing the
street and there's
where you are. We're going this way
and there's a car coming this way at us
at us towards us. So we have to kind of
now move with urgency and there's a
parked car on the other side of the road
and I went to like squeeze right on the
inside. Like keep in mind I'm on the
right, Nick's on the left.
That's correct. That's a true fact.
Correct. Which means so which means on
therefore so therefore so therefore may
I say may I say mic are you Nick no
don't unplug my mic I'm not going to
unplug it I'm going to mute it
that's the thing too though don't mess
with the soundboard cuz if you mute me
for the whole video I'm going to snap
your collar bone I if you try to say
can I say something small something
something small and short
no I'm trying to take the closest route
I hand to the car and like hug against
it cuz I know that Nick's to my left,
right? And he's like taking the outside
lane and like pinning me into the car to
the point where I had to like shove him
and be like I was like Nick I'm like
there's a car here like I had to get by
him and I go he
I just Okay, hold on. I just want to say
be I know you're like on the end of
finishing your thought and Nick's
definitely going to state his opinion. I
just want to say I agree with Chris
before whatever happens.
Hold on. Actually, like hold this can up
right. And now Nick, hold my microphone
up. Seriously. Yes. You have to Nick for
the story. I'm trying to go like this by
the car so I can Nick has this much
space. And instead of us both walking,
instead of us both walking by the cars
like this,
he's like this and like pinning me into
actually.
Shockingly, I'm so like I'm really
really impressed by your story. Out of
my way.
Shockingly, it is the complete opposite.
We were walking and I was on the left
like like Chris stated and he was on the
right. And with you being on the right
means I am closer to the center of the
street and I'm closer to the park. With
that being said, with that being said,
Chris, before we got over there, we were
walking diagonally across the street.
When we were in the middle of the
street, I was on the left. Chris was on
the right. If you're in the middle of
the street and you're crossing it to the
right,
who has more room to walk? The person on
the left or the person on the right?
We're go We were going this way though.
We're crossing crossing. We're crossing
this way diagonally.
Your approach only makes sense if you're
going straight parallel across the
street. We're going at a diagonal angle.
You're walking diagonally from the left
side of the street to the right. You
were on the right. Correct. When we were
inside when we were on the outside lane,
correct? Therefore, you need to get in
room this way. No. Yes. So, it's like
this. So, when we were in the middle of
the street, the dead center, walking
diagonally at the parked car, say the
parked car's over here at the
microphone, right? If we were walking
diagonally at it, diagonally at it, who
had plenty of time to move out of the
way, me or Chris? Nick wanted me to slow
down and let him go first instead of
giving me enough room to walk together
down the street.
We're crossing the street. Am I wrong or
am I right?
We were cross You're wrong. We were
crossing the street to the right. If
we're crossing a street this way, right,
Nick's like,
I'm on the left side and you're on the
right side and this is all open. This is
all open street before we go.
Let's go to our garage and recreate this
right now.
I will too. This is the thing. We were
walking this way diagonal across the
street. So, when we're in the middle of
the street, which was like right here,
come here. And you're right here. If the
parked car is on my right,
right, which you say it is. Right now,
Right now, we're in the middle of the
street. Wrong.
Right now, we were in the middle of the
street when we were walking over. How
about this? We're walking toward that
parked car. I'll keep going this way.
How about you take four steps away from
me and back?
So, when I walk, I'm going steps behind
my back.
Sure. If that's what it takes, then
that's what it takes. This was the
This is it. I'm walking like this and
you're right here. So, I get to the
porch car. I'm like, "Oh my god, get
away from me." Where it's like if we're
in the middle, if this is the middle of
the street
and we already started over here. We
started on this point of Tell me this.
Tell me this. If your goal is to get to
the camera right now and you start right
here
and I'm here and you're here,
y
listen. Take a look. Look at where we
already are. This is where we're
starting from. If we walk to right here
and our goal is to get to the camera,
who right now
can go in a new direction?
Me or you?
Listen. No,
you. You can take the step this way out
of my space. And I'm here. I If I go
this way, I'm headed back to where it's
easily fitting by. This was what what
happened. I'm trying to get by the park
and he goes like this and like cuts me
off. So I deliberately go like this and
I push him. Story is not adding up.
Story's not adding up.
This is Nick. This is Nick walking
slightly ahead of me.
Fast.
This is me walking. I'm probably at this
pace right behind Nick cuz we're also
walking diagonal. So, we have to be
angled. There is no parked vehicle here.
I'm about to pass the car right here
thinking I'm free. No. Nick cuts across
like that and cuts me off to the point
where I have to push him forward to be
like, "Yo, it was either I fall back
onto this parked vehicle right here or
push Nick into a open road to then
squeeze by so I don't fall back." And
that is exactly
you're here on my ass. So it's like go
if this car is coming at you and this is
where we need to be, cross this way. Be
your own person. I'm accounting. Be your
own adult.
Accounting for our destination being
here.
The crossing is coming in front of this
car cuz I can't walk through it cuz I'm
not Casper the friendly [ __ ] ghost.
And I'm also thinking I have a normal
person walking with me. Like I don't
think you understand. You were
completely in the wrong. We have to find
a street and do this on a street.
Yes, we do. You pinned me against this
car.
Liar. Liar. Liar. Cuz look, by the time
we got to the car, you had you had 20 ft
of when we were at the dead center of
the
These were my three options. And let me
and tell me if I'm right. Go ahead.
Do I
can I sit this video out?
No. This is all I have to say.
These are my three options. Pause and
wait 5 seconds while you proceed and
then I follow belong behind my brother.
Yes.
Is that option one?
Well,
yes. Just say yes and that's it.
Next. Next. Next. Next. It's not opt
no. Let me list all three then you tell
me. Option two was if you are crossing a
street with a person left to right, left
side of the street to the right side of
the street and the person on the left
has gained no ter gained new no new
territory. You have more room to
explore.
Okay, listen.
I got out of Chris's way. The last thing
I got out of your way. I am backtracking
in my space. That thing's going on to
me. To me, I'm like, why don't you cover
more ground?
You cover more ground. Get out of my
way. The last enough.
No, you listen to me. The last thing
that I'll say.
You listen. The last thing that I'll
say.
What have I been doing?
The last 20 minutes.
The last thing. The last thing. Let's
hear it.
There was a parked car to my right. Nick
immediately to my left. And then like
eight more feet of room to Nick's left.
So you tell me who's in the wrong.
Old old space. That's it. That's all I'm
gonna say.
Old space. Yes.
There is room to I'll be the first to
admit there's room to my left. But why
why should I prove it to Why should I
walk? The only thing to my right is a
parked vehicle. The only thing to my
left is a nick. You wedged yourself
there. Toast doesn't get blamed for
going in the toaster. You know what I
mean? You put the toast in that position
where in this story, in this story,
you're the toast. I'm creating Can I
talk? I'm creating a space too thin
enough for you to get by. Can I talk?
Get out of the way. I will say
no. Hold on. And I'm disregarding the
entire conversation just had. I will say
every time I'm walking with Chris, I'm
like, "Okay, I'm walking with my friend
and we're out and about and we're having
fun."
There's times where I'm walking with
Nick where he's either 15 feet in front
of me 15 feet to my right.
Unpredictable.
Yes.
Also, and then also when we get to our
destination, I will go to look down at
my feet and I will see a boot on top of
one of my feet and he doesn't even
realize he's standing on my own. I have
so much room. If we're going to the
right,
I'll pull up our diagram for [ __ ]
sake. If we're going that way, right,
what I was saying,
I'm really conf confused. All of the
blacked out space is places we haven't
walked yet that Chris could have chose
to go. You know what I mean? So, it's
like to me, I'm looking at this, I'm
like, yeah. Yeah. I don't create like a
divide in the earth to like unwalkable
territory. So, it's like for you to turn
this path I was walking on into like no
man's land cannot cross. Sure. Like I
might have made it difficult for you to
cross
trying to cross. Get out of the [ __ ]
way. But I'm already stumbling over you.
It's It's like I didn't want to walk
past the parked vehicle
and that's for you to decide. I The
Earth provid If I didn't provide you
with room, the Earth did. On the same
token, Nick, all that all that blank
white space is room you could have
fulfilled.
Yes, but that's farther from our
destination.
Our destination's here. We're both
crossing the street.
Yeah, I'm going the quickest path.
I'm going the fastest path. Maybe you
should think about that poor couple in
Japan that you were stomping behind.
They were in the way. Do you not
understand this, guys? I don't know. I
guess I just move with too much urgency.
I should carry a siren with me. But it
drives me crazy.
to be walking. If I'm casting a shadow
behind you, how about you understand I
can't get around you? Move.
That made zero sense.
Move.
Okay, next.
Next.
Why do I forget everything?
Oh my god.
Tell them.
Oh my god. We went into an antique store
and there was a um a vintage cap gun. If
you are a
younger person and you don't know what a
cap gun is, which is crazy.
Don't want to even explain it, but a cap
gun is basically like it was a toy gun
made out of like plastic that if you
shot there was like a little cap in it
that made like a pop. Like you know
those little things you throw on the
ground, they make like a firework sound
and they pop.
It's like a gun and it like doesn't
shoot anything. There's no bullet.
There's no bullet. There's no trigger.
It just makes a loud sound. We found a
vintage one that had caps in it. I
didn't know it had caps in it and it
looked like a real gun. like it wasn't
made of plastic because it was so old
that it was like such good quality. It
was probably like all kids. They're all
bright and colorful green. This one's
literally like it looked like I was
holding a revolver. And so I see it and
me joking around. I pick it up and hold
it to my head and I pull the trigger and
the cap went off and granted like we
said, nothing comes out of a cap gun. It
made the loudest echo of boom I've ever
heard. It was like a
No, that was more of like a light of let
out of air. It was like a boom.
Yeah. Boom. All in one moment.
And I'm standing No, it echoes through
the store. I'm like
looking to see like I'm like, "Oh my
god." Like I I I I for split second
genuinely thought I'm like, "Oh my god,
I'm I have to be dad." You mean the
loudest. I
I let go. I kind of just like hand it to
Mac. to me like it like possessed me
with
and you said and I I go to put it back
down where Nick picked it up and there's
a piece of paper under it that says um
1960s cap guns with caps inside with an
exclamation.
I handed it to M. I had to walk away cuz
well the minute I realized I was alive I
was like I'm embarrassed.
And the whole store like echoed and
everyone was probably curious to what
happened.
Yeah. It was really [ __ ] funny
though.
Yeah.
Like I just couldn't believe um I I did
that. I and I would never usually like
joke like that. You know what I mean?
It's not usually like No, like I don't
like touch things out of place. Like if
I go into an antique store, I don't want
to touch things I'm not going to buy. So
for me to possess like take the gun and
like
what was I doing?
I don't know, dude.
So [ __ ] funny though. I don't know
about you guys, but I've been like roguy
like I don't know what's up with my
brain if it's developing in new ways,
but
get it all out first. I have been waking
up with intrusive thoughts like and it's
not even intrusive thoughts like you
know like when people like oh like his
intrusive thoughts won and it's like you
hit someone or something or like you
like what is like when you're intrusive
thoughts win like you say something
you're like not supposed to and you like
give me like that's what it is
like what is it like if like if like if
like there was like a really attractive
girl walking by and I was like oh [ __ ]
like damn like super loud and she heard
it I'd be like oh my intrusive thoughts
like Nick an intrusive thought is is
shooting yourself with a cap gun store.
So, like I've been waking up with
insanely intrusive thoughts of just like
like bizarre like nouns like a person,
place, or thing. And it's not like I
need to be there. It's not necessarily
like a a craving or a need. It's just
like a concern. Like in my brain, I'm
like, "Oh, how's that?" And the other
day it was the Bellagio in Las Vegas.
Yeah. Like specifically, more
specifically, like the outside water
show like I was just I woke up and it
was just like the Bellagio water show.
Like it was the first thought in my
brain.
And you were what about it though?
Nothing. Nothing about it. Nothing. Like
it wasn't even like a craving of like
wanting to be there. It was just like
out of breath. It was like it wasn't
even a craving of like wanting to be
there. It was just like my consciousness
was like Bellagio. And I was like, "Yep,
then it's like it's there." It was like
in
so weird. And then
I've only had it was strawberry wafers.
Wow.
I woke up. I was like, I need to eat
strawberry wafers today. And I did. And
it was exactly what I wanted the minute
I woke up.
The only other time that I've genuinely
had an experience similar was Jordan's
furniture. Like really?
Yeah. Like specifically the one with
like Wall-E the green the the green
monster that like
holds the glove like this.
Uhhuh. I'm familiar. I that's the exact
like I I've I've literally like woke up
and like felt the jelly bean floor. You
want to know what's crazy? Go ahead.
There's a water show there. This isn't
just my social anxiety speaking.
Shopping in person has to be one of the
worst experiences ever. I could
literally have like $1,000 in my pocket
knowing I'm going to buy something and
I'm still scared to like enter a store
even if I
Well, no. I'm just talking with like
100% confidence. I want something. I'm
going to buy it.
scared to go in two stores the other
day. The pants that I wanted not in
stock or not in stock in my size. So I
look at the pants. I'm like, "Hey, can I
get these? Sorry, don't have them."
Great. Go to the shoe store. Can I get
these? Sorry, don't have them in your
size. Go online. Both of the items are
there and I could buy them right away.
Yeah, online shopping is really great if
you like know your sizes.
It is. But like it's just stupid. I just
I get it's their whole job, but stop
trying to sell me stuff when I go in a
store.
No, literally most of the time I know
what I want. Like don't you don't got to
sell me on it.
Yeah,
it probably works.
Have you ever been persuaded by like a
worker?
I definitely have. I've definitely How
do you feel about the people in the mall
that are like fragrance or or or um
let me shine your shoes. Let me
We all know about how I feel about when
someone's interrupting my point A to
point B.
That's a good way to like talk about
like my my travel or my walk.
Yeah. You're interrupting my point A to
point B.
I love it.
Do you like
I really like it.
Do you like it more than that strawberry
wafer?
Depends. It's like two different things.
Can you put outgoing mail in your own
mailbox or No, it has to be like an
outgoing mailbox. But what's the whole
thing for the flipper? The flipper
switcher. The big flipper on the mail.
I even know
the red flipper on the mailbox. Isn't
that for like, hey, I have mail going
out.
I've never had one of those mailboxes in
either of you.
I know, but isn't that the whole point?
Um, I just want to share, we share a lot
of our life with social media, and I
just want to share a little bit of
insight of what it's like to be Nick's
brother outside of the world of the
internet.
If he has something in his mind like
Terramisu,
you're not going to stop hearing about
it until
all the terramisu in a 60-mi radius has
been bought and eaten. Nick, would you
like to tell them about your um
your Terramisu?
What was it?
You've got the whole wrong dessert,
brother.
Do I?
Yes.
My bad, dude. I just didn't correct you
cuz I'm like I [ __ ] with tamasu. I would
be I thought if you were going to
surprise me with something I would have
been happy with either.
No, you know,
tell them tell me what your creme brule
tell me the difference between tiramisu
and creme brulee. Like I want to know
every little
creme brulee is like
a it's less high off of the plate where
like a tiramisu is usually like a cake.
So, it's like there's like it's like
higher up where creme brulee has to be
like part of the creme brulee is I
honestly don't really know what's in
there, but the top gets torched on fire
so that like the sugar coating on the
top kind of like burns. So, it's like
you have to do that to the whole creme
brulee. So, creme brules are usually
flatter.
Got it.
It's like what's the flavor? What's the
flavor of it? I don't know what the
flavor of a creme brulee is, but I know
that the flavor of a tiramisu is like
it's like coffee cake, but it's not like
coffee cake like cinnamon roll coffee
cake. It's like coffee cake like coffee
ice cream
with like coffee in it.
Wow. What's the most nostalgic thing you
can think of like off the top of your
head?
Uh a DVD like a thing where you just pop
it open, you got the DVD.
Good one. Yeah.
I think the smell of pine.
I think grass in overall is a big one
for me.
Really?
Yes.
Just grass. like long real grass. Not
turf.
Not turf. Okay. But like dirt in between
your toes.
Like you know when you're a kid and
you're kind of like playing and you're
like running around or you're going to
get picked up or you're getting dragged
and you're just like your feet are just
so dirty.
Grass burn type of vibe.
Like kind of more of like I'm thinking
like when you're on when you're on a
swing when you're on a swing that's
above dirt and you're trying to stop
yourself cuz no one's near you. So you
have to like drag your feet through the
Oh my god. Should I tell them about mud
blasting?
Remember Mud Blasters?
I know. Do you remember that?
There was this thing we did in school
where you had to have like a team name
for your classroom.
I feel like you're starting at the
finish line here. No, I'm not.
Yes, you are. You describe it then.
When we were kids, Chris used to go to
the beach and get wet sand and throw it
at people and say he was mud blasting.
That's the divergent though. That's the
lie.
That's that that's what makes the story
funny. Oh. Oh. Mud blasting and like I
can't even say it.
Mud blasting like taking a [ __ ]
It was just like
there was like a competition thing, but
it was like each home room had to come
up with their own name, but it had to
coexist with the teacher's name.
Like it had Yeah. It had to be like an
alliteration. So Chris, because our
teacher's name was Miss B, it was Miss
Be's mud blasters.
Yeah. and he ditched it to the class and
the teacher was like the teacher like
that's a little inappropriate so like
that's a lot and he was like no it just
reminds me of like a childhood memory of
when I used to mud blast at the beach
and I like lied and said mud blasting
was like throwing sand at my brothers
when in reality it was like taking a
[ __ ]
and our team name was almost they came
in second place the mis mud blasters
misbe mud blasters
all I wanted was you
my favorite saying.
Do you Are you going to try to guess?
I have no [ __ ] idea what you're
talking about.
Neither do I.
What is your favorite saying?
If you're praying for the rain, you
better be ready for the mud.
I've never heard you say that before.
What? I've said it to your face in a
video.
Really?
Yes. Like they're going to clip the old
time I said it and be like, "Yeah,
if you're praying for the rain, you
better be ready for the mud cuz that's
what comes with the rain." It's like a
It's like a metaphor. I get the
metaphor.
Okay.
Well, don't act don't say it like you
don't like don't say it like you
question.
I fully understand.
You want to know mine?
Be careful with those things,
bro. How lit was it when we were kids
like drinking tea with the little bowl
underneath the saucer fire
and then you like dump the tea in it.
You
I swear to God our grandmother thought
she was like British or something.
No, we used to have crazy tea parties
with Graham.
We did crazy. Like it was almost like we
were drinking tea just for the [ __ ] of
it. I think for one time we had a
stuffed animal like pulled up to the
table too. Like
of course
like it was legit.
Of course. So legendary actually.
Wish I bought more milk at the grocery
store today.
I've been Another one. Not necessarily
something I've been craving when I've
been waking up, but something I've
needed in my life.
Lucky Charms.
Sing it. Sing it.
Um hearts, stars, and hearts, stars. No.
Hearts, stars, and clovers. Horseshoes
and balloons.
Hourglass.
Hearts.
Is he going to get the box? That's the
thing though. I I used to think as a kid
like, "Wow, I would love a box of Lucky
Charms that's all marshmallows." I kind
of like the the kick is something else,
you know?
No, Nick's running over.
Matt, I can't believe you said that cuz
I was eating Lucky Charms earlier.
You're You read my mind. I was thinking
like I my phone died. So, of course,
when my phone died, I'm like, "Let me go
plug it in downstairs." I spent like an
hour off my phone and I'm eating the
cereal and I'm thinking to myself while
I'm eating the Lucky Charms, I'm like,
whoever is in the [ __ ] ratio
department at Lucky Charms headquarters
raise cuz I'm getting a scoop and it's
like the to the tea. This is the biggest
perfect ratio every single time. Giant
size.
Every single time. Oh my god. Where's
the slogan?
Where's the slogan? Like they don't have
it printed on every box. It was on the
last one.
The plastic took care.
Hearts, stars, and mushrooms.
There's no more mushrooms.
Hearts, stars, and horseshoes. Clovers
and balloons. Hourglasses, rainbows, and
tasty red balloons. But they got rid of
that.
You just said balloons twice.
They got rid of the hourglass.
You said balloon twice.
No, it's cuz they [ __ ] it up. cuz they
added a unicorn and got rid of the um
the
Can I see?
No.
Pots of golden rainbows and red
balloons.
Well, not exactly.
What pots of gold? It used to be
hourglasses. Then it was pots of gold
and now it's unicorns. And there's no
anthem.
Is there a pot of gold here?
No.
What?
Hearts, stars, and I feel like that's a
hearts, stars, and horses horseshoes. We
got down hearts, stars and horseshoes,
clovers and blue moons, hourglasses,
rainbows, unicorns and rainbows, and
tasty red balloons.
I can't. I can't. Why ruin a good thing?
Anyways, thank you guys so much for
watching this week's Friday video. We
will see you guys next Friday. And then
the Friday after that, we're 22 years
old.
Disgusting and gross. That's not true.
Sick that one.
Oh, wait. No,
it's right.
All right, guys. is we will uh we'll uh
catch you next time. We'll let you go.
[Music]