at the end of the time
go don't play with Maddie don't play
with Maddie
boy we did we said we going to Trav from
the island to Madrid we had a lot of
plans but they
all why because of some kid but
it's all right mother [ __ ] today
we're back here filming another video
and today what are we going to do
Nick sounds yeah it sounds like aliens
are coming um today we're going to be
discussing dis discussing things that we
just cannot grasp things that we cannot
understand that are just truly make no
really difficult to understand who wants
to kick us off I will let's hear it Matt
all right I got four that are very like
similar so I kind of want to read all of
them before we like yeah yeah yeah just
go okay I didn't need that whatever it
takes Nick's style Nick's haircut Nick's
attitude and everything that comes out
of Nick's mouth oh my God those are my
first four you couldn't wait for wow I
thought for sure it was going to like it
ended at Nick style and then he never
stopped Noe well let me just read my
first one then if you wanted your joke
to be Nick's still editing on Thursday
nights that's a good one too you guys
wanted your jokes you guys wanted your
jokes can't understand as a comedian or
a jokester
myself insane or someone I'd say has the
most comedic eye out of the three of us
genuinely I'd say that in order for like
just this is just advice you say like no
this is just advice I want to give you
sh put your fruit roll up away if you're
going to yell at us it's freaking me out
mat
no okay that was great
CRA what were you going to say just some
advice for you guys for making jokes in
the future and like you know really
wanting them to hit usually you want to
wait a little bit and give the people
like a little bit of time to like settle
into like actually what's going on
before hitting them with the joke like
it was kind of too early on for that to
beun too early you know like I think he
kind of like self sabotaged by like
starting with that I fully disagree
there a funny start to the video it was
all right I don't need your let's see
you make a joke then it's not my time
yet I don't get smells
smells
yeah yeah I can tell cuz you [ __ ]
smell like [ __ ] all the time so clearly
you don't [ __ ] understand it cuz you
smell bad constantly like that's so not
even funny at all I never smell bad in
my life well you do you just don't
understand smells I legit got allergies
by cleaning your closet like I've
literally am sick right now like I legit
I have to agree we clean Nick's room
last night I legit have been struggling
breathing my nose is
runny clearly it needed to be clean yeah
so let's talk about smell your closet
gave me a [ __ ] disease or something
you're not talking about smell
sweetheart you need to stop getting it
confused don't call me sweetheart
genuine smell you smell like [ __ ] no I
don't get like how does gasoline just
specifically smell like gasoline like
how is nobody bite in anyone's flow
unlik
scent that is kind of true like how does
like each thing smell different mhm it's
kind of overrated and how we make colog
like how do we stuff all that scent
true I don't know but I each one smells
the same no it's a little crazy cologne
stupid no oh my God you don't know what
I mean I mean like each like that each
separate bottle
smells the same the same one yeah okay
get either like how do they get the
exact proportions right well that's just
obvious oh guys is endangered or like
extinct animals like how are we aware
that like they're bundling down how are
we aware that there's none left also
there's so many species in the world
that like we don't even know of like
sometimes I'll be watching those Nature
Documentaries and they'll pan to an
animal I'll be like what the [ __ ] is
that like what on God's green earth am I
looking at looks like a little like
crossbreed between like a sphinx and
like a [ __ ] like some crazy [ __ ] I'm
just like what are you I do I like how
are we aware of like I'm with you on
that cuz it's like when it's birds that
are endangered how like who the [ __ ] is
keeping track that's that's so easy to
track speci you here we go it is true no
you can literally [ __ ] yourself moving
on no you literally all you have to do
is put a little like tracker in it and
then okay okay yeah the bird fish sea
animals fish sea animals sea animals
easy peasy that's actually easier than
all of them cuz they travel in groups
all you have to do is TR I understand
you can see them all what I don't
understand is how everyone can talk but
not just to like put a GoPro on a fish
that's literally it's not a GoPro you
[ __ ] fool it's far bigger technology
oh
it was like a different voice there's a
fly right there in the car yeah but it's
a fly I thought you were talking I
thought it was oh did I get it there's
there was nothing there I there's on
camera there was a little fly there's a
little fly it was right there a little
fly heavy
babies
what you just how could a baby be super
like heavy like it's dude you just got
born shortened names Matt what mean like
like how like no Matt makes sense CU
like Matthew but like how is Richard
shortened to
dick that that one I don't Billy is
William like are you for real like I
don't get that and then Bob is Rob Rob
and Bob is the same name like Bobby and
Robert Robert and
Bob wait what you just said like four
different names all the same Bob Rob
Bobby Robert all them no way all four
I've never seen it's both names then
it's them both shorten like Bobby and
Robert and then if you shorten Robert
you get Rob and if you shorten Bobby you
get Bob so it's Bobby Robert Bob and Bob
Rob and it's the same thing naming land
and naming animals when they're first
discovered like who's just like [ __ ] it
North
America well like it's kind of just like
if you found something you make it the
name of you okay like if I were to find
an island I'd be like oh Christopher's
Island and then boom it's so how did we
get Massachusetts someone was probably
like Paul moch chuso or some [ __ ] like
that and then he landed there and he was
like I deem this like
Massachusetts boom cuz
Connecticut Steve
kuta you're just making [ __ ] up setting
clocks backwards or forwards I have this
written down too like why are we doing
that what's the point it's because of
time zone CH yeah but if you put it
forward if you put it forward and then 6
months later you're putting it back to
where it I what if we just never altered
it that's what I'm trying to the days
become night and the night become day
see I don't know and also another thing
I wrot down I don't get how like you're
not it's not like you're putting it
Forward two times in a row it's always
forward then back forward forward back
so it's the same so it's like why are we
doing like the whole hour switch for no
reason if it's I bet you some [ __ ] with
the government to distract us maybe they
use that day to do something else crazy
because they know everyone's going to be
focused on the time zone change
or maybe they need more time in the
winter to prepare for something evil so
they want it to be darker sooner so then
by like 5:30 it's dark and then that's
when people start looming cuz they're
like oh now we have our evil night like
oh my God you know what I mean I feel
like you got a bigger plan than every
yeah I feel like honest God you might be
actually on to something new I feel like
what if one day we all
disappeared okay well know what I don't
get Chris what predicting the weather
the weather you're telling me the
weatherman knows it's raining in a week
and a half it's not the weatherman it's
stats he's just the communicator don't
shoot the
messenger you know the weatherman's like
hey guys I know you might be get mad at
me but it's going to rain this week and
everyone's like [ __ ] you weatherman but
he just got the stats I don't think
anyone's everever been mad at the
weatherman himself I've definitely been
mad at the weatherman but then I think
you hear the weather like oh blizzard
this week well it's just we just have to
separate him from the facts like we know
it's not the weatherman telling us the
weather okay he needs like a looser
title
yeah weatherman was kind of like ungodly
you're like the weatherman like he PL
out that [ __ ] could tell me his
favorite season and I think it they want
us to listen like you're the weather man
like you need something like the like no
no the thing is they tell us what to do
and oh wear a rain coat tomorrow don't
forget your umbrella okay [ __ ] you bud
you just know the you know that vine and
like that the kid leaves the firework
place he's like what's the best time of
firework bu like wouldn't you like to
know
that was soti but no they definitely
need a looser title Hees it needs to be
like weather reporter um stat stat Giver
stat Communicator yeah weather stat
Communicator I like it weather announcer
yeah a lot looser weather man data data
collector I don't get that the data
collector or the data collector data I
said it say sorry I I don't know why go
no cuz I don't even like that I just
said that go okay it's all right the
data collector yeah what how do they
know it's raining in a week and a half
cuz someone tells them the stats Mother
Nature who's looking at the stats God
that's so true like who knows like I it
all has to do tell the weather man like
is he like do you think he checks the
stats oh my God we might have it all
wrong like he actually might be the stat
collector as well and that's why it's
the weather man cuz he might like have
put the satellites out that's like oh
it's raining this week I don't know
about all that but
he definitely getting you think he just
goes outside he's definitely getting a
tip about it and what to say and [ __ ]
what if it's all a green what if the
person who was supposed to like cleap
the weather what hold on hold on he's
just [ __ ] CHR what if the person who was
supposed to collect the weather and then
be
like what if the person who was supposed
to collect the weather was supposed to
like tell the weatherman oh it's
supposed to be this is just like tell
the world but he went up to him and was
like yo and like he lied by like 10° and
then we all are like expect expecting
the weatherman's truth to unfold the
bearing week then we all get mad at him
Don't Kill the Messenger I'm going to
start saying don't get mad at the
weatherman instead no it's Don't Kill
the Messenger no don't get mad at the
weather man like as the phrase yeah okay
these two go together
GPS and and etas one don't I [ __ ]
hate like more than anything what when I
look at the ETA and like you're in
traffic and the whole point of the ETA
is supposed to be like oh you get there
like this is the amount of time till
you're at that destination and you're
looking at the ETA and then it's like as
you're driving and you're in traffic it
like keeps going up a minute it's like
you're not doing your [ __ ] job at all
yeah like figure out what the traffic
ahead of me that's what I'm saying yeah
so it's like that like why well it is e
is estimated time of arrival so it's not
really like if it was like PTA like
precise time of Aral said ta time
arrival like time of arrival no I liked
the additional thank you PTA sounds way
more professional parent Teachers
Association it's taken
no it is now precise time
ACC [ __ ] you loser precise time arrival
no hold on why they should have an ETA
and a PTA like oh this was your ETA but
your PTA is now but they don't know the
PTA that's
what I thought there was a bug on me but
it was just like a little like it was a
charger that was actual I don't get you
can't have PTA and ET because we don't
know the PTA that's why we have an ETA
what's up with miles per hour too we
don't have a p that's why I don't get
Chris you want to know what I don't
get what you say Easter egg I say EAS
you're list listen listen I said PTA
listen if it's estimated time of arrival
that's what it stands for and it's ETA
why aren we throwing in an O for of time
what estimated
of arrival oh I hate when there's like
estimated time arrival throw in the O I
hate when there's like don't let don't
let of get get National Association of
Basketball throw in the o oh wait no
it's actually National Basketball
Association that one's right I said it
wrong I feel like sometimes when the
word of or like the is in those they
like exclude the letter for what though
dude include the letter what I just said
no I know that's what I'm like I'm
reiterating I agree like every no you
said in that one particular I'm talking
the overall well that's what I meant as
in like it's okay we're on the same page
so don't AR get it [ __ ] you back to the
weatherman bit okay right how are we
tracking meteors and they're like 0.3
estimated near Miss [ __ ] you I to know
about it you doing anything I don't get
why taking a [ __ ] is embarrassing I
agree like when you go out in public
it's like oh you have to [ __ ] in like
the public bathroom like you don't
really want to like everyone has to [ __ ]
yeah on the same note I don't understand
why people trash public bathrooms like
let's let this be a place of serene and
peace yes correct I don't know what that
means I don't either Serenity that's
what I meant to say I say let this be a
place of peace and calm where people can
go and use the bathroom you know what I
mean let this be a place just a bunch of
hooligans Go in the bathroom and if
trash bathrooms like nothing beat in
high school when they were like throwing
[ __ ] at the wall and like like dude
things I've never seen before legit the
bathroom like and like like trash dude
I've seen [ __ ]
[ __ ] and everywhere like you're you're
absolutely just trashing a bathroom
you're the worst just like I don't know
how they don't get caught like how do
you not walk into someone just like
throwing their [ __ ] W other students the
teachers have their own bathroom so I if
I walk into a bathroom and some kid
throwing the [ __ ] at the wall I got
other things my dream bathroom scenario
everywhere in the world would be just
like 10 individual person no bathrooms
for any I agree ful I fully agree but
the plumbing just can't probably keep up
with that I definitely could it's just
like 10
toilets I don't understand I also don't
understand why urals were made for like
the boy's bathroom it's like we can pee
in a in a stall you know what I mean
butal Journal only you can only pee in
it's like why are we creating a less
useful device than the one that's
already there that I I think it's
water like you don't have to fill up a
Ural full of water it like saves water
well I don't understand it's like food
and baking and how like everything has
an individual taste but we're just going
to throw all these things together and
get this meal ingredients that's
ingredients is crazy you know what I'm
saying like Chris Chris said it the
other day if you're you threw an extra
fourth of oil in there your brownies a
cake that's I'm genuinely shocked by a
little bit more oil your brownies it's
not even just that like it's even like
with different pastas like oh we're
going to like like who is the first
[ __ ] to make pesto like I love
you thanks but why another thing hey I I
don't get is like three grains of salt
doesn't really taste like much but
pepper on the other hand oh oh pepp like
it's insane like the amount of different
like food Creations it's like you know
people are like oh this is the most
secure passcode ever and it has like so
many different like like because you can
choose from 1 to N9 to zero and you can
be like oh my God like how many
different outcomes like with the food
world the ingredi throw like the
craziest [ __ ] together and why wouldn't
it be good and that's why I don't get
like weird food combinations technically
everything in my mind is a weird [ __ ]
food combination you just made [ __ ]
pesto and I don't know why what is pesto
who are you how you do that revealing
yourself yeah The Wizard of Oz creating
these ingredients come back from behind
the curtain [ __ ] how I don't get
it all like every single food takes
ingredients sometimes meals up to like
30 up to like 30 I'm like oh my God God
when are we going to end this like do
not it's like people are starving let's
lower the amount of ingredients and feed
the hungry it's also like you know the
extra little leaves on the top isn't
doing anything the baay leav what are
you there get out of here extra
ingredients does truly blow my mind
ingredients is like the most how many
how many things Do's like cheese in
really well maybe it's because I'm white
and like I've been I have very lack of
seasoning in my life like I don't think
I've had like a single really well
seasoned meal but
regardless ingredients shock me to my
core I agree especially like different
restaurants it's like how are they not
like when you go to this restaurant you
go to this restaurant you like things
that like shouldn't be together and then
it goes together so well and it's like
wow you sounded like you're about that
everyone's got their even french fries
from like you know people like oh what's
the best fast food french fry how are
they different they're all potatoes
they're all french fries and they're all
potatoes well they're french fries well
it's like great mommy's like pot pie
might be better than yours cuz it's the
ingredients the ing it's not the meal
really it's the ingredients it's the
chef if it's made with oh my God and
it's like it is crazy that a chef puts
the ingredients together I agree mhm and
then like a recipe imagine dying with a
secret recipe of something that's the
thing too what if you what if you know
how to make like the most killer meal
ever and then you're just gone and you
haven't taught anyone this recipe it
might someone might come up with the
next if I dude if I was in with like the
guy from like great gal's pie I'm like
running over to him tell me that [ __ ]
real quick before
you no if someone has hold on if someone
genuinely has cooked me a meal and I
know they're the only [ __ ] that
knows all the ingredients to make it
like that and they're about to die screw
like the come on you grey [ __ ]
no it's like screw like the I love you
and I'm like sad that you're going I
can't focus on anything about you going
other than the fact that this recipes
dying with you share the news give us
come on feed the people you know you
know the two people that know the
recipes to can't fly together I don't
believe that I don't either I read it
somewh okay we all see the same color I
get that get the [ __ ] out here no we
talked about this in video before cuz I
always think this no yeah you say red
red because also listen listen Matt
listen listen we're triplets right oh
God we're all born into the world right
and then we're all sitting with Dad and
we're like 2 years old and he has a list
of colors on like a wheel like a color
wheel we get it we talked about it
before go Matt red Nick Chris I'm seeing
GRE Nick red and you're seeing green
you're seeing pink and I'm seeing yellow
but he just told us that that's all red
so we say oh that's our red like the
that's why like what if everyone has the
same favorite color but like when you
see like you your favorite color is
orange and my favorite color is purple
but what if when I look at purple and
you look at Orange we're looking at the
same color and it's like both yellow and
we just think it's our orange and purple
whatever crazy it's a crazy world we
live in what's up with Meats being like
medium or like medium well it's like
cook it a lot and give it to me and I'll
eat it no it's more of like it's like a
quiz every single time at like small I
had to look at my mom until like two
years ago and be like what do I get it's
like let's just make this easy same with
Starbucks Trenta venti it's like [ __ ]
off give me a drink 100% you're throwing
last names at me I just want a [ __ ] pink
Dr [ __ ] you that was funny pink Drink
isn't that from Starbucks yeah but like
you never I don't know I'm just making a
joke you ever heard of one yeah it just
wasn't funny cuz I was like actually
trying to relate to what you were saying
I just couldn't see it you've had a pink
drink before not yeah you have no I I
have not I hate Starbucks first I've had
a mango dragon fruit refresher which
purple I've never had I've been there
I've never had a [ __ ] pink Drink ever
in my life whatever I don't know where
you think you've been but I've never why
are you ashamed about it you know James
Charles invented the pink Drink
no genuinely like when you go to like
the Barista and you're like oh can I get
this ingredient this ingredient this
ingredient he made like the pink drink
and then people liked it so much and he
was blowing up on YouTube that all the
people would go and order his custom
thing and then they were like oh we'll
add it to our the pink Drink let's do it
let's figure yourself genuinely I'm like
8% we have to find the most elaborate I
have to Google that did James Charles
create the pink drink so that's crazy if
you said that and it's not true I'm like
concerned of what you saw I thought I
saw that cuz I saw him like wait can we
we got to do this we I saw him with one
of them and everyone was like oh like do
you get like your check like I don't
know if he gets paid like he invented it
they proba stole the [ __ ] out of it
that's still cool though create why
would he get paid he's just buying [ __ ]
in establishment create the pink
Drink invent the pink Drink let's you've
had one before so I've never [ __ ] had
one ever yes you have I have not I know
literally pull up a photo cuz you're so
I was in the moment I could pull up a
photo with a day I don't have a picture
of you holding it but I know exactly
where I was where who were we with and
what's going on for him to get one
freshman year oh my God this seems
reasonable yep walking to um you know
the little the little place from yeah
yeah yeah we were walking there with the
you know who crew at the time and that
was a good and he 100% got one and I One
my life what is it you had a pain you
had a never had
a everyone ever after school at the
local Starbucks with
the one that we always went to with that
whole also it wasn't James Charles but
it was born out of social media and a
viral Trend in 2016 it says so like
someone created the list I think he was
probably like the first person he was
probably one of the first I got a few
more I've never had a [ __ ] pink I was
about to say I don't get why you're so
ashamed to admit you've had a I've never
had one he's had one Fair what's up with
unsweetened tea okay get out of here
I've never had one if you could pull up
a photo i' believe you but I know that I
haven't had I bet I think you did I
fully agree Haven I'm going to ask
definely he definitely has I'm going to
ask who are you going to ask the [ __ ]
you know whoo crew that that was there
you know who crew that's kind of hard he
us I like the you know who crew ipped
one of theirs but I didn't have my own
to my name went up to the register said
hi what's up and name on the cop ever he
wouldn't he wouldn't order pink drink
though that's out of character they also
have like coconut Nick you're telling me
you Vans crew Vans crew was that like
the dead giveaway Vans crew neck bald
head black earrings is in order in a
pink drink from Starbucks you got
profiled no I'm not I'm just saying that
version of you I know you got a pink
Drink I put it on my entire it's made
with coconut milk and [ __ ] and I like
have never had that you had a [ __ ]
Nick why is it made with coconut like
your dad cuz I don't like coconut milk I
wouldn't like to drink that's why I keep
saying like oh I haven't had one cuz I
don't like coconut milk and that's what
it's made of so I was like oh I don't
like the [ __ ] drink so I know I
didn't get one that's why I do that's
why I keep no I didn't I'll call them
right now what time is it on the East
Coast I've never had one I'll die on
this [ __ ] H they're all as [ __ ]
I've never I am so confident just you're
like Googling the lyric the lyrics the
ingredients and you're like oh it has
coconut milk I'd never have it I will
what you check before got it in eth
grade you dummy yeah but I wouldn't like
it like I never ordered one yes you
would Nick something first shut up cuz
you listen listen you same reason like
oh when you're you don't like a food
you're like oh I don't like it because
of blah blah blah and you explain like
one of the ingredients in it that you
don't like so I'm here saying like oh
I've never had it cuz it has coconut
milk in it and you're this confused it's
like insane to me don't have [ __ ]
they're allergic to oh because they
don't want it because it has something
they're allergic to in it like I don't
know why you need more of a further
explanation other than [ __ ] want it
I've never had a pink Drink ever in my
life in my
whole know in my whole life I'll [ __ ]
when we die and whatever we go to in the
universe gives us our replay of like oh
this is what happened during your life
and then we can both stand there dead
together I'll wait in heaven for you for
God to give us our replay that says I've
never
[ __ ] that light shut off okay no Nick
hold on in the okay in the legit
darkness of this video you're telling me
you haven't had enough [ __ ] pink
drink in your life to fill up a [ __ ]
Trent guar shake my [ __ ] when we die and
go to heaven we can ask God together
I'll wait for you at the gate I
guarantee I I swear to God he's had a
dragon fruit for fresher though I that I
for sure I've had that okay so either
way that means I wasn't with you when
you when you had I've never [ __ ] had
you were not with me because no one was
with me cuz it didn't happen [ __ ]
youing and what you saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
that we did we going to from the island
of MRI we had a lot of plans but they
all why because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
saying nothing with [ __ ] my brothers