ready watch
this get
ready oh my God I felt to get like
bigger yeah that's what it does
yeah we going to travel from the island
of Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
Alla CU of some
it'sing that was crazy stop chewing that
loud I wonder what that chemical
reaction is I don't care but I'd love to
know like I don't care enough for
someone to teach me about it ask Bill I
no I don't care I'm just saying I'd love
to just have that knowledge I don't want
to learn clearly you care I don't yeah
you do I clearly don't care I don't care
at all you're talking about how much you
care it it reduces the surface tension
of the soda one Mento ah guys I feel it
in my tummy yeah it's reducing your
surface tension happy Friday guys
welcome back to another car video and
also just wanted to add on Happy
Thanksgiving if
youing Thanksgiving that's crazy Happy
Thanksgiving if you celebrate I think
it's a bum ass holiday
but um it's whatever Matt share what
you're thankful for I really don't care
I'm thankful for
music okay boring
answer I was thinking of saying that
like in my head when to my turn but I'm
like oh I'm not going to say that that's
basic I'll say like my favorite artist
music in general is boring okay I'm
thankful for my friend Lil
Skies who makes music got it I'm
thankful
for Pepsi Cola okay boring say all my
shit's boring not just saying average
chrisol I was going to say soda but then
I got more specific like you just said
love it Matt what are you thankful for
friends family and life talking about
mine being boring no that was actually
like the most classic like correct
someone can make a sign about that they
just put exactly what you just said on a
sign and Mom would buy it you want this
nut that's a crazy thing to just have in
the car CRA you ask me I'm thankful for
Melanie Martinez okay I'm thankful for
DOA cat I'm thankful that I have a house
okay I'm thankful for my friends I'm
thankful for my friends pets okay and
and of course I'm thankful for our dog
Trevor and our parents and I'm excited
because right now we're filming this
right now we're filming this video in
Boston but our parents are probably
celebrating Thanksgiving with us in La
so what an amazing experience that is
true moving on today we are filming over
or underrated with random objects things
whatever I asked you guys for some of
them on our Instagram story and you
delivered per usual so let's jump right
into the video topic I [ __ ] hurt my
eye when you did that you I know I was
going to ask you to check in on him he
looked really upset while I was you
heard it or I heard it you did you okay
then don't make Po decision don't
[ __ ] if you're in pain why would you
punch someone else are you [ __ ] dumb
the godamn Mentos down you're going to
explode eat it then I don't [ __ ] want
that I told you you shouldn't have
bought that many goddamn Mentos that's
an unreasonable
amount eat the Mento if you're a fan of
me the way you stood that out so fast
was [ __ ] priceless was
it never
mind are you
done yeah I atat the Mento if that's
what you're trying to talk about you
want an autograph no okay can you stop
those sunglasses if you're fan of my God
where that shirt if you're a fan of me
have that length over underrated
brownies brownies I love them I love I
don't know it's because you said it so
quickly that I thought it was part of
like the the like question like you're
like over underrated brownies and then I
thought there was going to be something
else it was part of the question shut
your mouth it was part of the question
you know no I thought like over
underrated brownies okay um how about
cars I like brownies like I thought it
was going to be like part of the this or
that or like what no I thought it was
part of the rating like over underrated
I knew what you meant it doesn't make
sense well yeah you said it like an
idiot over or underrated comma dot dot
dot brownies comma dot dot Dot's crazy
we're not writing a novel over or
underrated comma brownies that's not
what you said you said over underrated
brownies okay over underrated brownies
there we go that's the question you
wanted to ask you never could do the
brownies have nuts walnuts they can in
this theory if you want I actually
really like Matt always throws a tantrum
if you don't actually answer the
question and I always don't actually
actually answer the question cuz you
drive me to the brink of insanity so
let's answer you already are at the
brink of insanity you insane yellow
Beast well you push me over the edge I'm
on the edge homemade overrated I think
oh fudge or chewy fudge well chewy fudge
that's what
normally fudge or triple chocolate your
the question is fudge or fudge or chewy
can you got can you stop adding to the
question we're just talking I mean chew
or cake the cake brownies are gross Che
or cake cake no store bought like one
with the sprinkles on the top money
total opposite for me that's fine store
bought overrated every [ __ ] store
bought Brownie's mid is [ __ ] unless it's
like that real good [ __ ] like the the
like like bake shop brownie that's
different but if you're going to like
the grocery store and get brownies
overrated every time I like when
they're's really choc like cholate I
want I want to take a bite into and all
be all my teeth like all the chocolate
like that's disgusting I like I like
brownies that are um homemade and
crunchy on the edges like the corner
ones okay o those get me just want to
eat some brownies okay love like Corner
brownies there's actually this thing on
Shark Tank and it was like and it was
like a brownie tray with like liners so
that everyone had crisp on it that's
awesome okay did they invest I believe
they did I would have invested so much I
know
okay oh wow thank God okay over
underrated St Patrick's Day overated
over next arguably the most overrated
everyone's just drunk in green and
thinks they're cool agreed all
right I can get behind that over or
underrated
go Oh I thought I was going to do the
edit of Matt with the cup literally the
first one I saw oh my God [ __ ] over
underrated underrated overated we need
more of them no the fact that what
really threw me over the [ __ ]
absolute Breaking Point The Edge was
when we were on tour after that Tik Tok
went viral and some girl her friended
brought a Chick-fil-A cup to get Matt to
have Matt sign like the cup was like an
actual Moment In Time yep it sure was
and that song's [ __ ] awesome I think
it's underrated I think more people need
to see Matt with the cup I said we bring
it back bring back the cup bring bring
back the cup bring back the cup I want I
want my for you page to be flooded like
this what' you do what was the move
key saying that I winked but I I blinked
and only my right side of my face is on
the camera can you recreate it debunking
the cup the cup video live okay can you
recreate it no come on I'm not
recreating it Matt's left arm that's not
real swear to God not on there you made
that up okay fine Chris actually do it
oh yeah ready read the first thing you
see Ready Set it and
go chicken noodle soup that's also not
on there what are you doing Black Ops 3
not on there I'll do try again i'lli not
there okay
cargo
trousers cargo trousers what's your
opinion what's your opinion on the cargo
trousers the only word probably worse
than trousers is arguably
dunger I remember Grandma used to like
do our laundry when your dungar get your
dungar I'm like are you talking about it
sounds like a breed of kangaroo a
dungare like I wouldn't be shocked if we
went to like the zoo and then kangaroos
on like the little wooden plard platet
plard don't say stupid words I hate when
Nick says dumb [ __ ] is that not what
it's called like a plard no when
someone's like oh Point Blank like point
blank is the lamest saying ever I never
say point blank no you said it once I
was like don't ever say that again
that's corny like I say I just say sign
the little little wooden thing I say the
sign if it said dungar outside of a
kangaroo exhibit I wouldn't be that
shocked if you were outside the kangaroo
exhibit I wouldn't be that shocked what
why you saying he likes kangaroos no I
say he likes to bounce around and look
like a hooligan and have a little pouch
sounds like you where's my pouch I don't
know Nick always has a pouch like a
little bag the the only thing you're
missing is the pouch paper brag lunch
bags that's actually on there paper bag
one got you think it's was
wasteful M it's he believes it's
wasteful it's completely recyclable it's
paper
M got that wasteful Health R is okay I
think the planet needs some more
recycle okay comos all my veggies Matt
hammerhead sharks
underrated it's not really a hammer it's
more of a wrench I don't think it's
really more a te yeah wrench a wrench is
like has the open a wrench is not a tea
a wrench is more of a tea than a hammer
correct Hammer has Shar wa no no no
Hammer's the other way rotate if you're
holding the hammer rotate it 90° oh it
looks just like a hammer it's a hammer
oh my God Chris 90° if you're holding
the hammer at you and it's like this and
it's like you're looking dead on all you
see is the big knob and then like the
little spikes are in the back like this
it's like this what are you looking at
look this is what the hammer looks like
then if you flip it it looks like this
and that is what the shark is the hammer
on its side if you hold a ham I was
thinking the side the whole time it
looks nothing I've never thought that
I've never thought it like that either
crazy it looks just like a hammer Almond
Joys delicious I love Almond Joys I like
them what's the difference between those
and Ms one of them doesn't have almond
Mounds Mounds don't have almond us name
the city I don't know what that is
mounds m o u n DS there's a blue one
there's a red one the red one is called
mounds and it has no almonds in it it's
just a joy Matt are you hot or are your
pants on fire cuz you're a liar liar no
there definitely a thing Chris what
Mounds look up Mounds it's a candy Cris
are you you're talking like you got
mountains of [ __ ] in your
mouth it's a thing M what the [ __ ] I
think they're good where they're at I
would change him mob TI song always good
where I'm at Junior Jazzy Baby J tell
him when I die put my money in the grave
I've sang that exact song on this video
before not this video not this video but
in a video probably guys mm what about
joggers hate them I hate them what
almost every pair of joggers I have I
cut the sniff them no I'm talking about
joggers that run like a jogger they do
they do go off I'm just not just kidding
pranked again I met the pants the first
time you guys are right you guys just
got you're [ __ ] weird it's like
daycare with you sometimes that's crazy
it's like I'm in an elderly home with
you sometimes cranky and sad whiteboards
underrated amazing lovely I think
they're underrated I think everyone
should have a whiteboard to organize
your thoughts and feelings I agree one
would be the craziest thing ever isn't
it crazy that a Blackboard is just a
chalkboard and a whiteboard is a dry
erase I hate chalkboards worst thing on
this Earth what it's dumping me you know
whiteboards like what would be the
coolest thing ever is if they had
whiteboards that you could draw
something and then' be like oh I need
this forever you can like lock it in and
then it like doesn't terrible that's
stupid
so what about I could already see the
amount of errors that that would lead to
like accidentally locking something for
eternity on your whiteboard and you have
to buy a whole new one I'm going to come
to a parking lot lat at night and just
start a bonfire and then invite everyone
in the city ared that'll go over well
I'm going to say hey bonfire at parking
lot over here everyone come what about
jelly and jam I love jelly and jam never
had Jam actually or jelly jam these nuts
in your mouth boys that play the
piano don't care how do you feel about
house plants love them fake or real it
just say house plant I feel like they're
completely n fake or real it just says
house plants you're a house plant Matt
looks like a leaf guy like you look like
you just collect like leafes like oh
this is my finest Maple Leaf I found it
on my walk in 2016 with my friend and
it' be like a FR I'll take that as a
compliment thank you yeah were you okay
uh-uh
W green bean
casserole I think I rather Chris stop
there's so many things like dishes and
foods that I just rather like actually
can't say that don't yuck people's yum
I'd rather don't yuck people's yum I'd
rather don't yuck people's yum i'
I'd rather oh I'm not going to sit here
and let you yck who are you the food
police [ __ ] no I'm a respectful
kind man I'd rather throw don't make fun
of people's yuck I mean don't make fun
of people's yum I'd rather throw up
don't yuck their yum I'd rather throw up
blood than eat green bean casserole
there I said it I'd rather actually
gargle piss shuie
boards shuder board always made me think
of a board game I never really thought
of the che cheese display don't limit it
at cheese it's just cheese no that's
disrespectful and like raisins and a
couple crackers and you think
disrespectful that you're limiting it at
cheese whatever imagine do you not agree
do you not agree imag do you not agree
do you not agree that I agree imagine
that sounds like oh imagine if in a
horror movie imagine if in a horror
movie they were doing like a really
really quick like oh we need to talk to
the ghost we need to talk to the ghosts
and they wiped the Shak shakuri board to
clean of everything on it and Drew all
the letters and used it as a Ouija board
Ouija board your brain's in two
different sections it sounds like a
royal family like it sounds like oh the
sheries are going to be here at 8:00
tidy up your room yeah I love D I want a
Sherie board right now I want a titanium
fishing rod I feel like i' be way more
the weirdest [ __ ] ever you don't
fish yeah but if I didn't I had a
titanium rod you don't need a titanium
rod you look like a titanium rod Matt
has a titanium rod what that was insane
that was insane I didn't mean it I
didn't mean it you walked in you look
just like the dude from cloud Chance of
Meatballs right now Flynn what's his
name
subur ain't it like Flynn gold pack or
something it's like Flyn scur suburb it
ain't scurb shurb I got yes it is I got
to get home it's Flintstone no it's like
fln Flintstone Flyn scurf shurb it ain't
Flint skfb search up his last name right
now what's the motherfucker's name skfb
you're going to die just kidding just
kidding just kidding just kidding just
kidding I actually never wish that upon
you theam please keep my brother safe
amen the camera's blinking red I'm not
no what if you were blinking red oh my
God guess what it is what Flint Lockwood
lock Flint Lockwood yeah I should have
known the police I should have known
what's the name of the machine crazy
Flint or something Flint SCB okay what's
the monkey's name Fred no Jeff Steve
Steve oh you sounded like um Steve
Steve I'm Steve Steve the monkey brayon
shoes goofy idea bad idea he's got him
off for the rest of his life can't take
him off I know what's the girl's name
she kind of
bad um Mayweather or um that's a boxer
no it's like has to do with the weather
cuz she like loves that [ __ ] nickname
probably I don't know Nick can you
search it up you think it's a nickname
Sam Sparks Sam Sparks what a hard name
that is I love that name when I had a
mullet overrated was even a mullet I
know it was a f uh fet it was a fauxhawk
it was a fake mullet fallet love
gestures like letters bouquet and [ __ ] A
that's I think it's sweet I think it's
nice makes me sick what being honest you
have no heart my heart's bigger than
yours yeah okay butd you're the Grinch
you're the Grinch don't call me that can
I have a mentor no I care more about
everything I just pray to God cuz you
said you're going to die that's good I
actually said you were going to die I
know can I have a Mento you can keep a
trophy that you don't deserve I might be
a bus boy but you just got served here's
a nto I'm not going to do the airplane
thing I'll take it though it's not
airplane what is it train
uhoh Matt just take the train hey yo
over or underrated catch the sped up Tik
Tok sounds I love them I think it's
ruining music I think it's cool I just
think people feel obligated to make a
sped up version of the song I feel like
the whole world is rushed now I and we
just all need to sit back and relax and
take it back to the good old days when
we didn't rush songs what if he slow a
song Everybody's on Tik Tok nowadays
shortens the attention spin that we have
to listen to songs faster to get over
with them no sit back and enjoy the song
I think it's cool but if embrace it I
think it's cool but if I ever get into a
car and somebody plays the sped up
version of a song I I don't care I don't
care if they're going 80 in the fast
lane I'm throwing myself out of the V
you're really bizarre I can't be in
there that would hurt it hurts more that
I have to listen to sped up version
Don't ever hurt yourself do you like
sell Andros I do I love those what about
Chris we're done like we're done I was
trying to wrap it up we've been talking
for like 40 plus minutes well ask you
guys a few more questions okay gayon do
daughter stop sign or yield symbol yield
symbol why the stop s so Stern I like a
warning stop like that yeah crazy come
on settle down there big
red okay yeah exactly that I and then
the just like hey slow down hey watch
out yeah
stop it's also like a stop sign a sign
like that Rick or cinder block Chris
Rick or cinder block you heard me what
am I building not can I can I talk more
about my question hold it can I talk
more about my question you're going to
throw it brick can I talk you're going
to build with it can I talk more about
my question a house can I talk more
about my question Chris for the chimney
cinder blocks for the foundation sayara
I want a million dollars and step right
up to win it here we have Nick stolo
step up to the game show the Chris in
the car I'm in front you're in back
break your back have a heart attack
what's up are you down for the challenge
tonight woohoo all right guys we're
going to step on over to mat behind the
camera what do you have to say nothing
nothing at all nothing at all ladies and
gentlemen nothing at all no can do not
saying nothing and neither can
you you miss me and all the things that
we did we said we going to travel from
the island to Madrid we had a lot of
plans but they
all oh because of some but it's okay cuz
I'm moving different don't be saying
nothing when I P up with other [ __ ]
for my brothers