[Applause]
Next up is a product that ensures you'll
always have an essential accessory when
you need
[Music]
it. Howdy Sharks. My name is Zach and
I'm from a small town just outside of
Dallas, Texas. I'm seeking
$350,000 in exchange for 15% of my
company, Permapug. Sharks, picture this.
You get home from a long day of work.
You finally get comfy in bed or on the
couch. Your phone's on 1%, so you reach
for your charger. Wait, where is it?
It's missing again. So, what could you
do to try to fix this? Maybe you could
try a sticky note. Zach's charger. Do
not move. Use extra bold lettering and
exclamation points to make sure that
they know you're serious this time.
Maybe you could just buy dozens of cheap
chargers every few weeks and hope
there's one around when you need it.
Maybe you could even try supergluing
your charger directly to the outlet. I'm
kidding. Do not try this at home. But
somehow someway that charger will still
end up getting borrowed but never
returned. This is a daily dilemma for
millions, but not for those who've been
lucky enough to
discover. The permlug charger lock.
Permoplug charger lock is a proprietary
fully patented locking system that
secures your charger and cables into
place so they can't be moved, stolen, or
accidentally unplugged. Let me show you
how it works. First, you'll simply
remove your existing outlet cover.
Assemble your permlug system, which
includes the locking cover, a dual fast
charger, and up to two charging cables.
Then, you'll place the permlug charger
lock directly on your upper outlet. And
then you'll screw it back in using the
included standard screw. Or you can
upgrade to a security screw for added
protection. And boom. Start charging
without ever worrying about your charger
or the cables growing legs and going
missing again. So Zach, honey, sweetie
poopsy baby. Wait, let him finish. Oh,
you're not done. I know you're excited.
I am,
too. Good job.
Phones, headphones, tablets, and other
devices are a crucial part of our
everyday lives. They're not going
anywhere. Protecting the lifeline of
these devices is a no-brainer. So,
Sharks, who's ready to secure your
chargers and a deal with Permablug? Good
job. Oopsie baby. The issue is this
solves the problem in your home, but if
you're like in a hotel or on the road,
it's not really practical, right? It's
just for permanence unless you're the
hotel. It depends. The hotel would be
the one that purchased them from us. And
there is a ton of unique applications in
commercial settings. Oh, that's an
interesting point. You're saying the
hotel can then do that so that they
provide it for their guest. Guests don't
take them away or even their staff in
the background. Yeah.
I do not deserve to rip you to pieces if
you have sales. Okay. Do you have any?
Um I do. I have about uh $2,000 in
sales. Okay. I am now going in sales so
far today. I have uh $456,000 in sales a
year to date.
That's a good answer. That's a great
answer. That'll go down in Shark Tank
history right there. How did you get
450,000 in sales? I brought the sales in
all myself. So, I originally filed the
patent for this in 2019. So, it goes all
the way back really to whenever I was a
kid. I grew up with cousins. We all grew
up on the same street. We always stole
each other's chargers. And then in 2019,
I went and stayed at a friend's house.
And when I stayed at his house, I slept
on his couch and I had my phone plugged
in to his charger. It was super glued to
his outlet. So, light bulbs flipped and
I knew this was a good product and
brought it to life. This is for anybody
that has one child or more. I got three
teenagers. It happens by the minute. How
are you selling it today? The 450,000.
So, by the way, is that for the year?
That's year to date. I'm 665,000
lifetime, which is 12 months last year.
Who are you selling it to? Fully direct
to consumer. My customers range all over
the place. So, parents tired of their
kids moving the charger, siblings,
roommates, and a huge one right now is
schools. They're buying them so they can
charge the tablets for their kids.
social all through social media. All on
your website or Amazon. So, Amazon's a
huge channel for me and I was resistant
to doing that at first, but it's
actually 60% of my revenue is Amazon
now. And I don't love that because I
don't own the customer data. You guys
know how that is. But I incentivize
people to try to buy on my website with
better pricing. Are you buying a lot of
ads? Most of my marketing is organic. I
do have a retargeting funnel set up so I
can just retarget the people that have
engaged with my organic. Yeah, good for
you. So, and I'm I have a SEO
background. So, I built all of these
automation tools using automation and
AI. So, for instance, like if I'm
talking to somebody and they say, you
know, what's the best Father's Day gift
for 2024? I can text myself that,
generate a blog post, make sure her a
plug is number one uh Father's Day
present automatically published on my
site and indexed by Google. I want to go
back to this 350,000 15%. What are you
going to do with the 350? I I'll use it
to help increase my flow. So, I've got a
decent amount of money in the bank, but
I am playing cat and mouse a little bit
with inventory buying cash flow in the
bank. What's the container? I have about
80,000 worth of inventory right now. Um
that's that's a lot. That's my hard
cost, but I mean I'm selling 15,000
units, so I'm I'm moving them pretty
quickly. You're making any money on the
465,000 you're Absolutely. My margins
around 58%. So what do you put in your
pocket? And what do you sell it for? So
I'm I buy those for about 650 each and I
sell them for about $35 on average. Do
you know your customer acquisition cost
in the last few months? They're they're
less than 15 bucks because I'm only
doing warm retargeting. that have not
engaged intent intently with one of my
organic videos. It cost you 15 bucks to
acquire a customer and the average order
size it's around $58. All right. Look, I
I thought this was a joke. I got to be
honest with you, Zach. Obviously, sales
say no. And you you sound very credible.
Um so here's an offer for you. I'll do
the
350%. I want two bucks a unit in
royalties in perpetuity.
I'm curious who's on your team. How
much? Just you. This is all me and my
wife. We have a 24-hour fulfillment
promise notice. We're up till midnight
packing orders. Doing everything. It's
your full-time job. Yep. And do you have
any debt? Do you own it 100%. I own it
100%. Zero debt. So, I am doing this
full-time now. I'm living off of my
savings for now. I don't plan to take
any sort of profit or salary from the
company until 2025 just to make sure
that I have enough float for the company
and there's enough inventory and I'm not
fighting with paying myself for that.
So, I've saved up enough from my job to
live off of until then, but I do plan
on, you know, obviously taking a modest
salary next year. Good for you, man. You
know, everybody I meet wants to be
successful, but so few people are
willing to make the sacrifice and pay
the price. We've made a ton of
sacrifices, too, honestly. Like, I mean,
we've, my wife especially, she's put in
tons of work with me. She doesn't have
to do any of that. She's got two
full-time jobs taking care of a three
and a halfyear-old and a 2 and
1/2month-old right now. So, and she's
out there grinding with me. I'm I'm here
right now and she's at home packing
orders. back. What's your reaction to
Mr. Wonderful's not so wonderful offer?
Well, I I figured coming in here I may
get an offer something like that. I
would not be open to a perpetuity deal,
but I would be open to giving a royalty
to anybody for that matter until your
money's paid back because I don't like
borrowing money. Zack, why is that
interesting to an investor? Because I
give you my money, I put it at risk, I
wait two and a half to three years to
get it back. I make nothing on it. Could
be sitting in the bank making 5.24%. The
only other value is an exit on the value
of the patent, which may or may not play
out. So, you're putting your largest
investor at 100% risk. Well, I'll give
you your $350,000 for 25%. No royalty.
Okay. If you don't mind me asking, what
does that put the valuation at? 1.4.4.
Okay. He's doing 1.4.
I have good news and I have bad news.
What do you want first? Um, that's for
the bad news. It's I'm a delayed
gratification type of guy, so I'll go
bad news first. Always get the bad news
first. There you go. Always.
Want to know the good news? That's the
good news. Yes, ma'am. I'm back in.
Okay. Goodness. Okay. My next question
was going I just I had to do that to you
for like your whole what you did to us.
Yes. 2000. I thought you'd appreciate
that. So, I'm going to offer you
350,000.
I would like 20%. Okay. And I'd like a
royalty of $1 until I get paid back my
money because I think together it'll be
a powerhouse. That's my offer. All
right. That's a great offer. What are
you going to do? Thank you. Here's my
thing. I'm like Kevin. I didn't I didn't
think it was real. I thought you were
That is true. You were negligible at
best. But congratulations. I uh you're
you're doing great. Um it's just not for
me. Yes, sir. I'm out. Thank you for
your time. I appreciate it. Yeah, Zack.
I'm kind of in the same boat. It's a
great product, but you know, SEO
already, you know, maybe some cash flow
things. You got this on lockdown and you
know it, right? So, yeah, it's just not
a fit for me. So, for those reasons, I'm
out. Okay. You have three offers. She's
got the best offer on the table. Well,
no, she's not Mr. Wonderful. What does
that mean? Well, it means what it is. I
did my research on all this. You guys on
the table, I am also the best partner
for you. I I grew up not caring about
being an athlete. I didn't look up to
any athletes. I didn't look up to any
actors or anything. I looked up to
people like you guys. So, I know
everything about all of you and I know
what you've done with companies and you
and everything you guys have all done is
extremely motivational. It's it's
inspirational. This is everything I've
ever worked for. Lory's offer is by far
I mean in my opinion just I came here to
work with you. So, there you go. I would
love to close a deal with you, Lori.
Thank you. Congratulations. Congrats,
Zach. I love it. I think it's so really
smart, smart, smart. Thank you so much.
Thank you. You're blowing up. There
should be like five in every home. There
definitely will be. Every single plug.
Good job. Thank you. Thank you all. I
appreciate all of your time. Thank you
so much. Great job. You're really
impressive. Thank you. I appreciate you.
Good luck. Have a good one.
Thank you, Jesus. Thank you, God.