[Music]
Hello
dragons. My name is Will. This is
Lauren. Hi. The business I run is called
Above Below. And over the last three,
four years, we've been developing a new
outdoor
activity. We call it crosscountry
swimming.
What we do is we combine the above,
which is a hike, with a swim, the
below. When you combine these two
things, there's a magic happens, an
alchemy. There's all of the mental
health benefits of being outside. Then
you've got all the euphoria of being
immersed in cold
water. Our objective is to get as many
people as possible to enjoy this
activity. And we do that by being the
first. And we think the best at building
the roots, the
events, and the kit that makes this
whole activity practical, accessible,
possible. Events. We've had 2,000 people
do our events. Um, we host a sort of
slightly infamous event in London where
you run and swim during the winter
through all the parks and ponds. It's
called the swimmer.
Uh, so what Laurens's doing is
transforming with our ruck raft. This is
the first product we made and we know
it's a niche, but it's patented. It does
what it says. Uh, it's a raft for your
rucks sack. And then around that over
the last 12 months, we've started to
build some other bits of kit that make
that transition to land to water a bit
more comfortable, uh, a bit more
accessible. So when you've been
swimming, warm up your head and your
trunk. So we've made a hat. Will, this
is supposed to be a pitch, not a story.
A whole So be really clear on what
you're pitching. Yeah. Is it the product
or is it the activity or Yeah. So it's
our whole business is how to get more
people to do it and we make the kit and
the roots to make it possible. So how
much do you want at what percent? Yes.
So we've sold 20% of our stuff all over
the
world. So we think what we can do for
our sort of slightly we we're small.
We're small. You haven't answered my
question. What's your question? Sorry.
The What are you asking for? We are
asking for £100,000 5% of the business.
All right. That's better. Yeah. And with
your help, we think we can grow this
niche and that's what we want to do. Is
that the end of your pitch or do you
want to introduce what you're going to
do? a demonstration or what is what is
going on now? So, um this is what
Lauren's done. We're going to put this
in the water so you can see it float.
Great.
You can now set off for a swim and then
you get to the other side. You've got
all your kit with you. It unlocks the
landscape to new adventures.
A protracted pitch from fresh air fiend
Will Watt, who's seeking
100,000 in return for a 5% share in his
company. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
you, Lauren. Thank you.
Peter Jones is first to take the plunge
with the questions.
Will
um I don't often say this, but your
pitch was awful.
Oh, there didn't seem to be anything
there that you could hold on to that
actually says this is an amazing product
for this
reason. This is who is going to buy it.
This is why we're going to be
successful.
I don't understand
this. What is the business that you're
pitching? Um, as I tried to so
strategically we have roots which is
really important. I mean what we're
doing is in a way you're market making.
This is a new activity that has a you're
doing it again. Will the business roots
what does roots do? Shows people where
you can go. Roots is a race. Roots is a
race. It's like if you're in
mountaineering, you need to when you go
out. Sorry. Roots is You have this most
bizarre way of answering questions. Oh
god. Which doesn't answer them, right?
What's
roots? Is it a race? No. Roots are roots
that you can swim and hike in. So roots
are roots that you can swim and hike.
And then events are things that we host.
Okay. And then the third part is
product. this product.
So, Will,
I'm not going to ask you too many
questions about how this all works cuz
there's an expert amongst one of our
dragons. I don't know if we'd call me an
expert just cuz I've been out lake
swimming a couple of times, but I
absolutely love that you would put me in
the expert field when there's an expert
here.
Compared to me, she'd be an expert.
So, let's let's just start. What
proportion in the first year of your
sales was the event and what proportions
was product?
Yeah. So 2019 I mean we we're not doing
this properly at this point. The thing
that's funding it is actually the
swimmer event in London. All right. It
got very popular. I appreciate that. We
would put it into this. I just want some
numbers. 2020 26k revenue 8k loss. Yeah.
The end of 2020 we
crowdfunded. So how much have you
raised? So we raised 328,000
56k revenue minus 40 loss. Yep. And 22
to 23. Yeah. 55k revenue and minus 180
loss.
[Music]
So, I'm assuming you've got a valuation
of 2 million. Yeah. Hang on. Did you
miss that last number, by the way, cuz
that made me gasp. Yeah. Minus 180. I'm
going to I'm going to You got a
valuation of 2 million. Yeah. So, I'm
assuming somewhere you got 1.8 in cash.
No.
So, what are you valuing at 2 million
though? What part of the business?
Because the roots you you're not valuing
roots at 2 million. I don't imagine
you're valuing the races which you said
only 2,000 people have attended at 2
million. So is it this floating device
you're valuing at 2 million? Um I to me
the value is in we've created a whole
new category of activity. We've created
a worldwide patented product that
doesn't have any competitors at all.
What's the patented product? The RPR.
But it won't be patented. That's just
going to be a design patent.
Yeah, a a design. Well, that's that's
worthless.
What have you got a patent on? The whole
of the rock rafter kit. The design of
it. So, if I change a few things of
that, I can still bring out the same
product. You would have to make it
heavier. Why couldn't it be lighter? Uh
because anything below is it would
infringe the patent.
So, this is the thing worth 2 million.
Uh I think no. I I I would I would say
that the whole uh lifestyle, business
and brand around the thing and what it
enables in the same way that Patagonia
started making carabiners that enabled
climbing and then grew that's where we
want to get. How big is your brand in
terms of give me community size? 5,000
Instagram.
I don't think that's Patagonia.
Not yet. No. Not yet. No. I think this
is I've been in the den for three years
now. I think this is the steepest
valuation I've ever seen. And yeah, in
relation to the value that I see before
me and the business I see before me,
55k revenue you made, you lost almost
200k profit last year and the business
is worth 2 million.
Yeah, that is I mean, not to use one of
Peter's phrases, but that's cuckoo land.
That's really something. It doesn't make
sense to me, so I'm going to say that
I'm out.
Well, I I still sit here really
bewildered. This this is I'm going to
relay to you what this looks like
sitting here in this chair. A business
that's not just failing to grow. It's
actually going slightly backwards. And
then when you raise some money from
crowdfunding, you manage to make a
40,000 loss into 180,000 loss.
So, at what point does it make money?
Well, I mean, it would make money. So,
can I just talk about in sales terms?
It' be better if you answer the
questions. If we sold a,000 units of the
body warmer and the ruck, we break even
around a a revenue of 300. And when will
that be? Year five. We think it'll take
us 5 years. So, by year five, I've
recouped all of the losses that you've
made so far. Yes. And we've got a
business. Does that sound like a good
investment to you?
I think it I I think in all honesty, I
think it probably depends on what type
of investment you're looking for. We
know. We know. Sorry. Well, I'm looking
for an investment that makes a
return on my investment. Yeah. Listen.
Well, you actually seem like a really
nice guy. Okay.
But this is a really bad
pitch. There's there's just given me no
reason to invest. So, I'm afraid I won't
be will I'm out.
Will, let me tell you where I stand,
right? Um, you seem like a very nice
guy, but to me, listening to you, you're
like a raft stuck in the middle of the
sea. I don't know which way to
go. So therefore, I'm not going to give
you a lifeline, and I'm
[Music]
out. Um, without being brutal, this is a
really unfocused pitch. Yep.
This pit should have been very much
predicated on I've created a global
patented inflatable rucks
sack. And the reason why I've done that
is because 10 to 20,000 people are out
swimming up and down just in the UK
alone and they don't have this
product and they're all going to want
it. and then go to by the way I know
it's going to be successful because I
run trails at the moment from Lan's end
to Jona Gro and everybody wants to buy
this you've explained the
rationale you've explained what it is
you've explained why people will want
it and you didn't do that
yeah and you haven't given yourself a
So, for that reason, I'm
out. But I just hope you take a lot away
today because you could have something.
Yeah. No, I think that's a beautiful
description of what I was trying to get
across and I wish I had done that.
Will, I loved your pitch. I enjoyed
every word. I was right there with you.
I genuinely did look I wanted to invest
in this business so bad with my heart.
Didn't even let my head get a look in
because I was so excited. I thought I
can do this. I can get on board with
him. Really passionate about it. And
then I'm sat there listening to these
guys and I'm thinking by they're being a
bit mean
today. But you've got to think about
your
audience. One out of the five of us was
potentially into this. And to everybody
else's point, you've done a terrible job
of selling the
business. You've sold the dream, but you
haven't sold the investment.
Yeah. So, I'm going to say I'm
out. And I know it's been a tough time,
but I hope you've had a lot of learning
from it. Yeah, we we have. Thanks, Will.
Well done. Good luck with
Will leaves the den with plenty of
advice but no investment.
I'm a bit deflated.
Started badly and got worse. Peter which
had right out of the gate was like right
that was the worst I've ever seen. I was
like oh man. But you've got to do these
things. Got to put yourself under the
scrutiny.
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger
again.