Hi Sharks. I'm Tim. And I'm Scott. We
are seeking $250,000
in exchange for 10% of our company,
Paddle Smash.
Pickle ball. It is the fastest growing
sport in North America. And if you're
not playing yet, you are definitely
missing out.
Spikeball is a wildly popular outdoor
game.
Now imagine if pickle ball and spikeball
went out for a nice romantic evening.
Oh yeah. Ooh yeah, baby.
Things went great. And Smash, they made
a baby. That baby is Paddle Smash. We've
combined the best elements of both into
the ultimate outdoor game. Take a look
at this video.
Paddle Smash is played two versus two.
Teammates work together to bump, set,
and smash the ball into the court and
over the net. It's then the opposing
team's job to do the same.
Games are played to 11 points, so
they're quick, fun, and full of energy.
Paddle Smash is portable. Think Pickle
Ball to Go. It can be set up and taken
down in minutes.
So, which one of you sharks wants to
bump, set, and smash a deal with us?
What is the average age of who plays it?
I'm picturing young guys.
Yeah, we we say it's best for families
with kids over the age of 13. So, it's a
little hard to kind of come in. There's
some hand eye coordination involved. So,
older kids, teenagers, families looking
to play together.
So, you you guys know Spikeball came on
Shark Tank, right? People always ask me,
"What's the one deal I missed?"
It was Spike Ball. And that's blown up.
Yeah, it's blown up huge.
All right. So tell us about you and how
did you come up with this?
So we're not the inventors of Paddle
Smash. The story really starts with Joe
Bingham who is the inventor and Joe has
seven kids. He's a structural engineer.
He said to himself, "Can I create a game
that brings pickle ball into our
backyard and he created Paddle Smash? He
tinkered in his garage, glued a bunch of
stuff together, and made Paddle Smash."
He started playing this with friends and
family just at parties and over two
years refined it, but he didn't know
what to do with it. And that's actually
where Tim and I come into the story. So
Scott and I have a combined 25 years of
experience in the toying game industry.
Uh Scott had co-founded a chain of
retail stores and I co-founded a a board
game company and Scott was the first
retailer to pick up my game and both of
us ended up selling our businesses to
other big toy game companies and we
vowed to work together. We got along
well and Scott's a huge pickleball
player. So it was just kind of
fortuitous that we were introduced to
the inventor Joe. Shortly after we
having these conversations about what we
wanted to work on together and we saw
it, we brought it to pickleball course,
play tested it with pigball players.
They got it immediately and we were
like, "This is it. Let's do it. Let's
bring it."
Did you buy the rights or the IP?
We intellectual property.
So Joe gets a royalty for it, but
yeah, he gets the royalty. I know you
like that word.
Stealing one out of here.
Yeah, he beat you to it.
How much does it cost you to make? And
how much are you selling it for?
The retail is $200.
Wow.
What's it cost you to make?
$55.
Okay. Landed.
Does that include the royalty back to
Joe?
It doesn't. So it' be slightly more than
that. Joe gets a 5% royalty.
5% of
net sales of net. Wow.
What involvement is Joe? Or is he just
silent and he just gets his royalty?
Joe gets fun update calls.
Fun update calls
and then he gets a quarterly royalty
check and he's always excited. It comes
with four paddles, two balls, the net
system, and the base. The base folds in
half and becomes the case for the game.
Oh, really? That's quite easy.
This is the base.
That's very smart.
Have you sold any?
Have we sold any? That's a good
question.
What are your sales?
Uhoh.
Is that a good or a bad?
You'll tell me.
Okay. So, we're 9 months old and we're
barely out of the womb. We
have sold to date $700,000 worth of
product.
That's really good.
Yeah. 700,000.
Have you made any money on it?
We're break even right now.
Good for you.
Okay.
How are you selling this?
So, we started out as a direct to
consumer. Have a e-commerce store. Um,
as like a flyer, we sent some cold
emails and like LinkedIn messages to
buyers at Dick Sporting Goods, Shields,
Academy Sports. They're the three
largest sporting goods retailers in the
country. Um much to our surprise, they
all got back to us and they all said
yes. So, wait, wait, wait, wait. Stop
right there. Stop right there.
Wow.
So many people come on and say, "Oh, I
need a shark to go connect with
everybody." Right. You just sent a cold
LinkedIn email.
They like your pickle is hot,
right? They're looking for any angle.
Anything pickleball related, they are
snatching up.
So, what do you need the 250 for?
Yeah. So, I think for a couple things.
One would definitely be inventory. Um
the other is just all these
opportunities for growth. We have dialed
in what marketing works best and we
think we know
which is what
time to turn on the engines. So social
media marketing is the sweet spot for us
guys. I like it. I'll make you an offer.
It's a very simple idea and it works.
250,000 I want 20%.
We appreciate that offer.
Yeah. Thank you.
I think it's a great offer.
So Mark and I own a pickle ball team.
Yes, we do.
I like it. I mean, I think this is this
whole thing is blowing up. As you guys
know, pickle ball is huge. And Mark, are
you interested in doing this?
Sure, we can do it together.
Yeah. Uh 250,000. What do you think,
Mark?
I mean, 20% is probably about right to
get two of us.
Wow. He's so generous today. I was going
to ask for 25, but yeah, I'll do it for
20%. 250,000. 20% Mark and I.
You won't get Mr. Wonderful there.
Uh, would you be doing would you be
willing to do um
No, no.
No. No. Seriously?
Yeah. I mean, um, so would you want to
do 500,000 for the 20%.
No. I tremendous amount of value. We're
in this game. We own a pickle ball team.
I mean, you want the two of us on this.
I'll go to 15% just to squeeze heads.
You don't want a guy like Kevin on this
deal.
Yeah. You guys got to make a decision.
And I understand. And look, if you don't
want to do it, that's fine, too.
One thing is we're not paying ourselves
anything.
We have it all in. The equity is the
only thing we get. That's your uprise,
right?
You just got to decide.
Would you match Mr. Wonderful's offer of
15%.
No. No.
Can we chat for a second?
Yes.
Make it fast.
I'll have this. Could I have this
paddle?
Yeah. Use your paddle.
What do you want to do?
I don't know what you want to do.
It's a lot.
Okay.
All right. Well, thank you for all the
offers.
We want to take one more swing at you
two.
We would love to work with you, but we
really are looking for $250,000 for 15%
of the business.
No.
Didn't Kevin offer you 15%.
He did.
Well, there is Kevin.
Yeah, but he's not the right partner.
These guys are.
That's interesting, Barbara. But you
don't have an offer at all. I'm not
interested. Don't tell me.
Guys, look. Obviously, you don't want to
do it. Guys, look. Obviously, what do
you think?
Okay. We have a deal. Seal
decision.
We have a deal.
Wow. Are you sure?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Appreciate it, guys.
All right. Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
Did we just do it, Tim?
We walk out with a little bit of this.
Woo!
Yeah.