so I think the one thing that I wish I
had done differently is I wish I had
made these pivots faster sometimes you
have to change your DNA faster but then
because you are who you are and you
don't want to change something that's
quite core to you that takes a long time
at least realize that the things that
you're doing are influenced by who you
are and and by the human aspect for
example we used should focus on drones
and then we had people that were quite
close to drones companies that we work
with and then also they spent a long
time developing the drones cells and the
drones design and when we say now we
pivot to EVS we to let go all that all
the relationships we build with those
people all the work that we did all the
momentum that we build we had to let
that go and that's not that easy it goes
back to Pivot when you make a pivot
there is a risk and the biggest risk is
you are letting go of something it's
quite natural for you to be emotionally
attacked attach to the thing that you're
trying to let go but you have to let go
the sake of growth so I think I wish I
had let go of momentum the pass the DNA
faster so that we could actually pivot
faster my name is CH hul I'm the founder
and CEO of SCS aai we develop Next
Generation lithium metal batteries for
electric transportation both on land and
in the air we also use AI to accelerate
the pace of material Discovery and
improve EV safety we've been around for
more than 10 years we've raised more
than half a billion dollars now we're
listed on the lyc and we were the
world's first to develop Automotive a
sample and Automotive B sample lithium
metal sales and we partner with global
card companies including GM Hyundai and
Honda so when I was a child I was
fascinated by the universe and then in
terms of anime Transformers just like
any other kid that grew up in the late '
80s and the '90s everything that we have
today Once Upon a Time was an
imagination a lot of things in
Transformers for example cars flying
cars space travel nowadays we are quite
close to be living in a society where
you have these things everywhere I was
fascinated by physics show a lot of my
time and MIT in undergrad SCI physics
and then at that time when I started my
PhD in 2007 2008 it was a very special
time in the US
it's the largest lithium ion automotive
battery manufacturing plant in the
country and today the company A123
Systems will officially open their new
plant A123 was at the peak I would go to
these seminars MIT and then just hear
Founders top Executives at A123 give
talks about their experience A123 was
the American hero in American Battery
industry but then in 2012 they could not
compete I think A123 was too early too
advance for its time they had this lfp
technology but back in 2009 2010 2012
the popular Chemistry by the Japanese
and the Korean companies was not LP it
was NCM at that time the OEM like GM
Ford they would make A123 and the Korean
and Japanese salemers compete and
obviously A123 could not compete and
they lost and then they went bankrupt so
founder cosos and professional cosos are
really different founder CEOs are very
technology focused and they really care
because as like your baby but when you
are a professional CEO you don't know a
lot of the the Deep challenges and the
Deep issues and then you get funding
from the government and then you quickly
forget who you are then their
Professional Management forgot that
because they got a lot of funding and
they thought they could expand really
fast they hired 5,000 people in 3 months
build this giant Factory in Michigan and
then it was like from the moment they
announced this build out and the hire 3
months later they had 5,000 people they
had just barebone facility and then 3
months later they had to lay everyone
off growth was too inorganic was too
fast and if you make one mistake and
also they lost focus on quality they
were focusing on management focusing on
just public marketing they had an issue
with one of their I think was like a tab
welding those defects cells ended up
getting shipped to GM obviously that was
not good so they lost the contract to LG
so the A123 Professional Management care
a lot about revenue is a listed company
and revenue is important for your market
cap but they lost focus on the cost it
was huge Revenue with huge negative
margin just it was not sustainable and
the whole thing blew up I watched the
whole thing and I interface with
everyone both the founders Professional
Management back then I remember just
saying to myself don't let it happen to
CSI end of 2012 after A123 went bankrupt
because A123 is here in wam at that time
we were just just trying to raise our
series a we had no money so we went to
A123 because we had known those people
quite well and then their R&D facility
in Wan was was available it used to have
at the Peak 200 people at that time you
had like eight people and then all the
dry rooms all the equipment there were
new sale VR but then everyone's gone so
we went there and we just asked one of
those Engineers hey can you use the line
1865 line and help us build build a
couple of prototypes for free so they
did that so that was uh end of 2012 like
we would go to A123 and then just
leverage whatever they had and then just
build prototypes all for free looking
back that really saved us a lot of time
and then a lot of money was a a very
good experience no other battery company
in the US went through that we were the
only company in Massachusetts at that
time that leveraged that A123 and I
think both that experience leveraging
the A123 incubator learning from A1
123's mistake A123 had a good technology
but they expanded too fast they got a
lot of funding and they almost forgot
who they were I think one thing is when
the market is is really good we try to
get as much cash as possible but then we
don't don't invest many others for
example in 2022 in 2023 and also I will
say first half of this year when the
market was was actually quite quite hot
a lot of our peers invested a lot if you
go visit our peers in California in
other places I think you'll probably
like their facility more than our
facility we tend to be pretty pretty
cheap but then a lot of those companies
that invested in these things they are
now shutting it down the market is good
we trying to get as much cash as
possible which is what we did with the
spa in 2021 and 2022 but we don't invest
aggressively as many of our here
especially in CeX because I've seen
companies that spend $100 on cack fire
cell situation will have to sell that
for less than one
cent yes so when you run a company
especially want to become listed there
is a lot of work that you have to do but
you also don't have to do you have to do
a lot of work for the sake of of a
shareholders Market investors but those
actually don't really add value to the
PO Mission I mean I think there are lots
of challenges we F raise seven times
sometimes Market is good sometimes
Market is tough and you have to raise
from private investors from Financial
investors from strategic investors it's
challenging technology is challenging
deal STS challenging these are okay
these are challenges that we have to
deal with I think the biggest challenge
that I hate the most is um is a bad
board so when you're the CEO of a
company there's a board right when
you're private the board is consist of
investors when you have like a bad
investor that doesn't know anything but
wants to get involved could be this
investor has like a timeline and they
need to exit or they have say this new
fund and they have pressure from P the
most challenging and then it's the worst
kind of challenge it's not like a worthy
challenge it's not like technology or
business deals they're challenging but
they're interesting and they are worthy
of your time investment I think one you
need to be as an entrepreneur when you
raise money from investors you should be
very selective in the type of investors
some investors maybe it's a big name
investor uh but then if they are too
controlling you want to avoid that a
dollar from a bigname investor is the
same as a dollar from a less known
investor it's it's really the value of
the dollar and you really want to select
a good board and a good investor
investors that have good chemistry with
you when you have these agreements
shareholder agreements and the Border
agreements be really clear with what
kind of power you have and I think um as
entrepreneur now is not a time to be
nice you have to be really clear in
terms of what power the CEO has and then
what power the board has and it's it's
really not the time to be polite if you
don't give me the power don't make me
the CEO make someone else the COO if
you're going to make me the CEO give me
the power I think that's really
important if you get too complicated
there it's hard to focus especially when
situations get bad when you have to make
pivots if there is not clear and
concentrated power it's actually hard to
make things
happen yes so the current EV Market is
challenging we are in the industry where
the validation process takes a long time
it should be because for someone to buy
a car and then drive that car with their
family that car should be safe it takes
a long time to qualify a new battery
chemistry in cars when you change a new
material when you change a new
manufacturing process when you change a
new design it takes a long time to
qualify this is also one of the reasons
why we develop the three AI Solutions so
that we can accelerate that timeline
actually taking 10 years of seeing how
it behaves under different real world
situations let's take one year and then
take all the data from one year play an
AI model and then have that AI model
tell us how it will behave in the next 9
years so I think the the use of AI can
accelerate the time that it takes
customers and the market to get
comfortable with new Innovations the
three AI solutions that we are
developing AI for science AI for
manufacturing and AI for safety really
start to form a new ecosystem that did
not exist before and this new ecosystem
is now forming because you have more
data from all the gigafactories that are
becoming available and also you have all
these new models that are being
developed large language models New
Foundation models and all these new
models that we are developing when these
two converge the data from these
gigafactories and these new models you
can form this really exciting ecosystems
that never existed before and then we
are working with in addition to the car
companies that we worked with before
Hyundai Honda and and GM we're now
working with computer companies for
example like U Nvidia and and a few
others to really establish very capable
computer centers and also to develop
these new softwares new models that are
tailored to the type of computation that
we're doing so that we can really
efficiently and then quickly compute a
large amount of data from Material data
to manufacturing data to vehicle data I
think we are taking this this Challenge
and then turning this into a very
exciting opportunity where we're forming
a new AI ecosystem in the EV battery
industry that never existed before I am
personally very interested in
transportation related applications
Transportation a that's why EV
Transmission in the air so flying cars I
really believe flying cars will be
everywhere in 10 years worldwide it's
something I'm very passionate about and
I truly believe in when I was a child I
really like the Greek mythologist of
Hermes it was one that brought dreams
and then one application I'm
particularly excited about for the use
of lithium metal is high altitude Pudo
satellites so these are these drones
that fly in the stratosphere so 30,000 m
above the ground and then it's basically
a flying cell tower so you can imagine
these high altitude stud satellites will
fly in remote places and then provide
Wi-Fi provide signals to kids that have
no access to Wi-Fi in terms of the
spread of knowledge the spread of
information to uh people in remote
places I think it's a very exciting
application and also on the material
side we are building bigger and bigger
GPU clusters in the Arctic and this
Arctic Computing Center can power more
and more applications from batteries to
uh for flying cars but also I think is
going to expand Beyond transportation
for example there are many challenges in
climate change you can use this Arctic
Computing Center to address a ocean
plastic waste or to come up with new
antibiotics or to come up with new uh
models the Earth climate SCSI will uh
evolve from a battery company to power
company for transportation and then also
brain for to address climate
change I think as a human it's it's
quite natural to assign an emotion to
success and emotion to failure but
actually there are just different labels
of different States right I don't really
think too much about about these
failures obviously when these things
happen there is a cost emotionally
financially and whatever really in the
grand scheme of things it's just a state
temporary state I'm not that bothered by
those I'm a robot