hello sto Nation as if we're not always
doing it why did I I almost s like this
when you said that as if we're not doing
it every day already
today will you when will I like get like
just peace for a moment we're going to
dress to impress we don't know how to
play Roblox but we do know how to put it
on robblox Roblox stop we may not know
how to play Roblox but we do know how to
put it oning down in the Deep so it's
time to dress to impress all right guys
we are officially dress to impress in
real life bow BW paw BW never do that
again so all right all right I'll go
first on the fit breakdown we're not
doing a fit breakdown we're just serving
everything serving Queen if you have a
Keen Eye I repeated my summer smash
outfit you guys know what time it is
it's time for a sexy slow-mo Showdown
get the
oil oh
[Music]
man hey give us it give us
it oh he's served he served he served he
served fashion show and it's sadness and
disgust make all of these around this
are phone fashion theme yeah they're
still looking at like what are we
playing we're playing big one
dress we're going to serve everything
that we need to serve Jack we're going
to run that we're going to [ __ ] own
the runway theme is famous M come on
come on yeah
whatever uh what do I got to do run
around and get this money no you have to
serve yeah I know that Nick not buying
this [ __ ] I'm paying I'm paying when I
go oh I like her lips F Bo how do I turn
the screen
grab and click and turn hey hey hey you
have to have clicked the wrong button I
didn't how do I like so you you entered
like third person how I don't know what
you did idiot oh wait kind of like more
those are those are those are those are
puss
High I want the fuzzy ones what CHR what
what no that's like that's like Brandy
Melville like yeah [ __ ] out of there
[ __ ] out of that [ __ ] Liv broke we're
famous we need like we need like a we
need like a big like valenciaga I'm
going to lose my mind I'm going to lose
my mind why she
got I clicked it by accident and I can't
like no this is like not good like we
need to figure out how to turn this
camera you had to hit a button that you
shouldn't have hit hit like a Matt hit a
scap this what we'll do we'll click that
and we'll try
again it's not guys it's hard for me to
not be like the most flamboyant gay
person it's
okay really it's bear be as gay as you
want bow bowow bowow what is it just
broke up oh sad okay we need a blanket
and we need ice cream no no running
mascara first no I saw something now how
do I turn it oh my God I'm going to lose
my mind I don't think you were ever able
to turn it how do you rotate yeah I
don't think you were either that one's
oh yes yes she's devastated but she's
still serving Glam get out of the way
maybe no maybe gray gray is getting
Devastation I think
yeah oh They're copying our whole flow
talk about a clone happy it's not it's
really way too happy it's not I promise
wait what if we were just broke up like
we boss up on them like we try to flex
oh we can go the alternate route oh [ __ ]
Chris you're right okay you know what I
mean oh so we're we're going we're going
back to the classics no this is back to
broke up for just broke up this is M we
have to also recog his turn yeah what
the winner plac I want that belt okay
choic you can't even see it bro you got
a long ass shirt on we need hair I lost
this round it's yeah you did you lost
when you started babe period you're
never going to win what is up with the
kitty hat I can't put the the the hair
on so this is my only way of what Matt
you need to explore like the you're
going down the same hallway back and
forth can we try to find something good
please Matt just broke up with critical
thinking you're funny nick period oh I
got it okay hold on oh you got to take
that hat off if you get the hair on you
have 20 seconds shut up man so like just
like long flow long
flow dude you're a hideous that like
taste level down the drain get rid of
that get rid of the stupid hat oh God oh
God [ __ ] no she kind of ate it's really
sad you broke um up she she took my
whole swag she need to print ice cream
she took my whole sweat she ate she ate
she ate no she ate she took my whole s
swag the okay oh like the the call me
like I'm texting new boys you're too oh
yeah like you're giving me like I'm
scared scared Moss mid Mega mid M Mega
mid get some shoes what was that
flip she said oh he just broke up hold
[Applause]
on she she out here they all took my
swag with the [ __ ] ice cream dude yes
yes wait are you us your name is stolo
triplets 423 4 23 oh Jesus Matt you look
horrible oh yeah that's good that's good
that was good I was selling it go back
oh what is this like trying to she's
trying to serf that she's devastating I
don't know I'm just trying to do
something that I was trying to do
something that was
awful the winners are not
mat what she took my whole flow she took
my whole flow those the most beat took
my flow took my where were
you eight okay me and Chris have to beat
Matt I'm so confused this is the hardest
challenge any outfit you just have to
give us everything space bars get out of
the chair you have to give us High
glamour Chris that's the basic haircut
by the way like I don't think they'll
[ __ ] with that can I get one of those
yeah okay get me out of
here make sure you do a face a face a to
the right M no no no no no wasn't giving
love that love
that we'll go with um flare some flare
denim yeah boss here God
damn she got that thing on are you
serious I'm going for like honestly what
are we what are we giving yeah what's
the goal the goal is to look fly but
simple and chill oh I like that soft
green I know girls will [ __ ] with that
one of those that's not green is it yeah
it is the
oh how good am I um we're going to go
with handbag I'll take that we're going
to match our shirt yes Chris I hate to
break it to you girl the bag ain't
cute the bag ain't what did you just put
on type [ __ ] hold on I'm so fly like oh
my God wait I can't forget some shoes oh
that's kind of you kind of are you
feeling the surf I feel unbelievable
right now
chat you did serve like she's giving us
oh my God I cooked you did kind of cook
let's rate this stupid [ __ ] wait what
she went
hard the hair got beat yeah hold on and
that face and that skirt and that belt
now we'll do two wa hello I hated this I
hated this double
oh cheating they're cheating bow bow bow
I don't like the team aspect they're
trying to do like this dual thing oh oh
my god oh oh my god get alive go outside
[ __ ] get outside did I even rate them
like one what is this ugly ass purse
holding it like
this mismatch socks hate
awful who is this yellow hello oh I like
that little goofy hat I hate it I hate
the flower and the hat oh yes oh yeah
turn around yeah I [ __ ] with her
okay bow
hands up
said it's quiet yeah it's quiet it's
quiet for sure it's quiet I don't like
the bangs I don't like the necklace it's
quiet it's quiet she got to
fly what is this horny ass
mov welcome to the
lobby this bit loaded in its head 10
seconds any outfit oh she did the head
that's it that was ass who is that she
is hard hold on how do I pose right
there anyone she lock me in lock me
in hey hold on Cowboy
uhhuh confident you scroll there's more
you can scroll no that's all I did
period that was hard that was good that
was good they were
feeling
oh we did rate her High she did E scroll
down see where you're at
seven oh you beat Matt yeah there's only
eight people in my Lobby though o the
them is family reunion no it's not yeah
it is no it's not yes it is I know
exactly what goofy dress you're going to
put on family reunion Nick think think
like you want I'm trying to disappoint
my whole family no no no you have to
look if I'm going to be honest I'm
trying to disappoint Nick you have you
have to look presentable I'm trying to
have Uncle be like yo what is she up to
that's my vibe you start by putting
something on let's go Mini skirt I feel
we're supposed to be able to turn let's
go mini skirt we're going to need like a
nice little a little bow cute like this
is like do I do am I a stripper or am I
trying to be like or are things get no
that skirt that last one had some
Southern J to it I think like like I
think I'm going to go for a little
Southern bell I love look at Southern
bell this looks like an Instagram post
I've seen yeah I'm every other [ __ ] I'm
going to the family reunion I got to be
plain and simple it's so annoying love
the fur hat thing so hard like
wa oh [ __ ] you're getting dragged
you're
done this [ __ ] walk by is that a
copycat she's I'm serving
puss
what oh oh [ __ ] that's evil nah that's
a clone oh let's see what hair she comes
out with wait should I switch mine up
real quick after no [ __ ] you dumb
little [ __ ] crazy you need like a EXT Oh
no you're good you're good yeah oh be
you're good oh be good out severely get
out of here bye look at that walk Bow
Bow Bow Bow oh I'm I'm wi I'm taking it
pop those [ __ ] on coconut no coconut
Nick that's all your
[ __ ] no no Brown you got to go Brown why
can you even change the color on that oh
no oh no she's cute
baby blue wait can I change my coconut
umbrella you can wait you can I saw
orang is tropical wait this is cute wait
wait wait wait I just
remembered oh Nick a God I don't know
what to do I'm going to hit these poses
as they happen please yes yes Mt
move
um Family Reunion where girl one family
reunion where
this could be like the older cousin no
she's bad low key like kind of like love
Island walked into the Villa she's
serving no more B she serving sheing she
had two shirts on she goofy your [ __ ]
the Sunny's her ass and the skirt's
going above this thing oh beat beat beat
be beat she's not serving us
[ __ ] that was so
family here he comes here he comes here
he com and she ate H look at that
umbrella oh my God she's lowy oh let's
give him let's give him like a
little oh yes that was so family oh no
we don't want to do that don't lick that
skirt no
no
please oh girl one my she's trying to
steal the whole fish you look ass you
look horrible ass that [ __ ] was ass bro
she's trying to be a clone where are you
is your whole family dead fears is like
she's going to heaven to meet her F
that's just like easy though like you're
just going to like the one part she's
the VIP she thinks she's tough you look
[ __ ] you look garbage yeah you look
dooky oh
girl family reing at the Cupcake Factory
girl looks as [ __ ] oh my God please
you're
[Music]
not
[ __ ] first Podium good job yeah cuz I'm
playing against little [ __ ] with no
sty I'm happy like all three of us have
like good fashion sense like not only
are we awesome goodl looking and amazing
we're so kind we also all get Fly
especially me this theme is this theme
is lit monochrome this theme lit where
is it o cute little where is it where is
it where is it well you had a favorite
face I saw it and I was like yeah that's
no you're the worst Matt it Matt I would
literally vote you one star for that
selection single color are you doing red
uh-huh w we love this haircut huh do we
like no well no I'm saying like we keep
using it I use it mat you guys have mat
hit palette please dear God then select
a color like oh Matt like you're really
hard to support right now and I'm going
to be honest that's it that's it that's
it that's it I don't think you're
serving I I think I am hold on hold on
hold on you just got the sleeves you
need the shirt too no kidding wait
where's the shirt
Dude Where's the red how try CLA you are
red you need to yeah you need to now hit
the next Arrow here to do the bottom
part no I want to make it a little
darker red yeah no no hit that and make
it black that'll look good black black
Matt white CL I'm trying to do black
black is cute I got to [ __ ] do
this like it's giving monster
descendants I don't like it at all I
feel like I'm with like against Disney
villain oh Matt the competition serving
boots yeah that [ __ ] looks good they
look good as [ __ ] yeah cuz they went
white that's basic white and purple girl
how do I turn around what are the other
shoes why is it like so difficult to
turn around and [ __ ] we got to be doing
it wrong I think B the b m
queen queen you usually serve Queen and
tonight is not your night can you stop
talking to me please
you're giving like Vamp
stress that word it's like Vamp Mistress
of the dark okay Duos Duos automatic one
star for the Duos that's pretty good
like Sapphire Beauty o where's her
nose no nose no she's her three no what
he [ __ ] she
leaning o I love it is she
pregnant like I'm not
she looks like she's no five stars Matt
Nick I'm not
voting I need to win you're not winning
girl she went hard she got two shirts on
you should be shaking she looks good I
like it like rich but like I don't like
the iing money it's giving corny no the
iPhone's I don't like the iPhone it's
giving corny it's like you're already on
a device let's keep the devices off this
game yeah like you're like this is the
virtual world you're in correct like now
your virtual girl needs some
entertainment too grow ridiculous
Matt we don't look good coming no like
like the competition is not it's like
just mid bro yeah oh oh and the
oh you're falling apart oh what is she
jerking I don't know dude like am I
wrong or did she serve where's the
microphone at like that this is a pop
star like she killed I'm her biggest F
she better be number one she killed it
sir I like the Hat I like the mic she
did great I want to see her on if she's
not like top Podium then this whole map
can get scratched I love the lavender
queen and the win she said all right
three the is cute the bow is she came in
like this right pink lavender white
[ __ ] oh my God I was so close sappire
queen of course she's got that though I
hate seeing VIPs in this
okay oh the only view that didn't be
used the duo good of course Duos are
whack that's a good theme a good theme I
don't like movie night I don't love it
either yeah do we have like a ponytail
that's super like I'm inside right not
that one not that one not that one that
one's already on a grande though no yeah
that one that one that one's I'm in the
studio no you can't do movie night
they're going to think you're Frozen
they're going to think you're Elsa yeah
you're right you're
right you need like a bun like girls
like oh I want to watch a movie like
they throw it up yeah I like that
no guys no like come on no this is no no
I I promise you as your feminine gay
brother that's not the move that's like
cute that's good that's mov night then
they pulled it Forward yeah I've seen
our friends do this for a movie I think
I have too let me get out of the chair
that's like watching movie her eyes are
shy she ain't watching [ __ ] cute cute
cute scroll down though scroll down
scroll
down like I like this
one like not why is there not natural
look likeing the kids the wrong thing I
don't like that what are they going
outside like this I'm think an indoor
movie night right oh wait they might be
going to the movie Chris go back to the
hoodie the hoodie there's a hoodie tank
tops I'm feeling mad it's like a movie
that can be out of the house yeah hold
on this is cute like a soft blue no
we've done blue we've done blue you Yow
yellow yellow
yes all right you can have it all right
it's bright I'm not no I'm not get out
here oh no I need I can't do blue I look
like lyrical lemonade I'm not eating I'm
not eating it up I'm really whatever
I'll just do this I don't really give a
[ __ ] movie night trash ass pick bro I
hate to see this happen to a friend here
this is awful you need a purse yeah grab
that side bag no oh my God we look a
like this is worse than ma no this is
insane no this is I got [ __ ] by this
category bro give me like fancy dinner
night I'm going to cook category that
[ __ ] was ass bro yeah I don't really
like to see
that this is crazy what movie are you
going to see with that goofy ass hat on
want to see Lady in the thought lady in
the
[ __ ] yeah I I don't look bad I kind of
fit in when did you put that necklace on
when did he put the necklace on there
you look awful oh I got a post that was
your movie get snack oh yes that's movie
that was get snackie snack on neck you
look awful the kids might like it you
look
awful Elsa like all I can think is El
why are you
purple
girl oh if I could do zero I
would girl if I could go blind I would
get me a
knife yikes yikes bro [ __ ] you're on
fire liar liar pants on
fire yeah that [ __ ] blue balled me I
thought it was going number one no
Podium
scr sadly where you belong yeah all
right Nick which all right Nick close it
off with a amazing dress suit impress
you don't have to question me oh that's
that helps nothing what if you can
you how do you turn how do you do it
left
click oh my God how we've been playing
like little babies that don't know how
to use technology all [ __ ] night it
was probably the easiest thing ever to
figure out if I knew that these [ __ ]
would be these [ __ ] would be done we
can we do one more be no we can't
tutor oh you got to be a [ __ ] little
Tut [ __ ] you got to be the tutor that
like every kid had a crush on you know
yeah yeah yeah yeah no not here kind of
like I have like a little bit of a crazy
Choice like I kind of want to wear a tie
and this like a [ __ ] to I love it like
a little ooh yeah but that is the dress
I'm going to teach you a lesson type
situation Nick the the black is all the
way mat like yeah here go down go down
go down go down even though we down even
though we've done that hairstyle that's
the type you like throw in a pencil you
want to [ __ ] your teacher for
sure um take that one out I can't
believe you can move around like this is
kind of not fair no we need yes that's
teacher that is teacher te teacher B
she's about to spank you if you do bad
Nick go put the tie on before somebody
else takes it
yes stripper teacher like stripper
teacher like you know who's getting your
votes who is that Pilgrim you're she's
teaching her how to [ __ ] rob booty
from the local pirate
ship you teaching her how to get booty
off other ships ass and then look you
got to put the tie on but the tie got
yes yes
ni oh put those glasses on yeah and the
scarf low key no no we had a tie on girl
Matt you're
tasteless we're keeping these glasses on
for a minute but I want to find wait can
we get more opaqueness on the on the
lens that's what I'm seeing Oh no side
bag sidebag low key Matt no you're going
for a goofy nerd teacher I'm trying to
like dominate DX's realness actually
Nick this is like our fans are learning
so much from
just guys I'm a gay person and I love
this [ __ ] dare I
say yeah Nick those are them dare I say
push
you're insane I'm serious Nick we need
some jewelry these people are about to
see me in my gay form like oh oh there
big sui still in my V but you look ass
you look like [ __ ] look at this
mannequin how bad is that fit God damn
like this is cute this is so cute oh my
God I actually served everything like
like tell me y'all wouldn't smash this
tutor Nick wait you guys I didn't even
read it it's t d o r this is a different
theme what does that word mean it's not
tutor with a T I just realized that I'm
looking at everybody else everybody else
looks like a pilgrim what does that word
mean wait what does that mean
[Music]
Matt it's like a period outfit like it's
like you're supposed to look a royal
Dynasty it's like
Bridgton oh I look
stupid I didn't know it's t for the D
the [ __ ] is that I look crazy never even
I never even read I look crazy I look
[ __ ] nice I've never even read that
at all I didn't even glance up I just
thought you guys saw like oh but I'm
still serving everything wait let's
switch it up or do we get RS like this
or do I throw this dress on I have 10
seconds what do we do buy it for
$6,000 oh no girl that sh better be the
best we got to get in this VIP thing I'm
putting my credit card information in
this later for real we get in robot my
God you should getting Robo you're first
oh but I'm giving everything if it was
tutor who would
[ __ ] who smash no no give us give them
oh okay I got to get out of here guys
that's like embarrassing that we like
didn't read that like I thought it's a
teacher like I didn't even look I didn't
look either I thought one of y'all said
teacher this girl's giving it and we
made fun and it's crazy the clues were
in front of us all along we like our
pirate literally like goofy
[ __ ] guys this is insane I can't
believe I just played Roblox kobby Brock
F oh my God I'm a Kobe Brock fan wait
type in chat type in chat say I know
Kobe
Brock I know Colby just put Colby say I
I'm a fan
[Music]
too shout out kobby shout out Kobe and
Sam I wonder if he knows that he has a
fan on that that I'm out dressing not
really yeah not on theme but you big fan
can we be besties say ask if she likes
the Sero triplets insane feel like so
nervous guys you're making for she's I
met them at one of their tours oh my God
[Music]
wait this is cute this is C is like so
nice what show
wait did we vote her low for sure wait
oh I got a but like I was serving wa
keep talking to
her if I had to pick out either Chris or
Nick would
what if you had to pick out either Chris
or Nick would you
[Music]
pick Nick Nick just like gassing himself
up to this girl his energy is so
funny for
real all right guys that was so fun
actually like we have a new streaming
activity low key God like lowy if you
want us to do that again knowing how to
actually control our character and maybe
throw on some Roo at it for real then
get this video to 150,000
[Music]
likes pleasure doing fashion with you
boys not really I didn't really I I
didn't dress too impressed at all no you
did I was lacking in the corner trying
to figure out how to I can't believe
that last [ __ ] thing like I'm
ridiculous I'm dressed like a [ __ ] and
these [ __ ] are dressed looking
booty
unbelievable literally I'm slutting it
out I'm slutting it out on
Roblox and these people are dressing in
Period gowns like what all right y'all
goodbye see you in the next one and
thank you so much for watching thank you
for watching we love you
[Music]