instead of filming interviews this year
like we did for the last two we wanted
to post this video reflecting on the
past few years instead the last couple
of years of our life have been
absolutely crazy and very hard to
believe let's take it back to the very
beginning quickly at a young age we were
always passionate about videos getting
to look back at them and seeing the time
we were at the pool last summer or the
time I was shoveling 6 Ines of snow a
couple Winters ago the point is videos
hold memories and without videos you
could lose some of those memories or
they could start to fade from a young
age we all knew that we wanted to film
everything school started to get a
little harder and we started going to
friends houses or spending a lot of time
playing video games and couldn't find
the time to pick up a camera and then we
hit an alltime low our house catches on
fire and we lost almost everything we
had we move into an apartment across the
city navigating a new way of life with a
family of six in a small apartment the
start of covid-19 and being stuck at
home it felt like All Odds were against
us but we didn't know that after hitting
an alltime low it would bring back that
love for filment fing again and going
out and making memories overall that's
what we love to do together whether it
was sad memories happy memories or angry
memories they are memories and we get to
share them together and then we started
putting our videos on the internet and
you guys got to join the memories with
us from us just starting in our mom's
old minivan three kids just having funny
conversation to escape the reality of
school work and stress nothing else
matters when we get to laugh in that car
together all of reality just Fades away
then our dreams came true filming videos
together went from being a hobby to get
us out of the house to something special
to bond with you all we get to live
together in California we started to
complete our goals one by one last year
in 2023 we have gone on two tours across
the United States and we have climbed
our way to 5.7 million subscribers we
started a podcast and we have
accomplished personal goals that we have
never imagined like starting a clothing
brand and meeting people that we looked
up to as an inspiration when we started
creating content and now we enter 2024
and we start to think what's next next
we're so happy and so grateful for where
we are but we constantly think do we
keep doing car videos is the podcast
really interesting if we stop we could
have more time to visit our family and
friends back home do we want to go on
tours again and if we do what should we
do on stage you start to overthink and
doubt yourself a little bit and to be
honest we don't know what the future
holds for our content or our life all we
know is that no matter what we end up
doing this year we will be happy
creating memories that we will be able
to look back at one day and say we are
proud of ourselves for so let's not put
a label on it it's never worth stressing
about let's just keep living our lives
and keep creating memories for you and
for us our goal with this video is to
tell you guys how we are feeling and
tell you where our head is at we feel
like we want to change our content up a
little bit but we want to tell you guys
our ideas so you can tell us how you're
feeling because we are nothing on the
internet if not for the people that
watch and care about us and we are so
grateful for all of you basically as of
right now we feel like we post videos
that are quantity over quality and
posting three videos a week including
podcasts makes it hard for us to get the
videos as good as we want them to be
lately we have been feeling like we want
to cut out Wednesday videos but keep
Friday videos and podcasts if we cut out
Wednesday videos we will make the Friday
videos higher quality and a mix between
classic car videos Vlogs and challenges
and our content will be longer before we
Implement any change in our posting
schedule we will let you guys know but
we are very grateful for all of you and
super happy and excited for the future
what you guys been watching right now is
a behind the scenes look of a photo
shoot we did for a new profile photo
because it's been a while and we feel
like we're entering a new chapter in our
lives and here's our new intro if you
guys like it we'll keep it but if you
guys hate it we'll probably never do an
intro
[Music]
again with all that being said this
video is now over we hope that you
enjoyed it and let us know what your
thoughts are on our intro and everything
if you hate it totally fine we can get
rid of it it's up to you
guys
Trevor I hereby deem you the smelliest
dog
ever he really did pizza big pizza
guy
oh you're going crazy huh you're going
[Music]
crazy how do you feel after that get
away oh my
god oh dropped the chicken pistol
chicken but he got the pistol one
hey hey watch out watch out don't hurt
him to yes take it back
nowall right
fo what are you eating here Chris these
are more purple than they are blue what
are you eating here more purple what's
the name of those CH who doesn't count
drinking Pepsi too go [ __ ] yourself
what you eating there look at these guys
fueling up for today's shows off
blueberries I'm eating my enemy righto
yeah yeah okay whatever
wish well we didn't start the first one
CH you got to record my face first and
be like I'm about to light my leg ha on
fire like welcome to jackass type [ __ ]
then just
oh bur
go stop why are
you
I don't got it you got to go low you go
pirate
girl oh wow see you don't need a lot of
Swip pivel wow Swip pivel hip swivel
swi like I really don't get it they
should not be allowed to make a mistake
and then when you correct them on their
mistake on something you ordered tell
you you can't get it
fixed
what oh [ __ ] hold on hold on mermaid
Squad oh hold on hold on hold
on all right mermaid
Squad
oh my God you
[Music]
people that was this week's Wednesday
video we love you all so very much and
we will see you next Friday
whether it was sad memories happy
memories what the
[Music]
[ __ ]