I have to go pee pees we just started
right I know
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
guys
[Music]
it's been years what well it feels like
it's been yours we haven't filmed an
updated q a in so long and I think it's
just time we're gonna do a Q and an a
which stands for question and answer you
guys are gonna ask questions and we're
gonna answer them would you look at that
how long has it actually been I think 11
months but I could be wrong if you take
like if you look back
like if we all take a look back in
memory lane
I was just looking you see it yeah yeah
memory what was it
just the differences in Q and A's
incorrect okay well then I don't know
what you're doing I wore this hat in the
very first q a in car video ever
wow that's amazing that's like it's
giving special vibes you're going on
tour
whoa
I don't know when this video is gonna be
posted but if tour tickets are still
available come see us in any of our
location make sure you stay updated with
us on that tour follow our Instagrams
down below what does Dorothy say
home sweet home that's it okay where can
I answer questions for you guys easy and
plain and simple and yummy and good
so many she won disturbing adjectives
um if you guys want to possibly do it as
well exactly you guys want to come up
with questions
I think I should take a break from
pulling stuff up in car videos
opinions on camera every time what is
this dude like
he's doing his job I know but he's like
it looked at the back of our car like
extra dirty or something I'll leave him
alone
but I think why are you like defending
this dude with your life because you're
talking down on them well I speak behind
his back like I defend people behind
their back that's the type of guy I am
lifestyle getting out of control
lifestyle getting ludicrous I wish you
would shut the [ __ ] up because I can't
focus on anything I do when you just
talk talk and say anything do what do
you wish I what I wish I gave a [ __ ]
but dumb [ __ ] you say all the time
dumbass if you could have anything in
the world what would it be told you get
off your phone you shut the [ __ ] up you
baby Matt sorry I was talking down yeah
I don't care contraction who Malcolm
intro
don't do it again okay actually I'll
collect the phones
that was so funny all right the
questions I did I asked you as a
question neither you answered yeah you
said what's our favorite water wrong
I don't know no one ever said that ever
but we can answer that I thought you
said not Dasani
[ __ ] Springs the [ __ ] goats Poland
Springs is top tier I really also have a
little soft spot for smart water I think
it's underrated
core water was life-changing correct I
love core water core water is good
um but the question I actually asked if
you could have anything in the world
what would it be if I could eat anything
in the world anything in the world
anything at all Beyond Your Wildest
Dreams a nice big house
that's a great answer
Beach or a pool I'm a pool guy yeah you
are a poop guy what if there's like one
of those pools that are like near the
beach looking onto the beach I'd want
something like you can look at it you
could have anything
superpowers you're weird as [ __ ] Nick
um I gotta go with the um like I I don't
think of like when I think of oh you can
have anything in the world you don't
think fictional exactly well superpowers
are real so neither do I yeah um put
that away put that away probably a HD3
hard drive what the [ __ ] for what I
don't know I made it up like a member
like a flash drive
chuckled no it wasn't funny I was
working like can you [ __ ] stop you're
gonna hurt someone Chris you [ __ ]
stopped I did not say like that yeah you
did give me it
Chris also saying like at the house
that's like a it's like one home but
it's like a three-parter like we could
each have like a section like it's like
like three houses with a pool in the
middle like that connects with all three
of them and we each have a yard and
someone can have corn holes we just
explained neighbors but like you're all
friends no but like a try no it's not
neighbor
and there's doors from like each other
okay we're gonna keep looking Boom Bang
Pow pool in the middle ping pong table
here pool table there and then like
Bridges going to the other house bridges
are cool but we need like over there
over the pool
so it's like my bridge goes to your
bridge over our pool so I can walk to
yes and then if we I want to go on the
plug and just jump off the bridge
oh
um
I hate when you do that I hate when you
have stupid goggles on I'm thinking of
the most comedic person in the world
this isn't funny did I just say one
thing I did just realize he's wearing a
crossing guard vest and safety crossing
guard Fest he looks like he's just gonna
walk out of like crossing guards
this is a top tier construction worker
vest oh it looks like he's about to
leave sector eight with like goop on him
like that's what it like yeah like you
know when they leave the sector with
like alien and then it like splurges all
over him and then he has like the
goggles wait like the alien alien like
it looks like he's running sector eight
and then there's like a mishap code red
and then all the sirens go off and then
he like leaves in like slimy goo from
the aliens like that's what like when I
see goggles and like vests out of places
like splurge on you like no like like
like like
um what's his face I have a news
yeah he was
done everything
I remember when he yelled at one of the
Power Rangers and he said one of the
taglines in like the show when he yelled
at one of the Power Rangers was you
snooze you you snooze you lose correct
you're not paying attention and he was
giving all the kids his zoos we talking
because then they'd go back to their
parents and no the parents if the
parents touch the Ooze they became like
they became enslaved to the to the Ooze
yes and then he made two big bugs out of
ooze Curry took on the city let them
[ __ ] Power Ranger Megazords correct
while the Rangers
they're on another planet whatever and
that's exactly what I mean like when he
looks like sector eight like I looked
like I got oozed on first like the
beginning of the Ooze takeover so you
yes you you lose I lose I oozed I lose
all right next question is Dawn no I got
oozed on so I lose because I snoozed I
lose
because you used no I got next question
okay so basically if you have knighted
we just said Watch Might anymore from
Power Rangers the movie it's my favorite
movie and I have the Pink Ranger's
tattoo in my arm and I love that movie
so watch it it's so fun
any Cravings right now like what do you
think a soft pretzel with a oh
boy with cheese
cake yeah it can stay on the counter
Charo from Costco what's your least
favorite word and why tug
tug I'd say my least favorite word is
like
strawberry ooh unpopular they're so
popular
and just strawberry like I think of two
totally different things like I think of
a straw and then a berry every time
I've never thought of it like that until
you just pointed it every single time
someone's like oh strawberry I just
think of both items like a straw then a
berry well what's the berry and you
think of like a straw than blueberries
correct
very weird you're very weird sorry like
what if you did this song isn't that
weird like I think of something like
that and it's just like
like no one else is actually thinking
that like I thought that was a normal
thing to think of like a straw than a
berry no but no one you guys both just
said well like I mean I can see it but
like but it's not weird like if I said
like uh like uh like uh something you
could think of something that isn't even
how normal people like most other people
are thinking you're just thinking it
like that
okay like like when I said strawberry
when I say strawberries because I I see
a straw than a berry and you guys like
oh I've never seen like that I bet you
there's probably like a few people that
relate to my side that always think of
like a straw and a berry and there's
people that are like you guys I'm like I
never think I'm strong in a berry
wait if I said firecracker right now
like I I used to when I was little think
of like fire and then like a cracker
like a Saltine
no one else does that
what it's like like when it's like two
different things like a strawberry
firecracker growing up I used to think
of yeah I gotta understand that because
you're Gap pineapple
no because that's like two different
like I can understand
when you say Pine you don't buy a truck
yes when I was little I used to think of
like a fire and then like a truck like
that like I think their problem is
you're gapping the words out too much
when I was little now
like when you say fire truck and I think
of like a fire truck like a fire engine
but when I was little I used to so it
just took you a while to get used to
what about like apple sauce
oh cause what sauce Matt yeah but what's
berry
like if you're saying this is a
strawberry but if you do the same thing
to blueberries that you did the
strawberries strawberries and
firecrackers were both huge for me like
those were the two where I'd always
think of like the words separate I don't
know why what was even the question I
thought that was a word you don't like
oh that's not I feel like that had to be
like another thing for someone else
I'm feeling like what's a word I dislike
I don't know whatever
oh well one of my biggest fears That's
So Random and weird what is one of your
biggest fears That's So Random and weird
don't talk to me like that don't talk
like that man I'm thinking like like the
like foggy mirrors like mirrors that
they like make to look like vintagey or
old or like really antiqueish mirrors
that aren't like Crystal Clear they're
like I don't think they make them like
that like fox
or like some things that are like silver
so they're like Reflections but it's not
like a mirror like I get really freaked
out by things that aren't like partial
reflection like just foggy Reflections
like oh I hate it like a window
reflecting you
in the in the night sky kinda
a curb oh good one I hate that curb curb
curve sounds like a weird why why isn't
it like Uncle curbs here like that is
true I should have never thought that
was a crazy thought
listen poor design listen listening how
much wood could a woodchuck chuck if a
woodchuck could chuck wood I feel like a
woodchuck doesn't even chuck wood and I
for I feel like that's a good question
is it a woodchuck and Otter
oh can you sit down are you for real why
are you what's a woodchuck that's a real
animal I can't agree with you I'm
thinking it's just water are they are
they no because now it's in something
odd one I don't think can you sit the
[ __ ] down sorry I'm like the the seat
warmer's on and it feels really nice
you know like I got enough of it on my
back so now I'm just really feeling it
it's not really on my back it's on my
leg on my ass no like your lower back
like right here it feels good I don't
really feel warmth right there really
because I'm kind of like getting like I
don't know I don't know it feels okay
no not for me okay now what is oh mine's
on yeah yeah that's what I'm saying yeah
mine's mostly on my ass yeah see what
are we doing sorry what are we doing
what are we doing we're so we're so
weird
some like 10 wood shock at the facts
okay like don't you agree like let's not
like if I wanted to know about a rat I
wouldn't just compare it to like a
dandelion I'd just like look up a rat
like once again
what nick uh oh I want to know some
facts about a woodchuck let me just go
compare it to an otter like what let's
well that's reasonable because that's
what we're debating okay that's a
woodchuck yep okay now go back give me
ten like I want to know where region
like climate they like like to live in
what they eat like why is it called a
woodchuck like do they chuck wood or are
they like a wood Harvester like what's
their Source in this ecosystem like I
want to know like five solid facts about
a woodchuck what's this gonna do for you
are you gonna like I sleep better do
that well because I don't believe a
woodchuck actually Chuck's wood that's
why make a [ __ ] inside it's like even
the little Pun It's like what how much
wood would a woodchuck chuck
if a woodchuck could chuck wood so it
technically is saying he can't chug wood
because how much wood he chuck if you if
he would
I feel like
have wood
the woodchuck chuck if a wood chuck
could chuck wood this is such a giant
wooden chuck wood so it's implying right
now it does no wood chucking correct
Zero woodchucking from the woodchucker
but if it could how much wood would it
Chuck exactly I'm getting you but so
that's why I wanted to know the facts of
like so let's see why is it called the
woodchuck do wood Chucks what's the
question like why are you so flustered
by it do woodchucks chuck I hear you I
just think maybe do like a school
project on it and then come back yeah
let me just go back to you well a New
York state wildlife expert Richard New
York Richard Thomas decided to answer
that question some years back he found
that while a woodchuck doesn't actually
chuck wood they do in fact quite
a bit of dirt when digging out a burrow
so they burrow on a good day they can
Chuck around 35 cubic feet of dirt but
never would so who called it wood it's
dirt it's a dirt truck
how's it mean you rather Chuck dirt than
wood I feel like a dirt truck's just a
rude name
what Chuck sounds inviting and nice like
it's a woodchuck like we all know and
love the woods would you look a
woodchuck straight in his eyes and call
him a dirt truck absolutely have to note
how much he can chuck in a day
absolutely I feel like that's the
equivalent
apparently 35 cubic inches I feel like
that's really me that's like going out
to someone with like glasses me like
except for eyes
it's like saying what's up glasses like
it's like you're just implying what it
they actually do no it's a you're a dark
chocolate
imagine like what other animals what's
up YouTuber what like I heard that I
hate it yeah it's like a little awkward
but like you know but Chris my thing is
like if
hold on what other animals are like
around the woods I think we gotta
reverse because listen you're a YouTuber
right if someone was like Hey Matt
you're a tick talker you're gonna be
like no I'm a YouTuber so now you're
going to the woodchuck and you're like
oh you're a woodchucker
correct so we just actually broke it
down and it wants to be the dirt chucker
that's what he really does and we went
we just went and gave him the name of a
woodchucker
that's upsetting exactly so I really
just really put on for the woodchucks
because now they're like the dirt Chucks
correct but also I feel like if you if
we didn't clarify it like that what I
was saying was like what other animals
live near like a woodchuck and they
would probably go outside and be like
what's up dirt shock like oh yeah like a
squirrel like what are you doing over
there chucking dirt dirt Chuck like
oh I feel so bad I just picture like a
woodchuck I think squirrels are just so
squirrely though you'd be a wood chuck
if you're an animal a dirt truck a dirt
truck these squirrels are just so
squirrely
squirrel makes so much sense to be
called a squirrel same with the stingray
and I look at the stigma I'm like yes
you are
next question
is perfect yeah what else what it
doesn't matter yeah
rhinoceros is perfect oh agreed perfect
zebra is perfect maybe the [ __ ] on um an
ostrich is amazing really they name that
thing really really good really good a
wild dog
[Music]
whale could have been way better I feel
like it needs something like hippo or
Rhino like it needs like a snake name
whale whale it's like well um it needs a
like a like the right holy Mammoth was
amazing yeah
hippopotamus the whale needed like a
whale megatronum
no whale needed like a well tundrum yeah
well Tundra would have been awesome well
look at how big the real Tundra will
abilium oh great whale a billion well
Thomas
whalarillo would have been amazing no
next question well for we're doing too
much right yeah we are don't ask me why
I'm gay
whatever they learn why Nick
I don't want to say it okay next
question what's an absolute deal breaker
for you
like friendship or relationship was just
like a deal breaker for the person like
a liar oh I'd rather be hurt by the
truth than lie I feel like inconsistent
not inconsistent like inconsistent like
you make a plan and they're just like oh
I can't go okay but like every time
if you could have been there for any
moment in history which one would you
want to be the signing of the
Declaration of Independence terrible
answer I want to be with the people who
first eat a [ __ ] Apple off a tree so
oh my God oh my God like oh my God look
at that [ __ ] glorious red ball
hanging from that stem let's go indulge
and then they all walked over an AP
Apple I don't know
discovered fire
whoa
I I just wanted I don't want to be there
for anything other than that like I want
to go back in time two seconds pen on
paper first first car because like 50
people signed the Declaration of
Independence never mind I take it back I
feel like it'd be boring first cell
phone call
um oh my God wait I'm trying to think I
want to go back to stranger things times
that's what I want to do you mean the
80s I'm surprised because you didn't say
Piedmont is strange
oh my God Peak fortnite all of this oh
my god
dude go back to Pink fortnite you could
say anything no if I had to go back in
time and then stay there like I'm
picking Peak fortnite 110 percent
I used to wake up at seven a.m play
fortnite for an hour and then go to
school like I used to wake up an hour
early for school to get in the good
fortnite win I was filthy Fortnight oh
my god dude I'd so go back
oh my god when I would like stay awake
for the item shop or if I was like out
of the house I'd like go on YouTube
oh I love Prime fortnite
oh my God I need the Tums
oh
[Applause]
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things