shout out to my man are these called God
God sees or bullseyes whoa my God he's
gonna [ __ ] called gun bullsies
that sounds like a circus clown
s
he becomes the best circus tear ever
and then what you're saying how you miss
me
[Music]
the circus is such a weird the great
clown Bambino I kind of really wish
they'd like bring back like the circus
like nothing's better than good old
cotton candy scary clown man at the
circus and like they used to like just
go to Downtown LA it's the same thing
they used to use all the animals like it
was really scary back then oh my God
that's like kind of like what I just
said was kind of a joke was I was like
50 true no I know which is kind of
terrifying but Chris the type of guy
that they do the tightrope and hold the
beam no I could be like the circus
announcer okay Christopher cerniolo's
take
I was gonna say Something's Gonna sound
like sexual innuendo so I'm stopping
myself say it no because it was just
like say it no no say it no no that
would be the goofy dude that like does a
trick in lands or something and then
like that's like
like that like a loud bang yeah and like
makes everyone I'm the person in the
crowd to just throwing popcorn like
they're like wow Nick would be a popcorn
seller no that could be the game guy
feeding the elephant peanuts have you
seen that guy oh my God this is a bio
clip on Tick Tock this guy goes it's
like dead silent like an arena and he
goes
mommy screams
dogs
good job dogs get your hot dogs here
that's how he does it that was insane I
think that was the loudest you've ever
screamed
guys
thank you I wore my cut off again today
oh you're strong okay anyways I have a
thought that I've been dying to say it
loud
want to make good let's trip Mercy yo if
I wasn't in the circus tea if
if I wasn't who I was Ferris wheel or
something if I wasn't who I was
I'd think Febreze is a magical word
I was taking a [ __ ] today and I looked
up and I saw Febreze and I'm like if I
was not who I was like if I was a little
kid like you know you can make little
kids believe anything yeah if I watched
Harry Potter and someone was like oh I
can't wait for the Febreze like I have
no prior knowledge of Febreze I'm like
oh they're gonna [ __ ]
Febreze that [ __ ]
up and like it's such a perfect corner
for like you're gonna freeze it up
okay it doesn't sound like a [ __ ] if
I had a magic one away Febreze what do
you think is gonna happen the air is
gonna smell better that motherfucker's
gonna stop in his tracks I think it's
closer to freeze and that's why you
think that fabri oh that's true yeah
would Febreze be an action or a person
definitely in action correct well I feel
like there could be the great Febreze I
completely disagree no I feel like there
could be a person named Febreze like The
Fez like the first name and the breeze
like the last name don't say that like
it's a febreze why just embarrassing the
great Febreze yeah oh my God that is a
great I've been dying to tell you guys
this I saw a video on my for you page
the other day and this woman was at an
airport like freaking the [ __ ] out and
she spat on a police officer and I
genuinely I saw that and wonder what my
one takeaway was I'd kill her no what I
think it's someone's spat if someone's
spit no I was about to say shut up no
I literally thought my first thought was
if I ever got spat on
I'd end up in jail I'd be imprisoned in
30 seconds
I'd handcuffed myself in a walk to the
prison I agree because oh my God I would
spit back at them and then beat the [ __ ]
out of them oh my God it's like
genuinely it makes my toes itch and my
[ __ ] Nose getting spit on like is the
most disrespectful thing oh right here I
think that if I got
someone out faster than [ __ ] Mike
Tyson in the [ __ ] 90s I'd knock
someone and fight in the knife and I
have no idea to knock someone out faster
than the Bubonic plague bro I oh my God
it it would be like that person's
biggest fear would then be what they had
just done to me give me a great garbanzo
please okay let's talk about it because
it's a thing yeah
people throwing [ __ ] on people at people
on a stage ah ridiculous
ridiculous I'm just the dumbest [ __ ]
it happened to Bebe rexha and then it
happened to like four more people back
to back to back I think most people
other than the
the guy who through something at beer
actually literally said he thought it
would be funny but most of the time
people throw [ __ ] with like a a good
intent I disagree no no because they
want like they wanted to like oh like a
stuffed animal or flowers or something
you know what I mean if you're throwing
something with weight to it no if you're
Hocking something that doesn't belong on
a stage at someone on a stage you need
to be imprisoned why don't I hate what
when people oh actually I just remember
what I was gonna say if you had to pick
one option of item like garbanzo you
could only have anything that could fit
in your hand what item would you pick to
throw in the crowd if you had to hurt
people I'm not saying like obviously we
don't promote violence so we don't want
to do that in this hypothetical question
if there was a large crowd of people and
you had to injure as many as you can
what okay is the comment and say
something there was a herd of zombies no
no heard of people like an actual herd
of just okay fine everyone
today thank you for accommodating well
no I'm gonna switch it up a group of
Rude mean people group of people that
are just bad boys
a group of bad people all right and
you'd put them in a [ __ ] just a large
crowd and you can throw only one handful
of things what would you throw because I
have two options in my handful of things
is that like it you have to pick
something what's your ideal weapon of
eight pound bowling ball that's all bad
bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad pig
really bad pick you're hitting one
person doing a lot of damage and it's
bad you wanna it's like the whole point
is injure as many as you can Nails
that's a better option that's a better
option what about you I was gonna say
Nails I was gonna say as many rolls of
quarters that could fail oh my God
yeah a sack of coins no I think even
though
they all run they'd be stepping or golf
balls okay what would I hate more than
anything like probably top
10 biggest pet peeves oh that's a lie
it's not top 10 at all but really
bothers me go ahead
when people
when people go into other people's space
and create a mess and don't clean up
after themselves kind of like how you
come in the car and leave your company I
was about to say the car's the worst if
you're if you're no I'm not if you're a
mess leaver in the car
no this isn't even my goal I know way
too many people that's coming this isn't
even my car this is not my fault okay
that's not my thought my thought is like
oh sleepover at Jimmy Joe's house
everyone come over and like you know
like be a hooligan and make a mess of
Jimmy John's house like and then now
Jimmy John's like oh let's watch a movie
and everyone gets in Jimmy Joe's bed
like drink a soda you have ice cream you
eat your things you know and then when
you're like oh my mom's here and you
leave your bowl your dirty spoon yeah
it's ridiculous
unpopped kernels littering the floor
your rappers for the candies you
individually ate like nothing's worse
than like the muffins like Starburst and
like they they unwrap each one and leave
a [ __ ] confetti show of Starburst
rappers everywhere like you are the
worst person ever pick up after yourself
and then leave we learned this in
kindergarten Barney said clean up clean
up everybody everywhere that was Barney
no
let's talk about love oh cup noodles
unbelievable I don't think I've ever had
cup noodles in my life
do you know one time funny stuff I
showed you that I didn't have the other
day and you yelled at me
because you probably didn't no I said I
don't think I've ever had that and you
were like
shut up and then I was like whoa and
then you got Chris and made the whole
deal
I can't remember pop noodles are
unbelievable I've never had cups I had a
[ __ ] thought and I can't remember it
fun time story one time in high school
fun time story one time in high school I
went and got a cup of noodles and the
convenience store let me fill it up and
it was the most ridiculous hot water
I've ever [ __ ] held in my life and I
filled it too high to like the brim so
when I was walking into school and I was
like kind of like you know kind of like
you spill a little and it goes down the
side and it like dripped on my thumb and
my fingers and it literally burned it so
bad that I like threw the cup noodles in
the street
set a firework off in her car on this
outside of our school shout out hyper
Freeze from Cumberlands
from Cumberland Farms I'm like is this
the [ __ ] other dimensions version of
Frozone
huh Febreze no okay I'm going to my pet
peeve yeah go ahead
I don't know I don't have many pet
peeves oh my no I'm just thinking I was
like wait I I can't I'm really over the
corny [ __ ] I hate how many different
versions of like oranges there are in
apples
ooh grapefruit looks so similar it's not
even in the family well they all taste
different
it's all Malarkey to me
you know if if someone works I like the
usage of that if someone were to say
like oh they're so close just group them
together like that's us like you just
kind of disrespect it okay what's the
difference between a clementine and a
mandarin
[ __ ] figure out what's interesting
you and Matt I could ask the same
[ __ ] what's in Mandarin though
isn't that a language Chinese yeah so
what I'm baking I'm thinking it's like
what I said Chinese what's the fruit
Mandarin it's doubles bro it's a bat in
the bat no I just thought I was wrong
sometimes I can't believe my [ __ ]
thought just
squeeze like what's what would be your
ideal fruit or vegetable to squeeze
I don't think of this ever like if I had
a grapefruit I just like use both hands
and just like pounded down the
grapefruit to its pulp that'd be a fun
one to squeeze
oh my God stop Chris
what would be your ideal fruit to
squeeze I don't know nothing like a
handful of [ __ ] blueberries I don't
know it's a good one do you remember the
book about blueberries when we were
little and like the little bear went to
go eat the blueberries yes
correct didn't he fill it with
blueberries no
all right champion because the duck
walked up to the lemonade what the [ __ ]
am I singing You're the champion
I thought I was wearing a champion shirt
oh
where's this person oh neck sauce is
crazy get the [ __ ] out of here when I'm
really tired of
real added jackets with the Plaid on the
inside and not the outside no
hate them I'm tired of them I don't
actually have any feelings toward that I
think that's kind of fun I don't know
it's like why put this one pattern on
the inside in the outside
yeah it's the last one like why would
you put the most super fun pattern on
the inside of something because that's
what it's all about unless it's on the
edges I think it's more sentimental and
it really preaches about like getting to
know somebody beyond the outside okay
once they take the jacket off
it's not about the cool pattern that's
on the inside it's about how they
portray the outside wait no I just said
that wrong dude what's the worst oh
what what would be your go-to
celebration if you won something nice
what you know
no but you're you saying that remind me
I didn't eat today
you like pizza pizza okay I'm good what
would Nick what would your celebration
be I don't celebrate
oh can I tell you what I hate I hate
when I say I hate something in a car
video
and then like I do it and people are
like
oh look at he's like betraying his word
or something yeah because I can say I
hate taking a [ __ ] every single day I
still got it yeah no but like I said
there was a clip it was like I said I
hated Disneyland's not finished I said I
hated Disneyland then I went and I got
fired but it's like in that moment of
time
do you know how many times they caught
me about that Stripes like [ __ ] well
no it all comes down to like how shut up
it all comes down to how how it's like
happening like what I'm saying oh I hate
Disneyland I'm imagining going with Matt
and Chris and like four other people and
like having this big entourage crowd
walking through Disneyland and then it
being a million [ __ ] degrees and hour
long waits in every single ride and then
every single [ __ ] snack your picture
in the worst of everything yes like
that's what I hate would you rather wait
at the snack sand or for the ride well
it's like I'm speaking shut up so that
is when it puts into perspective next
and that's when it puts in perspective
for me like oh I'll say hey Disneyland
and then down the line if I have a good
day at Disneyland it's like who cares
what I said a year ago
who I am in a parking the internet will
haunt forever oh like a ghost yeah the
internet is permanent say I hate ripe
apples from a great apple tree
one day if we went apple picking spare
me that was a little bone
and what did it mean it's called apple
tree spare me by Chris Cornell I like it
thank you I just said that apple tree
spare me yeah
if I said I hate a good strong apple
tree
then one year went apple picking you
should give you should give it I mean
once you make the poem like you should
print it out and give them out for free
I love that idea and use paper from a
big old tree I don't know what I like
that building is all blue but there's a
red door I hate when poems repeat
something and you're supposed to say it
a little different
so give me anything in the world cone
traffic cone traffic cone traffic cone
cone traffic cone
what are you guys you're just like you
don't have to talk about like poems
repeat something like okay we've heard
it
we can't we can't back down
we can't can't back down
can I take really hot take extremely hot
take actually cool ranch is the best
Dorito no
that's true but keep on well this isn't
the hot then yeah just shut up I'm
saying this is a true fact I thought you
were asking us
[Music]
that makes no sense
extremely hot take you ready
some soundtracks
spicy
some soundtrack albums and like some
soundtrack albums and albums for like
Disney movies and [ __ ] are harder than
some projects like people
I disagree completely
there's not one movie soundtrack I could
ever hit Shuffle play on ever
in the world of the world Lemonade Mouth
that's true
I wasn't thinking of it like that yeah
cause that's a show where there's songs
Incorporated I was thinking for like
normally I couldn't turn your head
that's why I had to write this instead
let's be friends start out slow get to
know you be on your glow
would you rather my name
is
let me tell you guys a crazy fact
the other day we were at Cumberland
Farms how many days ago was that when we
were at the one in
uh three days ago Chris yeah how many
days ago was that I don't [ __ ] know I
peed in a cup and that cup is still in
the car you're disgusting is that not
crazy I did empty it out but there it's
here
is that not disgusting don't say that
why didn't I [ __ ] throw that out why
is it just told the internet what could
I thought it'd be funny it's funny
I feel like more bushes that are local
like when you walk around you should
have just berries on them like have fun
with like your walk be then I feel like
that would lead to so many problems
little kids with dirt on their face no
kids with allergies eating berries no no
no the tree right outside your house is
an apple tree you just walk outside oh
here's my breakfast I feel like people
who do hold on I do have to say this
though I feel like people who do have
like plants out there you're still
supposed to I feel like people who do
have plants outside their homes like
with berries in it and such like they
treat it better than they do their
firstborn child yeah it could be talking
to a stranger on the side of their road
but but the stranger could come over and
grab a raspberry and then they hang up
like a whole fence like a sign that's
like these don't touch my berries these
berries are for everyone I grew these
they take eight months oh God okay
might as well call you jam
you're so like I just hate it here's my
thing right oh you're supposed to clean
fruit and all this Jazz right
natural animals eat it right off the
floor animals yeah but animals also eat
like raw meat like a bear rips
you're talking about the bear and he
takes the salmon out of the river you
know I'm gonna have like a [ __ ] mark
on my arm I see I saw it he takes the
salmon out of the river
he skins it and it's still moving and
the fish is like
oh I think it's funny as [ __ ] dude I
can't lie
I love bears yes
we imagine how much more
imagine how much better life would be if
you could just go on a stroll and eat
some berries
just bring them buy some no I'm talking
about just like more than that like but
you're not supposed to hog them all
because you gotta like leave something
yeah you can't be a bush hogger you have
to like go and hop Bush to Bush and take
like a little Berry as you go
one Berry per Bush what about
honeysuckles
I think those are a goddamn scam I think
you're a scam
Nick you look like the type of guy to
like thaw out food what's your favorite
fruit what's your favorite fruit like um
second of all that's literally what
ninety percent
sawing's ridiculous I just put in the
oven to warm up imagine thawing
something out you just a good meal get
it nice and hot if you don't let Matthew
Serenity a little talk right now I'm
gonna literally cut your goodness no
it's fine I'm good I'm really I don't
know what I'm tired of what the [ __ ]
corny [ __ ]
if you were if your life was a big
hockey game you left your shin pads at
the house
could you really perform your best
ability
no dude I can't deal with you it's like
who's gonna go to a basketball court and
not bring the air pump I mean the
basketball
like dude okay
I feel like happy Friday everyone that
has been this week's video I love you
all so dearly and we will see you soon
subscribe make sure that you look down
there and you smash that darn
subscribe button and if you don't
if you don't I'm throwing Nick in a
river with 85 alligators and he's gotta
jump out of him and then tackle all the
damn Gators down to the ground and then
as he's fighting the Gators I'm gonna
throw a crocodile on his head and then
he's gonna be fighting all these gators
one crocodile and one Jillian Gators and
then he's got to beat all the Gators in
the gator fight showdown of the lifetime
event he's got to actually share a
thought
shut up shut up I genuinely think that
like what are those scenarios that
happen in movies that like you think oh
I could easily handle that and I think
an alligator trying to bite me I'd kick
that [ __ ] in the snout it'd be done
for kick him in the face like like I
think