and goodness knows the wicked lives are
lonely wrap all of this up like what is
happening snow angel sow Angels on the
kitchen table and goodness knows the
wicked lives are
lonely apple
pie chocolate chip cookies what would do
you think would happen if we just
started like licking each other's face
can
you insane ni you ready put the tee I
feel like I I feel like I should be the
Zillow controller I feel like you should
literally lick my nuts and I will you're
the [ __ ] weirdest kid ever yeah so
don't say some weird [ __ ] to me if you
ain't ready for if you praying for the
rain got to be ready for the
mud what does that even mean anyway we
are going on Zillow today this was
Chris's
Idea new video idea
no more part twos no more part three
some real authentic stulo triplet
history going down today we're going to
go on Zillow whatever you want to go
look up and like what your Vibe is we're
going to rate houses and we're going to
rate them yeah and we're going to say
yes or no would you live in
it hotel for a dollar or hotel for a
million dollars hotel for a
dollar okay no one has ever posted that
video no one this is the United States
of America Oh Canada wa wow what a gas
gas station the only thing you can buy
in Quebec is gas be crazy Greenland do
you know that Greenland's actually ice
yes Chris and then Iceland's actually
cuz the Vikings played a trick I want to
go to Antarctica that's like one of my
favorite fun facts ever I'm so happy for
you the Vikings I think it was I don't
know so don't don't Antarctica they said
this is Greenland and this is Iceland
but it was actually different thank you
yes so then they tricked people to go
into Greenland think it was going to be
this amazing green land but it was
actually icy land okay all right we're
going to Florida really that's your Vibe
no not really but what's your Vibe Miami
make the budget 10 m Miami is not your
Vibe make the budget for saleon
minimum $1 million 10 mil Jesus maximum
any price wa big spender okay okay yeah
I don't want that lame [ __ ] 19 where is
that Tampa that's just acre boring is it
no I don't think it is is this Tampa
yeah it is
okay whoa okay six bedrooms for for $19
million
way hey Jennifer what look at the beach
I would what is this green ball on
theable look at how aggressive the Jets
look in that hot tub I want to like go
right up against them sit on
it you're weird like Arc a little and
it's the Jets are under
you I used I used to do that [ __ ] all
the time Arc a little yeah I like hold
no and I was like a kid like it feel
nice okay no do you ever like sit in a
hot tub and then the Jets are so
aggressive you just take your pants off
and no one those no I haven't done that
why are these trees so weak they have to
be held up with posts yeah that tree
looks like it's [ __ ] breaking yeah
that tree is not worth $19 millionth
with toothpick with a pube on it
if I own this house I'd stand right
there naked every night and just look at
my
view that's good
next okay okay this isn't screaming 19
M I'd love to hold someone hostage in
this room I know people that need to
live there is this just the garage yeah
M goes I know people who need to live
there I hate how white it is like I just
imagine when I see a house that's go to
the kitchen when I see a house that's
this white I just imagine being like
covered in Bloods yeah no literally genu
imagine cutting your finger like in you
just said literally covered in blood
okay it next what is this what is up
with the green balls of grass slame
chair hate those chairs hate those
chairs ha looks like individual boots
yeah look like they just sliced a
couch one of those deli meat slicers
anding Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck back
all right can we get into what's worth
what's $19 million worth here ceiling
pan whoa that's a good bathtub D dude
two showers intense that's like really
me and you could shower there I would
shower with yall every night if we had
one of us could take a bath yes wait
that' actually be perfect yeah that
bathroom's insane oh my God go back
Matt's dream yeah obviously my dream's
the [ __ ] no look look double
washer amazing
you could do laundry twice wait that's
actually a good investment we should
make in our next house a second one of
you guys also no move quicker no I'll do
it I seriously will help they chill the
[ __ ] out no one French you're going to
eat soon see now this is what I'm
expecting when I when I see oh Key West
that's nice oh Key West that's nice
that's nice see that's more W this is
way better than the $19 million house
wow look at that be
like the beach VI yeah I don't love it I
love wooden ceiling like no I would have
some I this is like screaming like a
childhood memory place oh I love though
I love how homey this home is this a
homey yeah it's like super nice oh I
love that little room you'd have to drag
me out of there by my balls hate this
this is ugly really ugly this is ugly
they searched up wall artart for Florida
Key West and printed this ho out and it
up like literally
that I love yes wait what is that is
that a microwave that's in the bathroom
is that a microwave it's like a it's
like a lotion cooler a no I swear to God
there's like things in the bathroom
you're supposed to keep cool and like
it's like a it's like a it's like a it's
like a moisturizer bathroom cooler
fridge like you're supposed to keep your
your like say that again it's like say
that again without changing a word I
can't right yeah okay that's a nice pool
Mr banana lives here
pey from fortnite lit this is where he
lands this is where he rests his head at
night after a long day of killing Jonesy
wow I love a nice Vibe I love this whoa
that's a nice Vibe I do love this I do
love this I do love this outdoor movie
projector but where where where can you
watch the movie sit on the grass you
have to stand you have to get get a
blink there's not enough room there I
love a buoy lava buoy boo lava buoy boah
oh my God love this vck Matt Chris what
is this is this the runway that's where
you walk in that's where you walk that's
where a hot new bombshell enters right
there that's where you serve everything
boots down okay let's raid this lady's
fit literally such a beach mom look this
like this is like a Mary L closet oh no
not even going to hold you I like that
bag mom's got a jacket like that she's
got hats like that and then you go
keywords what do you want dle Castle wo
wo wo wo is not a castle yeah it
is oh my God yeah that is insane look at
that that's like pavement waa oh my God
we got to play a massive game of Clue
here yeah this would be nice the second
house is the cheapest and the best so
far I feel like I've seen like 40 rich
people go IG live in this exact pool
wait this house is ugly to me oh my God
something that's like not even
comfortable in my opinion no I want to
be like snuggled up with my friends no
fact want nice couches correct don't
give me this lame how am I going to sit
with the [ __ ] in there literally next
next house ugly [ __ ] no no no I got to I
got to get one without that filter let's
go to like uh I want to go to like see
what like a multi-million dollar house
in like Maine is oh don't cuz this is
like just crushing my hopes and dreams
okay I'm doing it $16.3 million oh main
is like one of the best places on Earth
oh my God man 10 bedrooms this is what
I'm talking about this is actually like
our dream house could get away with
murder oh my God this is like the most
beautiful house I've ever seen in my
life
dude oh oh
wow I love it you could shoot someone
tried to escape you could shoot him
right dead right there yeah it's like a
horror movie this where they limp away
and they go into the woods and they see
like a dead deer and then like the
killer no the killer the Killers back
here and then the lights go on and then
then you see him creep down the street
oh my God oh my God love the flower pots
in the I was about to say I love a
Flower Basket I love a Flower Basket I
also love I love this love that unique
garess love it unique garess All the Way
Love This Love This oh oh imagine
getting there right there's no sitting
on the bench and then you can take your
shoes off outside before you even enter
to the home and this is nice and
clean I love wood this is giving House
of Anubis realness right here like I
know that every night they go there and
they drop a pin and see if they can hear
it uhuh you know they actually do that
in House of Anubis no way serious to God
yeah obviously I've seen the show okay I
always feel like when I open a really
old dresser like this like there's going
to be fingers in it is that is that
fingers yes every single time like we'
be at like Grammy's house or like like
somewhere with old furnit
I feel like I'm going to open a drawer
and see like fingers like real human
fingers that's a crazy taste all you
were getting was Pirates Cove coins I I
don't know what it is
oh I can't I feel like I can I'm getting
allergies can smell that couch literally
they don't have to do this outdoor
furniture can say the same that's fire I
love a wicker chair me too love it look
the [ __ ] is that the capital Bell yeah
they ring that the Liberty Bell it's
time for dinner
look at the drapery in there this is a
nursing home this has got to be a
nursing home too many chairs am I [ __ ]
up for saying that this is a nursing
home to many chairs 100% this is too
many chairs chairs too many chairs who's
that that's the
king n look at all way too many chairs I
love that I'm going to get a vintage
cabinet dresser thing like this love
that Vibe not cabinet
dresser is that fire real is that the
Titanic no yeah that this is where they
sailed it from the back of this
house killer
hallway no the real killer whoever wears
that hat oh the heart engravement on the
chair really nice that's amazing I just
want to knock all those plates off with
one
finger love this room love this little I
love this I love the wooden ceiling they
got the bug Nets this got to be a nurs
oh go back go back look at that
wallpaper e that's ugly as [ __ ] this
one's way better this one's way better
nah yeah pinstripe wall it's like
[ __ ] dizzy there it makes the room
look taller though it's a
trick and if you want the room to look
shorter you paint horizontal lines wow
same with your body if you wear pen
Stripes you look taller if you wear
horiz Stripes you look F I just feel
like so dizzy looking at the AC cuz it's
the stripes going this way and
everything else is going that way I feel
like it's like one of those optical
illusion tricks look at your nose is
going to be all blurry know I'm talking
up wine cellar that's where you're
killing that is literally hedwig's layer
like do you the the movie Split love
that movie that's where the guy sits
like seriously this is his like thing oh
hello get active ain't nobody working
out in this house yeah Cardiac Arrest
they they all got feeble femur oh a
painter of course oh oh love that I love
this oh my God that's like how that's
where I would walk into heaven oh
beautiful Botanical
Garden yes Chris I would sit there all
the time love this bridge I feel like I
need a baset and to skip immediately
over that bridge okay out of 10 what's I
give it I give it a seven five seven as
well it needs so much work yeah no
actually I give that [ __ ] like a four
what am I talking about no The Vibes are
high The Vibes are so high i' love toing
like that girls room girl I I like the
house empty it take everything out
Furniture restart no that big desk
cabinet thing you love yeah take it out
restart so some old [ __ ] just freaks me
out to wreck love I love seeing like an
old thing that I feel like has like bad
juju attached to it like a haunted piece
of furniture is like my favorite thing
ever little weird confession there I do
I love it 93 Matt Matt the other house
in Maine is the vibe really dead ass ooh
hello is this wait it's got like a ice
cream com oh that's beautiful that's
actually amazing yeah this is really
nice no this house has more Integrity to
it wa it does I really like the opening
of this window these chairs are nice
they're hideous I feel nicer than the
[ __ ] saw half
couch kitchen can have some work I love
it look at the cute little bunny with
the
ears that thing is dead they got to like
up this furniture dude I love this Vibe
though I love this Vibe Ao no no no I
like that go back
love this bathroom what Chris this
bathroom creeps me out kind love it's
giving The Shining I love it it's creeps
me out house has got to be that's creepy
that's the timeout
Zone that's where you go and look at
someone across imagine oh it's it's a
game and you're supposed to sit on
either side when you're waiting oh
that's what it is I thought it was a
staring contest bench oh I love this
would you do any gardening what would
you grow I would if you had a garden if
I had time if I had time that grows
marold it's my favorite flower pumpkins
carrots I love carrots if I had time
outside of the um what's it
called okay let's look in Texas I feel
like Texas got big arms absolutely 19
million where I said that like I just
want looks like four bedrooms for $19
million got to be a crazy house I like
oh my God I like Lake ooh this is the
best one we saw so far this is gorgeous
this is the best one we saw so
far wow this is a really nice house I
just want to lay on the floor of this
room and smell it that floor does look
nice oh my gosh ooh no that's creeper
Vibes that gives me like I'm good
creep no oh my God I hate when I see a
bed and I'm just like I know I someone
died that what that I love this what is
that it's wood wood it's a really nice
deck that's a really cool deck not even
remotely close to being worth what they
have $19 million ain't no [ __ ] way I
need to find a castle I don't give a
[ __ ] with no dude stop no dude stop do a
cabin instead Castle I want a royal
[ __ ] Castle is what I want $ 108
million go down go down Nick go down
Nick 8 m what I knew we'd find the good
stuff what look at that average Street
like right above it San Diego what the
actual Frid heck
108 N dud look at that is this is insane
this is sick you could play a I could
live right here forever pitch a tent
literally oh dude look at the
handcrafted ceiling what decisions do
you think get made in this you can't
play it you I hate a house like this cuz
you can't even play a game imagine
breaking out a a board game in this room
it's like it would look like it
literally only play traitors pulling out
a board game in that room would be like
if I just went back to the '90s in like
a like a a modern day fit like it would
just you know what I mean Back to the
Future like Connect 4 can't be played on
that table a little bar like what what
games do they play in this what what is
that marble toss or something like yeah
they play Yi that's a door in the cave
go they play Shoot the person across
from they Russian Roulette that's the
only literally Russian roul that's a
door in the cave
whoa where does the cave leave you could
I would take IG picks right we should
rate the houses bed on how wait it
doesn't show you where this leads to oh
my God it's the probably like oh is it
this room no way
that's guys we should do like we should
rent a mega mansion for one night for a
YouTube video like living in this Mega
Mansion dude this has my balls on the
floor right now this is insane dud not
your jaw balls your balls that are
falling yeah wow what wow literally
Equinox in the house
literally stop making fun of my laugh I
hate when you make no heart no brain I
when you make really gross oh my God
that's like a rotted green wood I know
they cook some good food in there though
like that looks like a Chef's Kitchen
some of these are ugly oh I like that
that's really nice cute that's really
nice I feel like this is like its own
City like this house should have is own
ZIP journals journals at home dude I
feel like I'd have a contrail walking
through this place like I feel like I'd
like have like flowers contrail yes you
know in fortnite when you Glide down you
have a contrail that's the craziest one
out of 10 what would you rate it that's
like kind of liveability like eight
livability that's a good ranking thank
you good way to rank houses
livability see I'd rather live in this
yeah get this [ __ ] off get this [ __ ] off
get this [ __ ] off is that a giant Pine
oh my God it looks like squilliam's
house like what the [ __ ] zebra that
better be a fake zebra is that a peacock
oh this [ __ ] a freak yeah this
is crazy c a freak call the police freak
alert let freak alert freak alert send
them here freak alert freak
alert [ __ ] high radar freak we need
some we need some backup we have a level
1,000 freak in the building are we allow
we're freak alert dude what is up with
this is like the nursery too they're
getting try start no this is freak alert
they're getting the baby straight into
the animal habits freak
alert this wow is amazing wow that
literally looks like a gingerbread this
doesn't even really doesn't even look
real
wow I want this one that makes that
house look sad though cuz how bright
this one is yeah but just turn some
lights on in
here I got to lay on that table naked
fish I want to fish I want to fish I
just want to like I do anything to live
here I love it I love that I love the
boat lights I do love this I love that I
love everything about this I love I want
a deer head in our next house is that
okay that's a freaky thing no it's not I
wouldn't want to kill the deer I just
want to get a pre-owned one look at this
elevator what is up with the elevators
with the random doors cuz I feel
satisfied me too are we making any
purchases or what all right guys thank
you for for ranking house that are very
unrealistic for us to own and that was
so much fun I love looking at these like
really it's just like so cool to look at
houses like this yeah thank you guys so
much for watching if you guys want to
see us do this again I mean Zillow is an
never ending platform with Millions
plethora of home literally so if you
want if you found any interest in us
doing this and want us to do again hello
if you want to hear Chris's idea we tell
you oh I know it I know it it would be
like if an intruder tries to get in and
they get eaten by the crocodile it would
be like see you later alligator
that's it that's it
[Music]