But what are we doing? What is up
everybody? Welcome back to the Stern
Triplets YouTube channel. It's been so
long since we filmed a video because we
were just on tour and all that other
jazz. But today we're back and we're
making the tier list on different
categories. Let's [ __ ] go.
We are going to be ranking a bunch of
different things in a bunch of different
categories on our custom tier list,
including the top of the tier list being
incredible, major, mid, trash, and then
the bottom tier is mega. What would you
rank? Have you ever been to your brother
surprising you with a dozen crispy cream
donuts a minute away from the house? No.
Stop. Where would you rank that? Are you
that ass? Where would you rank that one?
Incredible on our list. Incredible.
Honestly, I'm putting it in mid only
because Incredible.
What the [ __ ] dude? Cheers.
All right, guys. We're about to rank
stuff.
Don't All right, guys. We're about to go
rank the category. We'll see you at the
tier wall.
All right. Number one, Chester.
Chester. Whenever something like that
happens and it actually like blows up,
it blows my mind because it's like that
was so like there was we saw that frame
in our YouTube video and didn't think
anything of it. It's definitely above
mid. It's like here. It was like a major
like it's not like pivotal. Like it's
not cool. It's not impressive. I think
it's like not major. I think it's mid.
It's It is mid. Matt to the Aoogie
audios on Tik Tok. Holy [ __ ] Where's
the tape? No.
Chill. We have to I think this is
incredible. I think it was an incredible
pivotable move. I think that everything
changed. The earth shook. What? Mega
mega mid trash. Trash. God. I'm like
starting to feel physical pain. I'm so
scared. Is it the same vibe? When we
were Twitch streaming and they thought I
was jerking off, but I was just warming
up my hands.
Chad, I'm cold. That was an incredible
moment. kind of agree. Now it's just
like it was incredibly
incredibly ridiculous. That's a mega
mid. Get your mind out of the gutter.
Blonde Nick. That's not really for me to
decide. Okay, I have a couple thoughts
here. Let's hear it. I think the initial
pivot was fun. Like going from brown
hair to blonde hair, but I think that
there's a photo of me at La's birthday
party where my hair was literally orange
and I look like Ronald McDonald. And
that was a mega moment. It was like, but
then I think that photo that you have
was peak where I was like, "Wow, I look
incredible as a blonde." But then it
grew out and it started to look bad. I
think the more it grew out, the better
it looks. I agree. I would say major
because it's also like in tripletood to
like break that bond of looking like it
was an individuality. It was I would say
that was major. I'd agree. Major major
moves, Nick. Good agree. Good agree. The
worldrenowned debate heard across the
universe. This is middle part, Matt. No,
it's not. Middle. I hope that's in
there, but it's a close second. Let's
see.
Boston versus LA.
Like, holy [ __ ] I understand that it
was like a pivotable. I think it was
like to me trash, but like to the fans,
I understand how it could have survived
at like a mid level. I think this is a
good mid level. Yeah, I can get that. It
was just mid mid. No, I I don't mind the
I don't mind the debate. I think that I
honestly I like how much Boston is an
always conversation because to me it is
an important part of I agree and I'm
happy like I would hate to just be like
oh I live in LA and never talk about my
hometown I I like that people like that
we're from Boston I think it's pretty
major I but I think that the whole
debate and discussion is correct but
like Boston in general that would be the
first correct what pisses me off though
and is not true is I saw someone and
they were like, "How OG of a fan of the
triplets are you?" And they were like,
"I remember when they were the Boston
boys." And I was like, "What are you
saying?" What are you talking about? And
they're they're saying like they're
claiming that like our YouTube channel
names like not be like Boston. Yeah.
Like never happened. Never. We were
starting triplets from the moment our
YouTube career started. No. Nick
starting and then it was
starting never Boston boys. OG Twitch
streams in my room.
Never talk [ __ ] about Mr. Worldwide like
that. Ever again. The microphone and
camera quality were so ass and trash.
But the vibes were good. The vibes were
insane. I have to be honest here. What?
It's it's it's the closest to incredible
we have so far. Are you serious? In my
opinion. And this is like peak like this
is like peak like filming content and
mom and dad could also come into the
room and yell at us still. Yeah, I mean
really fun. I'd say this is major. I
have when Matt sneezed in the world.
Incredible. How do we feel about that? I
think that that car video like the topic
of discussion and the humor one of my
favorites. Oh, it was legend. Like I
think Matt sneezing and this video
concept was incredible. Matt, no mid.
It's not mega mid. That and this are
equivalent to me. Yeah, you're actually
right. They're actually mega mid
overlook.
You're so right, Matt. You're so right.
Can I pay with my looks? Burger King Tik
Tok. How do we feel? We're in the Burger
King drive-thru. I record the lady and
Nick goes, "Can I pay with my looks?"
And she goes, she goes, "Yes." Said,
"Yeah." Didn't have to pay. I think I
paid for like a $40 meal with my looks.
No, it was a drink. It was one drink.
Thank you. Can I pay with my looks?
Thanks.
money.
Oh, it [ __ ] worked. I just paid my
wounds and furated. I don't think that
this reach is incredible. This is a
major moment. I think it was mid. What?
I think it was mint. Nobody else has
ever done this. It was shocking, but it
was You bargained. You bargained a free
drink with your Burger King. Correct.
Yeah, you guys can go major if you want.
Major moment. That's major for me. I'm
happy you guys think it was major.
Brandy Candy screaming and interrupting
me in the live. That was an incredible
That was incredible. I think like that's
the thing too is I think people were
like so upset by that and they're like,
"People need to learn tour theater
etiquette, whatever." I thought it led
to an incredible funny moment and I
loved that show. It was probably one of
my favorite shows of the entire tour.
I'd say incredible moment. I would say
incredible. I think that it did start a
trend of interruptors I feel like on our
shows, but overall incredible.
hilarious. Like I think that show was
just incredible and that didn't ruin it
for me and it gave me something to laugh
and joke about and it was like fun.
Stop talking. Stop talking. Do that.
When Matt scrambled our eggs and ate
them for breakfast. Your eggs were my
breakfast. Case in point, don't [ __ ]
with me.
This was an incredible This was absolute
cinema. The plot twist of a century
because I truthfully have never been so
blindsided in our career. Illy right
there. Fully agree.
Beard Matt. Beard Matt. Where does it
go? Where does it go? Dude, this might
have to go in major. I think that I
think that this has to go major. Right,
Nick? No, cuz I think that there's too
many people like
Like I think it's like I think out of
all three of us, Matt gets the most
constant debate and discussion around
like the way he looks. Back up. I got
the tape. I got it in my hand. Relax. I
think it's a mega mint. I agree. Not
that you look bad. I think once again
the topic of discuss, but no, it's like
it is exciting to be a fan and be like,
"Oh my god, my like favorite celebrity,
my favorite person, my favorite
YouTuber, my favorite internet crush has
a beard. He looks different." Like I get
what they're thinking. I think it's like
to mega mid cuz I'm blood related to
you, but to the outside viewer, I think
it's a major moment, but I refuse to put
it there. So, I think we're going to
land on mid. I really love that
breakdown and that analysis, Nick, and I
couldn't agree more with you. Okay,
Matt. I just think like I don't know,
man. This is why I don't I don't
listen to Jubilee video. How do we rank
this moment in our career? I honestly
think it was an incredible moment and it
was so [ __ ] fun and it was like a
crazy like YouTuber pivot moment, but
the fact that the people at Jubilee told
everyone to match and we were one of the
only people who did match was really
embarrassing. Um, if we weren't all
wearing white hoodies, I would say
incredible. I completely agree. But
because we're matching head to toe, it
was head to toe was major. One of the
craziest moments. Come on, bro.
The Doc O moment, dude. Her entire spine
had metal on it. Shorty looks like Doc
O. And I'm like, you're surprised?
You're surprised you're setting this
[ __ ] thing off and you're walking
through with a [ __ ] metal vest on.
Like, are we for real? You look like Doc
O going through [ __ ] airport
security, setting this [ __ ] off. You
didn't think to tell him, "Oh, I'm
[ __ ] laced with metal. Let me walk
through this metal detector." You
[ __ ] sure he's all shocked getting
detected with metal. This right here,
that was a career establishing rant.
This right here, that was a This was
when I realized like, holy [ __ ] Nick
ranting in our videos is like the
funniest thing ever. The key to success.
No, and that's the thing is like I've
met so many people being a YouTuber and
this is one of the moments that they're
like, I knew that you were funny when I
watched this clip of Wow. And like
watching it back, I'm like, I don't
think it was like that funny. It was
unreal. It was really It was a major
moment. This to me is incredible. I
think it was incredible. Hell yeah. Hell
yeah. I believe this is a moment all
young YouTubers look up to
YouTube. 100,000 subscribers. That was
probably the most incredible out of
anything on this list. I totally agree.
Like I think that that was a really
pivotable mental moment in my life. I
fully agree. Yeah. I think above
incredible. Really? I agree. I think
that's going to be like the best one on
here. It was joy. It was It was bliss.
It was um It was um It was confidence.
It was courageous. It was on future day.
And look at me now. The zoo video.
[Applause]
Oh, round incredible. Like we need to
get back on our get back in our bag.
Yeah, for sure. And we need to invest
some money. I'd say this was sick. Thank
you. Feeling like Mr. Beast. Feeling
like I was not feeling like Mr. Beast. I
was You were feeling like Mr. Beast.
Bonazoo for 24 hours. I was feeling like
a beast. Merch collection with the with
the
subscriber perfectly aligned. Nothing.
Nothing could have been better than
that. It was a great time. I feel like
it was our first ever boys trip as well.
That was like bros. It was like a really
big as Bros experience. It was and we
haven't really done No, but it was like
I think that we also like the As Bros
[ __ ] like you guys joke around about.
But truthfully, doing all of these
things here from mega mint all the way
to Incredible. Like I love doing it as
bros. Get the
next aolo Christmas. This was a really
fun series. This was crazy. I think What
did we do? You want me to read it? Post
every Monday to Friday. The first video
we posted was reacting to your
Christmas. I don't need to hear all
this. Five car videos, four holiday
vlogs, four podcasts. Wow. That is
actually crazy. I think that that moment
was the most amount of content we filmed
in one period of time. Is that when we
did the Christmas intro that people
hated though? Yeah, but that like look
what everything else we did. I know. I
actually don't think that that's the
same time frame. It's a different
Christmas.
I think this was major. I don't think it
was incredible. I agree. I think a
serial Christmas was like a major fun
moment. It didn't blow my [ __ ] socks
off. Yeah, I thought it was fun. I think
this might be incredible for Nick. Let's
see it.
The Cut the Camera podcast. Yeah, I
sound like Jojo Se being guest on my
podcast. Okay, the first thing that
comes to my brain is that one clip of us
dying the the murder mystery pod when we
were dying laughing when someone was
getting struck in the head or something
and then the team orange the girl got
that got killed in the orange socks
song. So I think that our podcast I
think I think that our podcast was
incredible. I think Matt's speaking and
you're interrupting me. You just scared
me. I thought so many of you scared me
too. back with no regrets. But we did it
and we were posting three times a week
and it was pretty exhausting. But what a
[ __ ] blast. Major. I'd say major. But
like but like it cheater's incredible. I
think I think this is the first teeter
totter. I can get along with that
cuz next up y
I'm right. Let's go. What's next?
What? We have the collab with Quen,
[ __ ] Incredible. Don't put a
hole in the [ __ ] wall. You think I
could put a hole in the wall slamming it
like that? Yes, absolutely. I think that
that collab and then also just all of
our other collabs.
I hate talking to my brothers. So, if
there's another person in the room that
I can talk to and bounce off of, oh, who
is you?
You stop. You don't [ __ ] disrespect
Matt. What I'm saying is that where did
we put Nick's new haircut? Incredible.
Okay. I think growing up, every single
person that we met was like, "You guys
are so funny. You guys are so funny. You
guys are so funny." And I think it's
because the three of us find ourselves
funnier when we're with another person.
Like I think we were YouTubers who are
meant to collab. Like, and if I'm not
mistaken, we went number one viral.
That was like a lot of like AI. Like it
was like having like an attempt to
almost start fighting. I went number one
training.
All right, Matt, are you ready? The hate
line's directed towards me. What? It's
not. I'm just talking to my lovely
brother. Okay, freak. Okay, freak.
You're comforting.
Our collab with Sam and Colby. Exactly
what I just said about Quen's same
experience. You know, I had to double
it. And if I'm not mistaken, we went
number one viral.
Were you trying to scream?
Try again. I'll end it viral. And if I'm
not mistaken, we went number one
trending viral.
You know, I had to do
it. Incredible. Now, yes. Top three
cheeses. She Vermont sharp, seriously
sharp and mozzarella and parmesan. Those
are four. What's um Kobe Jack? Colby
Jack.
Colobby Jack was my favorite thing in
our whole career. This one? Are you dead
serious? Serious Jack, it's time to
[ __ ] do some soulsearching. Stop
Jesus. Are you serious? Stop.
This and I'm being totally truthfully
honest. It's another cheater. That That
was like, dude, the MLB. It's the
second. I think it was such a cool
moment. I think that it's like it's not
funny to me now cuz it it's it's been
it's been hammered into the ground
deeper than earthworms scavenge. You
know what I'm saying? Like, it is so
dead. It's so dead. But it shows our
energy through what car videos are. It
emulates the perfect car video humor.
And it is like analyzing our car videos
like he's like a [ __ ] How about the
tier list on the wall
giving me [ __ ] for analyzing the videos.
We're analyzing everything. We created a
[ __ ] paper tier list that we're
utilizing pasted to our wall. Shut the
[ __ ] up. Are you kidding me? You shut
your [ __ ] ass up. These like bros
analyzing our videos. Take a look at the
wall. All we're missing is strings and
pins.
We're halfway to detective status, you
[ __ ] freak. Are you serious? Oh,
giving me [ __ ] You printed this [ __ ]
out. I'm just saying you're yapping
about it like it's a video. Chill out.
Holy smokes.
Joking. You're joking now. Oh, who is
you? I like you on. It's her grandma.
All right. Best video ever. Oh, who is
you? It's her grandma.
I love that baby. Danielle, stop it. Oh,
who is you? I'm your grandmother. Lean
back. Acting like you going to get up
and do something. Get up and do
something then. Do you remember Bobo and
Coco? Who?
Oh my god. No, we never said that on the
video. I know, dude. These are the
scariest looking people on Earth.
Seriously, this is like a mega. be
scary. You, Matt, and Chris always joke
around cuz there's this one video of me,
Matt, and Chris were like I don't I
don't know what we were doing. We were
like explaining something else. I just I
had like red hair. Matt's wearing tie
dye and wearing like the baggiest like a
really tight pink hoodie. Imagine Matt
like a full literally had a full throat.
We looked the worst we've ever looked in
our lives in that video. What is that
video? I don't remember. Where did you
put I think we were like also editing on
a new software and it like mixed the
mess just like my hair.
I look like I got beat up.
My god, I look worse than you. You do
look awful. This might just look like a
photo of Jason Tatum. But if
you right between his legs
now hold the [ __ ] That to me is
incredible Bostononian moment. This I
have to say like us going to the Celtics
game and working with them to make
content and then and them gifting us
stuff and being able to sit courtside
bring two of our best friends ever. This
was an incredible incredible Yo yo
Incredibles. That's Teeter. That's the
Teeter line. Incredibles like Yeah.
Right there. Yeah. No, that right there.
See, I'm not even a big sports fan, but
what a Boston experience. I was bleeding
on the jumbotron. It was Yeah. That
said, Sternolo's triplets is you guys
name. Yeah. So, this is when I went on
stage with Skies. Wow. Someone tweeted
it and said, "Is that Chris Sternolo on
stage with Skies?" Wow. And he confirmed
it by saying, "That's the bro on
Twitter." Wow.
That incredible moment for young
Christopher. Yeah. I mean, the cowboys.
Honestly, the 7 mil vid was so fun and
celebrating 7 mil with our cowboy, our
horse friends. But the zoo video is
better. And I don't know when we're
going to hit 8 mil, but I hope to top
the zoo video and the cowboy video. What
a great I think that the cowboy video
and hitting 7 million subscribers was
major, but we could have went more all
out. We could have went more all out for
7 mil. I'm going to I'm going to do
this. It's self-deprecating and it's
putting ourselves down. But I think this
is a major mid teeter line to be honest.
I completely agree with you. And I will
say though, the only thing that makes me
want to bump it up to major more is cuz
video aside, I felt connected with
nature and the animal and I had an
overall great experience. I don't think
that I would have ever had besides
YouTube. I think that's major. When
Julia Ernst confirmed that her and Matt
never dated, I will I will say this is
going in the video. I will say that this
was incredible. A major clarity point
for me. Yeah. Finally. Thank you, God.
You know. Yeah. No hate. No hate. But
like, come on. What are we doing?
Rumors. Rumors. I love rumors. I love
rumors. I think that everyone we should
like start. I want to be hated on. I
want rumors. I want lies spread. You
know, every source of media. I'm dating
this person. I hate this person. Me and
this person aren't friends anymore. I'm
best friends with this person. I love
rumors. I love haters. Hate on me. Lie
about me. Let's do it. The last one. No.
The sterno triplets product campaign and
trip to Italy. First time overseas for
Matt and
Chris. I think that was incredible. I
think it was an incredible experience. I
think I looked the best out of the three
of us. I think that it was really fun
working with such a major brand. Going
on a trip with you guys was so fun. Such
a pivotal career moment and something
and enjoy. I think that this is it. I
think that this is a really good
demonstration of just everything. I
really do think that it makes sense.
Thank you guys so much for watching this
week's video. We hope you enjoyed it so
very much. And if you liked it, please
like it and subscribe.
Um, and let us know if you like the tier
lists, what you want us to tier list in
the future. Like, do you want us to tear
your legs? Like Matt in this yellow
hoodie. Stop. Incredible. Stop. Stop.
Stop. Matt with a beer. Incredible. Nick
in the stripes. Mega mid. Chris's jokes
on the floor. Terrible. One name for
mega below. Mega mega mega mga mega.
That's mid. That's mega mega mid. That's
it.
[Music]