you want to go check Matt no
in all fairness you said you were going
to
say and then what you're saying how you
miss me yeah you
yeah
[Music]
it's a good video when Matt makes the
first noise
oh okay what do you guys want to talk
about do you wanna was just crazy to me
what like the term on Tick Tock like oh
do an unboxing because I was talking
about it today and I saw someone
dead-ass like a little girl who must
like learn all of her lingo from Tick
Tock whatever like
say like she was eating breakfast in the
morning oh I'm doing like a like I'm
getting ready for school Vlog and she
was like first I grabbed my backpack and
then I go into the kitchen and she did
like a cereal unboxing and it was dead
ass like opening her cereal and pouring
it into the thing you know like no girl
you opened a box and you like you yeah
it's an unboxing but we all knew it was
she unboxed the cereal but it's like we
all knew what was it I hate the term
like people would say on Tick Tock now
like oh like let's do an unboxing and
it's like for everything like girl we
don't need an unboxing of like
everything like I feel like already like
I feel like I just don't know I feel
like the word reveal can come into play
way more often
see me and Chris just understand the
algorithm no but I also get like an
unboxing if it's like I just spent 200
at Urban Outfitters unboxing yeah
like an unboxing like you're opening up
but how much that could be like how much
more how much more how much more
intrigued are you if somebody says
revealing what I got from Urban
Outfitters no I I'm revealing my 200
Urban Outfitters Splurge I'm right here
at the edge of my seat I hear you oh my
god what do you think they got for 200
too like it could be like yeah
I'm like you don't know I hear you a lot
surprise is a good word yes 200 Urban
surprise oh that's a good one because
then you feel surprised even though you
didn't technically it could it could be
there's like clothes yeah yes Chris yes
Chris yeah it makes a something
surprising surprise a surprise unboxing
okay Urban gives you stuff in bags first
of all right where most places do right
so it's like are you really I feel like
the only time the word unboxing can come
into play is if you get sent something
in the mail literally in a box I hear
what you're saying I was just going back
validating like it's okay to call like
opening a package with five or more
things in unboxing that's all I was
trying to say that's cool yeah that's
cool but like let's get into the video
yeah I hear you I'm not disagreeing I'm
going back to myself because he just
keeps repeating himself yeah surprise is
better and so is reviews
crazy Matt I'm not listening I don't
give a [ __ ] I'm not listening you
telling me I'm repeating myself you are
correct you want to know what you do
yeah you're repeating yourself you're
repeating yourself simple how many times
did you say repeating yourself it
doesn't matter it doesn't matter it
doesn't matter
shut the [ __ ] up I bet you'll say that
one more time this video I just can't
handle it I bet you'll say that too it's
almost like what can you handle oh my
God shut the [ __ ] up two times all right
shut up anyway go ahead Nick tell them
what's going on I have [ __ ] nothing
to say you go motor mouth
don't laugh at me that's crazy don't
laugh at what I say that's like
SpongeBob calling Squidward sponge I
hate when you guys [ __ ] talk to me
and like I hate when you guys give me
[ __ ] for time I hate when I turn around
and look at you Nick I hate when you
hate when you guys give me [ __ ] for
saying things and then expect me to go
and say something shut up don't expect
anything from you actually we're
expecting it's not like we're asking you
to talk to us we're telling you to
introduce the video like you could be
mad at us it's still interesting
introduce it I don't know what we're
doing never [ __ ] no let's let's wait
let's just I'm not doing anything until
you say it no I'll just keep this
argument going no say
no you start something new I'm good yeah
I'll write that I don't care go ahead
Matt we are just sitting back there
repeating himself the whole time I
didn't come up with the video topic
today all right today we're doing
um we're gonna [ __ ] hey you just said
he didn't know and then he said he came
up with it so pick [ __ ] one of them
don't stop cutting it out no but he's
going to say I'm cutting it out go ahead
I'm gonna cut it out cut no you're not
yes I am Nick I will I won't I'm cutting
it out I won't let this video get up
uploaded okay I'm about to cut it out I
know what numbers are on commanded I
know fingers
I know what I'm about to say what I say
does not make it into the video I will
be smacking you so hard against the face
and we will be quitting YouTube so say
it for good say it we'll see if we're
good let's see what happens we're done
Nick you wouldn't say it for your own
well-being say it Matt three it's not
that big of a [ __ ] deal I could talk
about [ __ ] Bo Schmo and [ __ ]
Supercuts in T-Mobile for an hour and be
equally as yeah I know you can talk
about Supercuts for an hour yeah okay
yeah I know whatever just [ __ ] go
Supercuts all the way just Chatterbox
you [ __ ] Goofs I'll introduce the
videos
boom yes
yes today we'll be discussing
um super powers and
like what we do with them and rate them
out of like one through ten or something
I don't know oh my God we're just gonna
talk about super Nick what are you
saying oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
it's almost like he said the whole video
idea oh my God I feel like perfectly
fine he wouldn't have said or something
at the end of it okay here's the thing
though we were just talking about how
you can introduce the video if you want
to and you complaining it's just crazy
how little you guys would be able to
orchestrate filming a [ __ ] video I
didn't do not true yes it is we Chris
said it we're ready to go on to the next
topic but you're the one that had to go
oh my God
[Applause]
correct all right
um every day
um first of all I have a question give
me it would you guys if someone came
down and was like a big important figure
of like superheroism okay and was like
I have the magical powers to Grant you a
special ability come on
oh I got like go back up there no if
someone's like I have the magical powers
to Grant you a special ability however
like something detrimental will happen
to you like sent like would you take
that risk like if you had to like does
that even [ __ ] me I'm about to
explain it you [ __ ] quick bastard
I don't care no
and then I said wait and then I was
about to explain but go ahead I'm not
talking go ahead I'm curious
go Chris
Jesus what's the detrimental issue like
lose three years of your life like lose
three years hey shut the [ __ ] up
you motor Chatterbox motor mouth [ __ ]
[ __ ] shut the [ __ ] up
holy [ __ ] like holy [ __ ]
can you teach me how to keep talking you
motor mouth you [ __ ] Chatterbox
hey I have to blow my nose so bad I'm
like nasally right now okay what's the
stupid [ __ ] question I just want to
answer I need a tissue we don't have any
yeah I don't have [ __ ] for you I hope
that what was I gonna say I don't know
we all don't know what we're saying
something about a higher power and
detrimental incidents oh yeah Nick's
mouth was running faster than he's ever
in his life
that's what we were on right go Chris
please okay as I was saying like Nick
I'm gonna [ __ ] I'm just laughing that
you'll never ever
I didn't look to the camera my head is
straight you'll never look again is what
I'm saying because your head will be the
other way you [ __ ] dummy
oh
something bad would happen like you'd
lose like a chunk of your like like five
years off your life maybe like all four
of your fingers on your left hand like
[ __ ] like all four whatever four
you're four
oh you think it has a question
your four main like fingers you have to
like can't shower
oh my God I'm not never mind go go yeah
like I'm honestly it's like a chance of
something bad happening and then
something we need you to be specific and
say hey would you get super powers if
this had to happen to you
yes no okay yeah sounds good let's keep
going because I'm not I'm done with that
question thank God no the the answer is
no I wouldn't I would absolutely cool so
I got my answers there you go regardless
good job you good job um
I just don't know how you can feel
satisfied out there at least you're
satisfied after just being a goofball
for 24 hours a day at least I have one
main finger though right yeah you're
funny
oh God I had Nick's laugh I didn't lose
my mind
okay so we're talking about superpowers
and ranking them in which order we would
want to do that because you didn't so
let's get into the first one
super strained uh corny so overrated
yeah it's like the most lame one like oh
you can pick stuff up and throw it you
angry bastard calm down it'd be perfect
for Chris Nick I would destroy you
because he gets all upset and tries
like a melon you goof he gets all
stressed out
I thought that was a [ __ ] dinosaur on
T-Mobile
let's try to do super strength is like
he's like Hero on my list like
super powers it'd be really cool if you
had to move though I feel like something
I feel like it's on 10. yeah
um in the invisibility
that's a solid like four that's top five
for me I think right now I'm comfortable
with it at four but it may need to
switch if I was invisible the first
thing I'd do is rob a bank should we
write this all down or go to a store no
just a list off the top of the head okay
foreign
would just be running super super speed
number two no I feel like it's equal to
one because equivalent
is number two because it is the
equivalent exactly what you just said so
therefore number two why would why would
we tie it well because it's the same
[ __ ] thing no it's not it's okay
okay like one two thanks
guys
don't worry it's gonna be on two
teleport was so you can be somewhere
without getting out or run really fast
oh but it's the same thing they'll both
just be watching like are you serious
red delicious
oh they're both red apples same thing no
they're [ __ ] not all right
okay cool one two skip three
invisibility super strength to the ten
next laser beam eyes zero like you can
carve [ __ ] that's like a nine that's
giving nine for me that's switching in
ten I'd rather have super strength and
Laser absolutely true okay boom now I
got I think I got hey hey I think we are
here all night not anymore we argued you
are rightfully laser beam eyes what like
I feel like I just use it if I'm a
little angry or something like like I
said I wouldn't want to use it on
someone I'd use it to like carve down
walls and just walk through them sure
and I feel like at that point I'll just
find the entrance to things read
um what about I think I got my number
four spot what
shape-shifting I was gonna [ __ ] say
that like imagine just becoming a penny
and then rolling in the store like you
know what you know what like that's I
have something that's higher than that
and you can I'd rather shape-shift you
could become to anybody like I honestly
think we put super speed way too high I
agree I think we put it on like eight
that's why I equated it with one because
it's the same thing I think we put it on
eight that's why I just equated it with
well that would be stupid wait how the
[ __ ] would your number one number
teleportation's already there I'm not
gonna put super speed as high why
because as I say why do we make other
sponges in this world when we already
have a sponge it's just this it's in the
notebook no we don't we have a phone
what you're trying to do I'll put it on
my hand no no we're gonna eat no just
write them on [ __ ] phone are you guys
don't got paper two three four five what
next what do you think we should do
shape shifting I'm really feeling I
think that number two because now that
I'm thinking about it hold on I'm kind
of thinking no we can't once it's on
this paper it's a lot hold on I'm
thinking these are above teleportation
now hear me out no hear me out if you
can have one or the other teleportation
all you can do is teleport if you can
shape-shift you could shape-shift for so
many different uses and then not only
that if you shape shift in my mind your
DNA like shape shifts what you're
shape-shifting too you know what I mean
you're wrong like if you're like
shape-shifting to a tiger and someone
swabs your mouth you have tiger DNA it
won't be nixster I agree yes same with
like a fingerprint if I shape shift to
Chris my fingerprint that's incorrect no
yeah I'm completely correct so what I'm
saying is I don't know instead you could
shape-shift into like air if you want to
teleport to an airport Personnel famous
person the whole point is the way you go
I don't want to wait correct yeah but
I'm saying
I think that three is mine reading
oh I'd hate to have that what you could
think of what everyone else hold on
telekinesis
that's three in my in my easy three
sorry no I'm using my Jesus Christ easy
three hold on tell uh oh we forgot about
invisibility yes no that was four okay
you're right in invisibility
I feel like wait wait super strength is
nine confirm confirm confirm okay
um I I feel like we gotta go what about
Earth manipulation like grass and like
leaves and rocks
like I feel like that's like go to the
desert you're [ __ ] yes no like it
would include like sand and like oh it's
all like all Earth I thought it was like
green Avatar [ __ ] again all four air
water I feel like you gotta pick one
well I'm thinking about I'm thinking
more of the greenery Greenery girl from
Sky High she's stupid
wouldn't even put her on top I 110
agreement you're about the guy that
glows terrible what about like
elastigirls Powers zero those are
stretch yeah they're fun for a little
bit cool and they're fun maybe they get
old maybe I'm really like I'm feeling
like they should be on here though no no
no the elastic Powers whatever we have
we had oh mind reading that's gotta be
five mind reading is five absolutely
because I wouldn't want to know all that
oh no I know but it would help you so
much I think if you could turn it on or
off like specific moments you can I
don't know yeah
I just thought it was gonna be like no
no no no no no you're fine you're fine
um oh how about how about um animorph
like to an animal
yeah but that would be way more on like
a specific scale no terrible that's a
lame shape-shifting okay Chris relax
um
got it right there no there's too much
of a requirement I feel like they're
it's just you got to get looped up like
he doesn't gotta like no why he's just
gotta get a little wet like
Christopher yeah
Potter the whole time like see he has a
glass he has to get started he goes
don't let me get mine boring
that's too nervous I think freeze is
seven flying is eight
Frieza seven flying is eight I'll do
that
[Music]
I know we don't want to move him around
but I'd rather have super strength than
fly no no no no okay whatever are you
kidding all right six what's our final
our last one it has to be worse than
mind reading but better than freeze
powers okay worse than mine reading
better than freeze electric
no not enough really I feel like just
general magic like a wizard
what
if I if I wrote down a full list magic
would be [ __ ] 50 dick what like um
that's so wrong okay like magic like
whoosh what if you could like grow extra
limbs and [ __ ]
I hate that and like climb up like like
a Doc Ock no terrible awful awful awful
Spider-Man the worst terrible I don't
know better it's so boring you're so
specific for me what about I love
telekinesis what about
um
you can make things appear like that
hamburger
no I think that's just teleport teleport
to where you want to teleport back true
that's not it will go to you yeah but
you know if you can teleport what's the
what's what's okay yeah it's like it's
not even a superpower but like imagine
like just being like super like
I don't know it was so stupid come on no
Nick now I feel bad I think like a spy
like if you just be a spy like super oh
super hearing super hearing not even no
that's mine spy that's mind reading no
it's not no not like spiders make a
special ops agent like you were super
strong and powerful no just mind reading
I feel
would have felt like 100 accuracy with
like weapons and [ __ ] I'm not boring
knife 100
oh my God freeze time we never put
freeze time I think that's perfect where
it's at I agree freeze time would be a
perfect eighth slot uh sixth slot I
can't read yeah that'd be perfect oh my
God freeze time there it is that was
amazing how do we let that one slip so
now it's our total list all right our
list goes teleport shape shift yep
telekinesis invisibility mind reading
freeze time just freeze like Frozone
um flying ate super strain and then
laser eyes honestly I'm happy with it
I'm really happy with it if you could
roll a dice
and like hold on imagine like another
one right here that's like poop your
pants once a day would you roll your
dice and risk trying to get one of those
I feel like actually hold on hold on I
feel like you need two shitty ones
because dice roll oh I get your pun yeah
okay I have to pee pees I have to
go poop my pants for the first time
today
for my brothers