oh my God we don't even need additional
light I love that we're filming right
now
taking my pants off so we can't put this
in that's fine no Nick
what look at the camera
Pants On Hold on
shut up I hear you I can't do anything
about it is it good yeah I couldn't tell
if no why'd you just do that now because
he asked me to well that's gonna change
it a second because I didn't even set a
timer for how long
[Music]
shut up
look at I put a sticker on his shirt and
he has no idea I threw it I threw it and
it landed there and he like didn't even
take it off is it recording and it's
good yeah
video time guys it's been so long since
we filmed the car videos we had car
videos pre-filmed in Boston but we're
out which is so exciting to me because I
love getting to film these so it's time
to cook first things first the it's
bright out so I love filming car videos
in the day too it's not the day it's
like Peak night like let us know let us
know
if you like this um it looks now more
than you do oh I got two tattoos since
the last video Meg I got one tinny
I like your sticker I didn't even know
this was [ __ ] on me that's crazy
get up I got it for you Nick don't stick
it to like [ __ ] on the car why I'm
loving little kids used to do that
why did I just say that no yeah okay
today oh wait wait wait first thank you
for five million subscribers
oh my God
Bermuda memory guys five million man
shake my hand again all right pleasure
doing business yes of course I'm so
happy we've got it this far it brings me
tons of joy to live my life every day
I'm and I'm at a half a Mill by myself
wow give it up for Matt
uh Everybody 400k by myself whoa
what about you I am at 300. that's
that's good yeah
[ __ ] it you're just not active you gotta
get active I've only posted two videos
in my life I hated the first one yeah
yeah more content coming soon but for
all of us but right now we're just too
busy we got podcasts tomorrow on Friday
it's crazy that you still do this
how much money to drink this maple syrup
that's in the car right now 10 bucks 10.
visibly have deodorant on no like I hate
that Vibe no you don't no you don't you
hate that Vibe I feel like it's very
suiting for you
don't do that it's suitable for me no
it's you you said 10 bucks oh
you're gonna drink syrup bro
okay week as [ __ ] go kid what are you
blocking it with your tongue for don't
plug it up with your tongue suck it down
I don't know who Nick reminds me of now
that he dyed his hair
the barbarian from Clash of Clans
okay or the giant like before he got it
toned he was the giant okay the big the
giant the giant has the doctor
with the orange hair because that's how
it looked before this it was kind of
like
you look a little kid from [ __ ]
Horton Hears a Who
which one the lorax I mean Let It Grow
I have a couple things I just been
thinking about that I wrote down so
that's how I'm gonna just move forward
let's do it go for it I have
them come I ever got was I'm straight
but you hit different like okay girl who
you trying to prove I have that row down
okay very gay move yeah but is that not
crazy yeah that is really crazy
like I'm straight but you hit different
how do you even type that sentence to a
man if you're straight you're definitely
not
straight is definitely just not what you
are what's the craziest DM you ever got
I have a couple other things that I've
written down that are just like goofy
um my least favorite words and people
are like oh it's ethereal or ethereal
like [ __ ] what does that mean
shut up what does that mean it's like oh
like like I look ethereal or ethereal
like they think they're like a fairy
princess and so you look a little a
little better than mid
at all oh my God
I just hate that word oh my God I hate
that that was the best that was the most
you've ever flamed like something
he said you look a smidge better than
mid oh I love that word
thank God
it is true I really just don't think
that that word's ever suitable for like
a human being is that a real word let's
Google it is good to use if you enter
Narnia you can be like oh this place if
no yeah if you're if you're living out
of fable then go for it
it's extremely delicate and light in a
way that seems too perfect for this
world wow
you're so goofy I feel like you'd do
that that was that was so it's like
doing like the only way I would use that
is if I was like
I wouldn't use it yeah and maybe
entering Narnia or like visiting
Tinkerbell but those are like seems to
be the only two occasions also another
occasion is if I was in Smurf Village
for sure oh yeah you have to no question
about it damn bro Smurf at Loki she
gotta be rich
damn bro Smurf at low-key
this real like no it's because it's the
realest like that's like like are all
the smurfs gay
celibate
probably that option
I agree well if Gargamel made the first
Smurf at
how did the Smurf become
I don't need to know I also wrote down I
feel like can't get enough it's such an
underrated oh I love it it's such an
underrated way to say how someone feels
about something oh they just can't get
enough it's like one of those words
that's just like you can't get enough it
could be
oh I can't get enough of it like it
could be an exciting way you can make
fun of someone that way not that that's
a good thing no it's a great thing
correct like oh you just can't get it
off
go ahead bring it on oh yeah it's like
whatever you got Bring it on Bring it on
Bring It On is good bring it on it's
really good bring it on is good yeah I
don't know if this is [ __ ] up
but if someone was deaf I would whisper
surprises around them to feel risky you
know what I mean like if I had plans and
I couldn't tell anyone like if someone
was deaf or claimed to be deaf epic
whisper little secrets around them to
see like to feel just something you know
what I mean
Nick that's tough I'm [ __ ] up like if
someone's fully deaf and you're just
like
like it's like someone's seven years
a little sweet nothing that you don't
want anyone to hear sweet nothing's
crazy is that a little funny though no
that's terrible I hate children who
demand to do something and then [ __ ] it
up
like when they're like like their mom's
doing something like oh let me do it
like the mom's like getting herself
coffee right and like I want to drive
with this the mom lets them add like
something to the coffee and they spill
[ __ ] or like if you're building
something and like like a like a toy set
and the kid's like let me help and then
they're like dropping screws
batteries it's like you're so unhelpful
yeah like let someone who's got posable
thumbs at work do it instead of your
grimy little sticky gross fingers yeah
you annoying little [ __ ] no little kids
are like I want to do it and like they
[ __ ] [ __ ] up over and over the parents
are like you can't even pick up a third
of your body weight and you're 50 pounds
you Peewee Chum like grow up you know I
think kids should learn from their
lessons like I think if a kid spill
something in a store he should clean it
like even if he's like four like get to
scrubbing give the kid some napkins he
thinks he can carry the coffee he can
clean the floor okay that's a good one
I'm good with giving kids like a chance
like oh if they want to try and pick it
up like I don't get like repeated error
yeah error like if you're gonna get let
the kid grab your coffee and then they
drop it and then they drop it like for
the next three times the person remakes
your coffee I feel like some things kids
just shouldn't do
I got some of that syrup on my fingers
what do you want about it okay I know
finger sniffing weirdo
I also hate like pretending to be drunk
is the corniest oh you're [ __ ] lame
uh the worst like I I really can't do
like drunk Pretenders drunk Pretenders
are so embarrassing
but just get hammered
no yeah that's fine it's just like so
like attention grabbing it's like
attention seeking it's like you could do
anything else to gain people's attention
and your choice is gonna be to act like
a [ __ ] fool yep and it's like make
some change you know what I mean make
change for this world you wanna know
what I love what
pants
with a lot of pockets yeah you can
really fill them up does anyone want to
re-season where the [ __ ]
do you want one yeah I do actually
I'm good
I'm good liners out real quick all right
he will mix candies it's like oh like
like the way these are fun this is your
thing yes yeah I think it's ridiculous
because then you eat a KitKat smelling
like peanut butter no the worst isn't
someone puts a mince with oh you ruined
the whole container match yeah the whole
[ __ ] shabam what's it called the
whole shebang the whole shebang
definitely
I think you're on to something with that
one right yeah that's how I've heard it
before I think we're all something new I
think caboodle's like [ __ ] lucky
sounds like
like sauce you want that's crazy that's
giving Caboose if I said to you I want
to touch up on your caboodle where would
you think I'm talking about
don't say that please film that yeah
video and had Tom Brady and Pete
Davidson in it I don't even know what
you're saying he filmed a video about
like yeah it's like going on the most
expensive okay and then Pete Davidson
and Tom Brady in it that's crazy no they
were just in the Vlog like hanging out
like somebody brought his kids and they
were oh that's so crazy was he kissing
them on the mouth
I don't know actually why is that such a
viral thing I don't know I guess Tom
Brady just kisses his kids on the lips
how is there so many types of like door
handles that's like twist pull push I
hate when oh my God
they should just start putting boppets
on the [ __ ] door
some idiot yesterday slowest Walker I've
ever endured in my life you're some
idiot the other day I was stuck behind
him granted he was like 90. so I do feel
like oh my God it's just like pick up
your pace or let me pack you know what I
mean I hate old people who walk slow
that don't like realize that someone
who's fast is trying to walk can I have
a sip yeah you just had this water I
don't know why you took mines
they can walk for sure like I don't
think it gets mad and like rolls his
eyes but also shakes his head like so
flabbergasted again this old guy was
walking so slow I was stuck behind him
what was I getting at you he was going
it's better than being 20 and walking
crooked
you walk all the time anyways he was it
was a push they said on the door push
and I saw it and I was trying to get
ahead of him and he wouldn't let me buy
and I was gonna hold the door of her up
and being a good person
he wouldn't let me buy even though I was
like trying to get by him okay so you
call him an old [ __ ] push them no he
tried to pull the door and I said karma
Karma if I'm trying to let you go around
you to open the door for you and then
you're gonna put pull the push door
Karma
you look like a fool now I feel like
that would be hard like to just stand
the reason
I'm being rude about this is because I
got like I usually have so much patience
for this [ __ ] yeah I got to the door and
he didn't once he figured it out his old
ass he didn't hold it open for me oh my
God he let the door like [ __ ] you were
right there I was right behind him it's
almost like you got went through and
pulled it shut up like it felt like he
was keeping secrets in the bathroom
idiot maybe he had the Ethereal code in
there oh my God don't say that word but
I was just like are you a fool I feel
like the last time I saw a really old
person was at like the deli like I feel
like I haven't seen an old person in so
long
we don't really go to many functions
which the old would be attending no but
for real like I I think
no I just feel like I haven't seen like
someone old in so long like is that
weird to say
um a little I haven't seen a pregnant
woman in a while
okay she is bouncing on my booty what
are you saying what's your least
favorite word least favorite word oh I
got a really good word oh least favorite
or good like good okay like one of my
favorite words is grenade like it just
suits it so well I feel like a grenade
is perfect
if I was getting thrown I thought
through a grenade at me like I know like
bad is to come oh what else would you
think a grenade could be correct like if
I said like dude the only other thing
that I would think was near me if
someone yelled grenade is a pastry
what a grenade like say I'm a grenade if
it wasn't what it is it'd be a really
cute baby name no for real the grenade
little grenade I like it a lot wanna
know it's like I don't know what name
sits perfectly with
um what it is microwave
no no no no no no no I feel like that's
perfect no micro conventional heater
that's crazy that's insane
too much chocolate in the mouth heat
spin around that's the insane
heck you throw that in the Heat's been
around for like 60 seconds I really
can't get behind like cooking a whole
meal in a microwave I can't either if
you toss a frozen pizza in there you
better pray to God it comes out good
like use the oven use the oven
dude I've become such a fan of eggs
recently I've hated eggs my whole life
but I love like the eggs of the yolk
with the runny sunny side up oh oh it's
good
I used to make those when I was like in
high school yeah I did no you didn't not
those ones but like I used to like do so
correct no yours are what's a poached
egg I don't know dude I can't believe
how many variants of eggs there are
that's crazy like you're throwing crazy
[ __ ] at me like you can really do my
biggest fear was cracking an embryo onto
a frying pan like a little chick yeah I
still don't know the science behind that
I don't either yeah I've been trying to
figure it out for years I remember this
one girl he said that like every night
he goes to like a lab with this truck
I've been trying to figure this out for
years but I remember this one girl that
we went to school with had like a
um Chicken Coop Chicken Coop and we used
to have that's so hard bro a coop of
chickens no just the word Coop like yo
let's go to The Coop like yeah but this
girl had a chicken coop and she like
gathered a bunch of chicken eggs from
the thing and I didn't understand like
is that babies is it not like what's
going on here and
she was like oh it's gonna sit on like
my attic thing and we sat and she just
hummed the eggs at the wall and I was
like I was there because she had
convinced me that they were
regular eggs like no babies yes I don't
like the Halloween costumes that it can
be thing one thing two thing three I
know I know we did that but like it's
supposed to be just one and two yeah
yeah more than enough
monster it's like I love the Cat in the
Hat I'm like his biggest fan once it's
thing hey it's like cat in the Hat's a
little [ __ ] in my opinion and it's like
he's not in the Hat he's wearing the Hat
therefore he's a Cat in the Hat like I'm
not in a hat right now I'm wearing one
okay Cat in the Hat would imply he's in
the [ __ ] hat I think it's like a play
on words I think you're stupid because I
get it but like that's like the cat's in
the bag
you're in the bag okay that's crazy oh
oh where did you come from where did you
go let's start listening [ __ ] that would
be like a really good name if it wasn't
what it is fragrance oh that's a really
good
fragrance I feel like pressure
no it's like Cinder really Cinderella
that's like a tough kid I love agenda
what's on your agenda oh that's a really
good micro agenda oh that's my favorite
one I like that one a lot that's my
favorite one euthanasia
put down a dog
wow um
stairway no terrible no awful because
it's just way too imagine naming your
kid Taylor but it was like Taylor like
tailoring a suit like tea like that I
love that you're like I'm a big like
that's the biggest smile I've seen
because it's funny because Taylor's a
name but you could be like oh my name's
Taylor and then someone will go to write
it down by t-a-y-l and then I know
Taylor like I shoot like I make suits
yeah okay it's like like I kind of like
jewelry oh that's really good she's
expensive that's really good jewelry
what about like
I feel like if Nick was a baby and we
had to rename him and know something
else I'd be like like Flintstone I think
I'd give breakfast
yes you do
you do bro that's my friend
oh Avalanche that's awesome
Yosemite
one too
oh like me and my I was using a sentence
be like oh do you want to hang out with
me and my friend handicap okay
I don't like handicaps kind of what
about pavement no I love that me and
pavement are gonna run to the store
I like that one too what about column me
and my girl column
oh provoke provoke provoke security
another cute name would be
[Laughter]
clogs I love that sorry peace and love I
feel like that would be a really good
name bullet no if I was a little boy I'd
want to be named bullet really bad like
little bullet
peace and love Everyone we'll see you
next week you look like your name would
be corn on the cob you're oh my God if
next time you eat corn on the cob wear
that shirt
who's he who's eating corn off the cob
though like all this talk about corn on
the cob where's the corn off the cob I
feel like it's like in the can
I'm talking who's taking who's taking
corn
off a cop like decobbing
if you want to call it
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah
[Music]