all right guys welcome back to yet
another Sero triplet YouTube
video all right guys today we decided
Matt came up with the video idea do you
want to explain it or do you want me to
take the role this doesn't have to be a
big thing that I came up with the idea I
don't mind it doesn't have I'm just
letting you know it doesn't have
to I I beg your pardon but I did not say
that it needed to be a big deal I just
asked if you wanted to intro the video
idea you came up with I got it I'll take
have for you can put your hands down
yeah leave bubble you have a bubble
okay don't touch me what are you to do
about it [ __ ] knock your teeth out
not te the back throat [ __ ] not to tee
in the back of your [ __ ] throat
[ __ ] get off me all right Guys Mt came
up with the idea cuz every single time
we get donuts we literally get a full
dozen of glazed donuts it's so boring
and they always got that crazy [ __ ] o
disgrace you know what I mean like the
churo don't disgrace Cho churros are
great but don't jams can you [ __ ] off
and let me explain St being ridiculous
I'm going to [ __ ] Jam my fist in your
throat get out get
out I want to knock you out all right so
to break this curse of the glazed donut
catastrophe to break the glaze yes we
got to stop glazing these things bro to
break the glaz glaze basically I got us
12 dozen donuts of donuts that I don't
think any of us have had before cuz Nick
sick of the glaze some of them are
simple some of them are more extravagant
and fun but we're going to try 12 donuts
and which is we're going to try a dozen
donuts and rate them 1 to
12 oh cuz there's 12 yeah it's a dozen
yeah you said dozen and 12 like dozen
and 12 same number put an equal sign do
it equal sign equal sign first donut
let's go let me lubricate my
throat that that insane going down your
face
I don't know why I did that first dut
that we are going to try oh it's in
there I didn't see it first dut we're
going to try that we've never had before
I know we haven't never Cherry iced cake
is what it's called not trying it not
trying so it's a plain donut it looks
like with Cher old fashioned Cherry
plane old fashioned old fashioned if
you're 95 thanks [ __ ] this is the this
is the Cherry wa oh my God mat just came
through with a [ __ ] Med you cut our
Donuts into fors
please with your Infamous cut there we
go baby
girl there's a couple things you can say
I am
funny cool but one thing I'm not is a
fan of this [ __ ] dut I it's not that
bad eat mine then get away for me yeah
this thing the cake is good the Cherry
is disgusting there's no
cake it's a
donut that's called the Cherry iced cake
you dumb [ __ ] what are you tasting the
cake of I think I think they're good
just what are you doing actually I'm
removing the part I don't like all right
guys the next doughnut that I got is red
velvet and I've actually had this
doughnut before shockingly and Co I love
this donut but I know you guys aren't
really the biggest red fans I'm a fan of
red velvet I'm just not a fan of um
cream cheese what cream cheese frosting
that's cream cheese not not get this
away from me it's cream cheese icing it
doesn't taste like cream cheese isn't
that chocolate it's nope it's not this
is red velvet with cream cheese yeah but
isn't red velvet just chocolate frosting
I don't know isn't red velvet just
chocolate that's a question for [ __ ]
a baker I'm not I'm a consumer so I'm
just going to eat let's go hold on
Google it wait just eat it dude
no get after it Coco that's it they're
not oh my God this is traumatizing I
love these eat it
dude what are you doing I don't like it
it's really good it's better than
that yes is no what's wrong with it in
your it's just how gross the cream is
too creamy I you don't like creamy cream
what's wrong with the creamy cream that
shit's so gross I'm a fan i e this I I
tank this though on a side e it tastes
like I'm eating 12 different things and
I don't like it at all Nick Hand of
agreement that that's better than that
no thank you next you use my own system
against me the pink sprinkled cake this
dut actually looks fantastic we're going
to give it a try pink iced
cake what's going on it tastes a little
like
cigarettes like I feel like I'm eating a
cigarette no it's it's this one uh-uh
it's this one with pink frosting no it's
not yes that's a cherry Nick nothing
changes about the [ __ ]
dut it's the thank you idiot this is
Cherry the glaze that's glazing me
cherry this is not that did you not say
that you said oh that's that but with
the pink frosting you need to go to the
[ __ ] ear what you need to go get away
from me um worst one I agree what I
can't even eat it it's like [ __ ]
falling apart on me like I'm like you
are like but look at how clean mine and
M stations are compared to yours yeah
this isn't a cleanse battle it's a donut
review I didn't say it was a cleanse
battle but you're the one complaining
about cleanliness and you're making a
mess get me a good donut I promise you
won't see a little piece of it thank you
yeah all right this is still better than
both of the ones that are there or no
worse than what you shocked it's better
it's worse actually I put it in the
middle it's better it was just more a
task we're putting here no you're as
long as me and you agree this can look
exactly how we want so I'm just going to
do a karate move stop stop stop don't
don't leave it alone that was a really
interesting noise
yeah like I thought a falcon was going
to come well I pictured both headless
afterwards you're insane your hair was
coming through the Hat all right guys
[ __ ] off don't nudge me I'm not nudging
you something this like you're cool Z
I'm the big donut eater you're in my
zone I'm I'm going to eat a next another
one the next one we're going to eat is
the maple cake I love Maple Maple ice
give me this
one I'm so excited stop if you were
donut what would you be I don't Chris
that's the stupid question every time
you ask play these games I'd be I don't
know no I'd be CL I'd be glazed I'd be
glazed I'd be like classic I just
combined Chris and glaze that was funny
oh it smells like Vermont ready oh it
smells like
goodness
what just a
bur number
one what no no no give us a
minute dude you're a [ __ ] idiot n
number I like this one and this is this
first yeah it is y'all are sick and this
is going e no it was definitely better
than this [ __ ] crumbly mess wrong no
come on yeah you're wrong come on hand
of agreement for the how it is right now
yeah yeah yeah yeah all right next we
need to get another guest so that I can
have a partner in Hand of agreeing the
chocolate oh my God wait why did I get
nervous when I saw it the chocolate long
john look it's
like no no get
away I don't like that name the long
all right hold
on
when not happening they're all in the
right spot now no it's not happening I
just wanted to prank you and Matt
wouldn't even let me what the [ __ ] is
this it's the chocolate long john can
you stop asking what's coming when I
tell you that it's called the chocolate
long joh all right guys let's see how
much of this long john we can finish
okay ready I bet I could do the whole
thing okay let's go
I hate
it last no I got to agree with Chris
this
time it's such an overbearing amount of
chocolate I just not a chocolate guy so
the chocolate why I do all that I atat
too much yeah I saw you tank that you
want to know what it is for me what when
I think you
donut I like the classic M yeah I don't
want a Long John in my throat you know
what I mean like I want I want a circle
yeah yeah I understand
here it's just a donut why are you
holding your water bottle like that I've
never seen feel like that in my
life so thankful praying at the same
time all right don't drink the whole
thing that's mine The Long John is going
worse spot God you're not real all right
guys unfortunately I made a mistake when
get in the donuts and I didn't realize I
got two Maple Donuts but the other one
is a maple long john so it's not the
exact same I'm not eating that we're
going to try it Chris no we got right
here the maple long oh
no no get away from me Long John why do
you look so tall it's maybe how
professional you're saying wait how
would you put that in your pocket how
about you Mr Maple worse than the maple
Don it mm-m yeah that's I'm putting it
no yeah wait is that a little cream just
[ __ ] eat it why is it like a little
doughy okay inspector eat it they just
eat the same it's it's definitely a
little less because hey let's think
about it if we don't like that that much
then this is more of it so technically
we like it less cuz I'd rather eat
less I'm okay with that thought process
cuz I oh you got it what you understood
what I said no I just don't care I want
to put that's where I'd put it no right
there all right okay all right next up
we have Matt's Long
John
why would you ever Supply the internet
with that sentence coming out of your
mouth are you [ __ ] actually
delusional are you [ __ ] mentally
ill get the blueberry iced
cake this one is not cute she's not it
bless you all right look guys it smells
like a blueberry muffin it has like
purple dough it smells like a blueberry
muffin it's like blueberry like juices
what there's no juice in this Chris
we're going to try the donut it's a
blueberry muffin it literally tastes
like a it looks like a blueberry muffin
let's try it but whenever I think of
blueberry stuff I just feel like a
little like I'm in my dollhouse with my
blueberry muff in my dollhous I feel
like violet boa Guard from Willy Wonka
okay see this wouldn't be bad without
the cream there's no cream like the
frost icing Icing I honestly like it me
too it reminds me of a it tastes like a
blueberry muffin a little bite oh you're
right what a blueberry little bite yeah
muffin right no but little bite's
different than a muffin it's a little
bite yeah it's a little bite of a
[ __ ] muffin
idiot what are you talking about
definitely has has different
flavor a Chris you know a little bite
isn't like an actual food like it's
different like it's a the whole point of
it being a little bite is because the
size of it is a little bite of what it
actually is so when I say blueberry
muffin
but I would say oh a little bite but I
would eat a
blue I would eat a blueberry little bite
before I eat a blueberry muffin I'd
honestly say that that's the best one I
ate I agree I'll put it right there get
your [ __ ] donut out of there no I
liked it better than that I agree
completely 100% I'm sorry Matt yep sorry
no cuz for me map's number one mape yeah
are you his friend like are you going to
school it's a donut you can't nickname a
donut it's not your friend that doesn't
have [ __ ] Life Source it's not you're
not calling it I'm not letting you call
the Donut mape that's
crazy all right blueberry no cuz mape is
so much better than blueberry wrong are
you guys serious so Chris do you want to
agree with me that that goes there cuz
that's closer to Maple right how do you
feel about that I think blueberry is
better than that red one what do you
think Chris if you guys oh my God it
come Downs to me hand of agreement with
the order right now can I negotiate no
you can [ __ ] move that there or move
that there and that's your all what
about this order like this
Matt oh I actually kind of agree with
this as well wait no cuz that is there
this these are both better than the
maple you don't have you're tripping if
you listen you don't have the option
from me and Matt no no no no Nick how do
we feel about that no no that was
definitely okay it I think it should go
like this like that that's this is what
I think W that's completely wrong no hey
get Nick this is good I'm okay with this
Nick I'm okay with this thank you
whatever next got map up
one Ain moving again yes he is next one
is this hold on guys keep your eyes
closed I'll put what it's called on the
screen no you won't you're lazy open and
guess what it is what is
that
wait uh cinnamon flavor this is going to
be great it's apple fritter oh my God
I'm all in this is Chris's favorite type
of thing ever it just looks super scary
wait it has this good it has like this
good smell to it it's it just looks
terrifying it looks like a
meteorite I there's way too many
textures going on
M okay and enough you see it m- there's
a great amount of texture
top yeah let's
go I'll put it there number one all
three of these like red velvet blueberry
and mape are way better I love what
you're calling them mape all three of
these are Leaps and Bounds better than I
just got like a little bit squishy no no
no
there's a little bit a little bit
no are this [ __ ] is my worst
enemy I hate this this this is actually
right there for me no I can't even
believe that you guys are putting that
there man blueberry and glazed are and
maple are also better I can't believe
you guys think blueberry is better than
mape I actually can't believe that no
Maple Chris me and Matt what do you like
more Maple or this hold on let me
decipher this real quick if you guys are
going to the store are you getting
blueberry over mape yeah we have a
cinnamon roll that's not oh no cuz I'm
flying
saucer that's not a donut this is a
cinnamon roll all right ready all right
cinnamon roll in one two what happened
there no leave it leave it leave it no
no no no what's no was
not I'm sorry sorry not happening Chris
ever and you know me number one where do
you want
it
I was about to say I think it's oh I
think it's unfair to eat a cinnamon roll
against these Donuts cuz it's a better
dessert it's just number one yeah it is
put it there next one I don't know what
it's called I mean I don't know what it
tastes like but it's called the bear
claw and this is what it looks like oh
my God looks like a it looks like looks
like a vintage baseball Mt yeah it
does it looks like a bear
claw Nick stop being a weirdo sit down
okay all right be
claw oh my
God
sometimes silence is louder than when
can say a picture is worth a thousand
words
yeah next one I'm not excited to argue
with Chris about its placement oh God
cuz he's going to want it don't don't
tell me it's like he's going to want it
in first place oh [ __ ] you caught me
he's going to want it in first place
what's going on here yeah move that over
thank you when did you do that Maple
iced with Cho's on oh my God it's like
Christmas
Maple ice stop Maple ice with Churros on
top I didn't realize how much maple I
was
getting the CH is worse than the
maple no man it's not worse than this
apple fritter in fact I'm eating both of
these over this fritter you're losing
your mind losing your [ __ ] mind get
checked out buddy you're losing this is
not good you're not good I'd actually
rather put it here the apple fritter the
the apple fritter i' put dead [ __ ]
last except for that bear paw but your
opinion is mid it's wrong get
out right in front of our [ __ ] eyes
too what do you think you're going to
get away with everything s'mores donut I
love s'mores I do too take a look I want
some more oh no that does look good but
like there's no Gram I'm going to hate
it no there's gram crank there's gram
cranker gr crer there gram crackle gram
crackle [ __ ] God my least favorite
thing ever is when people claim
marshmallow itself as a dessert like can
you [ __ ] off set
go yeah last place yeah really really I
hate it I'm not eating this ever again
okay no no no no oh no yeah one yeah
here I just don't like marshmallows like
this unless it's in my Hut cocoa and I
don't like Hut cocoa all right
dude before we wrap up this video we're
going to get a dut expert to come share
his opinion on this you can have my seat
wa which one is the best this is the
best it's a cinnamon roll and that's
that's not even aut that's the wor
that's what I'm saying and what is that
a bear ball oh what yeah it was
awful that one's blueberry that one's I
I had that one earlier Maple yeah you
like it yeah it's great it like how much
do you like it like probably up here oh
yeah let's go I was for that the whole
time are you kidding I'm not even going
to lie I wish that you were here the
whole time I had one I had one earlier
and it was great you these earlier I
don't even know what that is try try
whichever ones you want all right hold
on that's the cinnamon roll it's good as
[ __ ] no it's good but like it's not a
donut that's what I said right it's it's
not even on the list no stop don't throw
away not even Don and that that that
really [ __ ] hurt no I'm not going to
like this do you like apple no there's
Apple inside try it it's so a little
bite little bite it's going to have to
be a little
bite no I can't even eat this oh oh
that's a big bite that's a big bu I
can't even eat this to take a bite oh
God it's we don't like that either no B
I kind of like this one like it's so
good we got it we need your opinion on
on the Maple in that big time I need a
drink that's something I need is a
drink dude dromen these things
down I actually really like that
one not more try it try than compare
compare hold
on God come on come on I literally
nickname this kid mape it's my favorite
and I literally it's my child I need you
to like this one no I know I like it all
right we got to see if it's more than
this little
red
nice he was whispering nice in my ear
it's
weird which one was more of the pleasant
experience be honest be open be
honest it might not like my oh my God I
think that this one is the best one you
guys are [ __ ] it's just like it just
brings more to the table thank you all
right well you had a whole one of those
earlier just keep that in mind I did but
I didn't you eat would you eat a full
but I didn't finish it would you eat a
full one of those yeah guys that's been
us trying these Donuts not sponsored but
shout out ry's these are all from ry's
Donuts so shout out see you guys next
Friday for a Friday video peace and love
thank you Don that expert yes I got
thank you needed it