introducing
[Music]
me and then what you saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
that we did we said we going to travel
from the island to Madrid we had a lot
of plans but they
all why oh because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
I'm going to chug this as fast as I can
and see if I I can't really tell okay
you're doing your best that's what all
that matters all right guys today is
officially the [ __ ] day if
you're asking what day it is it's
[ __ ] Halloween I probably shouldn't
swear that much cuz I don't want to get
the video demonetized we are back in
Boston Yahoo yippe in the spirit of
Halloween even though Halloween is over
we are going to be reacting to some of
your guys Halloween costumes this year
as we're going to be as brutally honest
as as we want to be guys this is also
like when you guys submit something like
your [ __ ] snail or your pet or like a
costume or something you're fully
opening to like okay if I get roasted
it's all for humor they still love me
and appreciate me but you know what I
mean moving on to the roasting I have
collectively brought got some of you
guys I asked you guys to uh first things
first whose costume out of us three do
you think is the best seen it before
heard it before zero I think yours is
the best and then I got like you know I
think yours the best I like Pikachu a
lot I have collected all of the photos
and I put them in a h folder on my phone
called weenies cuz of Halloween Nick
like dude if you if I found a [ __ ]
photo album on your phone called weenies
I'd be really concerned I fully agree
just people's Halloween costumes anyways
we should all say what we want to see
what I I'll tell you what I don't want
to see I'm sick and tired of the [ __ ]
I don't know I don't know what I'm sick
and tired of I'm sick and tired tired of
everything Mario Luigi boring don't say
that it's boring it's classic done a
million times classic and the Mario
movie literally came out this year it's
a perfect time to be it what's this big
spill what happened to you I don't see
anything big spill [ __ ] one drop
1 2 3 4 five six drops um I I I I
I sound like [ __ ] the introducing
SpongeBob in a second I hate the like
the seen it done it before type of
costume good elaborate group costumes
with a couple of buddies well you're in
luck cuz the first one I'm going to show
you is exactly check in your box okay so
this girl submitted a photo of her guy
friends and her and her girlfriends and
then a photo of all of them together
okay so the guys are Alvin Simon oh I
love it y the girls of the chipet yes
and then group photo of everything wow
they killed it like they actually you
guys I really like Alvin's pose in the
third one you see it no yeah he's like
he's like this like means business like
Ser i l got like two seconds of that no
you guys look really cool like I I'd
want to be friends with these people I
agree like I want to go hang out with
you guys and be in your costume gles I
want to be I want to
be Dan with the [ __ ] the bald guy
with the glasses in the earpiece that's
what I want to be I think the chipet is
an underrated costume mat oh I didn't
even know was called the chips Nick I
didn't either that's brand new
information to me you don't know that
the chip ATS the chip ATS I had no idea
that they were the chip hat it sounds
like you're trying to say chip like
something
else what does that sound just like it
sounds like something I want to say
chipet yeah it sounds like something I
like something oh Chee it not Che it
chipet it's so close to something um not
[ __ ] it's not [ __ ] it what is it
bucket it's not bucket chipet chip Cadet
no it's not Cadet CH fet it might be
Chez it all right we got a minion oh I
love
it it looks I can't believe how small
the legs are cuz it's a real leg that's
so [ __ ] funny I really like the
inflatable costumes but you really can't
do much on like like are you going to
really have that on the whole night it's
hard to tell come on like it's too
unrealistic to me like I like costumes
where you can still kind of see it's the
person I don't like when it's like
you're basically just like your bag of
it has to no no it has to it always has
to be your your kind of twist on it you
got to grab it choke it twist it you
can't just wao no like I I would like a
yellow shirt overalls and like goggles I
think that's a cooler minion than like
the air full minion I remember going out
trick-or-treating and some kid was one
of those and he stopped every 20 minutes
and had like one of those sleeping like
the air mattress things air mattress
pump up repumping fck no I also if I had
that I would need an oxygen tank I'd be
so nervous I couldn't breathe I need I
need like a tu of air I I love the
costume where your candy sack is
included oh like the bank robber and
they get like oh it's so clever it's so
good I just love it like if you're if
you're if you can include your your
candy sack in the costume it's awesome
automatic like you're a pirate and
that's like your bag of loot your booty
yeah your booty I love it some girl sent
the whole godamn crew I was like let's
see your costume and someone submits
this holy [ __ ] I whole S I don't even
know what I'm looking at hpe down can't
recognize one of you guys this girl is
just wearing all black girl all red all
black all red you all just went on a
night out for Halloween all their
costumes what's going on but no hate but
it's like I we asked for costumes here
the only thing I see is a witch hat yeah
and she probably had the most fun no
this girl her dress is the most like
like character can I see it like she's
dressed like a character oh she's like
yeah like mermaid or something no no no
no not a mermaid I don't know y'all just
didn't have that much fun in my opinion
yeah where's the costumes where's the
fun where's the having a blast correct
y'all must have when is like the girls
night out or something I don't
know they dress up as the girls night
out that's really good joke all right I
love that someone literally just sent
this what the f that's actually
terrifying especially like you're in a
dark room alone yeah it's actually
really scary yeah this person I'm
terrified of you I love [ __ ] like that
though this [ __ ] dressed up as
the mall Easter runny yeah no I love
that I can't lie I love when you dress
up as other holidays on Halloween yeah
it's kind of funny what the
[ __ ] oh my God it's a giant rubber
chicken I love it okay I can I can get
down with that little love it how do you
do anything in that see yet again it's
like super obstructing but I would it's
awesome it's good it's cool it's really
cool I like it a lot even are you a
rubber chicken it's a chicken that makes
the noise I what is that it's a rubber
chicken n it's a [ __ ] rubber chicken
you stupid [ __ ] yeah I don't a
bugs my gum landed on me I didn't get it
out the window I don't know what your
question is you're like what is that and
it's obviously an inflated I want to
dress up as you for Halloween
okay I just want to be Matt I want a
nice cute little shirt and some nice
pants and some boots what are you
looking at I'm going to cut my hair a
little bit and I'm going to say I'm Matt
look at
me that's what I'm going to do y next
I'm going to eat all your favorite foods
I thought this one was I'm going to
sleep in your room okay I'll be matte
for Halloween soldja boy pretty hardcore
no joke definitely turned my swag on and
sent this photo of her and her friend I
don't know what your friend supposed to
be but you look great her friend's like
a motorcycle girl boring I like the
Double Cup too she really pulled up with
so I like the it's the backy pants the
glowy the glow necklace no I really
think she put that [ __ ] on you look fun
be around too I agree like I'd see this
person dressed up a soier boy I'd be I'd
be you I would walk over and like crank
it in your you'd be someone I'd be
intimidated to go up to no not me really
yeah cuz she looks really cool like you
just look like I agree Chris that's like
the first thing I'm going to do a lot of
Soldier Boys actually I love I like it I
really like the soldja boy costumes I
really do what does he say kiss me
through the phone is that him yeah
that's a good song all right this person
said a very last minute Minnie Mouse
costume I can tell it's last minute that
that's so rude not girl you just went to
Disneyland like this the average
Disneyland day how else are you going to
do it though is she going to put the
whole Minnie Mouse suit on well like
this is an average
Disneyland if you had to dress up as
Minnie Mouse what are you going to do I
wouldn't I wouldn't you dress up as
Mickey Mouse you big what would you do
he listen shut up Nick I wouldn't if you
were I don't where what Matt go here's
my thing you put a hat on called
yourself Pikachu oh yeah and you can
tell this is last minute as well all I'm
saying is I didn't say say it's bad I
didn't say mine was good either I didn't
tell I didn't say it's bad I just said I
could tell my thought process is more
just like this is the average I'm going
to Disneyland fit for not cuz she put
the face on too the but nose the one
black little nose that's not I would
nobody does that to go to Disney oh
you dude hardcore there's some people
there people that actually makes me
nervous we should go to Disney and get
like I'm with my fam or like triplet
triplets at Disney triplet day triplet
day did you know if you go to Disney if
you go to Disney to dressed up as a
character they can kick you out cuz
little kids could go up to you thinking
you're the real character and like you
they can't I can totally see why that's
a problem exctly that makes perfect
sense this isn't mine but my dad W your
dad killed it fle I thought your dad was
literally Nicholas Cage for like a solid
2 minutes when I saw it looks like he's
photoshopped Nicholas Cage do you know
what he looks like Nicholas Cage the
actor it looks nothing like that they
have the same
face
wow you're Absol are you guys crazy Nick
you're crazy looks nothing like Ben
Franklin are you guys crazy like the
front of a dollar bill well obviously
he's dressed up as like a pilgrim George
Washington whatever but he looks like
facially all right Nick skip this that
you're terrible you're so annoying
that's actually the worst thing I've
ever heard I would hate when kids would
just throw a mask on in like a hood and
be tough I'm a little if I mean if I'm
an adult I'm giving it candy to little
kids on Halloween if the kid if it's
like a teenage boy and he like didn't
try and he's just putting a mask on and
taking candy it's like bro go get a job
and buy candy on your
own even if it's he's like like 13 no no
that's a little anyone over like like if
you're 18 if you're over like 17 18 and
you're trick or get away from my house
all right King Grist from the troll
movie who the [ __ ] is King Grist I don't
know but they were she killed it I don't
absolutely killed it I don't know who
King who is it Grist I don't know who
that is but she she killed it cuz I can
I get I got a really good understanding
I love the cape I love the green I like
I like that you gave us you with no face
paint on she did yeah and with face
paint on what if she didn't paint her
face and she's like is becoming the
costume like I don't think that's write
this down it's a movie concept made by
Chris stolo it exists it's not going
anywh it exists for sure everyone
dresses up for Halloween that's
literally the plot Halloween Town yes
yes yes yes CU I'm not done oh yes it is
I'm not done Nick it happens Halloween
Town two or three done stupid idiot [ __ ]
you I think I think she just painted her
face scen yeah I think paint to
be yeah yeah y'all have no spirit I also
like that the costume is literally like
a shirt that doesn't fit I like her
socks what about the slippers are those
slippers they're flipflops I think
that's part of the meme you're a meme
Matt it's not a meme it's a costume
respect it I love it wa it's Grimace
Nick I love it are they small is it a
kid who is that um it's something they
little it looks like a four2 Grimace
yeah literally four two is treadmill
yeah 42 what is going on 42 is generous
you look 3 feet tall no that's like a
crumb that's a little crumb that person
literally looks like the gyv Happy Meal
like that's what you get I like that
they're going like that though oh my God
I'm sick to my stomach dude I I feel bad
your dog is clearly blind in one
eye you're evil eyes are I'm laughing
cuz I you guys are evil people I can't
do this I'm laughing at the fact that
you sent a photo of the dog and then
also felt the need to send a photo of
the dog like choking like I feel ter
Nick that looks like a cough or a hack
or a throw up I wouldn't be surprised if
2 seconds after this throw up hit the
carpet you're evil Nick no no I think
that they took advantage of the dog's
age and dressed them no your dog's so
cute she's really cute and pretty and I
hope that she's having a good Halloween
oh my God we should have just been each
other one year I like it I love it I do
love it too you guys look alike you got
like I like that you all got like a
different hairstyle going and you're not
wearing the same black fit like like the
shoes and like the tights and the canes
and the glasses and the ears match but
like you're you're like picking your own
style like this is a great way to bring
yourself into a costume I think a little
face paint like three lines to really
like a pink nose but you're asking for
too much I feel no a pink nose would
have been great a little pink then like
they can like take the sunglasses off in
the in the ears and they leave no but
they did great y all slayed down
absolutely Victorious reference Tory
Vega officer peso love it I really enjoy
costume I thoroughly enjoy this costume
it's a really good one really good one
well that's like the type of costus is
just awesome it's a great show well
that's also the type of Cosmo I'm saying
I love like you really did your like you
had a thought that's that's also a great
episode of Victoria I agree I just like
that versus like something boring like
thing one thing two oh my [ __ ] Mario and
Luigi like it's boring as [ __ ] Thing One
and Thing Two is the worst if you were
thing one and thing too then you need to
[ __ ] go away and shoe made a rhyme Dr
Seuss okay buddy did you like it yeah
keep your day job buddy it was not that
good [ __ ] you Nick okay this person's
dress up as
me you got the hair right what they got
the hair right they did really good what
is this pose have I done that maybe
something I'd see you do for sure this
person sent a
video what is there someone else in that
it's the one person what the
[ __ ] do they sell this or did she make
it they got to sell it you're a balloon
dog that's actually the craziest costume
ever wait how they how could they see I
don't understand that's actually absurd
no yeah that's like a little like that's
actually can't do [ __ ] in that costume
you can't trick or treat you can't party
you can't take photos that are good like
you can't do anything nothing literally
the whole point of Halloween for me
would be ruined if I was obstructed in
that you purchased an inconvenience
that's what you like you literally
bought [ __ ] nothing all right this
person did this one oh my [ __ ] Christ
oh wow I feel like in order to dress up
like this like no hate to you at all no
hate at all I think that
you're what are you going to say Nick
all I'm going to say is like if you
dress up like this you got to also make
sure your breath stink like this girl's
like the character's breath stinks like
I feel like your breath got to also
stink Nick don't say weird [ __ ] disagree
you know what I mean like in order to be
dressed like this monster your breath
better be stanking like put it all I've
never understood when like really little
kids want to be something insanely
absurdly creepy like
yo like a monster ID doll or something
if my kid was like four like I want to
be like a bloody killer with like blood
and knives I'd literally be like holy
[ __ ] get away from me yeah that's
terrifying I'd be really scared if I
always thought just something fun and
not like that like when I see a little
kid like under 10 well that was
definitely a teenage girl so I'm aware
Matt oh okay what do you think I thought
it was the real [ __ ] zombie [ __ ] the
real ghost goblin tby a Teletubby just
walk by us happy Halloween that's a
Teletubby right I think so the red one
that's how it's crazy what's his name
Bobo
Bubba I don't know what they're called
we knew like there like some stupid
noises it's
like the teletub names are legit like
onam on a p it's like P pom bum bum dude
you sound like you sound like a baby
what are their name bu bum you literally
sound like a baby dude it's like popo in
poo Poo's definitely po Tet tuby
names Ipsy laa twinky W Tinky Winky and
no no and no no no no and Sunbaby Sun
babyn Sun La wait Tinky Winky is a real
Tu Teletubby is it t chubby is it wait I
don't know the name of the red one tiny
winky what the [ __ ] po po that was po
that just walked by po po Dipsy laa
twinky
winky say laala say it again laala laa
la la twinky minky is scary [ __ ] dude
yeah I don't understand the teletub he
still twinky linky la la makaka my God
they low key look like who's like from
Horton hair aoo Oh I thought it was from
[ __ ] I thought it was from De
Grassi I think mattt would be Tinky
Winky Tinky Winky don't say
thaty I'd be Dipsy for sure Nick you'd
be Sunbaby Nick you'd be Sunbaby Nick
Nick said this the same hair as Sunbaby
Nick could be smelly Sunbaby is crazy is
that an actual character in the show
Sunbaby this is Nick I think if I
watched one episode of solies I'd be
really scared like bad all right this is
someone in in their best friend's
costume oh my God it's me that's
actually funny oh yeah they kind of
killed that you guys did it top to
bottom yep yeah they killed that yes we
got The Lorax hold on oh they're on
their knees were like an oare air ohir
oh killed it I love these costumes I
love a good group
costume I love the colors is that a
shark no it's just here where Oh I
thought we were like looking for an
actual
shark where's his head he's right there
oh where it's his head what oh my God I
thought it was the long way no his chin
is blooding what are you saying chin I
didn't know he was sitting up I was
looking for the dog's head I had no
[ __ ] clue where he was blending in
with the the the cabinet I thought it
was the [ __ ] headless horse I was
like who the [ __ ] is that I don't think
his head is blending into anything that
just looks like I do a
thing oh God I want to be like Mike for
Halloween you're nothing like
Mike that's not good I hate you Matt
you're nothing like Mike at all oh
that's a really cool concept of a movie
that was a really good joke Matt made a
good joke oh my God bring out the
[ __ ] cookies and start the parade I
want po twinky Winky and laa at the
front of
it we have PO on the float with sun when
sun when sun baby's in the sky that's
when the parade will start for mat's
annual onee joke everybody
yipp Welcome to the YouTube channel I
hate Sunbaby so much yeah [ __ ] little
[ __ ] dude I just want to kick him in
the teeth I I pr imagine every day the
Sun comes out but it's just a baby
looking what the
[ __ ] awesome where'd you get that Nick I
like Sunset baby that's my favorite when
he goes away yeah when baby goes away
dude sh what's the difference between a
speed hump and a speed bump hump or
longer actually well I feel like it's
more humpy than a bump like a hump is
Humpty Dumpty fall off what what did
Humpty Dumpty fall off a wall the wall
boring it should have rhymed Humpty
Dumpty had a great fall Humpty Dumpty
fell off the brick wall that's wrong no
it's not they didn't specify what kind
of wall yes they did no way the words
brick in that rhyme Nick okay fine we'll
[ __ ] search up the ridd hum Dumpty
sat on a wall Humpty Dumpty had a great
fall it's a brick wall Humpty Dumpty has
a middle name what try to guess it
Robert nope egg nope Shelly nope Shelly
was a great guess thank you chicken nope
chicky nope chicky was a bad guest Nick
Humpty does it rhyme with Humpty and
Dumpty not even close Humpty Herbert
Dumpty no Humpty Cornelius Dumpty no
Humpty Edward Dumpty nope Steven nope is
it like an an OG name or is it like a
like a like a name like OG like
Bartholomew or something it's kind of
old like bethoven Humpty Beethoven
Dumpty no Nick um Benjamin nope great
guys Humpty Humpty Alexander buum
Dumpty I hate it I didn't know look it
he's on a brick wall Nick he may be on a
brick wall but they didn't specify that
in the [ __ ] poem okay oh read the
story Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall Humpty
Dumpty had a great fall all the king's
horses and all the king's men cannot put
Humpty Dumpty together again that's the
rhyme they never said brick
wall you guys are so stupid you really
just love sucking those huh you love
sucking everything get away from me
what got ball in the back of your head
turn
around he's got nuts on the back of head
feel like it's been a while since we
film it I feel like it's been a while
since we've been able to just sit and
talk to you guys and I know we have a
podcast that's more for talking
seriously but I feel like we haven't
really said Thank you in forever like
thank you guys for five almost 5 and 1
half mil road to 6 mil I feel like it's
just been forever since we said that we
appreciate you guys and that we have a
massive following get to do what we do
cuz every single time we're back in
Boston it kind of sets in and feels like
real again so I feel like we've kind of
just like checked into reality and it's
is really wild yeah it that's all I
really have to say but I just appreciate
everyone that watches and supports our
videos cuz we're seriously able to do
this for our life you know what a crazy
word is what gutter do you have anything
positive to say yes I do so grateful for
everyone that supports me and my
brothers
and um you know life's full of up and
downs ups and downs like a rodeo not
please
cornut don't do that Nick that's kind of
weird open real soon you need to stop
doing that weird chill why like the hand
motions actually freaked me out a little
bit it will never end until you put stop
oh my God Nick
stop what you saying how you miss me
yeah you miss me and all the things that
we did we said we going to travel from
the island to Madrid we had a lot of
plans but they
all why because of someid but it's okay
cuz I'm moving different don't be saying
then when I P with other [ __ ] for my
brothers