I can't even read what these are yeah
they're in foreign languages Matt I
think most of this is Japanese hey guys
welcome back to yet another video on St
triplet Channel today we are going to be
trying if you are this video is not
sponsored by door Dash but on door Dash
they have a bunch of like different
grocery stores that like I've never been
to before and one of them had an around
the world section and I was very
intrigued and I was like I want to spend
all my money on this but then I thought
why don't I spend Matt and Chris's money
and then we can make a YouTube video
Once I buy it all so I used their credit
card and now we have a ton of snacks
that we wouldn't usually have and we can
try them and rate them today we've done
a couple videos of these before with
friends and family members so go see
those ones if you don't know what the
[ __ ] we're about to do yeah this one has
vitamin C what's which one's that from
the Sun from the Sun I think no that's
vitamin D vitamin D okay all right all
right they're sour vitamin D sour oh
super sour going to blow your face wait
this actually smells like it's like
grape and it smells good grape smells
really good it doesn't smell like bad
grape though it smells like that good
grape like the stuff you
step hold on love it not sour that's my
first day not sour it's tingling a
little in my throat grape Aid it's
tingling a little inside in your throat
do you feel it going
down I will say definitely not sour not
sour stop I'm getting as much flavor as
I can yeah doesn't no actually I hate
you're doing this but doesn't it feel
like you have to put a lot of effort
into getting that great flavor I feel
like I'm
like I'm wiggling it around I'm tuing it
a bit you like suck the flavor give me
the grap give me the gra I need it let
go my like he laugh regard my tit like
what is
happening give me the gra give me the
gra give me the [ __ ] grape I'm
holding [ __ ] candy aesome give me the
grape
great right now right now since there's
nothing else in are you spitting them
out yeah I knew you would be you [ __ ]
idiot in a glass and a mug you're
washing that we have other cups that you
can use you make my life harder by
spitting up in a mug I just didn't want
to overcome my grape flavor before I
tried to eat didn't want to overcome
anything yeah okay sunkiss sour grape
Aid right now we haven't tried anything
else first place I think it be ear
infection cuz I'm like sucking too hard
you know what I mean is that's a lot of
suck like you got to really put that
work in Melody pops little suies let's
do the little suies I got us each one
they're only a dollar each so if we like
buy a bun of them that's a lot of money
yeah that's a lot the dollar lollipop
wait is it a
whistle that just came out of the sucker
wow
wow that's
good you're
good what is this just like to extend it
so that you can really push it back oh
maybe it's a slide
whistle hold on of course this
[ __ ] maybe it's a slide whistle
first thought that would be the last
thought I
had I'm never eating this a slide
whistle
[Music]
wait one car
[ __ ] we got to
move
there it's like I
slipped oh my God this is [ __ ]
amazing
[Applause]
[ __ ] why is mine not good mine's
L our neighbors are going to shoot and
kill us I think that this is like this
is like a 100 out of 10 on experience
but like a seven on flavor but first
spot on the little suckies okay well no
cuz like if we're judging off flavor
that genuinely beats it okay experience
just know that overall everything we
tried today this is number one for
experience but we going to judge flavor
this is behind that now it's moving into
number two on the bracket for real next
Pocky Pokey Pocky Pocky I think it's
Pocky I've had these before yeah me too
strawberry cream covered have you had
these before no they're really good I
like them me and Nick used to have the
chocolate ones in school I used to get
these the chocolate strawberry mid fun
good experience you want know what it
reminds me of so much and oh my God I
need the fan help to find this what back
in the day if it was on if it was on a
pretzel and not in a Biscuit I'd like it
more no this they used to have I think
it goes in the three spot they used to
have little bread stick Pringle pizza
bites awful so delicious please someone
find those for me please on the internet
all right but these are getting the
three spot I agree mid mid mid mid mid
three spot let's go for the first Bev W
wo I didn't drinks yeah Red Bull but it
looks like a bean can that's like 3 oz
wait it looks just like Red Bull do you
need a cup should we cupy oh wow it
peels look at
this oh I don't know if I like that oh
looks just like Red Bull if this is just
red it looks like y looks Little Red
Bull looks like y it has less
froth what
my good Red
Bull it's Red Bull but it's like sweeter
and less energy wait wait correct no I
think it's a non-carbonated Red Bull yes
it's like flat Red Bull it has no
carbonation but it's Red Bull no I think
it's here I just really like drinks yeah
moving into second place yeah okay next
up better than those yeah flavor wise
flavor no no agree I agree I agree I
like the melody flavor wise I'd rather
drink one of those than eat one of those
Okay Hand of
agreement three spot me beat my own
system freeze dried mini ice cream sand
oh it's astronaut
food well I don't think it's astronaut
food but it's like it's freeze dried
this is what astronauts eat anyways this
is freeze dried ice cream sandwiches
that might make me throw up Oh I thought
that was it ew it's already falling
apart um can even bite
it might as well get a covid test I feel
like I have no taste it feels like just
milk like just snack milk like yeah I
feel like I've had an equivalent
experience eating sand at the beach as a
toddler so fifth position
wonderful it looks like icy flavored
Skittles maybe are they Skittles
popsicles what wait it's not actually
Skittles it's like
pops okay oh it's actually really
delicious this is like flashing me back
to like fourth grade pool party
somewhere where were we near the near
the barbecue restaurant wait yeah hold
on this is a real nostalgic memory whose
birthday was
that I hate oh I love the S I love the
s this is actually really good I'm I'm
I'm saving this this is fantastic yeah
hold on this is number one position all
right yeah Skittle smoothie things
moving into first position agreed hand
of agreement I can get that with that
all right we have these La chips that
are fried chicken
flavor fried chicken flavor La chips
that [ __ ] godamn freeze dried ice
cream whatever like ruined the Vibes
yeah I agree
it made me sad yeah like how do you [ __ ]
up a good ice cream sandwich you made it
worse stop freeze rying
stuff we're not doing this no just I'm
just saying like stop the
GU all right fried chicken flavored Lae
let's do it really delicious it's like a
Savory snack
almost like I'd have this instead of
dinner I like this too I have this of
dinner one are you really Wonka and this
like the [ __ ] gum there there's not
better than that and they're not better
than anything else next to I'm fine with
this six position La barue so these are
La chips as well they're they're Texas
grilled barbecue flavor wo oh it's in
English oh this one has English like
subtitles subtitles essentially on the
bag of chips well leave it to I think
that is L is like bro they make like
ketchup they make like grass fertilizer
flavor like they just do anything ready
let's do it
worse than the others wait why does it
taste like
steak like actually though like it
shouldn't actually taste just like it
it's better it's better than the [ __ ]
ice cream sandwich disaster no I
honestly going eat the whole ice cream
before this you're insane that's weird
no I I just agree
actually seven spot seven okay is this
chocolate Cheetos it's barbecue Cheetos
chocolate where'd you get that I don't
know that was a lot to sniff smells like
hell says guilty meaty meaty what says
meaty it says number one though so maybe
they're like really [ __ ] it does say
number one straight on the bag
where I don't want to eat this I don't
either you have to
though I don't like
it flashback I feel like braing
wait huh not
bad what that feeling Nick where do you
feel got
it Ramen seasoning before you add it to
the
ramen I don't eat a Ramen like that yeah
I kind of agree tastes like the chicken
ramen seasoning before you put it on the
ramen yeah I don't like that on a chip
little better than the freeze dried I
agree eighth position let's do a drink
yeah let's do a drink get these chips
out of my mouth drink these let's do a
drink let's do a little drinky Mountain
Dew blue shock I'm very interested I
like the bottle do charged with
raspberry Citrus flavor oh I love
raspberry oh my God it's like a mini
it's like a it's like a mini Shield mini
Shield up 25 HP oh you can like walk
around now that do
that that [ __ ] drink from
friendly oh my God so
good it tastes like like the fibble no
not the fibble the the soda they that
poton candy sodas at friend it tastes
like that memory of when Matt threw a
fork at the old lady
yes it tastes like when you threw the
fork at the lady oh my God this is
number one for me I just love soda I
just love soda I love soda I love soda
like a blz this is actually like I'm
like so happy right now guys that's
first place that's first place first
place can we agree hand of agreement
this is like Ritz mango peach oh Peach
that's a peach wait if it has cream in
it I'm off I'm off it's going to have
cream in it it's a RIT with the cream
it's like a it's like a peachy ritzy
Oreo wait this is so cute this the
cutest thing I've ever seen in life this
so cute let's give it a try wo yeah that
smell my God oh my goodness I'm getting
a huge wave of like Peach smells like
bubblegum no it smells like
Peach okay no stop going back and forth
let's all get
one not good not bad never want it again
I I think that was delicious it tastes
like a high-u cracker it does hear me
out you guys are going to be like no way
better than these I agree I agree move
it all down yeah for sure all right we
finally got something Ritz peaches
climbing up to well I just really like
Ritz crackers and as a kid I used to
have it with marshmallow fluff Ritz
takes the 1 2 3 4 five six six spot Ritz
in the sixth let's do um these
strawberry Kit Kats okay oh I like I
like that package it's kind of like ther
it's
paper it's like recyclable yeah get me
off a piece of that Kit Kat bar oh it
smells like a strawberry
milk wait this is good it tastes like it
tastes like those uh strawberry Wafers
Grandma used to give us when we were
kids yeah yeah it tastes like strawberry
milk and I like strawberry milk do you
remember the bisqui breakfast meal of
course I do yeah if I was 5 years old
I'd be tanking these toes moving up to
fifth position yeah there we go Matt
pleasure doing business with you
pleasure pleasure what is this ooh this
we got the Sailor Moon So based off the
anime obviously Sailor Moon ocean bomb
sounds good to me oh it sounds delicious
I love drinks saor Moon ocean bomm oh
it's clear wow it has a pink tin it has
a pink tin no it doesn't it's fully
clear that's your eyes that's your eyes
yeah you need to get them I wish it had
a pant um I'm feeling like it could be
like a Sprite Vibe I agree I agree wo
Nick us said he cheated wait what was
that super strong it's sparkling water
yeah I don't like sparkling water it's
good it's like the you'll this will be
your favorite sparkling water for sure
oh I like it I knew it I knew it it's
like kind of like like orangey like
Tanger it's like it's like um acidic
salsa water and I like it Matt you're
very professional you just you just say
that like it's just kind of how do you
not like it you have to keep drinking
tastes like a bad juice um let's go to
sour ninth position Sailor Moon Bevy
yeah okay cereal straw fro Loops I was a
big fan of milk straws when I was a kid
I might barf no should we get go red or
green milky milky I'll do green okay
milky milk I'm going to pour a little
bit of ready
Matt ready you guys go first no get your
face in here I can't you could again
all right let's just do it one at a time
Nick okay you go first you can go first
oh I would eat this alone yeah it adds
that flavor to milk that you just need
not
really no it just takes like it just T
tast like milk coming out of cardboard
see i' buy I'd buy these these alone
very good oh that's Loop stick that's
good I do Wonder know what I do there
cream in these no I would say cream you
wonder know what I would do that's a
little protective coat to make it a
strong like a paste you want know what
I you want to know what I would do
that's a little weird what kind of like
Oreo style this like give it a little
swirl around like a dip and then just
yeah yeah let me do that o dippy di it's
just a waste of milk it's worse than
grabbing a handful of
Cher I'd rather hit the cabin and just
go give me some fruit loops and then go
on my Merry way I age I don't think this
is an experience I ever need yeah I'm
putting it here though oops it is good
it is good I'm put it write right here
it's just too overwhelming like I feel
like okay listen you're right wait no no
no listen listen listen I'm going to
break it down for you I think they try
to overdo that Froot Loop flavor so that
when you suck it up with the milk it
adds the flavor to the milk but it
doesn't do it right so when you just eat
the straw it's so much Froot Loop flavor
because it's trying to compensate for
the milk getting to your mouth yeah I
think 10th place on those okay ninth
place is fine hand of agreement yeah
Peach Diet Coke oh this looks good I
don't like Coke but I like or Peach Coke
no diet wait I don't like the smell kind
of it's giving baby throw up a
little I love it no you don't yeah hold
here yeah I've had this in my
past I said that like a
warrior I think it's awkward like to me
it's just really strange all I'm going
to say I like sodas this is my no this
is like it tast like when they did those
Pepsi fruit things
no no split yeah they did I honestly say
I'm crazy say I'm wild I'm putting it
right here I agree like I'd rather eat
this whole bag of ice cream yeah all
right so it's we got Pepsi
Cen it's it's Coke Peach dude not Pepsi
Coke we yeah Coke peach in 12th position
all right lemonade has that like
lemonade has that I'm supposed to be
sour vibe to it you know what I mean you
got it down it's not pink
oh my God this is insane super good next
one what's next red Sherry Cherry Lime
lemonade delicious oh my God it's got me
one the CH I wanted to spin second place
for me second place I agree call me
crazy second place I agree those were
phenomenal really I'm eating that whole
pack from the video second
place no but I will say similar to the
how you got to choke the grape out of
them I feel like I'm like give me the
lemonade yeah give me the lemonade look
like kind of mini they're so cute
they're pastel oh oh they it they do
they look like Easter they're like super
small little like they look like pearls
oh my God they smell horrible oh they do
smell badell wait it smells like paint
snip it again let me go show them it
smells like paint it smells like paint
let me go show them Nick get over here
dude they're like cute pastel I don't
like
it wait I do like it I like the
red or No the
pink
red wait I I kind of like them but
regular Skittles are better love hate
love hate relationship yeah yeah yeah
yeah awkward snack awkward
n Ninth Place yeah and that was our last
snack everybody Ninth Place
yeah all right so this is our final
placement for everything we hope you
enjoyed watching this week's video these
snacks were really [ __ ] good I agree
I I think none of them were
bad thank you guys so much for watching
this video if you liked this video
there's a like button for you to go
click and when you're down there you're
so close to that big red subscribe
button and if you're next to that click
that red subscribe button and subscribe
to us that you never miss a video we are
on the road to 6 million subscribers
woo I can't believe that I can't wait
for we a car D 25k I know so it just
really it life has been moving quick not
mad about it I am mad that I'm getting
like old like I feel like I'm 20 years
old someone's granddaddy okay but um
yeah thank you guys for being here since
you know the start of it we're going to
be at 6 million soon which is shocking
so subscribe keep your eye out for 6 mil
merch only available at St www. sterol
clothing.com
go check out our merch website we are
going to have new 6 million merch live
the moment that we hit 6 million
hopefully and everyone everywhere else
is fake for that yeah so don't don't go
bu our fake merch stay blessed everybody
tell a friend you love them give them a
hug and have a great night spread
kindness things that we did we said we
going to travel from the island to
Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
all why oh because of some kid it's okay
cuz I'm moving different don't be when I
with [ __ ] my brothers