it is time this is
crazy what that this is on my thing
right now shs boys lacrosse versus
Malden I'm so happy I I scored on our
senior night because if this video is
going to get popular I'm happy I at
least scored a goal yeah sure how is
that a yeah sure moment like no I get it
it's it's so fire like you became a
famous YouTuber and then people found
your your High School lacrosse
games you were serving everything you
giving us magic you were giving us wow
it was it was the full fantasy let's see
the most replayed moment to there's oh
that might be that might be a mat save
Chan 15 okay that might be a mat save
okay oh that's a mat safe a
mat I didn't even know I was that good
okay you I wasn't that I wasn't that
good at all but that was a good you were
ass okay but Nick look at how look at
how fast this ball gets shot here to
bring
you I'm eyeing that down and I'm
catching it
good good save guys the lore behind me
being goalie is just like too much to
get into right now I just didn't like
running I guess I'll Su it up like that
fat but that's a good that's a good save
okay where's your come on play it dude
what me yes cuz you pass it to Matt Matt
passes it to me and I score that's what
goes down yeah you got the double assist
I believe did I get the assist for this
let's see yeah pass to Chris chis Jes oh
my God drives back loads up takes a shot
and scores wait are we him yeah that was
a was a Duo I have an assist for that I
didn't even know I had that and the
craziest part about all of this and I
didn't know anything about myself and I
was going through a severe identity
crisis and thought that I liked a girl
but I didn't I was in the closet not at
this point oh yeah really sure really
sure yeah no you were I knew you were
gay while I was playing wait wait who's
that in the back who that in the back
LeBron James if somebody makes a LeBron
edit and that's the intro I would lose
my I'm praying to God they do I
really wanted to do I really want to do
a death drop on Matt's bed but I'm
afraid that it'll break in half and I
don't want to deal with Matt complaining
forever yeah it would break you can do
it though it's already broken do you
think if I did a death wait can we try
to break your bed when am I going to
have time
to what Chris out of context that's
probably top five crazy can I do it Matt
do I have permission I'm not gonna stop
where sleep you break his bed for where
is he gonna sleep are you gonna buy him
a new bed like tomorrow no I'm always
goingon to be a queen this is a full
this is a queen it is yeah all right can
I do it come on Queen come on Queen I
love that Matt sleeps in a queen bad
like it's just giving us I want to see
you jump into the you
got you
can't did that hurt that was so fun I
feel like I F Go Do It Go Do It N Go
on I'm not do it come
on what we're going to do some reacting
today it's probably going to make me
feel sick to my stomach um but yeah
we're super excited to do it it's all I
ever
wanted sit down sometimes when I sing
I'm just like wow I could become the
most talented and hot musician to ever
walk or Grace the planet who's telling
you that but I can't I just can't let
these other people like be outshined by
me the moment I try so that's
why I keep it chill that's good it's
good that you keep it chill you're
welcome everybody you're welcome
everybody cuz I know the competition
would be too stiff if I tried
it you ain't making nobody Stiff get out
of here which which count Nick of course
the pink and green first did
[Music]
you
C this is the worst thing I've ever seen
life oh my God immediately my favorite
one has has to be # selfie really mine's
the flick mine's the flick SC see you
get iconic iconic piece of
art what song is that been waiting no
it's not for a day like this to come sh
by it's it's it's it's I
wish snapping is and in my way okay wow
that's I loved that song Let's see the
comments oh comments turned off Nick
what were you doing thank God I'm going
to kill you first let me that's a funny
that's a funny moment that's a good one
Chris you so cute wow I wasn't even I'm
happy I had fun as a kid and I wasn't
like rotting my brain away doing like
stupid like the fact that this
channel has 76,000 subscribers would
make child version of me my
pants no seriously iconic of them all is
the Dark Horse music video no it's not
it's webcam from February Valentine's
Day that was like 3 days ago I just got
actual W this was exactly 11 years ago
11 years ago I just got littleit
goosebumps that's actually SI
you rock the cut # Supercuts all the way
the the alternate switch to the other
hand p is like oh my God guys wait let's
analyze this this bedroom this
dresser had all of our clothes in it
remember that we didn't have separate
clothes yeah do you remember I I don't
like it I remember that that wicker
basket up top had all of our underwear
in it y socks and underwear and then
Chris's friend in fourth grade made him
this drawing and it's him ninja n yes Y
and then that's Brad Marshon right there
it is yeah I love this video so cute W
the Dark Horse music video wait what is
no homework twice two times how I feel
right after my teacher assigns me
homework
[Music]
how I feel right after my teacher
assigns me
homework oh my God The Walking Dead new
tonight is that relatable to you still
Nick or no it is like when you're like
oh I have homework I'm going to blow up
I'm going to blow this building up
that's Lally my thought process no I get
it though is I was like damn I have
homework I hope that this building
it's just
funny it's just funny cuz I know Dad was
rewi you made him rewind it and you like
that's good content great content that's
exactly how I feel when I get homework
yeah you saw that the the thought was
like wait when I have homework that's
what I need to
happen yeah the first video well let's
go back and check out the regular noew
this was a this was a when your teacher
tells you you have no homework this is
just you have no homework you have no
homework that was good
good when the teacher tells you have no
homework it's like you have no homework
it's like had a visual of that what do
you mean it's like when they throw the
towel on the head in Vine to like girls
this was like you you were ahead of the
time yeah it was a really quick seamless
swap also love the living room color of
GRE house house pre-fire really makes me
emotional so so devastating um oh my God
the kitchen that's enough and look
everyone comes out we're all so hyped
that we have oh God I'm in this hey oh
my God everyone's in this
yeah the the crunchy audio is
unbelievable I wow listen to these
little kid
Giggles
P oh my God no this one's really bad
this is really bad video star video star
like
Prime pause it pause it no no no no
no please I can't
heit Nick look at Nick that's a profile
picture low key dude I think floss was
your biggest enemy in this you need no
it was his it was his best friend no he
need he wasn't even flossing with floss
he got a rope from Home Depot literally
literally that you can literally have a
bungee cord I
can it looks like you have three front
teeth watch out watch out it looks
everything right there it does what the
front teeth Nick literally those
are look I can't even tell if that's a
front tooth or if that's a front tooth
which one look at how handsome you came
out to be now pick a door any
[Music]
door what are you looking at me for Matt
I just want to know your
opinion I don't I don't get that clip
like what yeah like what's going on
you're just so like I had a joner I had
a jean boner yeah and I had
[Music]
to let's get more unique with with the
clips oh you looked really good then I
really have no clue what happened to you
are you dead ass you went down you
looked way better then than you what's
going on that was like last year no but
the like the earrings the earrings are
prime the haircut is prime the haircut
was fire your hair looked better I think
it was also the summer so you had like a
nice like you didn't look hibernating
inside for years I always feel like I
look horrible when it's not yeah you got
to get back to this no but got out
that's rude you got to get out in the
side and it's realistic it's not and
it's realistic because I literally saw a
Tik Tok and I already showed you when I
was in Hawaii hot this did
oh this actually this video is the most
emotional video I don't think I can
watch this one no this one makes me want
to explode oh my God guys I seriously
can't watch this one I'm RI low key I
got
back your back I got to start in the gym
look at that I got like low like I had
like look dude dude Matt Still hits this
move all the time fix his hair like this
and rais his eyebrows and goes like that
like that look look
it the hairline is
look at that
face you're so precious Matt hits those
emotes to this day to this day Matt hits
those emotes oh I can't
chub bunny challeng I'll go
first good tactic look at Nick's like
practicing
already
good dude Nick grabbed his dick cuz he's
pissing himself I used to PE my pants no
we used to always I used to constantly
piss my pants same like anytime we'd
make each other laugh it was just like
everybody's pissing it's not good
[Music]
I wish I found simple things as
funny dude look at Mt chubby bunny
[Laughter]
oh my God this is I still hit that
too oh my God I don't think anything can
make me more emotional than just the
concept of time itself
wow I'm dead I'm dead serious I'm dead
serious wow man dude look at your you're
I was I need to get back to the gym dude
oh my God look at your jugular did you
see yeah cuz Nick throwing
I'm pissing myself I I did the leg cross
said I'm out who said that me yeah look
at
that you look like the kid of that book
no David no oh yeah dude that camo is
fire on your pants yeah Chubby
Bunny chubby bun I got you want to see
me do three like ready to go wow and
Chris is like Chris is like oh CED he
knows he's cooked
that's
two
look Nick flies in out of nowhere Matt
you're falling apart now yeah but you
have four in your mouth you're cooked I
won oh my God
cry oh my God
[Laughter]
oh my
[Applause]
God holy
it's
truthfully dude it is truthfully my hair
that does it for me I have like the most
chopped Mohawk go back 5 Seconds no I
already did just watch do man oh my
[Laughter]
god dude ho what say is I know that
there's an action shot coming so I grabb
the camera I'm going to throw look at
you look at you you you literally are
foaming at the
mouth suck oh my God the bathroom listen
to Chris go back he said that
sucks I said I'm the winner and I
want that's it that's that's it that's
our new outro that's it I'm actually
down we got to rep that oh that's so
funny that's it it's cuz it
wasn't styled that was like at night
like every every morning I like spiked
that up that was this was like a
this was like a so unique and so I had a
mohawk literally sixth grade you're you
just such
Mohawk such like a mohawk I just I
played guitar and had a Mohawk
when I was you just the coolest fifth
grade sixth grade and like seventh grade
my God you are so cool
yeah is you instantly laughing and US
using well I was just like I was just
like I was scared that I was going to
piss him off more than I was going to
back to back videos where I'm wearing a
Batman
shirt you just got sh the cre to the
face
oh that's worse than the Matt Nick slap
incident that was I scraped it
offing to the
face got shaving cre to the face said no
you did I need to just appreciate
One Moment In this video look at how
small I
am like I was half di in the
door now I'm like at the top of a
doorway look it I was right here on this
door fights back he fights back yes he
does thank you
narrator it's in your eyes you're like
no where the hell is the
sink that's so good good content good
content what are you writing down at a
friend's house
I'm here with the St
[Applause]
[Music]
tripl I don't know if you were trying to
give me a hug I was I was okay I just
like got to be in the part of the group
we're like we're super tripl right now
like super Tri all huged up I was so
scared that was funny I love
quen this was top three Sero triplet
collab I want to film with quenlin again
quen invite me to your house I want to
come film with you again it was like the
best day of my life wait hold on we're
still going on the edit I don't get
this worst audio ever declared now worst
audio on on internet time ever no
there's worst
[Music]
ones no nobody say a word nobody say a
word go ahead and log out for me nobody
say a
word you were sliding we to run it back
sliding we have to run the studio back
I'm not running it
back
why I would go but I don't have the
talent to rap on beat and I wish I did
but I'm never going to attempt to do
that I wouldn't I wouldn't do it well
you have to do it one day I'm never
TR I'm never doing that oh I cannot
believe that that video right there of
Justin was celebrating 10,000
subscribers it felt like we had a
million at that point already I thought
it was like him oh my God no cuz I
remember in Vlog number seven we
literally were like are we going to be
YouTubers full time and we were like
genuinely questioning it hoping it that
it would happen Vlog number seven down
yeah right there oh my God yes we rolled
the dice we rolled the dice
oh my God we weren't even Stern Lo do we
didn't even have five out of five steps
completed to create the account wow 10
following 10 I don't know who was a part
of that 10 yeah I don't know 777
followers and one post what a relic dude
that's a
relic oh those those shorts do not fit
my body by the way in this moment no
oh my god look what just look at me hey
at least youve always been balding a
little bit in that Mo in like that mode
kind of like your hair your hair has
always been like that that comb over
when you get that you kind of get that
Hut spot sometimes you know what I'm
talking about at least we know you've
always had it leave him Al my ass looks
huge it's a little the shorts it doesn't
look like it actually is hatched to my
body my ass looks
gigantic like that's kind of insane I'm
kind of Caked Up I wanted to squish
really bad I don't s a single one and I
wanted I just want one I don't want to
be like those
crazy see can you pause this I wish I
was more filled with freedom cuz the
thing is at this point in our career I
felt so pushed to say whatever I was
thinking talking about oh if you have
crazy this this this but now there's so
many eyes on us all at once that I have
to limit what I say because if I say
something like I used to say and I'm so
blot like I am I'm going to accidentally
Target somebody and then they're going
to make a Tik Tok next JY Olo hates me
and it's not true I just be like I'm
suppressing myself cuz I don't want to
cuz if that clip was posted in a
YouTube video nowadays I own a bunch of
Squish mows Nick hates me but it's like
that it's just my opinion it's a
joke it's a joke so it's like I need to
less I need to be less fearful when it
comes to joking we had to all let loose
no seriously
motivating it's motivating it's
motivating hwk why so
serious it it really is though like
motivating TR we used to literally say
anything on our mind Vlog anywhere and
let it roam free but nowadays we get so
scared of like like saying the wrong
thing hurting someone's feelings and I
don't give a to be totally honest W
the glow up is needs to be studied a
little bit for me no for of I that's the
thing though got I genuinely I sound
like a narcissist now but I felt so ugly
the entire time I was in Middle School
in high school so I allow myself to be a
narcissist now because I hated the way I
looked when I woke up every single day
and now I'm so aware that I truly am hot
as and it makes me so happy when I
was at the like I had the same haircut
since Co happened I used to have the
little side and then Co grew out my
hair and I feel like haircuts Co is what
made it well I I just I literally feel
like I've had the exact same haircut for
4 years and I hav't at all and it drives
me crazy you're like a cartoon
character I'm going to I'm going to do
something about it I hate that I look
that young bothers me this just makes me
really emotional
dude I often forget I have oh my God
wait I remember I edited something funny
right here I I often forget I have like
a freckle back here until I watch like
old content I have the same one no
mine's like on my job I have the same
thing what are you dead serious man
Chris how are we just figuring this out
I have the same thing look go back in
the thing watch
Chone right there I have the same thing
yeah
look Freckle friends how the is
this happen right side right yes this is
weird I feel even more triplet than I
just ever have in my whole life I have
the same thing
[Music]
should he play again oh my God that's a
good
ide should I play again wow
bro what does it
say sure Wast another doll gets the
minor prize should he keep
going Nick watch
out way to get out of the way
Nick look at us like arguing but not
getting mad at each other I know why do
we hate each other now you we're all
short tempered and miserable we
literally are all short tempered and
miserable it's so sad sad at least we
reflected on it and we realize it jumps
yeah it skipped it so SK the game's
right so casual breaking down the game
oh my god listen to these bars you know
at the end of the day it's not about the
big prizes in life it's about the minor
things and the way you look at them
[Applause]
and to think I i' I still fully stand on
that sit down and let's wow what a will
we make it in YouTube can will this be
our profession every day wake up
YouTube oh God it's still up in the air
wow that's actually kind of crazy
subscribe tell your family members to
subscribe actually kind of wild you said
let's give it a try let's give it a try
oh we got to bring this did it never we
left it up to fate mhm oh we're amazing
what a little fun little illusion it
makes me really sad and emotional I hate
it because we've achieved it and I feel
I'm I feel like I'm he's not as happy as
he should be I know you know what I
mean and life moved too quick for us to
like really Relish in it I agree and I
don't even relish have a um school
project and we need can you say
subscribe to the steros that we can
subscribe to the
steros he said yeah you agree thank
you is you better do it CU if you don't
that man who works at McDonald's is
going to be pissed he's going to be
fired from his job and he's never going
to be able to give
me that lady almost just went for that
hand bro cuz if he saying it he means it
yeah he didn't even say he's going to go
home and sub when he when he gets home
or he's going to take out his phone
right now dud that's so
embarrassing I used to all right guys
thank you for watching today's video and
coming on this emotional roller coaster
of the past with us we appreciate it we
obviously came a long way and it's all
thanks to you guys so thank you for
watching today's Friday video we love
you so much truly is absolutely
incredible and I can't even kind of pro
process things Nick say LeBron
James that's it that's it
[Music]