I don't know if I want to be like in the
middle I don't think I want like the
triplet sandwich like I really don't I
can sit in the middle I don't want to be
the meat of
it I can sit in the
middle what if you were gone I should
edit like you disappear okay wait can
everyone get up what are you guys
touching each other
for he's just very giggly literally saw
Matt reach over with one hand go like
this like that's all I
saw all right so did you take something
dude like get up what are you what are
you
want dude on funny juice with a riddler
all right
so stop we are going to react to Fan
edits that you guys have made of us I
need my glasses I can't see oh my god
dude today I took an eye exam and I like
no yes they give you an eye exam and no
and as I took the eye exam I was like
he's never going to pass this me it was
so far away that I was like yikes like
he's in deep [ __ ] oh Chris you just look
like Mr Crocker oh Bo fa parents
remember when we were I just realized if
someone edits this video it's like they
edited a video of us editing watching
edits and our
edits so it's like and like I'm going to
edit this video it's like when you time
travel and you have to go back to the
future then you have to go back like
it's just dude all right nipple boy
nipple boy are my tits popping out of
the
shirt come on man nipple boy are you
guys
ready yes I can't proceed like this in
these
conditions there it is is that like for
you that's like a big
laugh what is wrong with
it seems like someone's inside you like
suppressing your laugh every time you
laugh I have random things that remind
me of you guys I'll start with Nick
sleeping bag I don't know I just feel
like you'd love it Rowser go ahead
Nick you are like a fire alarm system
every single time it starts to speak or
talk it's absolutely loud nonsense
usually [ __ ] Incorrect and just
pisses you off or terrible like yeah
yeah Nick yes
hey it's crazy cuz when I was just
watching that clip I had the same
thought as pasted me and I was like
that's like such a stupid thing that
he's saying and I thought you were going
to show me like the clip of you being
like Oh wasn't this funny and I was like
going to say like that was stupid of you
and then I immediately said what I
thought now so it's good to know that
I'm on the same page wow I'm so proud of
you I do really think like you really
enjoy a sleeping bag like I stand by
what I said no like it's stupid like
just a little sack made for comfort and
warm like I think you love it what is
going
on the [ __ ] is going
on yep there it is yes yes yes yes yes
yes I love this [ __ ] so cute I'm so
happy for you Matt I love this [ __ ] Matt
like showed me that Tik Tok last night
like he went up to me and was like look
and he like showed it to me like it was
a piece of gold it's really cute it's
the first day of Honor
[Music]
yes I love this [ __ ] I wi the poo is
like dumb do not yell again like it's
the first day of autum what are you
talking about it's the F day of Auto
like when you're done what he sound
stupid playing again he was it's the F
day of
Auto Play it Again Play it again okay
what you mean it's the F day of all them
first day of autumn like he sounds like
a first of
a are you IDI I just said I just said
are you an idiot I to like be a hater
and I said he sounds like a 2-year-old I
said it like a 2-year-old the F that
involved
them I love that [ __ ] can you stop TR
this can you spit this gum out it's
bothering
me go spit this gum out seriously go
throw it out I'll I'm like I hear you
like like my can you swallow it I'll
stopit no
Myck I love that yeah that's insane we
should andol drink until our livers
explode I won't wake up in a [ __ ]
dude you're sick you are a sick bastard
10 10 million views you're sick you're
sick God like we should go to the LI
million views oh that's really funny
though just imagine like if you were to
wake up in a park or like some sort of
outdoor thing you'd be terrified imagine
if someone like caught you doing that no
what would you do if someone like woke
you up in a bush like a fan and it's
like hey Nick is that you and you were
just like blacked out in a bush don't
even say that good
[ __ ] hold hold hold down down down
you just saved my life we almost got hit
by that's insane you yelling like that
is unbeliev that's like top number one
Matt loud moment that's top number one
loud matte moment M D from
[Music]
Shrek what are you going to say
like what am I
doing
hey if your teacher says that you can't
where am I
looking where am I looking oops you're
sick stupid Don I love that we're going
to be able to look back at all of our
one day when we're like 90 years old how
amazing is that this this clip to me I
had to show cuz it's actually
unbelievable I'm excited where' you get
that spoon from our drawer under the
sink this is our house is that not
insane that I do so much for us if he
doesn't know where our [ __ ] plastic
spoons are I have a reason for this I
don't care you should all even if you
don't know where the spoons are look
around I have a reason for this let's
hear it I didn't know we had plastic
spoons you didn't ask for a plastic
spoon by the way said where's the I said
where did you get this implying the
plastic spoon you
[ __ ] why are you talking
is they are they pretending they're like
in the seat behind
me they're going on the date are they
pretending that they're like in the car
yes oh my God that that should be like
that should be part like that should is
this like the like sometimes this to the
this is the craziest thing sometimes I
see Tik toks make and I'm like you
should be immediately admitted to an
insane asylum this is about to be most
like gen Alpha take I've ever made but
gen Alpha yeah which is like the the new
current gen the like that needs to be
the rers the that like doing [ __ ] like
that needs to get placed into like brain
rot like that needs to be with like Livy
think most I think it's the most brain
rotting thing ever I'm going to be
honest I don't have an opinion on this
well you think it's
fun Matt probably does on a spare time
that's why okay can I show you this
I'm the black one that's me giving you a
hug and you're not reciprocating it cuz
you're a negative
Willie a negative that's not even us
Matt that's us that's us three yeah but
it has nothing to actually do with us
that's us Nick is he unbelievable no
like I get your like metaphorical silly
joke but the content like the person who
posted this doesn't even know who we are
Nick that's yeah like we're reacting
like triplet edits and that's like
that's us including ourselves in
something on the Internet that has
nothing to do with
us I think we'll be I didn't know like
there was rules why this right
here a
people she a [ __ ] Diamond chain every
bracelet you could [ __ ] imagine an
Apple Watch and then she goes through
and he goes got take bracelet
off he goes I've never heard a TSA guy
do this instead of like getting her
just go do you have [ __ ] do
oning fing
TR s
on vest on like are we for
real [ __ ] airport security
withal like it was so funny number one
number one Nick rant ever I agre I think
that Nick Grant started theck the Nick
rant lore like the fact that so many
people have seen that video of me is
just like that is the perfect
representation of who I am SCP the
script is one thing but the exact
is that girl I remember that being like
one of the first fan edits I ever seen
in my life that's really no I'm dead
serious like that I like really like was
like oh my God this is insane insane
like that that clip is just like an
iconic piece of our history I completely
agree that's the best Nix seral rant
ever I just couldn't believe I have like
I I have a story to tell you guys and we
film another car video that I genuinely
think is at par if not better than that
one and I am so
I am so it's so hard for me to not share
the story speaking of
History sharp seriously sharp and
mozzarella and Parmesan those are
four
Jack Nick like pinching his ears is
hilarious that's such really hard on to
listen to like it like it's a funny joke
yes in hindsight but the like the the
the level of which it's been played to
us oh it hurts my like I've like got
I've like met people and they be like
how do I know you yeah and I like oh I
don't know like YouTube Tech talk
whatever and they were like oh my God
like the colby jack video and I'm like
oh my God yeah like that's like I've had
people that I've like genuinely met like
refer to me as like that video like
hobby Jack Bros and I'm like I really
want to like explode if you did explode
on I want to just like I would like to
just burst come on bro you want to burst
Nick you want to see this edit of me
like Terrible No but no hold on I just
need to like I cannot believe how many
people like use the kobby Jack Jack
thing I can't believe how many people
kobby Jack
are what no but like everyone use that
and what makes me laugh the most is like
us reacting to that will probably be
some people's first time like realizing
that that's us it's like that clip is
hard like I've genuinely gone to like
flirt with people and they've been
like like they've like known me from
that like Kobe Jack I'm like why are you
speaking to me then that's the clip
you've seen yeah no but what's also
funny is that like the the audio that
blew up wasn't even how the natural
video went edit cut yes like some girl
like chopped it and like she like she
she made it funnier
yeah shout out them shout out
everybody what are you showing us this
is once again has nothing to do with
that that's me
who's that it's me Chris I hate an
armadillo what they're just like
muscular strong hedgehogs with armor if
you think about it they're like level
hedgehogs it's like what I imagine if
you had like a Hedgehog character and
like and it just got like more and more
arm like
evolved like armadillo like it's just
not that do anymore we have to do like a
Stern Little Fall yes
[Music]
you need a
cat no you need to just
chilles see
your
off I can't believe the people loved
that clip yeah cuz I think that's I
think that's a mediocre clip of me I
just can't believe how fast you can
respond like that I genuinely will
always have a respond if I say something
right now like the most random thing
ever could you make a joke out of it you
think like it depends if you volley me
if you don't [ __ ] volley me I'm not
going to be able to do
it can you
stop like it hurts you just punched my
dick in balls what would you do I what
would you do Nick if
um hold on let me think let me think
what would you do if do you know how
like at a store they have like washer
and dryers there to like sell sometimes
like like a Staples or like a home by
yeah what would you do if someone went
in and just started like doing like
washing their clothes I wouldn't do
anything it has nothing to do with me
unless I work at Best by then I'd be
like hey maybe
chill maybe buy that or go to the laundr
mat and use a [ __ ] quarter or
nickel like is that funny to you like
that's not like a fast quick answer
like that could have gone better in my
opinion but that was that was perfect
like for I wanted to happen it just
happened flawlessly like I said if I
think of something random could you make
me like laugh and giggle off of a
response and you just perfectly executed
it Nick thank you like you see a video
of Nick it's going to be like a fat like
pig or
something
no I just said that did you just hear
that does that actually
no
guys that's not really make that's not
so cute that's not really making that
noise it's not really making that noise
look at him is it not crazy that I just
said it going be like a fat little pig
or something and then it was terrible
Deja Vu what the whole the whole off
camera moment right there terrible deja
vu why would we were just like we were
just trying to find more edits to react
to and Nick gasped and reached for the
camera and goes terrible Deja Vu that
was part of it something either great or
horrible is going to happen soon cuz
that was Deja Vu like how how intense
was it like one of the more intense
scenarios really dude do you remember
when you were near I'm sitting at the
kitchen table by myself and Nick comes
down downstairs and he goes I had a
horrible I I had a horrible
Awakening somebody that's some you were
sitting just like you are right now and
somebody came into the house and stabbed
and killed
you I said I said wow I said I said what
are you telling it what just happened
dude I was freaking out and he was like
what and then he just walked back
upstairs swear to nck swear to God
because because I have like Visions okay
I swear just now I literally had like
terrible deju like something really bad
or really good is going to happen okay
and I'm scared Nick you are I just have
to share these things like you want me
to feel intense Deja Vu and not speak up
about it horny sternal triple edits is
that your search bar that's what I'm
checking for right now oh Jesus bro
[Music]
okay sometimes I do something that's
like so unsexual and like so like
innocent and just chill like trying to
knee a pumpkin like trying to kick a
pumpkin and like the other day did you
see this video I was streaming the other
day I was cold and I went like this and
then now they're editing it like I was
like Rin went out on stream like they
literally put it like I was like off
like y'all are y'all are crazy y'all are
sick you know what I
got send me that
one that's not how this one
goes that's not
this you sick [ __ ] dog get off that's
not of this one what do you want to
watch it again maybe you sick dog why
did I think I said
that that one was funny that was oh my
God bad Deja Vu again bad bad bad
Dayja like like
this stop looking at me with like tears
like bad bad bad like I'm like tripping
out I always think like what if someone
just came upstairs right right there and
just start Chris don't say that video
because watching Nick like rewatch
things that he never remembered was so
funny you saw that yeah I did oh my
[Music]
God it seems crazier when we catch y'all
right like POS ain't that big of a deal
when I'm watching it when we're all
watching it together seems a little
intense I have to see them have you seen
the ones that it's like try to maintain
eye contact with Matt for more than 6
seconds and then they searching no then
they scroll and it's like the picture of
me edited bald with like the watermelon
next to my head yo no cuz this is what I
have to talk about you got to gr your
hair out no I like my
haircut no one what I did realize though
Matt
what the
internet either wants me to date a woman
and it's not
happening I see so many edits of like of
me and people are like oh like I just
wish you'd like liked girls or oh like
Nick looks so good to my friend they
post their friend I'm like huh I'm like
you mean this
ballerina my type is bodybuilding mud
eating disgusting straight
men I love women I lift you up but I
don't want to touch you at all
I just be I'm a I'm a goofball and I
can't contain my
goofiness making the kangaroo work give
me him no give me him leave him be what
is
this no C no
e it was just a regular cut the camera
clip watch the whole thing this is Lally
me and ser I get so irrit this is me
turn off that light PA it pause it I
thought that that was like video of me
no I thought that can I just play it no
I have something to say dick face I
thought that that was the um Yukon
Cornelius from Rudolph and that's why
when I looked up and saw bug's bunny I
was totally thrown off turn off that
light turn off that light turn off those
lights be quiet shut
up this was crazy
neck what what are you here
for classic classic M that's insane does
growing up just change your body or also
your
soul maybe I could just stay the same
forever like I actually look like way
older than when we started YouTube maybe
cuz here's the thing right YouTube both
looked like
drastically did I say that right
different Matt says that wrong he says
Jurassic
dinosaur okay but you guys both changed
so much from when we started drastic I
got you I got you you guys both changed
so Dr I'll kill you both so much since
the start of YouTube to like now that
like whenever I see like seed whenever I
saw
old get
okay okay okay you guys both changed so
much from the beginning of our career to
like now but like I always kind of
looked a little bit the same so like I
would never really like see like these
crazy differences in how I looked but
when I watched that that was the first
time I was ever like whoo like I
actually look way younger seeing edits
like that makes me want to just like
erase my entire existence from social
media here on out and like disappear and
live on like a lake for like a year and
like not explain where I'm going at
all that's crazy it's I think it's
awesome that we have like the the
memories yeah well you're big on like
memories and like I just want to be part
of your
Sy uh so that was us reacting to edits
of us Nick wouldn't be as funny without
me or
me do you guys think that's true all
right everyone thank you guys so much
for joining this video we had a lot of
fun doing this and Tik Tok is an endless
platform form with millions of videos so
we can do this again with videos about
us or we can do this again about any
videos on the internet so if you guys
want a part two of more videos on the
Internet or a part two of this one just
let us know
[Music]