he just said he's not going to say
something stupid this video that's free
money for me million dollars I'm not I'm
an adult I'm grown shake my hand on yeah
I did wait do you want me to sit in the
middle I know you're probably going to
have like no I sit in the middle in the
car can sit in the middle here I just
want you to get your hand off me like
get the [ __ ] out you see that he's like
this I feel like this like I feel like
four fingers touching me you're spin
that and see if you you can all be seen
do you need Elbow Room I got to blow my
nose cuz I'm going to be like boogies
all day in this video boogies all day
like
old all right guys welcome back to talk
to a podcast today stop stop cut that
out to keep us in the Halloween flow
last week we tried the Halloween goodies
this week we're going to be doing
paranormal stories for you guys yes Nick
posted a link on the St triplet
Instagram he said share your scary
stories and the stolo triplets Instagram
like God what it's just crazy that
that's like us yeah it is us oh was on a
link on the stolo triplets instag
like
what would you have said it differently
you're overthinking this no I probably
wouldn't it's just weird okay that's us
okay yeah big shot we posted it on our
group Instagram big shots is crazy
coolest people in town yeah those wait
sorry wrong triplet
hey hey Matt hey what's up you want to
tell Nick about our scary story the
other night okay so the other night me
and Matt went on a walk yeah at a local
park that we like to walk okay yeah I'm
familiar we're walking around I'd say
it's what 1130 at night Matt mhm which
day was this where was I we get to the
place we're trying to like just like
have a good healthy Walk and Walk a lot
right so we're walking for like a half
hour and then we're at the point where
we're like kind of tired and like
deciding like do we want to go home do
we want to keep walking like what do we
want to do you're good to stop looking
at me like that who me no he's freaking
me out a lot fre me out I feel I'm
you're talking then he goes like this
over here I just feel bad like my head
away from you no that's fine I that's
what I I would hope if I was listening
you guys would look at me the way that I
would like oh that's so sweet I would
look at you that way can you just keep
going to this awful story it's not awful
basically we're at the point of the Walk
where we're like do we go home or do we
stay whatever and then we're like let's
just walk for five more minutes then we
start walking down like the creepier
side like where it's like you know what
I'm talking about the Twist and Turn
it's like super dark right so we're
walking through the path and we get to
like right under one of the lights and
we hear like Zing ding ding you like
know how like electricity sounds like
how it's like kind of like T I love that
sound yeah so it was likeing ding ding
like that like kind of like stranger
thingy like mystical tin like tinkle
right a little mystical tingle exactly
so then we're like what the [ __ ] was
that so we kind of like are already like
looking at each other like kind of weird
and then the light goes out as right as
we get under it the light like turns
back on and then we're like still kind
of like we had like full like probably
five to eight seconds of like what's
going on Boom oh like that and then the
whole place we're at looks like daytime
and I'm like what the [ __ ] for like 2
seconds and then me and Matt like Duck
and we like start running away no and
and then a second later pitch black
again peaceful as ever like nothing
happened wow and the only thing that I
thought I could explain was like I feel
like I was just like right next to like
a strike of lightning lightning like
nothing did your butt hurt after or no
cuz it's feeling like you guys might
have got like abducted by aliens and
like they might have like probed you or
something that's what I'm feeling it
feels like an alien attack no can I have
another SI of my drink there's the tax
for making me lift it oh I got Phantom
taxed like you guys are
unbelievable I don't know why you're
laughing so hard that's the definition
of phantom tax now
no is that is that not true that that's
like what f is like I'm confused I'm
trying to just see hip I guess that like
ruined the Sip for me cuz it bubbled up
in my mouth have another pH taxs me
again this is not
funny like so stupid he's laughing this
hard we had a chicken bake and a double
chunk chocolate cookie you got be like
double chunk chocolate
cookie that that am I that funny think
you guys funer than anyone else down a
double chunk chocolate cookie good oh
yeah you're just like really funny to me
I don't know I don't know why like I
think it's cuz you're my brother but
also like I just know you so well and I
love
you you're awesome hug yeah of course
dude I think you're the best just it
just in that moment of me laughing at
you Nick it made me feel like how they
probably feel like they probably love
you like they you just make them laugh
and I just had like a a wholesome moment
I just thought I'd share WIP the [ __ ]
off your lips from kissing his ass let's
go oh yeah you're funny Matt sorry I
care okay so I I like this mini pocket
you got here it's not it is a mini
pocket yeah all right guys we took a
moment to space
out cuz I needed a quarter inch between
we we gave ourselves a fist of Ro
between each other so we we have just
one one fist one fist so that way we
have more allergies the other night I
one of you sorry sorry go ahead I wish
my allergies didn't put me in a
suffering amount of pain each day it's
oh my God I ha go to the doctor you
should go to the doctor I was I was
going to say something go go go the fist
of room thing reminded me I wanted to
kill the man at the movies the other
night the other night at The Joker it
was like a full P The
Joker bar what's his name the guy I
don't know and he's like um okay just
let's go with the
story that's what it was M you want to
drink the guy at the Joker movie kept
like like taking up my whole armrest
like that like hitting me like direct
contact to my being and I was like dude
you can have the rest but like you
shouldn't be touching me once do I know
what I would have done what that man
would have turned around and heard I
would have shot up oh wow neck that's a
lot yeah I think like I wasn't done with
that you just took it out of my hand and
put you hand no I was holding it up [ __ ]
my bad I genuinely think the use of a
shotgun cocking like the noise and the
action actually is one of the best uses
of sound effect Machinery in all movies
like you know like a bad [ __ ] is like
like it's like like I think of I think
of a quiet place when who what's Emily
Blunt's character's name I don't know
why you like what that me thinking I'm
Italian the drink done it's empty it is
should we hooray yeah hooray
hooray
wasay children
hooray oh Nick you're awesome yes he
just said it like Matt shut the [ __ ] up
kindergarten with we're having fun as
brothers he's like I hate you I hate you
you're so stupid and childish you're
earing a
sideways you got to stop caring about
that I do care I don't want to it's
[Music]
like my best friends literally saw a
lepon when she was younger and says it
was the craziest thing ever I think your
best friend is stupid bro scary but
humbling I slipped on the school stairs
and the lads a year above me was coming
inside what is and everyone this isn't
paranormal are you an
idiot I'm so brutal when I was younger
there would be times my parents would
catch me talking to myself but I told
them it was a little boy sitting on my
fan and he looked like he was from the
60s and then my dad started having
nightmares of this lady in a white dress
and was supposedly his mother how did
you all put that together like why I'm
really confused by the connection there
why is he sitting on a fanboy and
and when I was eight every night I would
wake up to seeing a girl's body covered
in leaves and whenever I'd try to speak
or hit her
she'
disappear wait that's actually really
scary well why would she going to hit
her you're in the leaves bow no it's
like she's freaking were were the leaves
in a room or were the leaves also
imaginary it was probably all imaginary
like imagine if you were sleep in your
bed and you woke up and you see a he
like relates to this [ __ ] way too much
to much yes cuz that's scary he thinks
it through a lot what if you what would
you do if you woke up and then you
looked over in your bed and there was
just like a scary lady like covered in
leaves of course you're trying to hit
her be terrified right one time when I
was at work the light started flickering
and went out and the door slammed shut
so I was so scared but then everything
went back to normal I think you're all
right all right mopy dick get up mopy
dick is not the name of this the whale
it's it's a play on words cuz he's
moping around I know I know it's m M's a
good word Moby my dog is dead I feel
like that's going to be the next AI Moy
I'm
here F dick
you're an idiot it's just such an AI
robot name m or Moy whatever the [ __ ]
chis yeah I'm saying that like Moby
reminds me of like Baymax like it's like
okay yeah that's good you're a toddler I
can't do this okay okay no they're not
similar at all are you an idiot dude why
does every joke I make make Matt feel
like that like he like everything you
find funny he's disgusted by you want
know what I feel with Chris
often when I was a kid my grandma died
and after that I started seeing her
sometimes not like full body but
sometimes when I turned my head I saw
her face in the
window my God it hello yeah we need your
he quick it would it would be more
normal if it was full body than face in
the window yeah yeah you like and you're
the dude and you're like oh you want
anything for coffee and I'm like
what and I look and it's like actually
the B stuff like it's just like that
yeah
sorry I walked into my room blanket was
moving by itself it's like her dog it's
like a sheet ghost like a
hamster like running around the blanket
yeah yeah yeah dude is is everything I
say because she's probably doesn't have
a hamster she probably would have
thought I also said it's probably the
dog if she did it's the perfect thing
like for what like you're making an
excuse for you don't know who this is I
said like the dog under the blanket you
don't know who this is and you're like
oh her blanket is her hamster it could
be it could have been it's not she'd be
like oh I have a hamster who are you
looking at one time I was home alone and
my bedroom do opened and SL lamed shot
then a week later I was in my kitchen
and a cup flew off the table come to
find out my house was haunted you don't
like find out yeah how' you find out
like are you an idiot
Nick stop I thought I was being choked
in my sleep by an old lady in old old
ladies in all caps wait that's terrify
thought I I don't have dreams that are I
wish I had crazy nightmares oh my God I
would never say that I would never I
love the feeling of waking up like
terrified like I just love you love the
feel cuz it's like a fun little like
story I feel like I can pretend I have
life experience you sick if I survive
like a killer in like a in like my
nightmares I'm waking up and I'm like
that's hard like I'm no I was I was I
was that was up you're the type for like
your boyfriend to be cheating on you in
your nightmare and you get like angry
when I was younger I thought my sister
was pranking me by pulling out my
blanket but I yell out her name and said
to stop it but she oh I hate this but
she replies with what and I look beside
me and she's laying next to me I still
wonder till this day who pulled my
blanket that's actually that one is a
chiller that's a good one that's similar
to my story no that one's spooky no your
story the other way
though that's similar to that no that is
like a triplet thing dude cuz the other
the other right I was in my room and
I've
been I thought that it was I've been
seeing things in the corner my eyes I
agree no I agree ear yesterday I was
saying to like wow I was seeing like
monsters in the corner of my eyes I look
like oh it's fine the other day I was in
my room and I for don't do that what I I
had sleep paralysis once where I woke up
and there was a guy pointing a gun at me
through the window which was supposed to
be closed I couldn't move and I thought
I was going to die because he was going
to shoot me all I could see was him
dressed in all black in the gun I
couldn't scream or move wow that's night
I think we're confusing nightmares with
paranormal stories though the other
night I had like a nightmare type of
sleep paralysis no it wasn't a fun one
it was a bad one and I was it was like a
nightmare sleep paralysis combo okay
that's the same thing I feel like well
no cuz it wasn't like like I've never
experienced sleep paralysis where Like
My Eyes Are Open no one
does oh my God like you know when you're
no cuz I I'm pretty sure you're like um
up um I had sleep paralysis I think cuz
I was laying down trying to wake myself
up and my by trying to wake myself up I
was like get up so I did and it didn't
wake me up and then I woke up standing
oh that's and I'm dead serious sick SI
awful I'm dead have you ever had that
thing where you wake up and you like
check the time on your phone and then
like scroll on your phone and then you
like are actually still asleep and
you're like poof back in
bed love to see this text
who is it when I was younger around
kindergarten time I vividly remember
always seeing a green hand resting on my
shoulder in the corner of my eye any
time I would look there would be of
course nothing
there some of this got to be made up for
dramatic effect right a green hand like
why a green hand like does she mean like
green like green screen or like
Frankenstein probably Frankenstein if I
had to guess ever since I moved into
this house there's there's a little girl
who sounds an intro of a movie there's a
little girl who sings in my bathroom and
it's it's a joke it's a joke with my
family and I and we we named her Emily
she's nice we got her her own little
Halloween we got our own little
Halloween doll of
her oh so y'all crazy yeah that's a
little okay googly booly ass yeah that's
a little Okie spooky o I hate that can't
get gifts for the Paranormal no dead ass
that's how they you wake up and they
inside you what yeah like one day the
girl's going to wake up and she's going
to like come home with like a dead
rabbit or something the family what's
wrong Emily took me over like like okay
when I was little I was in the car with
my parents and I started singing Radio
Gaga by Queen my parents have never sang
or listened to the song around me before
they think I'm reincarnated from my
grandfather or someone who was around
when Queen was good but I think I am
queened okay this [ __ ] thinks
they're Queen the scariest part about
that is that you think that yeah that's
crazy I do I do get I feel like hold
this no i' I've talked about this no
I've talked about this yes I've talked
about this on the internet before
everybody needs to see an episode of
Ghost Inside My Child that show is
[ __ ] crazy can I say there's like no
I'm speaking no I'm speaking no I'm
speaking no and this kid vividly
remembers I will never forget foret this
cuz I couldn't sleep he vividly
remembers being like like he'd wake up
in night terror screaming to his mom and
then his mom would be like what's wrong
what's wrong he's like I had to kill
them I had to do it and she's like what
are you talking about and he vividly
remembers like shooting people with like
bow and arrows and like hunting them and
killing them mus turns to find out what
that's not a that's not a thing come to
find out they're going on like a trail
right they're driving down this place
they've never been before and this
[ __ ] is screaming like I died
over there and they're like what they go
and like you have to watch this you have
to go watch this you're telling them at
all you got no no and he but basically
they go there they go to like the field
and there's like a monument and it's
like oh this [ __ ] came here and
like killed like um a bunch of people
and yeah like he he was like during the
war he's one of the people that died and
they come to do research and he
remembers he vividly remembers shooting
and killing people and he remembers
dying and he brought them without ever
being there to a monument of a war you
want to know what I was going to say
that is [ __ ]
bananas everybody needs to watch Ghost
Inside My Child get this episode I am
beyond dead serious I beyond it's just
the craziest [ __ ] ever there was another
episode where this girl literally was
like fully fully fully dead serious and
she was talking about like doing like
I'm beyond serious it's not too late no
she dead ass was talking about
start stop like she was talking about
praying for rain and like all this [ __ ]
yeah praying for rain and come to find
out she's telling her parents about [ __ ]
about from like Aztec and like [ __ ]
ancient like whatever like Egypt motopia
and they're like and they're like what
and they Google it and they find a tribe
of people that like existed way back
when and this girl's just telling her
parents about it it's like you're five
like how do you know this [ __ ] you're 5
years old crazy if I have a 5-year-old
and they come up to me start talking to
me about some crazy war and I search and
it's real I'm going to be [ __ ] my
pants yeah that [ __ ] is a phony like
literally a phony because you can't you
can't be Queen and you want to know what
I'm saying is if you're a true
reincarnate you don't know you don't you
no CL you can't claim it on your own
[ __ ] you can't be like you can't be like
oh I think I'm a Reincarnation of this
[ __ ] you got to just start
breaking
you're still him correct you can't
you're not going to record hey I'm a I'm
I think I'm abam L I can't go to the
movies cuz I might get shot and they're
like why and they're like I don't know I
have this like instant they're like hold
on weight you might be a you understand
yeah yeah like if your kid comes home
and walk in with a top hat and is afraid
of the movies he's like I'm not going
I'm not going the mom's like oh we're
here do you want to go on the photo
booth he's like Photo Booth yeah booth
if he comes in and he's like got the
whole thing going he's like oh like
you're playing for that's a school
project or something yes you're you're
kidding around you're not it's not
authentic it's not a lifestyle correct
yes are you done both of you oh I
feel happy we got that yes yes like it's
a major thing like you can't if you feel
like you're a reincarnate you're not
[ __ ] so some people in my family I
need to really clear my throat give me
second yeah hold on yeah so some people
in my family can see ghosts but I can't
oh in parenthesis thank God and one time
before I went to bed I was thinking
about how I missed my nana and Granddad
and then I felt a tap on my shoulder but
no one was actually around me boring so
maybe that was like her inauguration
into seeing ghost yes like the rest of
her family yes don't you worry you're
coming
yes my family's voices talking when
there was no one else in the
house some of you [ __ ] are just
schizophrenic I think around like last
year at like 2: a.m. and I was just in
my room and I kept hearing noises from
upstairs and I was so confused so I went
up there and I saw a bucket on the floor
moving around and legit thought there
was a ghost moving it so I lifted it up
and it was my dog inside the bucket
that's so funny it's like the hamster
blet a person doesn't have a hamster I
know one time I was in the hospital and
I went to the bathroom at around 2:30 in
the morning when I walked out of my room
to use the bathroom I saw this tall
figure standing down the hallway I don't
[ __ ] I don't think much of it I just
went to the bathroom when I came out it
was still there I walked towards it and
it disappears are you a psycho who sees
a ghostly [ __ ] shadow figure and says
I'm going to head in that dire really
insane my family and I were moving towns
and we had to move into a new house we
just moved in oh my
God or something I genuinely like firmly
believe that there's a ghost in my room
Matt can you not maybe touch the [ __ ]
out of me you should make a new series
that's called like ghost in my
room that's I kind of want like and I
don't want to say this out loud no Nick
I want like a good monthlong haunting
are you a sick old bastard why
out of like I think it' just be so cool
if stop looking around after you say
[ __ ] like that hate when you do stuff
I'm thinking of all the things that
could I genuinely believe in like what
you say is bad and like I only I'll
think stuff and I I get scared I get
scared to even say it out loud I'm going
to wish all evil don't even ever Max
your don't even ever I hope the spider
can is so afraid of a word well no when
you say it out loud everything reacts to
that in life I hope you have sleep
paralysis I hope the spider king goes in
your room and lays all his spider babies
in your closet I would never wish both
of that upon either of you and that's
why I get so upset I'm going to put a
tarantula in your shoe if your just
think you're cool if we had a ghostly
experience you're just think you're cool
if we had a ghost go back to school
[ __ ] if we had a ghostly experience I
would hope it starts in your room Nick
I'm really going to be [ __ ] angry in
a second I hate when you do stuff like
this you always say like NE him stuff
out loud and it bothers me like saying
you want to geted for like a mon like
[ __ ]
up hunting would be kind of f even when
we film with Sam and Kobe I like tell
the ghost like you're don't mess with me
he talks to the ghost well no you have
to tell them Patty told us this like you
ghost are in your realm stay out of mine
don't wish for negativity like I hate
when you do that yes face what if a
ghost were to appear right now it's said
get away condemn it no I believe in like
I'm a firm believer not even on the like
spiritual if there's any ghosts in this
room can you stop that want to give us a
sign that they are here do something
now and then what if the house caped in
I genuinely believe ghost we have a
festival you can take over can you
actually stop that was crazy stop it no
you're not allowed to condem you're not
allowed to use any of us as a vessel
yeah cuz it's Cara you're going to get
[ __ ] by the ghost the ghost listen to
me [ __ ] you good if you speak it out
loud then your body starts to like react
to that and then like that's why even if
I said like oh something like I'm not
going to say it no stop you speak that
haircut out
loud really
Matt I feel bad you're so
rude he had nothing to say he said
really
M I feel so bad mean
that was a mean
one feel so bad but that was good it's
okay Chris I like your
haircut if you speak the negativity out
loud it happens and that's why I'll
never do it you can't in that room you
could always hear children laughing but
I never paid attention to years later we
remodeled the house and the on the days
that we fixed the room we heard a lament
that seemed to be
Laona a Mexican legend and the dog how
all night after many years we found out
that in that room a son of my
grandfather had died when he was two
years old get the [ __ ] out of here with
that [ __ ]
Bro she's in Chris's room
[Music]
bro yeah you're [ __ ]
up wait you're yeah you [ __ ] up no cuz
seriously guess what what you're going
to start having terrible days look at
this search how to summon are you
[ __ ] serious you guys are sick
of like good bu should we start should
we just say you guys actually pissed me
off yeah you guys are screwed you guys
are actually screwed because you guys
are joking but I'm going to have the
last
laugh he's going
to not I wish you nothing but the best
but you wish negativity on me is going
to affect you yes Chris serious I don't
wish [ __ ] against you he said the crazy
[ __ ] I didn't say it I just said I just
said she could I didn't say [ __ ] no you
said she is you did it too you're not
you did it too you're not thinking about
you also are being negative no I think
you're fine I
hope I would literally like I saw this
interview this and they were like oh
would you kill for your kids like I
would skin a and hang him to bleed dry
if he mess with my [ __ ] children one
day and I'm dead serious you know one
time I had a nightmare when I was a kid
and this is like almost crazy same with
you guys like if someone mess with y'all
I would literally hang them upside down
and cut their balls out and lit is not
in your room to Matt stop [ __ ] around
and saying her name when I was
don't I say it one more time when I was
with Bloody Mar bloody Nick Bloody Mary
Bloody I've been feeling it for weeks
eyes on me everywhere oh yo this girl
sick at first I dismissed it as paranoia
but tonight who are you but tonight I
Ridler this [ __ ] I saw him tall dark
figure lurking in the shadow who is this
this is Tim Burt on Burner I walks home
from library lost in thought suddenly
the side the street light this girl when
she saw like submit paranormal stories
she just copi and pasted something
suddenly the street lights flickered he
emerged from the darkness my heart is
racing I quick I quickened my Pace he
kept pace with me silent I darted into a
nearby alley mistake dead end he he who
are you I was walking the creeper behind
me
dark creep I was walking the creeper
creeps I felt the aura I felt this
negative Aura with negative vibe all
right guys thank you for watching this
week's Friday video we hope you liked it
subscribe my Instagram Linked In the
description down below Math's Instagram
Linked In the description down below
Chris's Instagram Linked In the
description down below st. triplet
Instagram link down below so that you
never miss an Instagram post from any of
us or an update of what we could
possibly be doing here every single
thing we reacted to in today's YouTube
video we got from our Instagram so if
you want us to possibly react to
something you submit you got to go
follow us on Instagram so that you can
be a part of the next YouTube video also
I don't know when or if it's appropriate
to say this yet but we're going to drop
some Halloween themed merch
yes more hallowe more Halloween spooky
fall Vibes coming coming your way for
the rest of
October we will see you guys next
[Music]
Friday my want to take it look
oh
[Music]