yeah basically
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
you're each McDonald's character who
would we be
here comes the American cheese joke
again I was gonna say he's Grimace oh
you put your hands I went to reach for
my drink there's normally no [ __ ]
clappers dude can I tell you what I
don't believe in at all yeah
tell me elaborate listen actually help
me elaborate Listen Hold on I just
sounded like Willy Wonka scratch that
reverse
I meant QR for free Apple Rock
oh unlocked
it's late this is a real thing that
exists
go ahead good move that was close I need
you guys to think like what's your
opinion on it okay yeah Stingray petting
zoos
um how is that happening
I think they like de-sting them yeah
yeah they do sting it so they're fully
de-stinging a stingray just so you're
not having like little kids can
gross little fingers into a little vast
of water and hold stingrays yeah
basically well you know you know how
they de-stank skunks or these all right
no D stink skunks they stank it yeah but
that's usually for medical purposes no
they just usually they don't want to
smell
you're telling me tomato juice is gonna
do better than like these stinking a
skunk has to be like it's like if I took
your nut sack off like literally like
that's literally that's essentially what
D stinking yeah like you know what I
mean like just give me your whole
manhood gone look at that rat just
[ __ ] spin it around in circles you
see him no oh
oh
he's fast did he just bang a left and he
was going I'm just thinking of like
would they not just be called raise at
that point sting oh yeah at that point
you're just a ray a little can't even
sting oh that's so sad actually [ __ ]
like I love the zoo but like I don't
like the idea of like enclosing the see
my thought is people like I [ __ ] with
like when the animal actually needs help
in the rehabilitation and they're there
for a reason yeah but if you just take
like a wild bear and throw him in a cage
for the rest of his life it's kind of
[ __ ] up yeah I don't believe in zoos
but like I'll go to the zoo but then
honestly sometimes
I'm not as one of those I'm not one of
those guys you know I don't know too
much about this but I'm gonna share mine
you're not a zoologist you don't have to
know everything right but dude I've seen
it unreal I was gonna say something
right here you're fine no go ahead no
you just keep talking about the rats
I think like sometimes with like zoo
animals and [ __ ] like that even though
it's like oh like they're in the zoo
like they're in that little box for the
rest of their life I think if you put
some of those animals in the wild it
wouldn't they wouldn't get it yeah some
sometimes that's at fault of the zoo
yeah but like
I don't know it's all too confusing for
me I don't want to think about it you
know Dad went up to me today I I went in
there it's like 3 A.M 2 A.M and I went
to get this Red Bull because he was like
talking about like get rest it's
important and then we went out to go
film so I grabbed this Red Bull energy
drink obviously and he goes I said [ __ ]
sleep while I opened the fridge and I
was expecting to be like oh Nick no come
on
sleep when you're dead no way yeah I was
like okay he just knew what I had to do
yeah uh Nick what were you gonna say
about that song what song you made us
wait until the camera was up so you
could talk about it because it was funny
what's but I don't think it's funny that
song's like a sad emo no we were just
jamming out to James Arthur say you
won't let go
and Nick said ask me about that song
see I've been so like I have been
fighting this knowledge in my brain for
so long okay like having this story not
telling anyone because of how like the
sheer embarrassment that it brings me to
okay so it's really difficult for me I
have an embarrassing story to this song
too but really yeah I'll let you say it
first before it was like the first guy I
had ever like romantically hung out with
ever and this song was on and I think we
were on like part two of hanging out
like ever and full tears
sorry
full eruption into tears no yeah it was
like the second time and I was just in
such a State of Shock
and that's when I knew that it was not
gonna work at all that's crazy I never
knew that I'm like so that's why I can
never listen to that song Seriously
again because it's such an emotional
good song about someone you'd like loved
for years you know what I mean yeah we
were on like hangout number two no that
that's my biggest my embarrassing story
was I just that's crazy I'm pretty sure
I danced to that song in my eighth grade
uh at eighth grade dance with another
girl that I liked you know oh
really disgusting gross but then no I'm
not gonna say what I was gonna say weird
[ __ ] say it no I can't say it I can't
not no because then I I think our I
think after that for some reason that
when they do that song it's normally
supposed
yo diamonds blinging okay
normally normally when they do that song
it's normally like you kind of like
gradually get back into the other music
yeah you know what I mean but I just
remember like the girl that I didn't get
I didn't hit puberty until like the
latest out of all three of us but we
were still all but we were still all
like four [ __ ] ten in like eighth
grade seventh eighth grade yeah but I
was in eighth grade I think I was like
five foot five one maybe no Max and the
girl that I had a crush on was like five
eight towering over you Tower and over
me she still liked me though don't know
why I don't know yeah I was also in
eighth grade really strange but that
song plays dancing to that song right
and then I'm expecting like like a clean
transition into like another kind of
lovey song but like upbeat a little more
so you know what I mean yeah it went
straight into [ __ ] what was it I think
it was like a Macklemore song straight
to a Macklemore song and then our eighth
grade math teacher was break dancing
seconds after me and her son that's
crazy I don't know dude but remember the
Cha-Cha Slide he just started [ __ ]
like doing the thing on his back
flipping that dude was crazy I hated him
that is crazy school dances were the
worst [ __ ] thing on this Earth
like school dances have got to be like
they're just like I never wanted to go I
just had like fomo like it's literally
like the impact Yourself fast legit no
yeah literally how [ __ ] quiet I
literally really didn't want to go to
our High School uh I regret going to our
high school prom with everything I
regret going to every high school then
my being yeah I agree like looking back
at life I genuinely
despise a lot of the things I did in the
past
even that are on social media that like
just like ew like I don't like the
clothes I was wearing yeah ugly I just
hate it well that's normal people are
just like I love this I miss this and
it's like that makes that [ __ ] that [ __ ]
I won't get that makes one of us I think
people Miss [ __ ] that I don't because
I feel like [ __ ] is being shoved down my
throat it's such a rapid rate
but it's just like a whole lot of like
when I don't miss you about my past and
people are just shoving it down my
throat it's not a fun thing yeah
anything forcefully shoved down yeah
that's not usually yeah sometimes here I
don't know
oh because I don't want to complain but
like sometimes I like scroll through my
40 page or like my comments and then
it's like that's terrible I miss Matt
with the middle part and then I walk
into the bathroom and then I'm like
looking in the mirror and I'm like is
that not going on right now no I think
it's so funny when people are like oh my
God Chris's hair like this he needs to
keep like this forever it's like people
don't understand that our hair
constantly looks different like I've
seen people freak out about Matt's new
style once a week and it depends on how
goofy he looks at the moment you know
what I mean Fair though Matt sure dude I
got a memory on my phone for like three
years ago the other day yeah and it was
like
hey guys I've never worn jeans can
someone like go shopping with me and I
put it on like my public Snapchat story
first of all really embarrassing too
like I wanted to like have a friend who
like was an added active like Genie like
take me to buy jeans like that just
shows you like three years ago I bought
my first no drip oh no I bought my shirt
every photo of me of high school if I
could put it in a cart and let the cart
roll down a hill into a fiery Inferno
I'd do it in a heartbeat no yeah me too
I don't need any imagery of me in high
school I rotated through the same seven
pairs of sweatpants I had like three
like I remember one like when by the
time by the time like Friday would be
coming around I'd be like hunting the
laundry room for the sweatpants I wore
the other day because like I only have
like three trustworthy pair of pants
that I like that's crazy so I would
always just cycle through them and then
I always had like Uggs on have you seen
that Meme
pretty much it yeah
and Michaela I hated that shirt and I
used to say that to you yeah I don't
half cheetah print half like [ __ ]
magma what are you doing yeah I actually
I really wish I had a nice cheetah print
item to this day you should cheetah
print could be a cool thing
I should have print like bucket hat or a
baseball the scariest [ __ ] outfit
I've ever seen walked by me the other
day and not to say I'm like the fashion
god or the fashion Guru but homeboy
walked by with a button-up shirt and the
right half was Checkers and the left
half was Stripes I'm like they're gonna
say God I felt like I was getting
hypnotized this is working better than a
[ __ ] clock ticking back and forth
behind in front of my eyes you know what
I mean metronome
wingle
what would a wiggle be it's I think it's
a Pokemon hold on if there's a wingle
I'm gonna it's a foot wiggle that's hard
if not trademarks trademarks I own a
wingle I'll tell you what it is
momentarily yes like an actual thing oh
it is a Pokemon if I got called a wiggle
I'd be pretty upset about it like it
sounds like something like a British
person would call you like if you were
lousy like oh yeah
it is only one word you know what I mean
I love how you said lousy a British
purse will call you this if they're loud
or you've never had crumpets at the
t-spot doing Winger you dumb Winger I
asked you guys what are some random hot
takes you have so now we're gonna react
and agree with or disagree with fans I
love that Matt put your phone down you
[ __ ] Pokemon
my slob is crazy
oh my phone's not loaded
[Laughter]
um
Mac agree or disagree they're strongly
dude anything baked is just getting a
little bit better and you're throwing
mac and cheese in it
baked lasagna I feel like it's like huh
most lasagna is big no it's like there's
this place I have baked lasagna like
super baked it's like double ultra-based
someone said granola bars are nasty
Brody it depends the flavor horseradish
[ __ ] nasty no I mostly agree I feel
like I feel like I really don't often
get down with granola bars yeah I love
granola though granola's delish dude
granola
one of the most foul disgusting Foods I
don't even want to call it a food is
yogurt yogurt it's just like it just
tastes like sour milk in a cup no what's
that what's up what's that one yogurt
yogurt Chobani
but Chobani has to be my biggest fear
and y'all throwing a big word at us too
like Joe Bonnie
you're Dynamics
[ __ ] them [ __ ] YouTube on me no it's
because I think like I remember the
teacher
oh my God I just got a terrible
flashback what a horrible sight oh my
God I remember our math teacher in
seventh grade or eighth grade I know I
know I know I know he used to eat
Chobani yogurt and I thought to myself
Nicholas maybe he has a fridge full of
Chobani yogurt because he's eating one
every day he's dead yes or no he one
every day I I ended up going in the
corner of the room because I asked him
for a pencil and they were like behind
it and I looked I looked under his desk
no mini refrigerator
refrigerator break dancing yes you're
eating unrefrigerated warm
Chobani yogurt Chris he eats warm yogurt
if you're eating yogurt first of all go
[ __ ] yourself and then try to look in
the mirror and say what can I do to make
some more friends because eating show
Bonnie yogurt isn't going to be one oh
it's just the whole classroom if you eat
Chobani you probably
yeah Mom like sugar I don't care this is
a rude awakening to her stop eating
Chobani in the car with me someone says
I like cheese and honey
items should be way more accessible just
for like pranks like a breakaway chair
yeah can we get them like I want to
fully furnish my house if it's just not
built properly no because Breakaway is
designed not to hurt you I stab myself
with a glass by accident in a break room
that's not break away glasses no I know
but like that's right like glasses are
just glass yes I know it's made out of
sugar I'll never understand that the
break room isn't though
yeah they [ __ ] made the whole break
room on the sugar what is delusional a
break room glass dumbass no [ __ ] oh I'm
sorry
um I just spelled that because you said
you said you said you said what'd you
say you said Tayo crew tell them how you
feel
what
did you just saying dude
me and mom were going through her
journey
my favorite song when I was 11 years old
[ __ ] can you guys stop talking what was
you saying about candy saying about
candy it's delicious sugar break groom
oh it was the sugar the breaker made out
of sugar I thought it made me think of
Wreck-It Ralph immediately they were in
The Fun Gym you know I'm talking about
fungen the fun dungeon I better call me
I thought you were mistaken it for
Funyun candy break room break candy fun
gin and then you're just sneak in London
in the movie Wreck-It Ralph and then it
made me think Wreck-It Ralph
if you can find someone on this road
hold on the bubbles go with me listen if
you can find someone on this Earth that
hasn't seen Wreck-It Ralph
I want to watch it with them because
Wreck-It Ralph has one of the best
Cinema plot twists of all time I would
do anything to watch Dragon Ball with
someone
Ralph post on your story because I
guarantee you there's someone out there
just like me dying to watch Wreck-It
Ralph with someone who hasn't seen it
before I don't think there's anybody
that passionate about it but definitely
do you know the plot twist I just felt
it in rap news I knew it would be here
you know when King Candy has the glasses
on oh can you go on the group account
no I'm gonna just leave it here flat now
I have my Poke Plus going on I really
can't be with you guys if you're gonna
just dedicate your life
sponsored Pokey pluses they catch the
Pokemon I can't like I need help dude
talked about this in that New Hampshire
Vlog yeah no [ __ ] dude that's all you've
been doing I bet you like Matt would
like trade mine like something that
really means near and dear to me like
math that's like to trade in like a
family heirloom for like a little like
Pokemon thing that's like rare no no no
he would yeah definitely like it's like
true okay dude a shiny Mew or like my
[ __ ] favorite pair of shoes
well no I don't need the I'm already on
my quest to get a shiny meat I want to
earn it
I'm already on already on Quest someone
straight up said most of us would have a
pet tiger if we could
that's
looking for a [ __ ] who's most of
us speak for yourself
to dot Matt sorry I keep singing because
I'm just I didn't think it was gonna
bring this back to you but shut up Matt
the other day I saw Nick fold a blanket
just to unfold it and use it like
moments later not true yeah it was Los
Angeles California in our home Nick why
the other day yeah the other day he
folded off in the other day when it's
like four five six two weeks ago
80 year old
mother on the bus for a nickel
obviously I can say the other day the
other day Nick [ __ ] folds a blanket
puts it away in the little basket we own
and then it's like Chris can you pass me
a blanket I go no and he gets up and
takes the exact blanket that he just
folded to unfold it I disagree I'm
telling you what I saw it's not a
disagree moment
it was a disagree moment no it wasn't it
was a full-blown disagreement
how do you deem something a disagree
moment I'm disagreeing with you
in my eyes that's a [ __ ] disagree
moment it's not a disagree moment I saw
it happen
there's no disagree or agree moment I
disagree do you get what I'm saying that
was like the first time I was like I was
fully in thought right there just what
about like Pokemon that probably thinks
like the weirdest [ __ ] like I don't know
I was thinking like whoa wait wait who
did I tell I had who did I tell about my
dream when I woke up today wasn't it
crazy would that be worth telling them I
don't remember who did I tell did I tell
you
I woke up and told one of you about my
dream life I think it was me but I
forgot what did I say I don't know I
just said I forget like like car names
like when they like in the in the shop
and they're like oh you want the CMOS
green
car
who's doing that someone said the
Birkenstock clogs are ugly go [ __ ]
yourself oh the clogs might be the
Boston ones are fire
are those with the clog is no those are
fire those are really cool if you think
these are ugly reevaluate yourself you
got serious issues you're ugly I think a
lot of people like like me in the past
like high school me who wore sweatpants
and hoodies every day would have called
like everything I wear now ugly and that
just shows like okay yeah I'm doing the
right thing if past me would be a little
bit embarrassed about it I know I'm
doing good yeah I put a vest on and it
changed my life one day when do you want
to tell us about it I feel like
well it wasn't like a yeah you sent one
or no here's the Texas I need me a
Bucky's pot pie sandwich or no just like
pulled pork what if I was a news
reporter I'd have to be in like Gumdrop
land because I think that'd be so hard
like if I was the news for like if it
rained gumballs I'd be really stoked
about it
um I'm sure the whole [ __ ] world
no like it would be in such a State of
shock for everyone I'm sure if it was
like raining gumdrops and Skittles and
y'all turn on your TV and it was just me
I was like guys I can't believe it a
fruit roll-up just landed on my [ __ ]
left shoulder and if you look to the
would you I think you had to be wearing
a colorful suit buddy
whatever comes that day oh yeah I'm
gonna just have my [ __ ] in case of
gum drop buddies I would but he's just
reading us but he's just reading us the
script to Cloudy with a Chance of
Meatballs and things no I'm [ __ ] not
dude literally no
[ __ ] title yeah there's definitely more
than a chance of [ __ ] meatballs how
about food storm
the massive great food store I love that
all right guys thank you so much for
tuning in this Friday we'll see food on
your head
we'll see you next Wednesday and then
next Friday and podcast every Monday
peace and love cut the camera podcast on
yellowclothing.com got new pajamas today
look real soft tell me how soft those
are
real soft real soft
look out of here