you want your sea heater on no what
level no off completely I'm y action
hold on no y action yet hold on we got a
mew I'm not meing me is not real I don't
know I don't know how to explain this to
you anymore meing is not real Matt is
like King me by the way I'm not King Mew
yes you are the other day actually mega
evolved
[Laughter]
Mewtwo um I just want to start this car
video out by saying for 2025 do you guys
have any New Year's resolutions cuzz I
have some I know you guys are were
probably expecting a 2024 recap that's
going to be next week the one resolution
that I have is to throw Les resolution
is that the worst is is to throw less
Tantrums as a 21-year-old I think that's
a good idea because I'm really afraid
yeah like when you whenever you like
kind of lash out mhm or Unleash the
Beast I know he's gone on what do they
go in zootopia when they get hit with
the thing um no but I do just want to
take this time to apologize
to absolutely nobody I you're going to
say that can I just say a couple things
and I don't want to we must address your
heinous Behavior Matt I like the cowboy
one sorry sorry sorry sorry I'd murder
him why is he
playing no because this is crazy this
just shows Matt is violent no I like to
show this cowboys while sorry sorry
sorry sorry i' murder him I didn't see
you
go grab your calendars and another gift
for somebody else to open actually slice
my face pay attention go you need to
learn about the word
accidents and the word
sorry I got so quiet and awkward that
was
scary
okay what so loud I'm scared all right
in today's video guys we react to this
clip a lot so you should see it break
down the first of all I bought Matt the
coffee maker as a joke cuz he doesn't
drink coffee so people were like Nick
put so much thought into like an
expensive gift that they would all
utilize that was a GI for yourself I was
[ __ ] joking everything I bought in
wrapped for Matt and Chris I bought for
my pure and only my benefit it might not
look like it touched me but Chris it did
no it hit Matt's eye and the thing
that's so funny to me too is Chris
literally goes I'd kill him Matt wasn't
going to hit me and then Chris said he
would kill me and then that's when Matt
hit me I think is so funny you can see
in Matt's brain that he wasn't going to
hit me and Chris literally provoked it
you guys are mad at Chris told Chris
said he kill me this is my takea away
from the whole situation Nick you have
to be more careful of your surroundings
so you shouldn't hoist something towards
someone's face I always do that another
thing another thing Matt's Flinch in
reaction you can see it first of all it
hit his cheek and anyone it's so funny
that anyone anyone I always tell you I
hate when you hit the back of my head if
you're going to hit me aim somewhere
else hitting I I can't look at you in
the eyes and smack you across I'd rather
take it on the chin than across the like
my [ __ ] brain okay wow you know what
I mean no but actually to everybody that
made videos about it um whether positive
or negative thank you so much cuz I
really needed the good laugh so I really
appreciate it no I know that this is so
dramatic because it's like okay wind it
back Jack in the Box like you're doing
too much right but I was really thinking
like really really
thinking and I was like we're back home
with our family and I was like like I'm
getting emotional and upset because the
reason is like I don't let people's
opinions or people's words genuinely
affect me and I truly believe that I do
not I'm past that point but what does
affect me is when I look back at things
and I think of things so differently
than how I did in the past and this is
like so randomly dramatic and I
apologize for it I think of me and Matt
and me and Matt 6 years ago and me and
Matt seven years ago and the difference
in our Dynamic and the difference in our
relationship and how it's constantly
changing is like I every single day when
I wake up no matter how bad of a day it
is for me and Matt or me and you and
we're arguing with each other or
anything nothing can be worse than a
position we were once in before anyone
on the internet knew us you know what I
mean and that's what I think of at the
end of the day is no matter what these
[ __ ] goon Goblin disgusting monsters
on the internet say about us they will
never understand the experiences we've
been through before we posted together
on the internet and I wake up every
single day and no matter if me and Matt
argue or not I'm blessed to be in a
position I am with Matt today I couldn't
and I'm so thankful said it better
myself I don't think always think of
that I always think of that cuz I'm like
every single day and us being roommates
and us being best friends is truly wait
you call me your best friend truly the
only thing I care about you guys should
and so theil the evil mean person inside
me do you want to know what wants to say
oh shut your [ __ ] mouth yes I know
but too much no and that's what the no
cuz that's what the mean horrible person
inside of me would say I didn't say that
the the mean person inside of me would
say if you're buting into business
that's not yours you're a loser and a
freak but I would never say that so
instead I'm just going to say I'm
blessed and thankful to be in the
position I'm in today wow okay personal
goals 2025 um my personal goals in 2025
I don't know I I I want my personal
goals to be just finding myself more and
more every day oh Chris well guess what
tomorrow you're going to know more about
yourself than you did today so real it's
because no like thinking about my
current status and then thinking of my
year ago who I was status no I do feel
on lately but um I don't even know what
that means I just saw on the internet I
thought I'd hop on the trend I thought
I'd maybe try like the kids but no
seriously I like see myself from a year
ago and I'm like I'm like joke was ass
fit was Goofy what was I doing like I
constant have those thoughts especially
being those thoughts so like shut your
mouth especially posting so much on the
internet I'm like I always have thoughts
of like damn what was I wearing what was
I doing this that like these are when
you look in the mirror like a
year you I every since time walk in like
the kitchen I'm like what is this goofy
ha what is your hair I did not have that
feeling at the end of 2025 but Chris the
thing is you will always I always will
but I want to be able to see and be like
oh that was a respectable choice at the
time there's something I see it and I'm
like that was not a respectable choice
at all I cannot respect past me for
wearing that for doing that for etc etc
whatever that's another let me finish
let me
finish when I see clips of me from it's
like our second video ever I'm like oh
my God I just want to likeing Big Flash
gone forever like that's the thing is
people take our clips and my thoughts
and my sayings the start YouTube time
and they're like oh throw back to this
and I'm like see but this is where I've
been at and call me a hippie freak cuz
this is where my brain has been but I
think of like like how how happy I was
like and truly expressive back then and
I'm like now am I just trying to like AE
cooler and like hop on the trend because
I think that that's what people want or
am I actually genuinely expressing
myself and that's a battle I face where
I'm like I'd rather feel like a 100
people are looking at me and being like
what the [ __ ] is going on but having the
sheer Joy of not giving a [ __ ] about not
about that but it's mostly other things
like some things I say in past videos I
disagree with you do that when you like
take a second to
think yeah I don't know it's no that's
what I hate when I when there's like a
video clip of me and I may have said
something like oh I don't like cheese on
my French fries and then there's like a
video of me [ __ ] four years later
eating cheese on french fries and
someone's like Nick but you said you
only chat on french fries what the [ __ ]
I'm like [ __ ] 4 years have passed
I've been alive for 21 correct my
[ __ ] opinion has changed oh I'd say
oh I would never wear like all black
shoes oh God forbid strike me with
lightning I get a pair of black shoes a
[ __ ] half a decade later you [ __ ]
insane person pulling up like like as if
you're like proving some crazy point
like no but Nick no but they're they're
they're not even disagreeing with me
they're prying past me to come
they're getting the past me to present
itself to me now I'm like you think me
then knew better correct well at some
point you're not even disagreeing with
me you're trying to show me that like
this thing that I once said you're
holding it over me it's like if I said
oh I don't like carrots and I they catch
me eating carrots they're not even mad
they're not even like bro you're eating
carrots I thought you didn't like
carrots they're like here's concrete
evidence of you saying you don't like
carrots and it's like God forbid I eat a
[ __ ] orange vegetable here and there
yeah you sick
freak sorry I didn't know you this no CU
it instantly
flashes reminding me at some point in
your life you were you were straight so
think about
that that makes things so much worse I
forget my opinion actually matters to
you there I say [ __ ] cuz I'm just
speaking I love I'm just speaking
there's there the new thing Nick's doing
is I walk in his room earlier and I said
something and he goes like
incorrect statement yeah I love that
it's like so crazy okay hold on so end
that conversation that was your New
Year's resolution yeah New Year's
resolution Nick you got any just like be
nicer every day and and like do more
that you want to do every day I'm not
going to say like go to the gym every
day and like say some hard ass answer
that I like won't maybe fulfill and I
believe if you do that it puts more of a
restraint like I'd rather leisurely
become healthier than like demanding it
on Jan I think New Year's resolution are
a scam and I think that they're a cheapo
way to pretend you're doing better okay
but with that being said my New Year's
resolution is maybe to I'm thinking
like really scared too I I have a crazy
goal that I told Krist and I can't share
on the internet oh I remember this from
a while ago at a friend's house yes yeah
can I hear it but yeah you can tell them
go on a date with
was yeah wow my actual New Year's
resolution is to take the piece of me
that is like has like deep social
anxiety and fear of like going out and
like my like fear of like leaving the
house and trying new things and brutally
murder it and destroy it and body bag it
and tag it I I love bag and tag that's
I'm going to destroy and kill my social
anxiety love that someone could got that
clip short
I am cuz I there's nothing I want more
to than to go
into my head held high like there's
lasers in my head that will destroy any
seeking person out in the audience of
the target oh I want to be I'm a be I'm
I'm a be I want to just be kinder I
guess and maybe a little more patient
what's yours Matt I think my New Year's
resolution is
to do the things that do the things that
really want to and make me the happiest
in life because you only live one life
so it's like why waste your time not
doing the things that you like really
really want to do you know what I if I
want to skydive I want I should be able
to be like let me go Skydive because
it's like I'm I don't want to live a
life of like oh these were all the
things that I wanted to accomplish but
didn't put any effort towards like I
just want to even if I put one day of
activity towards something that like I
actually wanted to do then I want that
for you should but then also my personal
project but that's going to be I want
this so B and thank you for patience for
everybody that cares my other one go
ahead put myself in other people's shoes
more oh you need to do that yes I'm not
doing that I like my shoes my shoes of
delusion I got to put myself in Nick
Nick's Nick's back of his head shoes
that could easily be like a viral audio
that you just made I need to put myself
in people Sho I don't want to do that I
like my shoes oh wait no can we say
something we want to leave behind in
2025 I'm going to say being impulsive
and too quick reacting MH well I want to
settle down on that so many things I'm
like I want to do this and then I do it
and I regret it or like oh I'm going to
like buy this swipe my car and I'm like
I don't want to buy that or like oh piss
me off or mt's pissing me off I'm to
freak out and go crazy nah I I have one
I need to like take a second some more
I'm want put yes on the similar
situation here for me I want to put
thought onto into things that are my
immediate case scenario there's to many
things where I'm like on my phone and
like I'm like just doing
whatever
what when I'm on my phone I'm like take
time in the present yes so like we're
working on something and I'm like
thinking of like a video we're going to
do in like 2 months or like somewhere
we're going in like a year or like what
we're doing in 4 weeks
yeah not even live in the moment but not
worry about what I'm going to do cuz
every time I'm there I'm like this easy
like just move on I like it [ __ ] I
like the color scheme I just feel yeah
you said that twice um oh yeah you have
nothing to say um let's all list a I
think he was going to speak I do too oh
it's something you want to leave mine I
forgot there was still a new point be
careful the thing that I want don't make
I want pee in this okay but I'm not
going to I'm not going to I'm not going
to I want to leave in 2025 I never get
to look at you this the things that that
the things that the things that affect
the decisions I'm going to make in
2025 is what I want is what I want to
leave in 202 puzzling answer is what I
want to leave in
2024 I think no let me don't cut this
out cuz I need to go in depth and make
sense of it I just want to leave behind
the things that are going to stop me
from making the decisions I never did so
if I want to if I want to Sky back that
as an example again I want to leave I
behind the
thoughts of of the thoughts that are
tell not the Skydive found a way to add
long division into that [ __ ] answer I
trying to [ __ ] I want to each list of
thing we want to do as a group in 2025
I'm going to start I'm going to go on a
triplet vacation ooh to where like us3
in like a nice Island Vibe maybe argue
less and be less reactive certain
scenario okay Matt go do together Nick
that wasn't an actual answer no yeah
like what was what did I
say I what did I say nothing go that no
what did I say you needs to give a real
what did I say what do you want to do in
2025 what did I say said be less
reactive and no actually stop arguing be
less reactive I want like as a group I
want to explain ourselves to each other
less and be less reactive like I think
that we're like reactive so it shuns
some of us away from like sharing no no
no like
no no no not I'm not scared of M hitting
me if that needs to be clarified even
more I'm what I'm saying is like less
reactive in a sense of like if like I If
I tell you I'm going to go do something
or you come downstairs in a certain
shirt and I'm like I don't like that
shirt or I I tell you I'm going
somewhere you're like oh really with
like them and like like just making like
like weighing less of an opinion on each
other's situations or outfits or
whatever so that we just and those are
two bad examples but just like I feel
like this is each something that can
stay in the video no that a good group
that's a good one I think I think just
letting each other breathe and like just
figuring things out and just I'll never
let you breathe getting on get it taking
your foot off my
tail and same for mine and yours I think
we're all standing on each other's tails
and we got to like oh that face you you
go something I want to do as a group in
2025 that's the that's what I'm
answering here may I say the four-letter
word that starts with t yeah for sure I
say yes wait CHR that's tour the revised
plan a better plan JY little tripet
comedy show laugh your balls off and if
you don't have balls we give you some
okay go on we give him a bag of marbles
and they laugh and hum marbles through
the air stop that's a bad joke all right
let's actually start our video
um I Nick was complaining the other day
that he doesn't like when people tell
him he looks like Matt or me it just
gives me the vibe of this
okay tell me tell me being a triplet and
being told I look like Matt and Chris
this is what it [ __ ] feels like okay
imagine and everyone you're going to
have to put your [ __ ] feet in someone
else's shoes for a second here imagine
you're a brunette girl who goes to
school down the street and every single
day you walk to this school you wake up
brunette girl mhm go downstairs M your
mom and dad go hey you have brunette
hair your brother go hey you have
brunette hair hey you have to go to
school hey you have to walk down the
street to get to school and then you go
outside I have to walk down street to
down the street to get to school and
it's every single [ __ ] step you take
down the thing you're [ __ ] some
something behind you says hey you got to
keep walking hey you got to keep walking
to get to school down the street hey the
school that's at the end of the street
you got to keep walking to get there hey
you got to keep walking on this Street
to get to [ __ ] school you know this
[ __ ] walking path you're on school's
just up there keep walking on this path
to get to school hey this this path
you're walking on to school keep going
and you'll eventually get to the school
hey this path you're walking on and
you've been walking on for 10 years you
got to keep walking on it you got to
keep going you get to school you're
going to be there
soon a minute of Silence right hey this
path you're walking on you got to keep
walking on it to get to
school hey this path you keep walking on
you got to keep walking on it to get to
school they get it Nick I'd have to say
it a 100 more times 100 100,000 more
times okay so yeah I get it yeah and
that aggravates you yeah I mean I like
it I just love it I just think it's it's
a little obvious
right couldn't be more
apparent it's like getting it's like
murdering someone and getting put in
jail and every single day the guard
comes in and goes hey you guys they're
going to live here for a while you guys
got to stay here for a while thank you
thank you granted we have like 130 car
videos on the internet something
something of the sort someone post a
clip of me and I wore the same shorts in
like five of them Nick loves these
shorts I bought them I bought and own
the [ __ ] shorts and I've posted like
200 something YouTube videos oh didn't
know I had to buy my 200 97th YouTube
video shorts to wear a new pair yeah you
[ __ ] sick freak that's how I feel my
gray sweatshirt oh my God Nick loves
these shorts I'm [ __ ] wearing pants I
own it's well that one they can relate
to cuz that's like the classic like oh
my when you wear the same outfit in the
same string of 5 days at school growing
up and then the kids like I own a
washing machine you know what I mean
yeah just like if I could wear it the
same every day it's like someone's
wearing camo and they're like where's
your
shorts where are your parents Crispy
Cream donut should pop up when you
search
unfair do you remember yeah I didn't
know that you didn't even give him the
background that was that was that
was that was a direct quote from if your
job to give in the background I just
apply the quote yeah I did say that you
also said that eating a crispy donut is
like is like eating a cloud a Crispy
Cream Donut for those you who haven't
had it do you want to know what it's
like I'll show you everyone
go congratulations you just ate a Crispy
Cream [ __ ] donut dead serious those
[ __ ] and I'm not getting paid
are as light and fluffy as a [ __ ]
cloud and they maybe weigh like the
grain of sand holy [ __ ] and they [ __ ]
disappear it's like it's like if coton
candy was a donut I bite into it it's
like oh that's gone that's shoveled down
my throat already slid down my esophagus
literally hurt a [ __ ] into my stomach
acid already broken down I'm going to
[ __ ] that out in a couple hours I like
the shortless Cowboys one the most sorry
sorry sorry sorry I murder him that was
absolutely so unbelievably unnecessary
shut your mouth and literally go get a
job could you imagine how he's in in
other videos too go watch him yeah let
me know y'all treating him like this is
play fighting he pieced him up over a
mistake you want to see it again I will
never I refuse to be allowed to be
described as pieced up by Matt this
[ __ ] would never piece me up I
pieced you up this what y'all mad about
with a question mark great question Matt
is such a middle child and it
shows those 2 minutes really crushed
down on
the way Nick was kind of scared Matt has
never scared me ever in his life that's
why you never mess with Matt oh oh he
over he overreacted a bit but it wasn't
that serious I agree I fully I saw
people saying it was terrifying like if
you were terrified of this please make
sure you never see a PG-13 movie or
above and bring your mother everywhere
you go cuz [ __ ] life has got some
really scary things hit him on on the
head which that's like kind of a brother
thing and then he threw the head thing
was worse than me throwing the head
thing was kind of a brother thing bro it
literally felt like when they a Looney
Tune hits the other with a thing I was
like I was seeing birds and my [ __ ]
head was on a tornado no that was the
worst part of it being hit in the head
if I was in that room I also would have
gotone quiet and it would have been
really awkward like it looked it would
have been awkward if you were there that
is terrifying I don't can I borrow your
phone really quick please I'm not going
to do anything look I just want to show
them
this problem
[Laughter]
solved you are insane my fears are gone
me hat and Chris have a actually a good
heart so we think let's not react to
someone who's actively talking about us
on the internet cuz we don't want our
fans to go and yell and berid at them
right yeah but then I think about it I'm
like you're talking about
me it's a two-way street and you're in a
[ __ ] car and I'm pummeling down that
[ __ ] in a bullet
train come on I'm sick of this [ __ ] my
God this is it Nick's a psychopath huh
Nick a crazy person yeah I guess so I
also I just need people to
know when we're filming a video and I'm
joking and I'm yelling this is me with
my brothers speaking my truth joking
around I don't give a [ __ ] is rule
number one and Rule and point number two
is I don't act like this when I'm not
filming or when I'm not with Matt and
Chris cuz people like have this belief
or fantasy that I'm on constant crash
out I'm filming an entertaining video
cuz I love to do it and that's why I'm
freaking the [ __ ] out I do not give a
[ __ ] and I need that to be known
something that I've learned in my life
everybody has one of these and it's not
an
[ __ ] it's an opinion some of them are
going to align with yours and some of
them aren't but we all got to put our
shoes on and walk out the front door
tomorrow or the back door I don't know
which way you leave your house I'm not
all right on a final thank you guys so
much on Final note 2024 was a [ __ ]
awesome year 2024 recap next week and
thank you so much for coming to 2025
with us for real means a lot also um
before we end the video we have a merch
drop that might still be available on
our website right now we couldn't do a a
photo shoot for it because we were
traveling home for the holidays but it's
still available probably we did a bigger
inventory because it's the holiday
season and we wanted people to have the
longer chance to buy it peace out
everyone have a good year Nick can you
please insert the video at the end of
this video of this of me acting like
King Candy of course I can put it in the
photo d actually for this week
[Music]