all right go check it damn seat heater
too kid your nuts must be sweating
[Music]
too kids literally had the heat on Mega
Blast why why oh my God oh my God who's
what is this damn an empty monster and
an empty Red Bull what a night for neck
separate nights oh separate nights so
clear the cup holders out what are they
still doing throw them away this one was
just now this one was yesterday and that
one should be thrown away and this
should be thrown away when we get home
okay well where am I where am I now
you're out Nick you look like this
pickup truck right here your mother yet
again we have the same um why does he
have a caution sticker on if he comes
over here I might actually might be my
last straw like might be the completion
of all my straws I might disappear oh
he's letting out his
dogs and they're
sniffing I think his truck literally
says caution K9 and now his Kines are
just running about hello another person
Hi get the [ __ ] away from our car what's
your [ __ ] issue [ __ ] oh she going to
hit the can9 dog people believe [ __ ]
that people definitely don't believe
[ __ ] that's happening around us this
lady this guy pulls in his truck opens
the door and lets [ __ ] eight dogs out
and they're like running around pissing
everywhere and and this lady just drove
over and about to
hit he's like yelling at his dogs in
German or something what the [ __ ] is she
doing put the window up what are you
doing I'm trying to talk about him you
have the window down she like decide
this lady's weird as [ __ ] she pulls in
and parks next to this poor Soul's car
like what are you doing I hear people
driving around looking like they ate a
[ __ ] Warhead like
this like go [ __ ] can I have a ment
nope you can't you'll get them as treats
if you make a good joke okay oh now he's
talking oh are they oh they're
mutuals they're mutuals Chris yeah they
know each other oh are you Jan from
Facebook Messenger well welcome back to
the stol tripet car videos with
Christmas festivities wow you couldn't
sound more unentertained Merry Christmas
it's December 1st and today starts our
Christmas Extravaganza we don't have a
name for it yet and is the first video
of it that we're filming so that's why I
am just saying that I don't know what
we're going to I like it Christmas
Extravaganza I feel like there's nothing
else that it is no no no it's like the
the stola triplet holiday special okay
we have some options that we can couple
contenders yeah as you can see I'm
wearing my all red Christmas attire I
hate the shirt I'm in um and it doesn't
fit me well but a white shirt I thought
it was fun to be in all red ready for
I'm really distracted by this wa they
just [ __ ] they just [ __ ] my God the
dogs just [ __ ] they did quick they did
[ __ ] each other it was like a look
look it oh man the lighter and again
here we go oh oh my God anyways we're
here again for another Friday try get
away this is not good all right we're
here again for another Friday video with
the some we're putting a fun festive
Twist on a video that we've done in the
past called Anonymous confessions this
one I posted an Instagram story and
asked you guys for your Christmas
confessions and I know that some of you
don't celebrate so I also put a
disclaimer about like any holiday um
confession that you have Hanukkah
whatever you celebrate I just cuz that's
our Hol but we are going to read some of
your guys Christmas and holiday
confessions every year near Christmas I
go to a hotel with my family and cousins
they were having a firework show and we
bought lanterns to set off L you don't
set lanterns off anyway have you ever
gone to a hotel that had a firework show
no have you ever set a lantern off they
they're bringing the fireworks
essentially yeah but why do they they do
a fireworks show there's no fireworks
show happening already and they happen
to approach it they are the fireworks
yeah but I've never seen someone do
fireworks for Christmas let them [ __ ]
live like go build a snowman or
something why else would you do
fireworks go play in the snow come on we
can't be doing this about every single
one shut up
Mt basically for what you wish for shut
up oh that's my biggest wish shut your
mouth mhm did my wish come true mhm
I didn't have to blow out any
candles I stumbled on my words I meant
to say I didn't even have to blow out
any candles they're going to say that he
can't blow out any candles cuz his Mt is
shot basically the whole hotel was
watching when we were setting them off
and one of them got stuck in the bushes
and almost set a bush on fire and and
the hotel luckily we got it out but the
way everyone gased was so funny and
still makes me laugh to this day the
hotel should kick you out and say never
come back you crazy Fox serious L yeah
shut up if I'm doing fireworks I'm going
to do them in my own proximity I'm not
going to go to a hotel and set Fireworks
off fireworks are like a personal
experience you know what about that one
night we went to canes and they're
setting off fireworks that was crazy
ridiculous you remember that the Roman
candles and they were shooting there was
caniacs everywhere they were fil fueled
up on cane sauce and ready to [ __ ]
light each other off imagine going to
get chicken you're like hey can I get a
box combo Bing Bow boom Roman Candle
popped in your teeth I walked in on
Santa giving my dad head on Christmas
Eve that's a real confession that wasn't
Santa no way that was probably your
mother even if it was Santa I feel like
he would have sprinkled some magic like
dust so you didn't see him do it you
know no way Santa's letting you he's
delivering presents all these [ __ ]
years but someone's going to catch him
giving someone like no if we're catching
Santa it's in the act of giving gift
under a tree I giving anyway I don't
celebrate Christmas but I celebrate
Hanukkah and a couple years ago I
celebrated Hanukkah at my aunt's house
and my cousin shot me in the mouth with
a play gun and two of my teeth fell out
and I end up the [ __ ] what type of play
gun was it a BB gun Dark Gun I feel like
if you do anything with something light
with enough passion it would do some
action
come those girls in our school you're
going to say Dr Su like you're going to
know who I'm talking about when those
girls at our school yeah
dummies huh you're stupid I know exactly
what you're talking about set
firecrackers off in their car and it lit
on fire no that I'm we're moving on from
that I was talking about the girl who
threw the muffin at her sister and her
sister's nose blood I'm like a muffin
making your nose bleed oh I would have
to try at least the scone like scones
are way harder than muffins what about a
brick okay that's a good that's a great
alternate Matt yeah if you really want
to make someone if you really want to
hurt them I was more shocked at the fact
that it made someone bleed but we can go
with that if you what would be your
pastry weapon of choice
eclair stck you in the face cream is
going everywhere you can see the radius
of your shot when I was a kid I would
download hold on I would download x-ray
apps to see what so that I could see
what my gifts were but it never worked
oh I wonder why that's actually really
funny when I was little you the extra
you're weird I was a bad kid and so and
so for that Santa would always bring me
a box of rocks damn you got coal damn
girl and and then she said I remember
getting so angry and tired of getting
rocks one year I wrote a letter
explaining all the horrible things I
would do to him if he brought me more
rocks basically sent him a death threat
you didn't learn your goddamn lesson
[ __ ] I feel like you'd get more rocks
correct oh yeah let me just send Santa a
[ __ ] death note and how about I'm
deeply sorry that I deserved these rocks
correct let me do something about my bum
ass
attitude oh let me brighten up the day a
death threat to Santa is never going to
help you get what you want I used to put
oatmeal outside my porch for the
reindeer and I would always catch my dad
eating it oh [ __ ] gross was he on the
porch like eating it I guess imagine dad
like on all fours like eating
oatmeal oatmeal disgusts me and I don't
even think the [ __ ] reindeers want it
why are you giving the reindeer
something they don't want and give them
carrots celery even cookies I bet you
they're S as reindeers they probably eat
cookies probably when I was like eight
or nine I was snooping around for my
Christmas gifts because my sister said
she would give me one of her gifts if I
told her what she got for Christmas what
a stupid [ __ ] godamn exchange I was
looking for Christmas gifts but instead
I found my mom's toys and other strange
artifact in a drawer and walked out
traumatized and completely forgot about
my hunt for the G gifts my level of
curiosity ended that
day stop looking any of that the word
artifact through me yeah artifact really
threw me off yeah like what is there a
vase or something or hieroglyphic
password to get into the thing literally
I don't know if it's crazy enough but I
found I find the amusement of going to a
shopping center on Christmas Eve like
the that very morning I go alone to walk
through the hallways and just stare at
the last minute Christmas Chaos I may be
insane but I love you yes I think you
are I kind of love that I think you if I
saw someone just stalking in a [ __ ]
mall not a particular person but just
loving the pure chaos that is last
minute christas like you are weird I
kind of love that that so like if I got
a group of friends that were on the same
crazy enough mindset as me I would
absolutely do this that's actually like
really troubling to me like I'm kind of
stick to my stomach let me read it again
if I like if I knew who wrote that I'd
avoid them at all costs they go on to
CHR they go to the shopping center on
Christmas Eve like that very morning and
walk alone through the hallways and just
stare at the last minute Christmas the
typ the type the way it's typed out too
like imagine walking I just picture her
walking through the hallway with like a
big old black long trench coat and
glasses brings them a smile watching I
just like I just think about all the
like other things you could be doing to
celebrate on Christmas Eve then go watch
like I know she's murmuring under her
breath like as people run out like last
minute like oh she's
like that's actually [ __ ] creepy my
mom and dad got married when I was like
8 years old and it was close to
Christmas on Christmas Eve my mom said I
could open one gift and my dad had
wrapped all of them like colorcoded my
mom didn't know which color was mine so
she assumed that I knew what color was
mine I ended up opening one of my Mom's
gifts from my dad and it had pink fluffy
handcuffs and a toy in it we never
opened up presents early
again or why is your father why is your
father first of all why is that at
access to you that's a gift you give
someone if you must in like behind
closed doors AG it should never hit
under the chist ever ever ever secondly
cuz like secondly your dad colorcoded it
and for
what if she like what if she didn't open
it then then would would the mom have
opened it in front of everyone that's
what I'm saying that's what I'm
thinking Dr Christmas of 2020 two of my
uncles almost started physically
fighting because Uncle number one asked
Uncle number two what year he graduated
college must have been a sore subject
because Uncle two literally lunged
across the dinner table in front of my
whole family and had to be held back by
my other family members I still have no
idea why that question s spurred such a
reaction he probably didn't graduate and
he feels stupid by the question damn I
kind of like live for like other
people's family
drama I love a little bit of chaos weird
no no I think it's so fun like I'd love
to avoid it happening in my personal
life but just something about two uncles
fighting at a Christmas Eve is just like
oh it doesn't get better than that
that's like the [ __ ] like would you
get Santa milk and
cookies don't get this reference at
all four years ago on the 25th night my
grandmother stayed for the night in my
bunk bed are we calling Christmas the
25th night is that what's going on here
I yeah
so 4 years ago the 25th night my my
grandma stayed for the night in my bunk
during the night my dad went to the
bathroom and when he flushed the toilet
my grandma got so scared that she woke
up thought that someone was in her own
bed and then so it thought that she was
in her own bed and that somebody was
bringing into her house so she started
screaming like crazy and while she was
trying to get off the bed she fell from
5T hitting the floor badly so she was on
the top bunk and she thought somebody
broke her their house she'll be fine
Grandma's good I can't believe she would
do that on the 25th night I feel like
old B I feel like I almost said old
babies I feel like elderly people and
like babies are just like okay with
anything happening like they could be
sucker punched in the face and they just
have like a fine reaction I strongly
disagree what this one year me and all
my siblings and cousins went to sleep
with my grandma's during Christmas break
and one night we were in the living room
and we were
all what you know when you sleep at like
your grandma's and they just got that
scent like of your grandma okay we were
all wearing I feel like every grandma
got a scent but like a good scent like
it's a nostalgic SC I feel like every
person got a scent no but especially
Grandma's you got a
scent okay we were all wearing onesies
so one of my cousins was wearing a
unicorn one and my grandma's dog started
dragging her by the unicorn horn across
the living room and what's even worse is
none of us helped her because we were
all
laughing one time I gave my little
cousin's kid wine sparkling grape juice
and I told them it was real alcohol and
they started acting crazy and told
everyone that they were drunk that's
that's my favorite type of thing ever I
really want to have like a little kid
just so I can do that like I just want
to give them F like root beer and be
like oh my God you're getting drunk and
like see what they do you're a sicko how
that's so funny it's the placebo effect
bro that is [ __ ] hilarious these
little kids think they're getting
hammered I feel like that's something
new and me and Nick could trick you like
nowadays what what are you saying to me
mat I think is very competent to not
yeah like what am I
stupid I would love to [ __ ] you when you
you guys have kids I'm going to when you
guys should have kids and they come to
my house I'm going to start telling them
things that are just like not facts
about you guys so that when they get way
older and you tell them like stories and
stuff they're going to have like this
set in stone vision of what they think
they know about you like I'll tell
Matt's kids like oh like he used to be
like an astronaut and he flew all the
way to like the moon and he walked on
the moon and he had this crazy
experience with the love of his life and
they were on the moon they were growing
the I'm going to tell Matt's kids guys
Matt's super kindhearted and talkative
and he just like loves everybody and
they're going to expect no but then
they're going to be like my dad went to
the moon like tell their friends like
100% like it's true and then they'll go
to you and be like the kids at school
don't believe me that you went to the
moon and then you'll also and I'll just
gasl your kid into thinking they're
crazy awesome great plan from Uncle Nick
yes funcle Nick don't call me that
Mick's going to be the fun Uncle we
already decided no Nick when my brother
was like two and he was sitting in the
tree for pictures and we looked away
from legit for legit 3 seconds and he
had pulled the entire thing down and
like fully knocked it over the tree the
cousin Hercules all of our all of our
ornaments broke oh the Christmas tree I
didn't get it either I was thinking like
an oak me too I fully thought we were
outside all of our ornaments my God I
was confused why she said the tree like
what is it the golden Christmas tree
okay when I was little I would love
sitting underneath the tree and looking
at all the lives from the bottom I also
had had
the I also had the intent to catch Santa
so I took my iPad and I hid it in the
tree to catch him but when we were
opening presents from Santa the iPad
fully just fell out of the tree and
broke like glass three ornaments and it
had to go to the emergency room oh it
broke three ornaments and she had to go
to the emergency I was about to say why
did you take your iPad in the Emer room
sounds kind of Dr catch it and the iPad
fell over so take it to Apple Care it
was just recording the tree and it
didn't work you guys for trying to catch
[Laughter]
Santa you're Terri so weird once I was 6
years old oh God I walked into my
mother's room to grab shoes because I
always left them in there and I went in
the closet cuz I was saw some wrapping
paper so I was going to pick it up for
her I was going to be nice and then I
accidentally hit my head off the shelf
and my elves fell on off off the shelf
my elves fell off the shelf okay did
Peter Piper pick them back up like put
on pepper like literally what's going on
Christmas I bit a mall Santa my aunt
cheated on her husband with her cousin
she and her cousin she and her cousin
was drunk but that don't make the
situation any better it
don't is this Christmas related or is
this just on her chest and she has to
get it off yeah I think this is just a
little bit of a venting St yeah I think
she just really felt like she needed to
tell somebody I'm sorry that's terrible
we just really avoided the cin shout out
cousin when I was six was the first time
I ever slept walked and experienced Deja
Vu I was 7 years old and loved the
Jackson 5 in their version of I Saw
Mommy Kissing Santa Claus Christmas Eve
I had vivid dreams where I went
downstairs in the middle of the night
thinking I heard Santa when I got to the
bottom of the steps I saw Santa laying
out gifts for me along with three blonde
ladies in red dresses and Santa hats
sounds like Dad handling some business I
couldn't speak but I could walk around
and touch stuff the song I Saw Mommy
Kissing Santa Claus started playing and
they started performing this whole dance
routine for me while I was continuing to
put out presents each Lady this is a
horror movie each lady pulled out a
Missle tone and kiss Santa on the cheek
at different points in the song
throughout this performance I could see
what some of the girls were let what
gifts were what on the gifts were an Ice
Age the Meltdown DVD an American Girl
doll a new bike what I remember or what
I remember I could see vividly I gave
Santa and one of the ladies a big hug
and after pulling back they they sat
down on the couch I got a better look at
the lady's face started to look just
like my mother's side note my parents
are divorced so the idea of my mom
kissing Santa Claus wasn't really creepy
it was funny still weird but it wasn't
like I had never seen her kiss someone
who wasn't my dad LOL Christmas morning
came and I was I woke up in my bed
upstairs and was going over how crazy
and realistic that dream was I went to
wake up my mom and my an and we went
downstairs to the living room to start
opening presents the first thing I
pulled out of the stocking no joke was
none other than the Ice Age the melt
down DVD as I made my way through
presents I also found an American Girl
doll under the tree unwrapped but in a
brand new box it was crazy that both of
these things were in my dream I didn't
see the bike anywhere though it would
have been perfect it would have been
pretty hard to miss it was outside sorry
but it was fine because I got a lot of
other great stuff my mom asked me to
help her with breakfast in the kitchen
when I got back to the living room my
nana had rolled out this awesome purple
bike with white wheels and tassels on
the handles bar and I screamed I knew it
I knew it I knew there was a bike
somewhere at this point I'm freaking out
and rambling on about how I saw this in
a dream I was so excited and they were
so confused later on when I calmed down
my nana asked me how I knew I was
getting a bike when I didn't ask for one
I told her I saw it in my dreams and
explained that in the details of the
dreams as best as I could she's then the
one who told me I must have been
sleepwalking and subconsciously looking
for presents now for the deja vu around
March of April or 2007 my mom started
seeing this guy the first time I ever
met him and he was at my house and my
nana had just brought me home from dance
class guy we were all going to have
dinner I walked and saw him sitting on
the couch in our living room with my mom
and my jaw physically dropped I swear on
my papa's grave that he was the young
version of Santa in my dream I hadn't
really thought about the dream in months
but in that moment it felt like the
events were so real in that dream and I
was having dja Vu without even realizing
what dja Vu was now I constantly you
can't have dja Vu unless you live the
memory now I constantly think about that
dream every you can't have pre Deja Vu
no that wasn't Deja Vu that was like
[ __ ] that was a
miracle Christmas miracle that was a
Christmas miracle that was you being a
psychic yeah you're a medium you're
literally you're literally like you're
Santa you're above all like you're like
right here and everyone else is here and
you can just see all see through the
veil yeah that was crazy to me
predicting your gift had a really great
like I was reading a novel like you're
great like punctuation and stuff I was
like getting a little
chills I predict that on the next full
moon I'll come out okay as a werewolf
what's more Christmasy than sledding my
siblings and I decided to go sledding on
the sand dunes I don't know why what's
more Christmas me than
sledding I said Christmas Le I don't
know why but we um what's more Christmas
than Sting with a hot cocoa and some
cookies
you're going to make me throw up like
Nick's the type of guy to go hot cocoa
yay look at that I would never why would
I [ __ ] do that cuz you love hug Coco
No I don't Nick you're I hate you tell
me [ __ ] I like like to say do Ty to say
hot cocoa instead of hot chocolate like
oh can I have a hot cocoa you're talking
about hot coco you would order it like
that that's why I thought I was I would
never in my entire physical presence in
this being life go to like if if we
stopped at Dunkin Donuts I'd be like
Nick go get me a hot chocolate you'd
walk up to the coun can I have two hot
CH hot Cocos yes he I would never say
Coco what size large please two large
hot Cocos can I have three large hot
Cocos with this Emoji okay I have to ask
one of you guys cuz I don't know if this
is like something I made up in my head
that church that we used to sled at did
yeah yes under the car which one of us
it was me I think it was me me I thought
it was me I'm 90% sure it was me I don't
know 90% sure it was it might have been
you 90% sure it was me we went sledding
and there was a car going by and I
literally went underneath the car
through like through right by it it
didn't get hit my life flashed I vividly
remember it actually all right my turn
oh no video's over good job though um
thank you guys so much for watching this
you're going to get coal and no hot
cocoa
oh no hot chocolate and no presents and
[ __ ] in your
stocking shocking [ __ ] in
youring W you're gross sant's elves I'm
to count them all one by one until I hit
a million cuz I'm so bored and I just
love Christmas o one elf two elf three
elf give me a hot cocoa I want a
treehouse I want it all I want
everything I want every gift I want a
little bike I want a game system I want
a PS4 my God stay tuned for the rest of
our Christmas Extravaganza yes it's just
starting guys real little Christmas
[Music]
yeah