[Applause]
Next into the tank is a stylish upgrade
to an everyday appliance.
[Music]
Hi Sharks. I'm Elise. And I'm Sam. And
we're seeking $600,000 for 3% of our
company, Rocco. Actually, Sam, before we
get started, I'm a little thirsty. Why
don't you just go grab a drink from my
kitchen fridge over there? One second,
Sharks. I'm so sorry. There should be a
soda in there. You might just have to
dig dig a little bit. Oh. Oh,
I hate it when that happens. I can't
find anything in here. There's
leftovers. There's produce. Where's the
drinks? I think it should be behind the
lasagna or or the pizza box, maybe.
That's embarrassing.
Sharks, as you can see, kitchen fridges
are crowded. They're cluttered. They're
just plain chaotic. That's why we
created the Roco Super Smart Drinks
fridge. It's designed as furniture so
you can keep all of your favorite drinks
away from those leftovers. And where you
actually drink them, in the living room.
You might be thinking, "This is just
another wine fridge." Sorry, Mr.
Wonderful, but nobody just drinks wine
anymore. We created a one-of-a-kind
shelving system that accommodates all
sizes of bottles and cans. Everything
from ginger shots to champagne. The top
doubles as a pour serve store station,
aka it's also a bar cart. And with our
patent pending site system, you can even
see inside your fridge right from your
phone. Imagine you're at the grocery
store. You're having friends over later
and you can't remember if you have
enough beer. Now, all you have to do is
look at the app and you'll know exactly
how much you need. So, Sharks, who's
ready to do a deal and pop some
champagne?
All right. I know what's coming. All
right. You know what's coming. You know
what's coming.
[Applause]
And in front of you are the um trays
that come with the fridge to kind of
turn it into a bar cart. How much is the
fridge? The fridge is $14.95 and we
currently offer early access pricing of
$12.95. Is that a lot for a basic? As a
matter of fact, I just bought two not of
yours. I didn't know about yours, but of
a different one. And I will tell you,
yours is the right price and what the
guy was trying to sell me was three
times as much. How does the app work? Do
I actually see into the fridge? So,
every time you put something in or take
it out, it automatically images it. No
scanning whatsoever. And your app will
update. So, so I see shelf. Shelf by
shelf. That's an innovation I haven't
seen. Now, tell us about the two of you.
Yes. So, Sam and I have a combined 20
years of experience in startups. I cold
emailed Casper, the mattress company,
and I helped build the brand from the
ground up. Then I went to Billy, the
women's razor brand, which sold a few
years ago to one of the biggest CPG
companies. Sam spent many years at Away
leading supply chain and product
development. And while he was at Away,
the suitcase brand, his work actually
took him to fridge factories because,
believe it or not, there are
manufacturing similarities between
fridges and suitcases. You sell it for
$12.95 or $14.95. What does it cost you
to make? So, our landed costs are
$575 and then after shipping, which is
another $130 to $160 depending on where
you are in the country, it gets to
around 750 to 775. So, you don't have
much margin. No. How do you how do you
sell it today? Director, how many have
you sold? Just over 3,000. Sam, have you
guys raised a lot of money? We raised a
million dollars about a about 2 years
ago. At what valuation? That was at $10
million on a post money save. Why are
you telling us you're worth 20 now? So
that was 2 years ago before we even had
a prototype. We've been in market for 8
months. We've done $4 million of
revenue. We're profitable in 8 months.
In 8 months that
ready that's shipped and we've ordered
enough units to be able to do a $12
million year this year, which is what
we're forecast. And on that $4 million,
how much have you spent to create the
buzz? So we have a return on ad spend of
five times. So, we spend about
$250 per fridge or 20% of our revenue.
Look, I like it. I like the story. I
like the pitch. I like the whole direct.
You guys are great. I I I just don't
like the valuation. So, here's what I'll
do. I'll give you the 600,000 for 10%.
Well, they're going to jump at that. I
think they should. I think they I think
they should. Wow, that was a very loud
laugh. That's why I laugh all the time.
Look, I don't think you're worth more
than six million bucks. I'm sorry, guys.
I think it's a beautiful product. I'm
not sure I see the vision. I just don't
see it. I'm out. Thank you. Thank you.
Appreciate guys. Here here's where I'm
at. Look, great product, great company.
Problem is a math problem. When you
price it at a $20 million valuation in
order for me to get my $600,000 back,
you have to do $20 million in net cash
flow profits. $20 million cash flow
profits. 3% of that is my $600,000 back.
If I want to get a multiple return since
it's a risky environment, let's just say
three or four times, you need to do 60
$80 million in free cash flow to give me
a return. That's the challenge of making
this investment. So, for those reasons,
I'm out. Yeah. And I'm kind of in a
similar place. It's very hard to imagine
that things could pan out in a way that
would be good for you and for us. I also
was thinking about how I could add value
to you and I probably could find a few
ways, but I don't know that I would be
the best shark for you for this deal.
So, for those reasons, I'm out. Thank
you, Lori. You know, listen, I love you
both. The real problem for me is your
valuation. I mean, it's rough. Mark said
it all. I'm not even going to try to
repeat it cuz he really said it all
quite squarely. What would you consider
to be reasonable? Yeah, we're open. Oh,
you guys would not want to even know.
Kevin was at 10. I I'm going to be
honest. Like to me, you're so startup. I
would have been at 20, which you're
never going to consider. It just doesn't
feel like the right deal. So, I'm sorry.
I'm out.
All roads lead to Mr. Wonder.
Well, I I I really think you heard it
from everybody in the same succinct way.
Valuation is a huge problem. Mhm. I
actually think your offer is generous. I
do. I gave him a 6 million valuation
with no path to liquidity. So, there's a
lot of risk in it. I just happen to
think my social would blow this up so
huge if you were able to figure out a
way to fulfill and I also think I can
reduce your CAC. Do you mind if we talk
about your offer for a second and speak
amongst yourselves? Thank you.
Sorry. Do you want to bring I want to
bring someone else back in.
Sorry.
Yeah. Lot of whispering going on. No,
I've actually been thinking about your
free cash flow comment, but this is a
category where the free cash flows of
say Whirlpool, it's a billion dollars.
Her who bought out GE, it's $2 billion.
How many products do they have? They
have five. How long did it take him to
get there? 100 years. What's happening
here? Kevin has an offer on the table,
which doesn't always stay there.
Actually, I have to be honest with you
guys. I'm out.
All five sharks are out. Sam and Elise
had an offer on the table from Kevin for
their designer beverage fridge, Rocco,
but their hesitation led to a change of
heart. The only offer you had was me.
And then you're talking to Cuban again.
You know, Mr. Wonderful doesn't feel
good about that. You hurt his feelings.
I now will forget who you are tomorrow
morning because there's going to be five
more deals coming through that door. I'm
out. See you guys later. Ciao. We wanted
to offer a royalty. I'm not sure if
there's a way to get you back in. What's
your offer? What is it?
We want to We can be a little flexible
on the valuation. So, let's let's do a
royalty particularly tied to your
channels. No, I'm not doing that. The
minute my name is on this, it's every
unit gets a royalty because all of a
sudden it's a Mr. Wonderful deal. If you
don't believe that, talk to my 54 CEOs.
See what they say. What's the royalty
you would give? Yeah, but only on what
Kevin generates. I'm not doing that. I'm
not either. Yeah. I'm not making up a
commission saleserson. I'm an investor
with a huge curious what's the royalty
you would give. What would you give? You
do the marketing numbers.
I'm not doing that deal. I I'm not for
I'm the one asking.
Where's the fridge? It was 50. $50 a
fridge. Until you get your money back. I
just want to throw something back at
you. Okay. No qualifiers, but
$600,000. $50 a fridge. That's it. If we
can keep the regular equity ask, we'll
do $50 every fridge back. $50 every
fridge. Would you do it till five at 5%?
4%. 5%. 4% 5%. Can we talk about that
for one sec? I do it at 3% in
perpetuity,
which is forever.
Take the deal. I mean, you're going to
We plan to be around for a long time.
So, a long time. As long as we're all
full.
4% and until you get your money back.
We'll meet you in the middle. How about
4% until I get my money back plus
another 300,000? Done. Done. There you
go. Wonderful.
Boom. Oo. Who knew? Now I bought that
other fridge. Oh my. Well, we're going
to have to replace them. I
mean, good deal. Good idea. Thank you.
Congratulations, guys. Thank you. Thank
you, everyone.