good evening world and people me and
Nick have been planning a prank for Matt
for a while now it's mostly Nick's idea
well cuz it's payback because of the
bird prank that I never got revenge a
year later it's like a year and a
half me yeah you miss me and all the
things that we did we said we going to
travel from the island to Madrid we had
a lot of plans but they
all why because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
saying nothing when I'm post to with
Matt has a favorite actor and his name
is Liam niss if you're not familiar he's
been in movies like nonstop taken I
think Star Wars and that's what he looks
like but anyway Star Wars I think so
Matt stays in his room very often so he
doesn't he hasn't noticed the absurd
amount of packages me and Nick have been
receiving but we've been buying him
bedroom decor covered in Liam niss so
let's get to it I want to show my dirty
bathro so two Amazon picture frames and
there's two more in this
box four Amazon basic picture
frames as of right now Matt has a poster
of himself hung up on the wall of him
and Vermont and we're going to take it
down and replace it with Mr n in nonstop
in nonstop gun drawn leaping through the
air ready ready to fire Matt right now
has a boring Basic Black comforter on
his bed which I decided it'd be nice if
we spice it up with e with a
gun obviously if he has a blanket he
needs a pillow right so right now he has
boring basic black pillows that don't
worry about it we're going to replace
them with so much spunk we got Liam niss
outside
there he is Matt also obviously he has
some graphic te's that me and Chris
decided to take the pleasure of
replacing with shirts to have Liam niss
on them so we have this nice black one
red carpet Liam niss photo and then we
used this photo that we used for the
blanket again yes he looks so strong
staple te uhhuh love it everyday tea you
know yeah and
then we've got
last thing but honestly I think the most
important 100 photos of Liam niss in bed
sitting
bedside wow so let's do it right yeah
let's do it let's get to it all right
guys it's like 2 3 days later and Matt
is currently is this onom me it's going
to die again I have to charge it oh my
God bro you never charge the [ __ ]
camera shut up anyway it's like 2 to 3
days later and um Matt's in the shower
right now and I just taped all these
photos and I have like this whole entire
stack to do and then Nick just framed
these four and we're having our manager
Laura like come pick up Matt for a
meeting so that he's going to meet with
her alone and that's when we're going to
stke yeah and we literally have a flight
tonight for Boston and we literally like
this is the last day that we could try
to squeeze this in and bro he's just
going to be so mad that his room is just
going to be Liam n right before we leave
to change till we come back yeah I know
this be fun yeah but just came in the
mail oh my godh you have to put that in
the car now no I don't yeah you should
we'll do it in a
minute
bye he you Matt okay we have to move
bro wait we should start in his room now
oh yeah
wait I'm scared okay wait let's go get
the Vlog camera oh [ __ ]
okay okay guys Lara just dropped off
Lara just picked up Matt for a meeting
which was totally fake and look it me
and Nick have been prepping all this I
have taped all those come here you have
to move I know and then I they're there
all over here yes they're we got to go
wait I need command strips this isn't
enough where are they where are the Comm
man strips got him
go okay we're starting with the massive
things my ass that's fine
CH he just it just got stuck on that
wall in that wall and I almost broke it
in half that was
scary he almost killed me okay command
strips are on the table take that down
take it down I just y just rip it off
yeah okay I hung it up with command so
be easy okay we're going to oh wa he has
this thing too we should take this down
and put a photo there oh yeah 100% okay
ghost is coming down on I'm going to
take his blanket and pillows hold on
hold on wait graphi first blankets and
pillows I'm going to bring up to your
room along with that poster okay word
and then should I take all his shirts um
yes wait I can't grab it just give me
just give me you go go go go go here
where the shirts okay come on he going
to take only his graphic okay go go go
has loose hanger just throw him on the
floor hold on Nick we have to move how
do I get this Nick we have like 15
minutes come on okay I got this
half uh we'll do we're going to cut the
camera we'll be right back okay all of
Matt's everyday shirts have now been
swapped out with his black and then
white Liam niss Essentials now that's
there come on this the most physical I
come on Nick where's the thing Nick yes
I put I hung them up come on on come on
you have to hang this up
Nick come on shut
up
awesome yes okay get the big one up get
the big one we're going just put this
one on his desk now
yeah oh that one's
sweet you have a blanket huh yeah you do
okay we good I have everything dude
can't get this off come on you got
it recycle it Nick just get this open
get thank you come on bad camera view
we're working on a time
restraint okay hold on I'm taking these
command STS down okay he's going to be
mad if I don't have enough for him to
like replace the photo me that's F
actually he might keep which is weird
have the
blanket the pillow the photo and then
the his other stuff the animal I just
stuck an ungodly amount of Li photos on
me you're insane where's his okay we
have to move we're
good okay what wall are we doing this to
I don't know here let's just do it all
over we have so many
okay all right is this good huh is this
good yeah that's good Nick it doesn't
have to be [ __ ] Center we're just
working quickly here okay hold
on what are you doing hanging these oh
wow I got one right there those four oh
nice they look good there here clean up
that trash um I'll go get more photos
Okay like that yeah
yeah then grab the command strips from
the table and hide
them so I think when he gets home from
this meeting we should sit in here and
then like when he gets home he's
obviously going to look for us going be
home in 10 minutes okay we got to move
go be like Nick chis yeah like he'll be
looking for
us you know yeah awesome okay here take
this I'm going to get the final photos
well we still have a lot I need your
help follow cut the camera
podcast by the way Shameless plug
Shameless plug okay this the other ones
from the
bathroom D don't record my camera okay
okay we got to go
Nick here you can you take I'm going to
put the camera in your pocket and then
Vlog me come down once you're done oh my
God Nick you can't stick onto you why
cuz then they're going to lose their
stick bro it's tap more go get more Nick
you're dropping them I'll meet you down
there okay I'll meet you down there I'm
shutting the camera
off Nick it's coming along so well
okay oh my god dude my [ __ ] back is
sweating okay Nick uh-huh you hang these
up I'm going to go get the rest okay
go hey I'm covered in Liam niss I think
a really underrated spot to put one on
the back of his door you know cuz when
he's alone in his room that spot's going
to look a little empty
so we got to make sure there's a couple
actually one was better than one Liam
niss two Liam niss this one just already
fell Chris is not taking these
well I feel like we got to get higher up
what if we cover here's the rest but we
have to move cuz I just stuck all these
together so we have to like kind of undo
them that's fine I'm thinking covering
the Alum cover
like putting Mr
Skies falling I dropped down the stairs
you're
good okay nice oh the album covers fire
thank you yeah I love that I put on his
chair too oh that's great and behind his
door oh awesome this is the last one oh
the
ceiling we have to the last
one perfect all right so now I think
when he comes in [ __ ] you you should
Vlog from that way and I'll Vlog like
from this way okay so that way we get
like full reaction as he comes in and
his room cuz like say he opens the door
like slightly like this I want to catch
his like first ini reaction so like you
get there and I'll sit in this chair and
Vlog that way on my
phone okay yeah I'm going to get an
Italian Ice and then just sit and cool
down okay we're going to we just
finished setting this up we're going to
sit down and wait in his room and stock
his location and basically what we're
going to do spend until he gets home for
the next 6 minutes is if any of these
start to fall off just push them back on
so that's literally what we're going to
be doing till he gets back but you will
see Matt's reaction
momentarily I think he's here I think
he's here
oh my I was FaceTiming the group
chat this is the prank Liam
n all over my bedroom is the
prank oh my God you didn't even see that
I didn't even see that
one take a look where's my other one
take a look around I'm sure you'll find
more in a frame
he's in a four keeping all of these
up on the little Sky oh my God keep
looking
around
where the Blanket's
amazing oh my God this is so comforting
like I literally feel so comforted the
pillow oh my
God I'm like trying to think where else
they could be try right behind you
in
here oh where' you put all my shirts it
doesn't matter you got two new
ones the fact that he didn't see them no
these are
perfect oh my God the word perfect is
crazy I literally don't need the other
ones like I'm fine with
those I don't know what was he sending
Nick showed me that and was like dude I
have the photo we're going to use and I
was just so mind blown I was like what
is that selfie but it worked perect took
so long to hang these
up oh great Heavens isn't it wonderful
this is
insane new room decor I literally was
calling the group chat and I was like
they're definitely in their rooms right
now and then it was
silent I love this I'm so happy yay Liam
n
what what were we waiting for nothing we
just wanted to like we kept telling Matt
we were going to prank him and we kept
telling like oh we're waiting for
something we're waiting for something I
love this so much we exactly what I
wanted who did I tell this to I don't
know how I said how comforted would you
feel with Liam n on a poster with a 9mm
pointage look he's on the ceiling too I
know I saw that one that's such a good
one no but we kep out we're waiting and
we have a flight literally
tonight bro we probably not going to be
able to prank you until like we get back
so he is totally wasn't expecting this
not at all Li n is my comfort I I love
Liam n well I'm happy that this
is these this one's a little scary this
one I love them like I literally did y
was my meeting with Lara like yeah you
didn't actually actually talk no one has
to do meetings today you fully went
there to leave the house I had a good
meeting with Laura yeah we told I
literally told Laura I was like can you
have a meeting with Matt but like make
it seem like it's like an actual
beneficial meeting like actually meet
with I feel like so much more protected
you know
yep okay well the the one on the
nightstand kills me well there's the one
on the night there's one on the
nightstand in the frame there's one on
the bed in the frame there's one on the
wall in the frame and then there's one
on your desk then there's one in the
nightstand right yeah
perfect I just I love that I can look up
at him what's going on well i' love well
I'm happy that this is a good prank for
you the most peaceful prank ever I know
I love it it's not even a prank it's a
benefit like I feel so good this is good
well we'll see you guys next week yeah
shut that camera off I'm going to change
my
shirt
well what saying how you miss me yeah
you miss me and all the things that we
did we we going to Trav from the island
to Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
all because but it's okay cuz I'm moving
different don't be saying when I with
other [ __ ] my brothers