last time we filmed our I was going to
say last time we filmed our one year ago
interviews they were a year ago
and then what you're saying how you
missed me yeah you missed me and all the
things
[Music]
welcome back to interviewing ourselves a
year apart from each other we're
supposed to do this January 15th but
that's the day of our La show so we're
doing it five days early so it's
technically 360 days apart
my name is Matthew Bernard cerniella the
name is still Matthew Bernard sternio it
hasn't changed much Bernard's crazy
though Bernard's ridiculous
[Music]
Saturday January 15 2822 January 10th
Tuesday
2023.
18 19 years old
52.3
000. 1.9 million Instagram followers
833 thousand 99.
what 833
000.
and 99. is there a different way to say
that am I talking about
I get recognized in public when I go to
the mall that's about it and like maybe
like everyone's sprinkling every once in
a while but that most of them all that's
about it honestly like a lot like if I'm
going to Target and there's a teenage
girl there just gotta assume that she's
gonna know who I am but like honestly
it's fun it's great
um but yeah way more often than last
time last time it was only like malls
and [ __ ] but now it's like if I go to
the grocery store so
foreign
real talk like like it sounds like a
joke but literally just don't be a baby
not to not to stress that much over
non-stressful situations and that
everything's gonna work out and be fine
[Music]
um
hit 100 000 subscribers
going on tour which is [ __ ] insane
like I we did a show in Texas this year
or last year but it's like the fact that
we're doing like our own show under our
own name is just [ __ ] crazy and it's
like 15 states across the United States
of America which is ridiculous
um
I love The Benchwarmers I feel like I
don't really like have a favorite movie
but like that's like a movie that like
if it's on I can't not watch it my
favorite movie changes all the time but
I will say the movie that like stuck
with me the most this year is
the Batman one with Robert Patton I
think
I have and I am not no
biggest regret is another this is also
gonna sound like a joke but being a baby
when I told myself not to be
dead serious like it it sounds like a
joke to people but like that's the
mentality I have don't be a baby my
biggest regret is not focusing on myself
and my feelings more
collagen for everybody
learned a lot of big things this year
but most important is stick with your
family family knows best
I don't I'd like to visit all 50 states
so I don't have like a place in
particular but I'd love to see like
every state just to see how each one's
off each state operates I guess I sure
said I wanted to visit every state and
now we're going on tour across the
United States which is ridiculous but
I don't know I feel like
I don't really want to like leave the
country I'm kind of good in the 50
States but I just want to go to all of
them that's really my goal
so let's say this last year same as last
year but like get more done
blue my favorite color is still blue
love blue
pretty good
I feel like I've been I've I've had ups
I've had downs but right now I'm kind of
like
a little past medium yeah
hey there's always always been better
but I'm just still chilling so we're
fine
I think it's gonna have to be
my lyrical lemonade sweater that has
like
it's like reversible and it's got like
the lemons on it and like it looks like
it's like plants and stuff it's cool
[Laughter]
it's like crazy the last I I didn't
appreciate pants enough last year so I
think pants are just like some great
things I think all my corduroy pants are
like my favorite things that I own I
just love pants
favorite song is whirly by Dominic Fike
Dominic Fike is definitely one of my top
artists but same with Skies which is the
same as Chris's last year but like my
music face is Chris's music taste just
with like one or two artists that he
doesn't like that much so
nothing actually
nope
never
someone I want to meet Baylor Levine I
mean mutuals with him on Instagram oh
and Johnny Ransom those are like the two
Mr Johnny and Mr bailiff my last year my
answer was Balin and Johnny Baylen I
definitely still want to meet but we
just gotta obviously both busy people
both YouTubers just one of us got to go
to the other one and Johnny is like a
good friend of mine now which is crazy
so I met him like this year
[ __ ]
got really close to them went on his
podcast I [ __ ] have his brand logo
tattooed on my arm now too so it's just
crazy how like you look at like a year
ago and then right now and I got his
brand tattooed on me for life so love
John
foreign
obviously I want to keep doing YouTube
stuff but
I wanna focus on like
I don't know what I want to focus on
that's that's the problem I want to
focus on more things that aren't YouTube
but keep YouTube as good as it's gone
if that makes sense I hope it does a
goal for this year that I have is until
it's literally like the same as my goal
last year but I just want to focus on
something like individually to get done
like Chris's accomplishment this year
with this clothing brand is like amazing
and I just want to do some [ __ ]
individually but I'm not sure exactly
what it is yet but I will figure it out
I know I won't
yeah
I don't want to hold the grudge against
myself
yes 100
.
first time going la
um honestly my birthday last year it was
[ __ ] awesome like Nate was in LA we
were at Palm Springs it was just amazing
there was no problems it was great it
was awesome
I have my ears pierced and no tattoos
I'm probably done with piercings
probably that's a big probably I think
I'm done though
um and then taxis I'll probably get a
couple not many though okay I have
Marvin the Martian for my dad because
when we were little kids he used to like
voice impression him and I'd love my dad
so I got that for my dad I have this key
on my arm with three four six triplets
us three and Justin us three and Justin
and my mom and my dad so like the
numbers of our family on a key and the
three Leafs is like for me it's like I
really just first I think they just look
really cool and second it's like now
that I'm out in California I love the
weather here but like the weather back
home is like my favorite [ __ ] weather
in the world like I just love the fall
love being in like Vermont and New
Hampshire [ __ ] so like that's like a
little part of like back home nature
here and then this is the Johnny's brand
logo
um license plate of the minivan that we
first started doing car videos in and
then this one with like correlating with
Nick like the shootout or standoff
three nights by Dominic Fike Breathe by
Lil Skies [ __ ] one of my top two
songs ever that and okay for now are my
top two songs ever both nice guys well
and Worley but
those are my top three
[Music]
hit 100K on YouTube Fly alone
move out of my parents house
and
time to just become an adult
[Music]
look at how far you came
oh
[ __ ] might not be easy but nothing ever
is so
far
my name is Christopher Owen steering all
up my name is
January 15th Saturday 2022. Tuesday
January 10 2023.
I'm 18 years old I'm 19 years old
I have 83 000 Instagram followers I have
2.2 million Instagram followers
my most liked Instagram post is just of
under 40 000 it is 39
30 39 478.
my most liked post I'm pretty sure is
like a booth by Bryant photo that I
archived
yeah my most liked photos 870 845 which
is like [ __ ] astronomical like it's
disgusting how many people that is it
like makes me sick to my stomach
but it's crazy in a good way
whenever we go to like a really public
place like if we were to go to like a
sports game or Bruins game or like the
mall or something there's a good
possibility but not every time probably
like
two to three times like a month maybe I
want to say maybe less than that once a
month dude Mima and Nick like if we're
walking us three get recognized pretty
much everywhere we go now which is like
insane to think about and um
especially like the airport I hate
getting noticed at the airport but
everywhere else is so much fun me and
Matt the other day had to pee and we
were on the road and we pulled over and
went to a Subway and the girl knew who
we were and like we did I took like a
selfie with her it was fun
I would tell myself not to let others
have total control of your emotions or
like don't let other people
tell you [ __ ] or tell you what to do
especially adults don't let adults like
be like oh you can't do this because
you have to listen to me because I'm an
adult
no you don't respect your elders be
respectful but just like
teachers and stuff I like tell you you
can't do [ __ ] are wrong you can do
whatever you want
just be safe about it
um
to slow down and look around and just
like see where you are enjoy where you
are and like just be more in the moment
instead of thinking like what's next
um probably going to LA or stuff in La
that we can't really talk about yet
because
it hasn't happened yet but
that's definitely the biggest thing wow
that's such a crazy question because how
of how many things
like have happened to me this year like
my my own brand
um I think one thing like the best thing
that happened career-wise and the
craziest thing is just the fact that me
Matt and Nick literally like live off of
YouTube now like and that's our only job
favorite movie My favorite movie is The
Dark Knight the Batman one but like
that's like a very aggressive movie like
if I have to go calm I'm probably going
to Grinch
I love the Grinch but any Grinch any
version of it it's fire my favorite
movie I feel like I like get out and
like
Us by Jordan po like those are crazy
ones
no neither
no I don't plan to be I don't want to be
I am not
I'm not starting YouTube earlier I feel
like Mima and Nick always wanted to do
YouTube but we took it seriously once
quarantine happened but um I feel like
if we started beforehand like while we
were still in like high school like our
our sophomore year
we'd be like crazy right now like
million subscribers or something so
that's probably one of my biggest
regrets my biggest regrets probably
trying to move too quick
which kind of goes for my advice thing
like just take [ __ ] one step at a time
like and enjoy it a little more because
I feel like I stress myself out with how
fast I'm trying to do things
biggest thing I learned this year is um
to keep your circle small and just be
friends with real people and um people
that aren't really there for you to like
just eliminate them from your life
because I feel like I have my closest
group of friends I've ever had in my
life right now so I'm very happy about
that
biggest thing I learned this year
is um
to Value people that value you and to
just
um cherish every moment with somebody
because
like I cherish all my moments to my
family when I'm back home I cherish
every moment with my brothers when I'm
here and I cherish my moments with like
literally everybody I meet and just like
soak in as much as you can
I want to leave the country I don't know
why I'm aware maybe like
I want Bahamas maybe that'd be cool I
think the my favorite place we visited
this year which is where I want to visit
again is Catalina Island because it's
just so small and like chill and like
just something nice and warm and just
water and sand and
stuff like that but yet again I also
like the polar opposite like I like like
forces and like trees I like love that
[ __ ] I like go to the park all the time
and just like sit at a park like I'm
like a little kid but I just love nature
and [ __ ] so somewhere where it's like
beautiful outside probably like the
Redwood Forest I want to go so bad I
also want to go to like just like big
foresty places
my favorite color Matt kind of stole my
favorite color but mine's like baby blue
or purple I like orange too orange is
really cool
oh my God my favorite color is orange
has to be
pretty good I mean I'm getting better I
I don't know
I feel like if I had to do on a scale
from one to ten probably like a four
mentally but
ups and downs what can you do how am I
seriously I'm like chilling because
you know I'm happy I'm with my family
and with my brothers and I've like I've
become very like a mental like
calm relaxed think a little bit slow
down like I really trained myself
mentally to just be better like
I don't take things as seriously as much
in a good way like everything you know
like life's gonna be gone before we all
know it so you might as well just relax
and
and chill out
my favorite clothing item I own
is probably my my new shorts I just got
that I haven't even posted in yet
they're like they look like an old like
roller rink carpet and I love them very
much my black pair of pants with like a
[ __ ] ton of pockets on them
my favorite song is right now is
probably Die For You by Justin Bieber
featuring Dominic Fike that's probably
my favorite song currently right now my
favorite artist is always skies and
always has been the Dominic fight this
year kind of like just
totally took over like he's like
my favorite artist of all time right now
him and skies are equivalent
uh my favorite song and artist
my favorite artist Skies like you guys
know that and Dom and uh Mac Miller I
love Mac I like Travis Scott a lot
lately I like Don Toliver I like nav
love nav
you know I just like I love every I love
all music like it's hard for me not to
relate I used to hate on like Billy
eilish and and like other female artists
when Nick would play it because I used
to just be like one of those kids that
can only listen to rap
but I've really expanded and like it's
hard for me to not enjoy a song now and
to pick a favorite song is like so
difficult like terrible terrible
terrible I don't want to pick like a sad
song
but I like come back to Earth by Mac
Miller I like cut the check by Mac
Miller I like okay for now by Lil skies
I like
when I'm Wasted by those guys I like
blue strips by Lil Skies like
yeah I could go on and on about favorite
songs I could barely talk about any
genre of music or anything forever so
I'm just gonna stop right there
I don't think I if given the decision I
would the only thing I feel like would
be cool is if I was like a little bit
taller but I don't even think I'd do
that if I had the ability to change it I
think I'd just stay how I am no
absolutely not
someone I want to meet Caitlyn because
we've been friends with Kailyn on the
internet for like over a year now and
never met I want to hang out with her
and her brother Johnny I want to meet
um
I really want to meet like skies because
like I don't know like listening to all
his music and like all throughout high
school and [ __ ] like I don't know it's
just like it was just so crazy so I feel
like if I met Skies that'd be like one
of the craziest days of my life
um I want to meet skies I think I said
that last year I also want to meet
Baylin and shout out to Johnny and
Kailyn because we did meet them this
year and they're they're homies now
they're awesome I love them so much
do I have a crush on anyone
not really I there's good looking girls
but you know
I don't like anyone so the crush would
require emotion yeah Crush would acquire
something Beyond physical attraction so
I do not have a crush on anyone
no I like a lot of people
um a goal I want to complete this year I
really want to hit like a million
subscribers this year which I feel like
is low-key pushing it but I feel like me
Matt and it could do it I think we could
do it
but that's like very very fortunate so
who knows but anything's possible all
right who knows what will be at
um I want to get into music more and
like try to like either learn how to
play the guitar which I used to I used
to be good at it and then I like kind of
slacked and forgot or like just do
something music related for myself or
just like get more in the music scene
with our YouTube videos like make videos
with artists and stuff like that like
that's one of my goals this year as well
I'm a goal after this year is just to
build my brand out to like a new
audience of like I want like
I want to reach people that are like
unimaginable unimaginable my brand I
want it to be for all ages for all
genders for all like everybody that's my
goal is just to expand it as much as I
can and just get everyone to love it
with my brand I also just want to just
like I feel like as a YouTuber and a
content creator like YouTube is fun and
all but there's so much more that you
can explore just for fun like I have
friends in music I have friends in
acting I have friends in like everything
now and I'm just so grateful to be able
to like think of anything I want to do
and achieve it so I think one of my
goals is just to like like
um
if life is a buffet I'm gonna go and
take from every single thing and see
which one I like the most is the best
way to put it you know I'm gonna grab
some chicken grab some rice grab some
corn and if I really like the corn I'm
gonna go back and get some more corn
um absolutely and I think
um
if I ever thought the other way I think
I'd be really sad
you know you want to like always be okay
with just like how you're living life
and I feel like that question is like uh
if you thought of that question every
day before you went to bed like your
mindset would just be so different so
if I could relive any moment is this is
gonna sound so corny but probably Prime
fortnite because Prime fortnite like
Season Two Season three like just with
the with my friends with Nathan with
like my older brother Justin like that
those were some some like my most fond
memories like and it was the beginning
of high school so like just that time
period probably freshman year of high
school I'd repeat
uh I don't think I have a particular
memory but I just go back and and like
like just probably witness more of like
our career happening before our eyes
like hitting 100K hitting 250k taking
the photos for that like
hitting a million hitting like like all
those moments in time where we just like
hit all these landmarks and like watched
our career unfold like I wish I just
watched it more and documented more like
real [ __ ] like just like emotional and
all that stuff because it was truly like
the craziest year of Our Lives ever
foreign
but I want to get I want to get my a
nose stud but I don't know if I'm gonna
I'm like on the fence about it I feel
like I'm just gonna send it one day and
I have zero tattoos but I want to get um
I want to get Rudolph I don't know why I
got nothing bro I was gonna get a nose
stud but I didn't do it I remember I was
gonna get it but my nose hurt one day I
like booked the appointment then I had a
runny nose and I was like do I really
want to get a no stud if I like have to
blow my nose and I just never went back
and got it and then tattoos like
I want them and I'm not scared of the
pain but I'm scared of the fact that
it's on me forever
West Coast Collective by Dominic Fike
Dior Runners by nav
one thing I did this year that I never
have done before is leave Massachusetts
on my own with just Nick and Matt like
without my mom or anything which is
pretty cool
so yeah probably travel with just my
brothers
um one thing I did this year that I've
never done before is my ability and like
my confidence of just like meeting and
communicating with people like I feel
like I am just like I I I'm terrible
reading and I'm terrible talking out
loud like to just myself but when I'm in
actual conversations with real life
people like I feel like I'm I'm really
good at that what is the [ __ ]
question
what did I what is something I've never
done before yeah I think I've like
learned a lot of how to just talk and
communicate and one thing I did let this
year that I've like never really done
before is just going into conversations
and engaging in conversation so much
more confidently than I ever have in my
life
don't trip over something that's not
worth it just
stop overthinking stop worrying about
[ __ ] everything's gonna fall into place
and it probably already has
what I said last year is just straight
bars that's it again
run it back
what's my name is Nicholas turn yellow
Antonio is the middle name Nick
sterniolo
Nicholas is the long version
[Laughter]
January 15 2022 January 10th 2023.
uh 18 uh 19.
I have 44
000. I have 2 million Instagram
followers
as eighteen thousand three hundred and
twenty seven
um my most liked Instagram photo is 646
100.
what all right 640 600 likes just
terrifying that wrong
000.
460. four six no six four six yeah
380. okay yes
please
hold on what am I saying
um barely ever it's like I feel like
whenever we go to a mall it's more
inclined to happen because there's like
hundreds of people there so it may not
Christian triplets so sometimes I can't
tell people are just staring at us
because they're seeing three of the same
person or they're staring at us because
they've seen us on the internet oh my
God anywhere that there's like kind of
like a swarm of teen girls I have a
feeling and then usually it's like yep
correct
relax like just relax you should have
been way more relaxed I was worried
about way too many things and I was
um insanely dependent on male validation
so I needed to just chill that's about
it just value the spot that you're in
because I'm not in that spot anymore and
it was kind of fun so I just say value
the spot that you're in
um probably assigned to management
making new friends through it
um
a hundred thousand subscribers
signing up for a YouTube plaque that
should be at our house hopefully soon so
we can take cool photos with it
um going to La for the first time a lot
of things a lot of nutty things
growing over 10K subscribers weekly for
over a month
the biggest thing to having me
career-wise is like ridiculous because
we're filming this early because we're
about to leave for a tour on the day
that it was supposed to start so we're
going on a full tour
um we've made just so many friends that
are like new people and I feel like
that's like just like a career-wise step
because it's like because of the career
that we have we're able to meet so many
new people and then I'd say like we did
so many fun things we met goals that we
set for ourselves like a million on
YouTube we passed that it was just like
just so many crazy experiences and goals
were
hit and it's just crazy like every I
feel like the entire year was a
career-wise accomplishment
I don't think the OG Mighty more from
Power Rangers with Amy Jo Johnson as The
Pink Ranger and Aisha is the yellow
ranger my favorite movie is mighty more
from Power Rangers and I also really
like Hercules
the Disney movie I also I'm like a
really little kid movie or I'm like a
severe crazy horror like fun mind
twisting movie so it's like one or the
other I also watched Insidious for the
first time this year and that was kind
of fire like and see this was good it
was crazy and scary but it was like
fun
[Music]
um I am currently not thank the Lord
Jesus Christ and I have been
I'm not in a relationship right now
um
probably isolating myself as a child I
feel like I'd be I would have been a
happier child had I not forced myself to
be alone that was my own fault so my
biggest regret this year is probably not
taking time to sniff the flowers
what I mean by that is just like I mean
Chris had so many successes and so many
fun things that happened for us this
year so I feel like we didn't really
take time to cherish every single one of
those moments
it's okay to be alone you don't need to
be in a relationship or even be
Snapchatting someone it is totally
mighty fine to be
by yourself
the biggest thing I've learned this year
is that Matt and Chris are and always
will be my best friends
um
I feel like Greece is really cool
looking and I really want to go on like
a ski trip and take photos on like like
a log cabin I want to like stay in a log
cabin somewhere that's not really a
place but like maybe like New Hampshire
Vermont has nice log cabins I did say
Greece last year but I also feel like I
really want to go where those around me
want to go like I've picked a crowd of
people I really enjoy surrounding myself
around so wherever they want me I want
to be there
and I feel like that's like a weird
answer because it's not like you're
thinking like someone asked your dream
vacation and you're like just with the
people but it's kind of like a home is
where the heart is Type Beat like I have
good people around me and I want those
people to enjoy my presence wherever it
brings me
my favorite color is currently
um it changes like weekly I'd say right
now black or purple my favorite colors
are purple and black still shockingly
ugh fine I guess like realistically like
all right I get see I think I'm fine I
feel like if I was an only child that'd
be fine because I'm not only child I'm
not fine because the reason I'm saying
this is because my energy goes down if
not Chris's energy dips so like if
they're upset then I'm just upset and so
they're upset right now so I feel like
I'm upset right now like if they weren't
here and I wasn't worrying about them
mentally all the time probably a 10 but
since they're here I'll say like four
six
46. I feel like there's a lot of things
that could bring me down but I feel like
there's also like every single one is a
learning point so I feel like I'm just
going to use them to create a really
really good mental health spot for
myself if that makes sense
so I wouldn't say I'm in the best mental
health spot but I'm gonna say I know
exactly how to get there
sweater I haven't taken it off since I
got in the mail like it's literally it
got here in the mail I put it on
haven't taken it off washed it once my
favorite clothing line of my own are
these huge black boots that I got
for our tour that I'm going to wear and
post on posting soon so I'm not going to
show you or describe them any further
but peep my Instagram because I'm going
to be wearing big black boots sometimes
too sometime soon I'm very excited
Billy Ash will always be one of my
favorites Ariana Grande Vlogs one of my
favorites currently though doji cat
hitting different favorite song right
now is probably like
oh my God Sweet Escape but not by Gwen
Stefani the girl Bella DiNapoli from The
Voice her rendition of it that's just
gonna put on Apple music it's crazy I
think it's pretty good I have a lot to
Buckle in Miley Cyrus
Doja cat Tate McRae sizza Melanie
Martinez Billy eilish Ariana Grande
Travis Scott
and I think that might be really what it
is for favorite artist my favorite song
right now is
um see it's really difficult because
when I there's like always like two
different answers to this question and
it's my Nick alone answer and then my
Nick with my brother's answer and I
don't know what I'm listening to when
I'm with my brothers but I know what
they play that I like and dislike I just
never really ask them what it's called
or have access to that library of my
music genre unless I'm with them it's
like my favorite song is 90210 by Travis
Scott love that song and then also I
have a song that I know I like that
Chris plays but I'm gonna take it back
to you because I don't know how it goes
I don't know the name but once no clue
I don't think I would
like because I feel like if you get the
opportunity to change it it's kind of
like magic and I feel like yo I feel
like if I were to change something about
myself it would be like the butterfly
effect might be a completely different
person somehow I feel like it's not like
a I wouldn't change something directly
about myself like right now be like oh
change
like this one thing but I'd say that I
know what changes I want to make to
myself moving into the next year that
isn't necessarily like
the answer to that question if that
makes sense
I want to meet our online friend Kalyn
because we've been friends forever and
then I want to like extremely blow up on
YouTube so that Doja Cat knows that I
exist and we can maybe get spaghetti or
something I don't want to meet this year
there's a couple people I really want to
meet
um
Dojo cat always she's my like dream meet
person but like also not like a freak
out way like I don't like cry and hug
Doja cat I want to be like yo
let's talk business
don't know what I mean by that either
but I also on a more like realistic note
sorry I gotta grab some pretzels you're
good on a more realistic note I really
want to meet
um my friend at least in my opinion Tate
McRae I think that she's extremely
talented her album came out this year
and I was listening to it on repeat I
just think she's a really cool person
um she follows me on Instagram we've
been in contact with each other I I hope
if you see this you don't think I'm like
a weirdo like no one no one post this I
don't want Tate to find this but like
we've been in communication I think
she's like she just seems like someone I
gravitate to and not in like a crazy way
like I promise I won't like I promise
I'm not a weirdo I'm not gonna freak the
[ __ ] out but I think that it's just like
she's someone that thinks cool as [ __ ]
that knows who I am I know who she is
and I want to
be friends
pretty much right yeah like I look at
dinner like you can come over we play we
all the time if someone posts this I
know there's a possibility of Tate
seeing it and that's why I'm scared fan
accounts if you post this Tate sorry but
I'm down to meet sorry I had to find out
on these circumstances but you're cool
and this is me vocalizing it
I know
no I can't even think of three gay men
so no no
thank you
um a goal I want to have I want to
complete this year is probably there's a
couple actually I probably want to like
I want to start a podcast really bad
I've been telling my Chris that but it's
a lot of money it's a lot of setup it's
a lot of
editing
um I also want to start creating merch
really bad or like cool merch you know
you'll figure it out when we drop it
it'll be cool but merch I want to do
things that are new for the first time
like I want to like wake up and be like
I want my hair to be gone and cut it all
off I want to go into a store and see
something that I would never usually
wear find my size and purchase it and I
also want to just oh my God like I want
to just do new things also another
goldfish I have is just to like really
like leave the house like I want to go
like sniff flowers walk through a park
learn how to drive [ __ ] learn how to
drive please because I feel so bad at
school man I can't rely on that for the
rest of my life so I need to learn how
to drive I need people to go do things
that I want to do
yeah I feel like
it would suck because we have so much
progress and potential but yeah we did
good I always have to say yes to this
um probably standing outside of Harry
Potter World
um with our La friends for the first
time or
Florida the week in Florida with our
friend Nathan oh my God I have a very
few specific ones I'd share a birthday
in Palm Springs was one of like the
highlights of my life
another thing I want to relive is though
moment we hit one mill and I was at a
Billie eilish concert with Maddie and it
was just like the sheer joy and
excitement from the concert and hitting
Windmill and being with my best friend
and walking out of the concert was like
a high
like it was just a great moment
I currently have my ears pierced my nose
pierced and oh that's it I just got
scared I thought I was missing something
I don't know just my ears I want to get
my doubles really bad and if they tell
me that my earlobe isn't big enough
which I've seen happen to people I'll do
something like up a little bit more on
both sides or like
you know I have no tattoos but I'm
probably I'm hoping that when we redo
this next year I have like
um so I really really really this is my
number one goal
going into like the next year so I
really did what I wanted to complete
last minute like a week and a half ago I
knew this was coming up so I got my nose
pierced here and I got my ear pierced
over here and I got my doubles earlier
this year so I've gotten
four new piercings since and then I got
I think about 18 tattoos which is really
good but I'll make a tick talk about it
I promise right now instead of showing
you guys and explaining it to like save
for the jeopardizing time but like
here's my arm I'll make a tick tock soon
explain them all I said I was gonna do a
YouTube video but I feel like we're
about to leave for tour I'm not gonna
really have time to film individually I
will make a tick tock of all of them
last song
Alone by doji cat that song I played was
Creep by Radiohead and that's a banger
song and I love that song so very much
Chris already answered said the same
answer but probably flew by myself with
my siblings that my mom and dad and
older brother so we met Chris went and
ventured off did something on our own oh
my God I did so much this year I've
never done I like shopped for
like major Furniture because me Matt and
Chris moved in somewhere like we bought
like a couch
um and I also just like
I just did a lot for the first time
which is great there's like oh I feel
like this entire year was doing things
for the first time
I hope you're keeping that productivity
up because like right now I'm pretty
productive I hope that I'm like moving
more I hope the church is doing what you
like your goals are I hope you achieve
them or not really goals like the
mindset you want to be in I hope you get
there if not who knows what the [ __ ]
I'll be doing I cringe every single time
I look at myself a video a week ago so I
hope you're not like crying at how
horrible you look right now
but okay I think I look all right like
an extra product better so I don't know
I just want to be in a position where
like
everyone I'm around is so easy to talk
to and like conversations are light and
I'm just like having fun
that's not the question what is it tell
your future self something yeah like I
hope that you're in a spot where
everyone you speak to is like it's like
light and bubbly conversations and
you're just having fun got 20 minutes
later and I hope that I have more
tattoos and piercings cool
say bye bye love you all and I will see
you next year do an outro for the group
account
um that has been our yearly interviews
part two but this video is getting kind
of long so we might have to chop it up
for next year but I'm excited to see you
guys next year and this is always a
great experience giving myself a little
recap on but I really did
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
[Music]