[Applause]
Next into the tank is a product designed
to blow away a common cooking hazard.
[Music]
Wait, there's no crying and cooking. Not
if we have anything to say about it. Hey
Sharks, my name is Glenn Smith and I'm
his daughter and business partner,
Madison Smith. And today we are here
seeking $90,000 for 15% equity in our
company.
Sharks, for generations, cooks around
the world have sought relief from the
infamous onion tears. The burning, the
itching, my eyes. Cutting onions is
painful. And we have tried all the hacks
and none of them have worked for us. We
have tried chewing on bread while
cutting.
We've put a matchick between our teeth.
And this guy has even worn yard goggles
in the kitchen.
And trust us Sharks, none of these hacks
have worked for us, which is why we
invented the Fion. The Fion is a
countertop cute cordless fan that is
placed next to your cutting board, which
simply blows away the fumes and vapors
of eye irritating vegetables such as
onions, shallots, peppers, garlic, etc.
You'll only cry tears of joy. It really
is that simple. So, come on sharks.
Who's ready to chop it up with the
fanion? And who's ready to be blown
away? Now, sharks, no need to get weepy.
You each have a fanion to blow those
tears away. So, you have an onion, a
knife, and a fan to really put this to
the test. So, there's a lever on the
back that'll turn it on, and you can get
to chopping.
And Madison, do most people cry with
onions? Yes, we've Yeah. Well, why would
you not? Like I don't really often cry.
I don't like this doesn't sting me at
all. Really? I am told that if you wear
contacts that can be something that
would wear if you wear contacts. If you
wear
contacts, you're lucky. You know, a
unique attribute about vampires. I'm a
vampire. We We don't have to cry about
onions. We can cut any kind of
vegetable. No problem at all. As long as
it's dark outside. Is this your
full-time jobs? And And also, please
tell us about you. You go ahead. I I am
a vice president of a large US poultry
company. I buy uh feed ingredients, feed
chickens. And Madison, what do you do?
After graduating from Georgia Tech, I
studied industrial engineering and I've
worked in the technology and supply
chain spaces for about the last four
years. So, this very simple product, I
get it. How much to buy it? We sell them
for $19.99 on our website. And what does
it cost you to make them? 809. Well, you
know your numbers. How many do you sell?
We launched in November and about seven
months. We have sold almost 1,800. We
have 28,000 in sales. That's not bad.
Not bad at all. How are you guys
promoting it? We've predominantly done
social media. We've put a lot of money
into running ads. And how much money
have you spent on advertising so far? On
advertising about $178,000.
And how much money have you invested to
get it to this? $468,000.
Hello. That's a lot of crying over on
you. Where did you get the money to
spend 468,000? Cash, credit, home
equity. Home equity, too. Home equity as
well. Correct.
Wa. But what did you spend that on for
this? Uh, mostly inventory. How much do
you have in inventory? At your cost. How
much do you have in inventory at your
cost? 31,000 units. Okay. So, that's 240
250 grand basically. Correct. You got
31,000 units. What is it costing you to
acquire a customer right now? Do you
know how much did you spend on
advertising divided by the number of
units you've sold? So 17,000 divided by
almost 1,800. Yeah. So right. So about
10 bucks a unit. Yeah. So you're
breaking even you're not making any
money right now. You're you're losing
some. Yes. What's the plan to sell the
existing sunk inventory? That is why we
are here is that we need help with that
where we really started trying to go
100% direct to consumer. Over 10,000
Google searches happen every month of
people searching how to stop crying
while cutting onions. I mean there's
viral Tik Tok videos. This is definitely
and it works. We know that it works and
there's not a product out there like it.
And everybody loves a kitchen gadget. I
mean maybe there's a reason why there's
not a product out there like it. Look
guys, I give you a lot of credit for
diving in and going for it. But this is
too niche a market, right? Because when
you limit it just to onions, that's too
small, right? And not a lot of people
are going to spend
$19.95 just to be able to do onions
alone. So for those reasons, I'm out.
Thank you, Bart. Here's the thing. It's
something that happens all the time. I
watch it with entrepreneurs. You get so
excited that you don't realize one of
the most perilous pitfalls when you
first create a product is ordering in
too much inventory without sales. You've
sold 1,800 in 8 months, give or take.
You've sitting on 31,000. This could
take you 10 years or more, right, to
sell it. So, what I think you should do,
a suggestion is sell it to someone at
your cost just to break even, but to get
money back because you don't want to sit
on that big of an expense. It's not a
journey that I want to take cuz I know
it's a rough road. Um, but I wish you
good luck. I hope you try that. I'm
sorry. carry them out. You got a bunch
of money tied up in inventory here, 250
grand. So, if you sold these things at
$9.99, you'd get half your money back.
And you say the other was a lesson in
life. Uh 31,000 units. Um that's worth
crying about, not the onion. I can't
help you because I can't help you.
I'm
out. All my friends have never started a
business. They think the starting a
business is like standing on the edge of
a cliff, ordering 30,000 units, and
jumping into the water. Great
entrepreneurs learn about controlled
risk. You never want to make a mistake
that's going to kill you. It's very hard
to come back from the dead. Kevin's done
it, but very way it works. You made a
big risk and now you're stuck with it.
But you got to get rid of that
inventory. There is no we're going to
grow our market. We're going to sell it
here. Get rid of the inventory that you
have even at a loss. Even if you get 50
cents on the dollar. I disagree. They're
being very melodramatic. No, they got
rid of dramatic. They took a line of
credit on their house to get here.
Welcome to the Onion Advice Bank. It's
not for me cuz it's not investable. I
hope you get some of that cash back. I'm
out. Glenn and Madison, um I love the
fact that you're working together. My
daughter's here watching uh Shark Tank
today and it's such a special thing.
It's the most important thing in the
world because my dad is no longer here
with me and um I wish he was around and
I just miss him and I love the fact that
you guys can have this journey together.
Um I wish you the best of luck but I'm
out.
Thank you very much so much meeting you
all. Good luck guys. I hope you make it.
Good luck. Get some of that cash back.