[Music]
Hi Sharks. I'm Reagan. And I'm Nathan.
And I'm the mom creator of the Burly
Wagon. We're here today seeking a
$450,000 investment in exchange for 10%
of our company. Wow. When we moved here
7 years ago from America, we ended up in
a beautiful spot called Burley on the
Gold Coast. We love the beaches, the
parks, the outdoor lifestyle that the
coast had to offer.
But leaving the house with two kids
under two was quite overwhelming.
Our daughter is on the autism spectrum
and we genuinely struggled to leave the
house on longer outings and keep her
content. We searched for an alternative
on the market and we couldn't find
anything. So, we wanted to create
something that helped us as parents and
was a bit more fun as well. So, we
started by adding a built-in ESI cuz
every parent knows that snacks and cold
drinks are the keys to all success when
leaving the house with young kids. When
we moved here, there weren't a lot of
safe options for children to ride in.
So, our wagon also has um safety belts
as well and complies with the AC safety
standards.
We also added a Bluetooth speaker with
two charging ports so you can plug in
all your mobile devices.
We can even plug in our USB fans so you
can angle the fan and chill out in your
wagon. Wow, so cool. We also added side
storage racks for your bigger gear.
You name it, you can haul it in the
wagon.
Can Rean and Nathan wheel the Sharks in
for a
$450,000 investment for 10% equity of
their business? Great pitch, guys. I'm
Davey. Hi Davey. So basically you've
created the most souped up pimped out
beach wagon. Is that right? Yes. So I
was pushing an empty pram a lot of the
time with bags hanging off the back. Our
eldest is on the autism spectrum. So she
would get out, run in one direction, our
other child was in the other direction.
And I just it was pretty chaotic. So we
wanted to make something that they
actually like to ride in. It is awesome.
Thank you. It is the best wagon I have
ever seen. I have 5-year-old twins and I
have every wagon you can imagine. Here
in Australia, wagons are kind of a
different thing that hasn't been around.
You mean Australia? People don't use
wagons. We lived here in zero. I must
have 20 wagons in California. So, it has
been hard to kind of educate as to why
this will make a massive difference.
With fellow North American import Robert
Robert Hersec on the bandwagon, he wants
to find out more about Rean and Nathan's
financials. How much is it? Uh, it
retails for $4.99 in Australia.
How much does it cost you to make? Our
manufacturing cost is $2.25.
Well, that's a pretty high cost. It does
take 14 separate factories to make a
burly wagon and its accessories. Wow.
That is a recipe for something breaking
down in in that supply chain somewhere
along the way.
I'm going to assume you sell it retail.
How much is the cost of If it
leaves Australia, it's about $1,000.
$1,000.
Let's talk about within Australia, guys.
Within Australia, we offer free
shipping. How much does it cost you? My
average is about 60 to 65. Whoa. With a
high shipping cost attached to their
direct to consumer wagon, e-commerce
giant Davy Fogerty is interested to see
if Rean and Nathan's modest margin can
be increased. So, you're making about
$110 a unit. Correct.
What do you think you'll be able to get
the cost of the product down to? The
most expensive component is the main
body. Um, right now just the main body
alone USD is $50. We're working with our
factory right now. They can get that in
half. Okay. So, can we can we talk about
similar products like this in the
market? Oh, for sure. For sure. There
are cheaper versions.
So, one of the points of difference of
ours is in 2019 the AC changed the
regulations in Australia. They said
anything that transports children in an
upright position must meet the safety
standards of a stroller.
So, a lot of people still do use the
Kmart one or the folding ones, but on
the box of all of those, it'll say not
intended for children. Not intended for
children.
When we were designing ours, Reagan
wanted something that can transport the
children safely and um carry all the
gear. There weren't any that had safety
belts. And especially for our two kids
in particular,
I can see how great the product is, but
you're asking for $450,000 for 10% of
the business. So that makes it a $4.5
million valuation. That's a big number.
So I'd love to hear about your sales. So
lifetime sales 2.8 million. Oh, great.
30 days ago, we did launch in the US
market and we've had a gross sales of
400,000.
Wow.
In 30 days? Yes. I'm really excited.
What's the price point in the US? 750
AUD. Nice. the margins in the US market
are much better. And so what do you guys
plan to do with the investment if you
got it today? So it's it's to to get
ahead in stock. It's a huge, you know,
Christmas summer gift. And we always run
out. Designed with safety in mind and
meeting Australian safety standards, the
sales of the Burly Wagon have blown the
sharks out of the water. Have Rean and
Nathan done enough to secure themselves
a deal? I've got three children. I get
it. So, I will be a customer. But my
skill set doesn't lie in streamlining
that whole manufacturing process.
So, for that reason, I'm out. Thank you,
Reagan. I'm I'm honestly I've been
sitting here being like, "Oh, it's so
great." But what is it's just
there's just so many operational
challenges that this business needs to
overcome to being able to
scale. I I'm really sorry, but I'm out.
That's okay. Thank you so much.
I am a tech entrepreneur and this is not
really my area of expertise, but commend
you for everything that you've done.
But
[Music]
unfortunately, I'm out. Thank you so
much. Thank you. With three sharks out,
will self-proclaimed wagon lover Robert
Hershe support Rean and Nathan to bring
this American staple down under? Rean, I
um I'm a highly creative guy, but I'm
struggling. How would I make a deal
without taking all your equity? I will
definitely be a customer. Uh, as an
investor, I'm out. Thank you. Thank you,
Robert. And then there was
one.
So, you have kind of cornered us with
the $450,000. That's a substantial
amount of money, but I do believe in
your growth and I do believe that I can
help you in all of the areas that you've
just talked
about.
So, I'm going to have to make an offer.
I'll give you the
$450,000 for
30%, but I also just want a $4 royalty
per
unit until the money's paid back.
[Music]
Can we take a second to chat? Would that
be okay? Yeah. Thank you.
He He would be amazing. He's the shark
that I think would be able to expand
things. I do want to leave here with a
deal with him. It's just at that
valuation that would take us down to I
think it's under two million. So it's
it's a low valuation. Nathan and
Reagan, time kills deals. So if a deal's
been made, do it in the shortest amount
of time.
Sorry guys, this is hard.
He says no. Yeah. Then don't buy then we
won't. We'd have to.
Okay, Davey, thank you so much for your
offer, but we would like to counter you
at 25.
What about the royalty ring? For the
long-term payment, if we have to pay a
royalty till you get your money back,
that's fine. 100%.
If you come to a $10 royalty,
I'll do the 25%. Until the 450,000's
paid back. Correct.
the end of the day, this is Reagan's
decision to make.
You have a deal. Awesome.
Great. Awesome. I can't wait to work
with you. Thank you so much. Thank you.
Seriously, we got a lot to do though. We
do a lot of work to do. But I think I'll
clear my calendar next week.
Rean and Nathan have done it. We'll fly
around. We'll have a wine in Adelaide.
We'll see you guys later. They've
managed to reel in the youngest of the
Sharks and land themselves a deal of
$450,000 for 25% equity. We did good.
Yeah. Yeah. That was tough. It was very
stressful, but at the end of it, we're
super excited. Davey's the perfect
partner for us. It was important to us
to bring a product like this on the
market. It helped our family
tremendously, especially with our little
daughter. So,
yeah, it's definitely worth celebrating.