Hi Sharks. My name is Aaliyah Marendis
and I live in Austin, Texas. Let's be
real, hair removal sucks.
It's a tedious task that we have to do
over and over again. As a hairy brown
girl with very sensitive skin, I've left
so many waxing salons with less hair,
but my skin my skin was collateral
damage. Wall Shark's hair removal has
never been sweeter. Literally. Say hello
to Sugar Dough at home. sugaring kits to
remove any hair. We like to say we got
your back and your front, arms, legs,
and anywhere else. Made with just sugar,
water, and citrus, our all natural
sugar-based dough gently pulls hair from
the root while exfoliating your skin,
leaving feeling silky smooth. And it's a
gentle, compostable alternative to
waxing. So, Sharks, I'm the sugar mama
to sugar dough. So, I'm asking for some
serious dough. I'm seeking $500,000 for
5% of the company.
But first,
come on.
Kendra, my friend Rishot here is in need
of some sugaring himself. Do you want to
come up and be his sugar mama and sugar
with me?
I do. I get to like remove.
Oh my gosh, this is so exciting.
Kevin's back. Make her do Kevin's back.
Yes, I know. Are you serious?
This is my dream come true. So, sugar
dough is made with this taffy like goop
and it is very fun to play with. It's
kind of similar to caramel or taffy made
with similar ingredients as well.
Okay. What do I do?
So, you can actually try on this side.
Okay. So, all right. Tell me if I'm
doing this right. Okay. I'm going to
mold it into your skin. I'm going to
have
I'm going to let it heat up a minute.
Exactly. And I'm going to help it. And
then you want to pull taut with the
other hand. So, pull the skin taut and
then 3 2 1. Woo! Oh my god.
You did a really good job, Kendra.
That's so satisfying.
That was awesome.
I'm going to dismiss Resot. Thank you so
much.
Good job.
Try to wrap my head around the 500,000
5% 10 million valuation. This innovation
is ancient. It was found in Phoenician
times. Women have been using it forever.
Yes. All through the Mediterranean. Yes.
And I mean there is zero proprietary
elements to it. Anybody can do this. So
help me, help me, help me get to $10
million.
We've actually worked two years to
create a proprietary manufacturing
process and also our own formulation. So
that's where we have some of our own IP
to be able to
you do your process is the IP.
Yes. Exactly.
So now would be a good time to tell us a
little about sales.
Sales.
I would love to tell you about our
sales. I launched in September 2020 as a
solo entrepreneur and at that point at
the end of the year I made 50k in
revenue. Got it.
Fast forward to 2021 we went viral on
Tik Tok and we made $2.6 million in
sales.
From 50,000 to 2.6
50,000 to 2.6.
That's what I'm talking about.
And then last year we ended the year in
$5.6 million in sales.
Wow. Wow. So, we first started in DTOC
and then we grew to Amazon and then at
the end of 2022, we made it in 300 Ulta
Beauty stores. Last year, we expanded
full nationwide and into 1300 stores.
And so, that's where we had that big
bump in sales.
Did you make money on the 5.6?
No, we didn't make money.
How's that possible?
We didn't make money. So in order to
make profits in retail, we learned the
hard way that you really need 85 90%
margins. Our margins were around 60%.
However, this year we updated our
suppliers and we implemented our
manufacturing process and so our margins
are now hovering around 80%.
Did you lose money or?
Yes, we lost money last year.
How much did you lose?
We ended the year at 777%.
So you lost $440ome,000.
How did you fund all those losses? Me
and my husband invested $400,000 of our
personal
lost more. You lost 400.
So then that's that goes into our debt
that we have right now.
How much debt do you have?
We have $1.5 million.
Hello. There we go.
Yeah. We also have $1 million in
inventory.
But it also means that you have like no
cash right now.
We have no cash right now. That's why
I'm here in the Shark Tank. Yeah.
That is what you need.
That is what I need right now. Yeah.
Especially if we want to get into more
retailers.
You can't afford to go into more
retailers. We have debt financing which
is at a high interest rate of 22%.
Wow.
Hello.
There it is.
So your total debt is 1.5.
Yeah. That's what's killing us right now
is because 20% of the money that we
borrow is just out the door. We had all
this money tied up in inventory and now
we're right sizing. So so much has
changed in the last few months.
Going through hyperrowth like you did
Yeah.
is hard. Yes. borrowing money to get
there put you even further underwater
because you're all it feels like you can
never catch up and and get even right.
Yeah.
I wish I had a way where I could just
say here you go. This is the approach.
But you know
I thought when I walked in and saw it I
thought this was food and I got hungry.
I just don't know this stuff at all. So
for those reasons I'm out. But I wish
you the best.
Okay. Thank you Mark. I appreciate it.
The ask is too big without even fighting
about the valuation. I would never value
this at 10 million right now. You've got
sales. I like that. But you got a long
way to go. It It's, you know, if you'd
come in here for like 100, 150, even
200, maybe I take the ride, change the
valuation a bit, but this is nuts. I
think it's nuts. So, for that reason,
I'm out.
Thank you, Kevin.
Yeah. So, it's hard because you couldn't
predict that you were going to go this
high and then as soon as you got that
that level, well, you had to learn what
you didn't know, right? the the amount
of margin on these things and then you
got to borrow money against it. You
can't leave uh Ultra empty-handed when
they asking for goods.
Yeah.
But uh you know to give you $500,000 for
5% uh you would have to distribute $10
million.
Uh if you going if you're doing really
well,
that's to get your money back. If you
just to get my money back, that means
you probably would have to do
in this model
$50 million.
You'd be older than the Phoenetians that
invented this by the time you got your
money back.
I'm out.
Thank you so much,
Aaliyah. You're amazing, by the way. And
I, you know, as you were talking, I've
been there. Like, I made some of these
same mistakes. I did my business on a
line of credit. I was bootstrapping
everything. I had credit card debt. I
mean, I it was hard to get anybody to
invest in me, you know? I know how what
that feels like, but what you're
accomplishing is really, really
exciting. I mean, you went from 28 to
56. Um, I love what you're doing. This
is just not my business and I'm a little
worried about the amount of debt that
you have, honestly. Um,
can before you say no, I'm willing to
make a deal and that's why I'm here. I
have worked my butt off for the last
four years and grown super fast to be
able to get to the point where I'm at
now. And I really would like
partnership. And you are sharks. You
guys love problems. This is a great
problem to solve.
Not sure we love.
We do know we love problems.
We love solving solving problems. Y'all
are problem solver. You would want to be
here.
The 500 that's just a big ask. And and
it's not even going to really put even a
little bit of damp on what you've
already got to deal with, right? It's
not going to really solve a lot of
problems. But I really do admire you.
I'm out.
Okay. Thank you. I appreciate it.
One of the things that concerns me truly
is just the competitive market.
And so I wish you good luck, but I'm
sorry I'm out.
Okay. All right. Thank you guys so much.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
I am disappointed that I'm walking out
without a deal. Um I really think that
with the sales that we had that they
could see the potential, but I love
surprising people. I love proving people
wrong. And so I hope in two years they
see Sugar Dough in tons of different
retailers and they're like, "Oh,