[Music]
Next up is a brand that merges function
with style.
[Music]
Hi Sharks. My name is Braxton Fleming
and I'm from Maze Landing, New Jersey
and I'm seeking $200,000 in exchange for
15% equity of my company. Six years ago,
the trajectory of my whole life changed.
I realized I was transgender. With this
realization came with the lifelong
commitment of taking hormone replacement
therapy in the form of injections.
During my first year of transitioning,
there was nowhere to properly store my
medical needs in a safe, neat, discreet,
yet stylish way. That's where Stealth
Bros and Co. revolutionized the way that
we store our meds and dispose of our
sharps. This was born out of my own need
as a trans man. But I realized there
were multiple underrepresented medical
communities who needed this product. Who
do you know that's a diabetic? Or maybe
you know someone going through
infertility treatment, a child with
injectable needs, or even cisgendered
individuals going through hormone
replacement therapy. All of these
underrepresented medical communities
need options to travel with confidence
for easy and proper atome storage.
That's where our DOT kits and Stell
Sharp Shuttles come in and save the day.
It's time to upgrade your plastic bags
in your old jugs
and store your meds in luxury. So,
sharks, who wants to fill the void of
millions of people and take a shot with
Stealth Frozen Co., let's go.
Yes. So, we can have a look at this
here. Absolutely. Please open up your
bags and um take a look at what you
have. What do we have in front of us,
Preston? Okay. So what you have in front
of you is a junior do kit and a stealth
sharp shuttle inside. So the junior dot
kit that you have is our foundational
junior do kit which is in line with our
sword interior. And then Lori, you have
our premium do kit which is made with
our vegan faux leather. So your
medicines and everything can go in here.
The vials. Yes, that is for the vials.
What's a sharp? So a sharps is part of
your injectable needs. It's a needle.
It's a biohazard container. Put your
needle in. So, after I use the needle, I
put it in here. Yes. So, you just pop
this top open like this. And then it can
close. And you can open it and close it
multiple times. Once it's filled, then
you want to take that little latch at
the top, stick it in that compartment,
and then it locks permanently and then
you can discard it appropriately. So,
this is the disposable aspect of the
needles. Yes. But does only one come
with your kit? I would think you'd be
using these like crazy. So, yes, we
actually offer them in bundles. So, you
could buy it for 1, three, or five on my
website. And we just received a major
purchase order from a large retailer.
And they will be sold in a bundle pack
of four. There are other dot kits for
injectables, right? Cuz I've seen plenty
of. Yes. And so, you just made them more
fashionable, more fashion looking.
Correct. And same with the sharps. Um,
absolutely. But what was missing from
the other kits? And is it what Mark
said, you just made it more fashionable
and cool and what was missing was the
effect that it was daunting to take the
injection for me. Even though I'm a
nurse, I've been a nurse for the past 11
years. I realized that yes, I give
injections every day, but when I was
watching the YouTube videos online of my
community taking these injections, I was
realizing how much anxiety was bring it
was bringing them. And once I created
something that organized everything for
them, they weren't all over the place. I
want to bring an experience to the user.
I want them to feel good about
themselves. And this brings happiness to
my community, and that's what I'm trying
to do. How do you how do you reach your
community? How do you sell the product?
So, I sell the product all through
e-commerce and I just been growing
organically through influencer. Um, and
now would be a good time to ask you how
much have you sold year to date?
Currently, we're at 110,000. That's
good. And last year, what did you do,
Braxton? We did 147,000. So, we're up
40% currently right now. What does this
cost to make and what do you sell it
for? Okay. So, the one that you have
cost $5.80 for me and then I sell it for
34.
$34. That's a big margin on the sharp
stuff. What your cost is for one of
these. Okay. And what you're going to
sell the one, three, and four pack, I
guess. Okay. So, if we buy over 10,000
pieces of that, it's at 28. And then we
sell them for $4 on the website. And
then if you buy a pack of five, it's 15.
And what are you going to sell for
wholesale to the retailer? So, I sell it
to them for $7.50 and then they're
reselling it for $14.99. So 750 for a
pack of four and it cost you 28 cents.
Yes. Thank you. Mark's going to start
selling them. Braxton, can you tell us a
little bit about yourself and your
background and Absolutely. Absolutely.
So I actually come from two
entrepreneurial parents and um as I was
growing up I was very accepted in my
family. You know my parents love me.
They never judge me. They let me be
whoever I wanted to be. And at the age
of 27 years old I said something is
missing from my life. And that's when I
realized that I was transgender. And
once I made that change, as I was
watching YouTube videos of other trans
men taking hormone replacement
injections, that's how I realized that
there was a need for this. And I was
indirectly assessing them with my
nursing skills, saying, "Oh, that's not
safe." Like, they're putting it in shoe
boxes. They're putting it in plastic
bags. And that's when I said, "You know
what? I really want to become a part of
my community because they've given me so
much that I wanted to give back. I
created this brand and it just blew up.
Is it just you running the business?
It's all me. I do everything. I
literally work out of my basement right
now. I have all my product down there.
Are you still doing this completely out
of your basement? Yes, 100%. And are you
nursing still or? Yes, I actually been
trying to slow down because I've been
putting more effort into the business. I
I'm just curious the logo Stealth
Brothers and Company. Like when you came
out here, I thought it's a great name
now. Now that we know and understand it,
it's great. I'll explain the name.
Stealth is because I wanted people to be
able to keep their medication discreet.
No, I get the stealth part. Why the
brothers and company is we're built on
the foundation of the brotherhood of F
tom, female to male brotherhood. And
then N co is and communities that we
keep our allied communities. That's
great. And then the swords are there for
because iron sharpens iron and more than
one community coming together makes you
better and stronger. And that's Do you
have that up on your website? the
explanation. I actually do not. You
should. I should. Cool. Thank you.
That's very cool. And there should be a
video there of you explaining it because
the power of how you just explained it.
Yes. Yeah. That comes across very very
well. Thank you. I think that it's kind
of the the perfect kit and I love what
you're doing for the community. I don't
think you need a partner. I don't always
say that. I rarely say it. I think you
should run this. I think you should take
all the profit and I think you should
grow step by step and you're going to
have a wonderful business and reap what
you sew. And for those reasons, I wish
you good luck. But I'm out. Thank you,
Lori. I appreciate it. So, Brax, the
greatest part of your business, not to
diminish the other parts of your
business is really you. I mean, you
exude an incredible warmth. Thank you.
And personality that draws people to
you. Thank you. I think you've got a
good business.
just at the size you are right now just
not something for me. I'm out. I wish
you all the best. Thank you. Thank you.
I've had some personal experience when I
was trying to get pregnant. I was in
doing in vitro for seven years to give
birth to my first born, you know. Thank
God it worked. God bless you. I remember
being in business meetings, in museums,
in theaters where it's time to take my
big shot, right? It was just as big as
this with a big plunger. It was made of
oil that burned when it was horrible.
Yeah. U but the ingenious ways I had to
come up with just to hide that. Not that
I was ashamed, but what do you do with
the damn needle, right? You know, my
life had to go on. I used to carry books
with me, cut out pages in the middle,
cut a page, like a stop. Wow. Carry the
book and stick the needles in there
because you can't dispose in a restroom.
You can't throw it in a garbage can. But
let me tell you something. You have
genuine warmth and love that your pitch
comes from. You feel it all over. And
you know what? I'm a believer. If you're
that sincere and you come from that love
spot, people always do well and they
buy. They just buy. It's like a magic
wand. And I think it's terrific what you
do. Thank you so much, Barbara. Thank
you. I'm going to make you an offer,
okay, of $200,000, but I don't want to
put in all cash. I'm going to give you
$100,000 in a credit line, $100,000
cash. And I do want 20% of the business
cuz I want to feel happy when you do
well and make money. So, I'd like to be
part of that celebration with you. Yes.
Yeah. I I think it has merit. I think
you have made something much more
fashionable and interesting to own. I
get it. Barb, do you want any help or
you want to do it yourself? If you want
to jump in, I think it's a good cause.
Yeah, I'll split it with you if you
want. Yeah. Okay. I like the fact you
know your numbers, right? Uh but it's
not a product that's going to fit for
me. Okay. But I wish you the best.
You're a good guy. The presentation is
very good. Thank you, Kevin. I'm out.
But you do have an offer from a
sharkette. and Marcus still I believe no
I'm I'm I'm very interested and Barb and
I were talking from an operational
perspective it's not just a cash issue
it's building your business issue as
well because you're doing it yourself
trying to scale it from the basement to
a business is going to be a lot of work
and I think between our two
organizations we we can complement each
other to get you there and so if it
works with you Barb and I will split it
so it's going to be $200,000
a h 100,000 of that that in cash and
$100,000 of That is a line of credit for
20%. What do you think, Braxton? Wow,
that's amazing. What do you think? Um,
it wouldn't be right if I didn't count
her. So, are you guys willing to go to
18%.
Well,
you guys got a deal. You got
congratulations. Thank you so much.
It's such a pleasure. Thank you so much.
Thank you so much, Barb.
Thank you so much, everybody.
Next up is a fashion line for
selfexpression.
[Music]
Hello, my name is Skyler Ellers and I'm
the creator of one of the hottest
fashion trends on the internet. I'm
seeking $100,000 in exchange for 10% of
my company.
Sharks, crochet takes us back to a time
when life was simpler and everything was
groovy. But most importantly, crochet
promotes positive vibes and makes people
happy.
And that's why I created my company,
Lord Von Schmidt.
My crochet designs are colorful,
sustainable, recycled, and repurposed.
But why take it from me when you can see
for yourselves? Hit it.
L'Oreal Indiana's outfits are aligned
with the slow fashion movement and come
with two fabulous accessories. Lower
carbon footprints and reduced weight.
[Laughter]
Anna and Azerai are certain to be the
life of any party. Crochet is addictive.
You might get hooked on the attention.
There you go. There you go. That's the
money shot.
That is the money shot. David, that's
it. There he is. There you go. He takes
his LEDs for a spin and the crowd goes
wild.
Nasty, nasty. So, Sharks, who wants to
jump on board this groovy train with us?
I love it. Oh my goodness. I have some
handouts for you. Damon, you should try
it on. Robert, I'm a little husky, so I
would look like a piñata.
You would actually. I would look like a
piñata for sure. Thank you. Thank you so
much. Beautiful. Thank you. I love a
good crochet. Thanks, Skyler.
How's that look?
[Laughter]
What do you think, Skyler? Oh,
beautiful.
Mark, yours is a little low-waisted.
Wow. You want to do a boot pants on?
I like them.
I can't wear those. Do it. I like it.
David's walking a home run right now.
Shake it, baby.
Whoa, that's hot. That is so hot.
You actually look really good in that,
Damon. It is a good look for you, Damon.
Interesting. Okay. Well, thanks so much
for trying them on. So, Skyler, tell us
about how you got into this. This looks
like a handmade art. And this is a
handmade art. Oh, it is entirely from
recycled crocheted blankets. Really? If
you're making them by hand, how can you
produce in quantity? Those are created
based on my crochet designs and they are
created in Asia. You outsource it. So,
you have a factory that's making them
for you. Yeah. Skyler, what do you sell
them for? So, the things that have been
manufactured are these parasols. And how
much is a parasol? To get a parasol to
the United States cost me $30, and I
sell them for $128 on my website. Wow.
And so, you have to get word out so
people know about this cuz we didn't
know about this on Shark Fake. Never
heard of Lord Von Schmidt. So Lord von
Schmidt started as my own weird little
project until suddenly it got picked up
on the internet and all of those blogs
ultimately culminated in a major
publicity boom that sold a ton of things
and mostly it was men's shorts made from
recycled Afghan blankets. How much are
the short shorts? Short shorts are $58.
What about the entire one? And then the
entire suit I can get 300. Wow. You
wearing those right now? Oh my. As a
matter of fact, I am. Dang.
Now, you seem like you're definitely a
fascinating and interesting person. You
have all our attention. What's your
background? So, I studied visual arts at
Columbia University. Nice. I was an
English teacher for years and I lived in
Barcelona.
So, from there, I got into knitting and
crochet. Just typical what everybody
does.
When I came back from Barcelona, I saw
Afghan blankets in the thrift store.
America has a ton of Afghans. We have a
glut of Afghans. So, I created these and
I put them up on my Etsy shop. Okay. And
then I took a little trip to India. All
of a sudden, I saw this bizarre spike in
men's shorts, which I hadn't sold a ton
of prior to that. And by the time I had
300 open orders for shorts, I had to
leave India and go back to the United
States to make them. I went to thrift
store after thrift store. Cut them up,
sewed them together. Cut them up, sewed
them together. How many orders did you
get on the shorts? Total total more than
300. 325. So, who's buying these? Like,
what is your demographic? My demographic
is a lot of people who go to summer
festivals. There's a very large LGBTQIA
plus contingent that follows this
fashion. Are you making any money today?
What are your sales? My sales are
188,000 so far this year. When did for
for four years? For four years. What
about last year? Last year was 37,000.
Okay. So, it's a small kind of hobby.
Your full-time job. Is this your full?
It is my full-time job. I live on that.
You're starving to death.
That's nothing. I can stretch money
really far. But but Skyler, if I'm going
to give you a $100,000,
that's like 10 years of sales for you.
It's crazy. You have to have a plan to
blow this thing up. I want to hear the
plan. The plan is to take the pieces
that I like the best and especially
something like this thong, which can be
produced very cheaply. How many have you
sold of the thong of the thongs? 10. But
I came out with them this summer. These
are basically works of art where you put
your heart and soul into it, right? So
why not charge more? A lot of times when
people see something and it costs more
than they expect, how they value it goes
way up. How's he going to make a living
though? You need to be able to make a
living off of this. He really has to do
it in mass mark because he won't
make money off. The only way this works
is if you sell that jumpsuit for $1,000
or more. I and I can't. You should have
no pieces that cost less than $250. If
you're charging 60 bucks, 80 bucks is
just a piece of clothing. Be an artist.
Sell it as artwork. You hand make each
and every one of these things. It's a
piece of art. Sell it that way. Oh, I
agree. For my handmade work, I totally
agree. You're still not charging enough.
You don't have to sell a ton of these
when they're art.
You only have to sell seven. What are
you doing, Mark? I I'm out. But I think
it's a great opportunity for you, but
you just got to be an artist that's
proud of their work and has some
confidence that it'll sell for a huge
price.
Skyler, being a great artist is not
enough. $37,000
is really insignificant. It's a start.
It's a start. But for me to give you a
hundred,000, you got to get this to half
a million. You got to get to a million.
And that is less art and creative.
That's art and business. There's no
plan. I'm out. I'm sorry.
As much as I love all of this, I want to
put my heart and soul into it and give
the very best that I can. And
unfortunately here, I just don't think
that this is like right for me. So, I'm
sorry I'm out.
Scott, I think we've all pretty much
agreed in the same way. I mean, you
remind me very much of myself. I stood
in the corner and I sold $800 worth of
hats. And I realized at that point I
will never work for anybody ever again
for the rest of my life. But it took me
10 years to figure it out from that day.
And I just don't think you have it
figured out yet. But you will never work
for anybody for the rest of your life.
But right now it's too early. I'm out.
Skyler, you had all the components that
you need on Shark Tank. A brilliant
idea. The face of it. Missing is a
person telling me, "Look, Skylar's doing
all this. Meanwhile, I'm back in India.
I've got logistics. I've got
distribution. I'm dealing with the
retailers we're going to work with. You
need that partner, whoever it is.
They're not there. I would love to give
you $100,000. I would love to give you
more. I mean, this this thing I'm not
going to because there's uninvestable.
It's uninvestable. There's there's no
way to make it. My guy
Thank you, guys.
But there's, you know, I I am an
investor and I got to get it back. I'm
just frustrated and I'm sorry to say I'm
out, but you're one hell of a guy, Lord
Von Schmidt.
Thanks, guys. Congrats, Skyler. Go in
peace. You're worth a lot to me. They
really do. All right, come on, guys.
Let's boogie on out of here. Boogie on.
Bye.
Next into the tank is a brand seeking to
be a better fit for all.
[Music]
Hi Sharks. I'm Sherice and this is my
wife Vicki. We're from San Diego,
California, seeking $250,000 for 5%
equity in our company. When you go
clothes shopping, most stores have a
men's section and a women's section. But
Sharks, neither of those sections work
for me. The women's section tends to
have more form fitting clothes, which I
like, but I don't. And while I love the
men's style, those clothes are just not
made for my body shape. Sharks, she's
got a booty. True story. We're all
unique individuals, and we believe the
shopping experience should be based on
style preference and body type, not on
gender. That's why we decided to forge
the future of fashion with Dapper Boy, a
genderless and size inclusive apparel
line made to fit you both inside and
out. Join Dapper Boy in being part of a
revolutionary solution that'll bring
confidence within us all. After all,
isn't about time that we all fit in.
Sharks, in front of you, some Dapper Boy
clothes we love for you to check out.
Good for you guys. Thank you. I'm really
intrigued. I mean, you sell direct to
consumer because you're asking retailers
to create a third category, right?
Right. And you know, obviously we're not
opposed to creating this third category
or not, but right now we feel like
direct to consumer is the way to go,
especially, you know, with being
missiondriven brand and just being easy
to shop online. Good looking stuff. So,
are you blowing it up on social or how
are you getting the word out to your
community? Yeah, so Facebook and
Instagram mostly. Um, we're excited to
start dabbling to some influencer
marketing as well. How did you come up
with this? I used to shop in the women's
department and those styles were just
never for me. I never felt confident. I
felt frumpy. I felt unseen. But we
started Dapper seven years ago now. And
literally, it came from a pair of jeans.
Jeans was the first thing I tried on in
the men's department. And it was the
scariest thing to go to that section,
you know, to maybe be judged. Um, but it
was exactly what I wanted to be. It was
like the confidence I wanted. That was
my style, you know, it was emotional.
But years later, I realized those
clothes just never fit my body type. And
so we we saw a bunch of people just like
myself with the same exact problem. So I
guess that your sales are less than a
million. Please
don't be wrong. So lifetime sales in the
last seven years, we've done about 3.5.
And actually the way we've run our
business is uh pre-order campaigns.
That's very good. So we bootstrapped the
brand. In last year we were at 1.2.
Yeah. Oops. I got you. So why don't we
get into the margins? What do you uh
what's an average marginal? Take this
shirt for example. Yeah, that shirt is
uh $9.40
and we sell it for 60. Landed price for
jeans $15. We sell them for $99. Nice.
What did you mean when you referenced a
pre-order campaign? How does that work?
Yeah. So, how we were able to bootstrap
is that we launched these products at
what we call intro pricing. So, it's
usually about a 50% margin at that
point. And that really creates a sense
of urgency within our customers. Our
repeat customer rate is 51%. These
people are waiting for our products to
come in. And how does it how do you
execute that exactly? I've never heard
that. So, we launch a product, we put
out on email, social, everywhere, and
then the customers go ahead and
pre-order the product and we usually
deliver within 6 to 10 weeks. But I will
admit here co, you know, killed us.
Right now with the co delays, we're
seeing six, seven months. Ouch. Wow. And
so, how much do you have in inventory
right now? 60 grand. Okay. But it's
across a lot of sizes and that's what
makes it tough. How much cash do you
guys have? Well, maybe $100 today. $100?
What? $100? I'm not Yep. We're at the
point here where uh we just sold our
house. Oh, no. It's It's uh vulnerable
and not fun to talk about, but we
believe in this brand like more than
anything. So far, you're losing money,
right? Yes. Okay. So, this How much
money are you on intro pricing? It's
killing your margin. Yeah. Wait, Kevin.
Kev, how much money are you losing?
Yeah, so I think we're about 150,000 ne
uh negative this year. What did you lose
last year? Uh 313. So you're 450 in the
hole, right? Yeah, guys, something
doesn't add up for me. Yeah, right.
Because your margins are like this and
your shipping cost shouldn't be that
astronomical. What happened was is I
also started spending in marketing. I
hired a consultant. That's where you
went wrong. Exactly. So how much did you
spend on marketing? I would say, you
know, it was definitely over 30% of Oh
my god. So, you have this rabid
community that wants to buy from you.
You don't need to market them. It was
our attempt and it was a wrong attempt
to try to expand and go further, but we
were not ready for that. We will be
ready for that, but not now. And that's
why we need experts like you guys to
come on board. The reason why the people
are waiting six and seven or eight
months is like you said, it it's a
community. It's a it's a movement. It
it's funny that fubu uh for us bias has
become used a lot in the LGBTQ plus
community. Am I right? And
you are for us bias. You know that
that's that's who you are. Why are you
trying to go any place else? If other
people adopt it, it's no problem. But
why are you going any place else?
There's so many people that identify
with you right now. Stop trying to be
everything to everybody. You know, I I
have to I have to argue that. And it's
because I don't want to be categorized.
I want to fit in with everybody.
Listen, I'm Listen, I'm pro black. I'm
never anti anything else. Of course, it
doesn't mean that other people won't
accept you. So, I have to be I have to
be honest. I have to give you my
assessment of the business. I got to try
to find a way to help you. I'll mentor
you. But as for the business, I'm out.
Thank you. You guys, I like to sit here
and say I've done a million products,
and I have, and I've done something in
just about every medium, but the one
thing I've really never done is jeans,
clothing. I don't know how I could bring
value to your business and help you out.
So, unfortunately, I wish you good luck,
but I'm out. Thank you very much. I
understand your mission. I respect it.
There is such a need for this, but I
think your problem is much larger
cashwise than you envision it to be.
Even you came in here when we gave you
the $250,000
for your stock. That's nothing that's
not going to get you over the hump. It's
just it's a rough one. So, I wish I
could be with you, but I am now.
I wanted to mention one other thing, and
it's pretty important here. We're about
to do a collaboration with another brand
that does jeans, and they do 3D
modeling. So what happens with that is
that guys guys don't do that. Don't do
the collaboration. No, you have a
fundamental problem. You don't know what
business you're in. You have this
community that's like this. Your clothes
are not the product. The community is
looking to your your clothes as their
membership as the way that they for them
to say we all belong together. That this
is us. The clothes are secondary. It's
keeping the community together that's
important. But I have a fundamental
problem as an investor because we're not
on the same page on what makes the
business. It's about I want more
inventory. I've got this collaboration.
I've got all these other things. That's
not the vision I would have. And it's
your vision that's far more important.
So for those reasons, I'm out.
You're you're not only all in, you're
all in 2,00%. There's only one
direction. Yes. It's up to the surface
so you can breathe some oxygen. That is
not a wonderful place for an investor to
be. Right. I wish you guys the best of
luck, but I know.
Yeah. Thank you. Good luck, guys. Thank
you very much. Fighting. God bless you.
Let me give you this. Yes. This is my
number. So, good luck. Thank you very
much. Thank you. Appreciate it. Thanks.
Thank you guys.
I think the Sharks reminded us that our
community is is everything. It's not the
end of Dapper Boy. And you know what? At
the end of the day, we came here to
build a relationship and I'm so happy
that we walked out of here with
hopefully a mentorship. Yes. So that's
huge. Yes.