I don't get like how we Face lighting
issues every day we've been doing
YouTube for 3 years and we can't get
lighting right we're the worst we're the
worst YouTubers worse or better
reaction
no I was fixing my balls damn all right
guys welcome back to the Friday car
video it's a Friday car video today
we're going to tell some stories because
we haven't fil the car video in what
feels like forever but it was actually
not that long ago cuz you're just in
Boston oh I didn't get the Shave Club
memo disgusting disg there's no there's
no CL
I hate hearing about it oh my God any
bit of conversation regarding facial
hair is one of those things that just
makes me wish I had matches and gasoline
so I can burn myself on fire until I
just disintegrate there's a lot of
scenarios that just like my first
initial thought while someone's talking
to me it's no longer what even what
they're saying it's it's me in my brain
seeing myself turn into Ash and fall to
the ground and just dissipate into the
air that the other day Nick said and I
quote if you really take time to look at
it a fork can if you really take time to
look at it look at a fork oh you're you
can't quote me and [ __ ] it up like this
cuz now I sound stupid yeah this is this
I already sound stupid was what you're
going to say now you're ruining it for
me you take the time to really look at a
fork you can actually realize how crazy
that [ __ ] is cuz I was doing the
dishes and I was holding a fork I'm like
what the [ __ ] cuz it's like it's not
sharp enough to like get food but it's
like it Scoops but it picks it up it's
just like it's nuts like some someone
had to think like this is going to be a
perfect a perfect thing to like pick up
and Source food with I really like the
weight of Sil a little bit love for it
it's the perfect like like you could jab
someone in the neck of the no like it's
just like perfect perfectly weight
distributed like whoever made a fork
like good job you could balance it on
your fingers it like teetering a fork
would be a fun feeling but it's also not
too light like I
like here like it's boinking halfway
through his Cent not too late yeah don't
remic it it's gross already it was gross
when you did it the first time by
accident you're trying to be funny dud
it again it's it was already it's
already embarrassing I'm going to sound
like the biggest hater I I can't stand
when children do like childish [ __ ] and
think it's like unique or funny like the
other day um I was walking around and it
was near Halloween and there was like a
um a big spider inflatable clearly fake
for the holidays and it had like a sign
and it was like a little kid made it and
it was like very poisonous like Beware
of the spider and I'm like this is not a
[ __ ] poisonous spider this is an
inflatable you bought at Target I
literally saw and I let it bother me
like this little kid like making jokes
about venomous spiders like this [ __ ] is
not venomous if I walked by and the kid
was there and he was like be careful
like the spider's venom like [ __ ] you
it's a toy you're an
idiot he makes me think I thought about
him like oh it's a small kid and he
thinks he's funny but I'm like just shut
up you ruined your front don't you like
this you were no like it was cool like
the spider itself was cool but I'm like
a paper sign in front being like beware
venomous I'm like are you an idiot wow
that's so sad like you're [ __ ] a lot
no it is [ __ ] up you could never be
like a kindergarten teacher no I know
it's it is [ __ ] up the other day I
hugged Matt and he goes oh I just want
to peel you like a banana I did not say
that swear on everything I make that up
I make that up I think would why would
he hugs me he goes o I just want to peel
you like a banana and like shakes me I'm
like
what I swear to God I I wish I wish that
we were recording I swear to God I swear
to God may God strike me with lightning
if I swear to him and I'm telling a lie
one day you're going to say that and get
struck by lightning no I'm not because
I'm always telling the truth like
Airport TSA [ __ ] yourself cuz are you
dead serious with me that I'm like I
hate oh my God I hate it's like when the
energy when like you're about to do the
dishes and your mom's like Oh do the
dishes you're about to like yeah like
take your hoodie off no no oh oh I walk
into the X-ray and [ __ ] put my feet
on the feet prints on the ground like
I'm at the [ __ ] zoo looking at the
animals they have like the stupid goofy
things like the lion prints I'm like oh
yeah that's what I think a l time okay
you know when you see like and you're at
the zoo you're like at the lion
enclosure and they have like the lion
pops on the ground like oh they think
they're cool like oh the lion walked
here and it's like not true he's in
there idiots okay anyways they have the
feet prints on the ground the X-ray I'm
like okay I'm going to stand there cuz
that's where you want me to stand and I
stand there and I'm looking straight
ahead stick figure man like this I've
been to the airport plenty of times I
live in two different states I travel
all the time I know exactly what I have
to do for this x-ray game I need to put
my arms up like this and surrender to
the X-ray and I'm doing it and the guy
I'm I'm literally like this I'm
literally like this I'm literally like
this and he's like oh put your hands
up they can't get any higher put your
hands up I'm doing what he's doing I'm
doing what the king's doing I'm already
doing it just scan me and let me through
please scan me let me through please I
have nothing on and that's when it beeps
then you got to feel your G and like at
the airport I didn't want to pack my big
shoes in my suitcase cuz it takes up too
much space and I wanted to save room for
my other stuff I don't care just [ __ ]
go okay this story actually just got
ruined by what you just said because you
are just like the belittling woman that
that attacked me at the airport okay I
have my big boots and I wore them to the
airport cuz I didn't want to put them in
my suitcase so I'm walking up to TSA I
put my laptop my phone my backpack my
everything and then the L my everything
okay the lady goes oh we're going to put
your boots in this bin and I go oh I
have big shoes by like they're big boots
by the way as I'm taking it off and
handing it to her and she goes I don't
care that's what she said to me oh that
is crazy like she's like We're going to
put your like boots in this one I go oh
they're big boots by the way as I'm like
taking it off and handing it to her like
this and she goes I don't care so you
will care if they have a bomb in it cuz
your job is to detect it Nick stop no
it's serious I really should have
smacked that lady I think that would
have gone over well youever so flight
list D me and ni funny story you ready
to hear yep awesome funny funny story
time oh my God oh my
God I'm like hiding my face cuz if
you're going to do that embarrassing
[ __ ] I can't even be seen correct me and
Nick could go to the grocery store the
other day because we came back from
Boston and our entire fridge and
cabinets were empty because we were just
in Boston for 2 weeks go to the grocery
store get all the things that we need
and then Nick goes in the line and I
went to the to the coold cut thing I'm
going to start whispering in the little
cracks of the car and see if it comes in
another way like hey Nick I'm going to
keep saying this story Nick feel free to
pick up and grab it whenever you feel
the most prise I will right so I go to
the deli to get like the Oh I like that
we're getting louder it sounds like he's
in a tin can Nick what I'm serious I
hear it all around me dud oh my God hold
on I go hold
on there's nothing going on I thought
there was like a humming UFO spaceship
sound yeah there's a [ __ ] alien on
the that's what I heard what's going on
right here get out of here Jeffrey Matt
keeps calling random people Jeff and I'm
okay are we ready someone I was talking
to today called like a group of people
the cats and I was like it's kind of
weird but I like it are we done okay so
I go to the deli to get the the the
sandwich stuff and Nick is in the
checkout line you know how like when we
used to do with mom when like really
young kids I got it you know so Nick's
in the line and then I walk over like 10
minutes after okay and I go and add the
the cold cut stuff to the to the cart
and Nick looks like he hasn't made any
progress at all in the line and do you
want to know why I look like that
because I [ __ ] have not already been
10 minutes and Nick is still the third
person and I and I don't think and I
don't think Nick switch grocery lines
you [ __ ] [ __ ] you've been standing
your feet are [ __ ] digging into the
[ __ ] ground moving to a different
line that's shorter no I'm [ __ ]
determined to go to [ __ ] Lane number
eight for God knows what [ __ ] reason
correct like how about you move to a
different Lane idiot correct so you say
my head so I'm like I'm just like oh I'm
here I've made my decision I've chose
[ __ ] my path I'm on [ __ ] road Rojo
aul I'm on the [ __ ] path already this
is the direction we have to take so I'm
thinking I'm already there I'm looking
at the deli for Matt and I don't see
them and I'm like where's Matt I felt
like when your when your parent abandons
you at the grocery store to go like oh
give me a minute I need to go do this
and you just feel like you're going to
that killed or kidnapped without them I
was I was waiting for M looking around
and poor sweet lady in front of me she's
buying like looks like she's doing a
margarita night or something with her
girls she's getting like wine and she's
getting like like mixers and like she's
getting a case of water she was
doing let's throw 10 items Max 10 it the
one so I'm looking at her and I'm like
this dumb [ __ ] could have gone to self
checkout no way no wait no way I'm like
you could have done self checkout with
ease but whatever you chose to be a
psycho you chose to be a sick [ __ ]
anyway so we got she's ahead of us in
line with her [ __ ] on the conveyor belt
and ahead of her we got Coupon Mom reel
down dead serious she's Chris how many
lanes were open give me like I don't
know this is our story this is where we
One path that's all path eight right in
front of her right in front of wine
Knight yeah is this [ __ ] crazy Lon
she's wearing like a [ __ ] Poncho okay
literally like a r like a rain but it
was like it it wasn't for like a
specific purpose like it was giving like
for whim like for whim
she was going for like a she definitely
has like she definitely has like eight
wind like dream catchers in her yes like
hippie Vibe woman like surpr she wasn't
[ __ ] rock and tie dye crazy I'm surp
it's like one of those people you look
at her and then you just see like the
three birds floating around her head I'm
saying she was out of it so she she's
checking out right and and and and and
and and and she's her entire the entire
base of her cart you know how it's like
metal yeah every single crevice and
cranny has a [ __ ] Vitamin Water of
this disgusting ing no hate to Vitamin
Water love you guys this your your worst
flavor Vitamin Water your worst flavor I
apologize like this kiwi lime green
oh Ki disgust she's got she's got Ki
disgust and it's covering the whole
bottom of the card how many like Chris
oh 36 36 she's drinking one of them and
one individual yeah she's she's
making let she's let let me one thing
you keep going she's making that stupid
face while she's she was drinking one
and she's going like this she's taking a
sip and then looking at the guy while
he's scanning the groceries and looking
at other people she
like I want to smack you I want to smack
you she's drinking one right so this is
hers she's drinking it are we ever going
to get to the end of this yes we're
getting there it it's a it's an edger
it's a builder just let it Edge so she's
drinking one it will be worth it swear
to God she's drinking one and one of
them's on the conveyor boat like this
and the guy SC grabs it scans once scans
twice for the one there and the one
there and then he puts it on the thing
and it goes down to the lady to bag it
right obviously obviously about hold on
hold on the guy keeps scanning the rest
of her stuff yeah this isn't all she has
he he keeps scanning the rest of her
stuff and then she goes oh the vitamin
water and like points at the one in her
cart and is like holding one she goes
the vitamin water and the guy goes yep
she goes I want to make sure you got the
right amount he goes yep that one and
that one too and she goes oh no and
points at her cart she's like 36 she
goes there's 36 it makes that same
stupid face like 36 I'm like oh if you
[ __ ] stick your lip out again it's
going to hit me dude that's what I'm
feeling like I'm feeling like your
bottom lips on my head so this dude
instead of grabbing the one that she has
or or grabbing the one that he already
put to the end of the conveyor belt he
Scrolls on the thing and finds it to add
34 more he tries to like instead of
getting he tries to like duplicated in
his
machine mi stop it's been 15 minutes at
least a and he's he's scrolling it's
been 15 minutes takes him 3 minutes to
go back up to where the Vitamin Water to
add 34 more then then this lady she's
like she's she's pulling out coupons
like oh my god do your thing whatever
coupon your life away and she's scanning
it the totals aren't looking like what
she wants it to look like she's losing
her [ __ ] mind and then she's done
we're like thank God this already took
20 [ __ ] minutes and then she's like
oh I I wanted to buy cigarettes and I I
need like money back so she starts
trying to make a return at the thing
like you need to bring your [ __ ] to the
Service Des she's decided she decided
that she didn't want like four of the
items that she already purchased and
instantly tried to instead instead of
also instead of also buying cigarettes
she was trying to make like a trade like
here's the items that I accidentally
bought that I don't want anymore I want
my two back two boxes of cigarettes
that's the that's what she want she
wanted she wanted to barter instead of
like return she thought she a [ __ ]
pirate like oh I'm bringing two
cannonballs in a Year's worth of py to
your ship if you give me your [ __ ]
yeah two goats and some [ __ ] maze I
don't know corn yeah yeah maze is
corn
and so he refunds her $9 onto her card
at the thing which I'm already like dude
you shouldn't have done that you should
have sent her to the service desk your
job was done and he's like he refunds
her $9 she puts her card in gets the $9
on her card and literally takes her card
out and doesn't she goes where are the
cigarettes he's like I gave you $9 on
your C goes where's the cash he goes you
just put your card The Mach so she's
like in her brain she deserves $9 so
she's like looking around out like in
the world I pull a 20 from my bag I'm
like if this takes another God damn
minute I'm going to buy this lady some
cigarettes and smoke one with her cuz
I'm losing my [ __ ] mind I'm losing it
I'm going to become a nicotine addict so
I'm looking at her so hold on
hold so it doesn't end there it doesn't
end there it doesn't end there
commercial break commercial
break so it's been at least not not
joking dude you have literal tear you
need it's been it's been not joking
anywhere from 18 to 23 minutes that's
where we're at dud you look like you're
crying cuz I just not kidding that's how
long it's taken 18 to 23 minutes not
kidding now round three the lady the
lady in front of us turns around she
goes I don't know if you boys are too
young Margarita night yes no she invite
us to the margarita I'm asking for
clarification are you drinking what are
you drinking I need it drinking her wine
and
then 36 of these 36 of these I'm going
give you 36 left then knock your
dentures out you hippie hippie freak
chis I think if you went back to this
store my feet would be like the [ __ ]
TSA x-ray you'd see my [ __ ] feet on
the ground where Nix stolo lost his
[ __ ] mind Isle eight dead serious
there better be a placard next time I go
there and a [ __ ] Express G pass like
give me the [ __ ] Genie the lady in
front of us turns around not the one
that's like causing all the problem the
one I had it she turns around and she
goes I don't know if you boys are too
young but I feel like I'm on punked
right
now I'm waiting for John I literally
looked up I go where's the film crew
finally are about to get to the
conclusion of like the guys explaining
oh my
God
all and there now he's about to go into
the final thing of like getting her her
cigarettes and checking out the store
that we were in the grocery store is one
of those that has a coffee shop inside
of it the dude from the coffee shop
walks over the dude from the coffee shop
who's the only one working at the coffee
shop walks over there's five lanes open
he goes to that guy who's scanning all
of her [ __ ] and goes the whipped cream
got stuck can you help me open it and
heister and he's like and our the dude
so this lady's bitching to him about
where her [ __ ] mag
are trying to open a Whi cream he's
ignoring her now so now we have three
him her Margarita Knight us and he's
twisting whipped cream for no reason and
the kid who comes over thinks it's so
funny that the whipped cream's clug he's
like he was sweet he he looked nice I
feel bad that I'm about to like eat him
up he's I kid you not he's like looking
he he's like definitely like this I I
know cuz I'm gay um Ally he like had a
crush on the guy that he like asked to
open it I think yeah and he was like
trying to like be like oh can you open
it like I need help and he was trying to
get him to open it you're strong type of
yes and he was like trying and he was
like so happy to be there that he's like
looking at me and Matt and the wine
night lady and he's like looking like
smiling and happy like oh like isn't
this funny that the wh cream's talk
isn't this funny I'm like the only thing
funny is when I take that whipped cream
and kill myself with it I'm sorry no I
have a serious question ask what H I've
never needed assistance with whipped
cream a d it's like the the Barista
one you know that viral video of that
guy and me and you always laugh at and
he go oh you want a some of this that oh
would you like a some of this on you
that he has the whipped cream now and
he's trying to like open it like this it
pops and went face the straw is like
pointing out where the whipped cream is
going to go and he's like this and the
straws pointed right at the Hipp and she
goes she goes wo don't point that at my
face she she like she's like w about
another 5 minutes Nick give or take goes
by and and Meanwhile we're still waiting
in line and hello finally opens the
whipped cream and gives it to the guy
he's back he's making coffees yes the
lady goes so where's my cigarettes and
my $9 and she starts doing that and the
lady in first of all the you can't get
both you can use the was delusional so
the lady the lady in front of me I
aspire to be her level of stupid cuz my
life would be easier cuz I couldn't put
that much the lady in front of us goes
I'm I hate to be rude that's what she
she says she goes I hate to be rude it's
been 35 minutes I need to pick up my
daughter in 10 she needs to wait so now
she the lady just goes the lady looks up
at us now she looks at so hold up she
looks up at us now cuz that lady just
like interrupted her and she looks up
she looks at the lady she looks at me in
M til her head like a a dog like she
goes she goes you can go she says to the
lady you can go and then she looks past
the other lady at me and Nick and goes
she tilts her head like a dog observing
himself in a mirror and she goes are you
guys Twins and we go yes we're Twins and
she's like you guys have been standing
there forever and I didn't even notice
do you know how every fiber in my being
had to be settled down by a deep [ __ ]
breath to go do you want to know why
I've been standing right [ __ ] here
forever yeah because the [ __ ] the
[ __ ] coven your Cen left you behind
and this supreme leader Witch is taking
forever to [ __ ] buy vitamin water
you're my issue I'm here for eternity
because of you you sick creature so now
she I think it's like you're making
you're choosing to make small talk
you're attempting to make small talk
with your enemy I want nothing to do
with you I want to see your face tumbled
into the ground and then the other lady
scans her hit and leaves before she
could even start to try to buy her
cigarettes again me and Nick just pushed
all of our [ __ ] to the front and he
started scanning ours I
think I worked at a grocery store and I
can scan circles around his [ __ ]
ass 411 Banas that was the story of how
me and Nick spent an hour 40 to 45
minutes in a checkout
line good story I'm surprised I'm alive
to tell the tale it was a lot you should
have super punched that [ __ ] in the
jump like with this fish she thinks this
one's coming nope Swit should have put
antifreeze in a vitamin water should be
gone by next week water squirt in your
throat I don't play those games don't do
that
thanks okay fruit cake edit boner I
know
what like a good edit moment like like
edit boner like yeah your little tail go
ahead all right like I had sleep prows
just again oh god dude dude do you know
how what's up with you suffering it is
to feel like you are defeated and can't
move that's how I felt my back I fell
asleep on my back of course which is my
le I feel sleep paralysis is for the
week I've never had it it's like just oh
my God no I I think it's like oh I'm
going to get curse now I'm going to have
it every day no it's that but then it's
also like it's also when you have broken
sleep like if you sleep for like an hour
and then go back to sleep like we don't
need the scientific no seriously less is
more we don't I just have need the
lesson what we need to know is let get
to us what was it about you that like
had sleep paralysis that's what we need
here I was asleep on my back like like
this and I never fall asleep on my back
never I never do that and I never fall
asle I try my very hardest to fall
asleep on my stomach every night it's so
it's like such a disgusting feel and I
hate it because it's like imagine you're
like just like you're laying down on
your back and then you feel stop making
faces you feel pinned to the [ __ ]
mattress I like it hold
on you wake up and you know that your
brain is awake and you physically cannot
move your body yet and it just feels
like you're being pushed that's how it
literally felt I feel like I'm at the
fourth grade science I I was going to
die anyway I'm having a nightmare right
and in my nightmare I like know that I
want to be awake right you know how
dreams are they're very hard to follow
but this was what my dream was I was
with like you guys a couple other people
and I'm like walking through like this
city right and then yes go any dragons
no dragons Okay that helps at the scene
then there's like imagine we're just
like walking through a city there's like
five or eight of us like just a bunch of
people that we know imagine like a black
portal type situation right and it
starts like sucking in like the city
like all the and like we start like
floating we got and then we all land on
like this wall like on the like we land
back on the ground but we're all facing
like this Bri brick wall like in front
of us I look to my left and the brick
wall is going all the way and then I
look to my right and the brick wall is
going all the way like there's no like
there's no you're in The Maze Runner yes
like it's just like one humongous like
humongous it's like a mural of like just
like people and other and it's like it's
like it says like a city name like we
land in like a new city that's like
fully like by like a brick wall right
and we're walking trying to get by and
then the the ground starts like slanting
like this so
now to start like walking up toward the
wall keep walking forward or else you'll
fall to like your death every there's
like I look to my left and I look to my
right and there's like 40 people to each
side like just walking up trying to like
get over the brick wall and it's like a
fight to get up and climb it and then
things start like falling out of it
people start like turning and laughing
like you're going to die like the the
Wall's going to get you like like
literally like that like I saw some
stupid some [ __ ] all black nightmare
yes and but the whole imagine this whole
time I know that I'm trying to get up
out of bed and I can't for the past like
3 minutes and I'm like literally like
stuck to my bed and I like the only
thing that's like not wake me up is like
I'm like I feel like I'm like pushing
down to try to get up and I can't get I
cannot get up awful like I'm stuck to
like my [ __ ] mattress like that's
literally how I felt like [ __ ] starts
falling out of the wall like the figures
start like falling forward and like
knocking people down and hitting them so
like so I'm like right next to someone
and so it's like crazy wipe out yes and
a [ __ ] like brick wall a brick a
brick like from the wall like flies out
and crushes the person's face next to me
and like they are gushing blood and they
like fall to the ground and like all
these bricks start like flying by and
like all these [ __ ] like like it
looked like I was in a tornado almost
and we're just like running up this wall
trying to get up it and like that I woke
up like to that and it literally like
[ __ ] was
insane wow and that was the whole thing
what a start to your dad like scrambling
I was like I'm never going to sleep
again I had just stay up awake for like
an hour get to stay up awake for and
then I I finally like built up the car
I'll just go back to bed cuz I don't
think it can happen again cuz I have to
be up in like a half hour um before we
finish this week's car video I just want
to let you guys know I have been in this
really cool new let's trip sh that's not
available to shop yet and same with
Chris and his blue hoodie but how cool I
get the baby T on under this really no
to your favorite video we've ever filmed
whether there was a car video Vlog or
some type of thing that we've done and
put it in the comments to let us know
what we can do more of I think think if
I have like a good story like the
grocery store I can just film a good car
video it's just a matter of getting out
of the house man all right see you guys
next Friday
[Music]