Hey guys, welcome back to this week's
Friday video. Welcome back to the Stern
Triplets channel. I am Nick. This is
Matt. And that is Chris. And we are so
excited for you to be joining us today.
Yay. I walked 10,000 steps today. And my
daily average is normally 2,500.
So, claps for
my legs are shattered. And um also
another thing I want to address and say,
last week me and Chris were singing
Luther Vandross. Luther Vandross. Luther
Vandross. I don't know how to say
nobody. And our video literally got
copyrighted because of how good Mine and
Chris's singing was at the beginning.
Yeah. Like we sang it so well that they
thought it was the real song and they
were like, "Yeah, we have I did also say
uh a lyric wrong." I'm pretty upset
about it. Which one? I think I said my
diamond light instead of my guiding
light. I almost wore a vest today for
today's video. Why? You didn't have
allergies today. Exactly. Huge news for
the Sternial Triplet community. Like
major news. Like everyone red alarm.
Everyone needs to know. Guess what
happened today. Hey, should I get a drum
roll? Then Chris, you can tell them what
you drum roll for me if you don't know
who's drum rolling.
I can drum roll.
[Music]
The plumber came. The plumber finally
came and he fixed our shower head. So,
our shower pressure is really good. We
have amazing hot water. So, I feel
genuinely like the highest energy I've
felt in a really long time just from
knowing that like not that I was dirty,
but it was so much easier for me to like
clean head to toe today and just that
refreshing kind of like spa treatment in
my own home. It really it really turned
[ __ ] around for me. A normal average
shower. Literally an average. I
literally I I took a twominute shower
because I was I was overwhelmed by the
amount of water coming out. I was like,
"How good is this?" Like, I genuinely I
think this is like the best mood I've
been in in like months. No, it's great.
And it's all due to good good water
pressure. So, shout out to two guys that
were here working on our pipes all day.
Because they killed it. They really
turned it out. They chewed. They ate
down. What else did they do? Clock it.
Guys, it's really hot in here. Like, we
so hot. Shout out to the two guys that
were just working our pipes today cuz
they they did it like I did not say it
like that. They did it like magic. Come
on. They did. Shop Space Camp Kool-Aid
collab. Honestly, they spent most of
their time in Matt's pipes to the point
where he actually has to delay the usage
of his pipes again. I know. OMG. The
Space Camp Kool-Aid collab is limited
edition. And so the minute it sells out,
it will never come back again. And
that's why it hasn't sold out yet is
because once it's gone, it's gone
forever. So there's a lot of quantities
of it. But I will say the one day that
it does run out and it does sell out.
When that tap runs dry, it's going to be
gone forever. So, shop now while
supplies last. I have to beat this level
of um
Give me your phone. Give me your phone.
I'm playing it. No, you're not. It
actually throws my energy. Like, I was
about to introduce the video, but now
I'm just like, now I know you're focused
on like matching colors and shapes like
a baby. So, it like throws my vibe. You
know what I mean? Why intro we're going
to do together if he's too busy [ __ ]
putting triangles and squares together?
It's diamonds, clovers, castles, and and
I don't know what that is. Bears. Oh my.
Are you done?
You just think you're the funniest guy
ever, huh? Um, I think there's actual
public records of you stating that.
We are going to be responding to you
guys, should we break up or not? We said
for an upcoming video, we wanted to read
and react to your guys' responses to the
question, should we break up or not? If
you guys are in a relationship or a
toxic friendship situation, give us some
stories and details and we might just
answer if you should break up or not. 5
hours ago, we posted that on our sur
triplets Instagram story and guess how
many responses we got since 5 hours ago.
I have no idea. I have no clue. 20,000.
I was a bit We're not if we land on your
story and we give bad advice, don't take
it.
It just because it's we're telling you
to do it doesn't mean it's the best
situation. We all know that. We are by
absolutely no means equipped to give any
sort of advice. Correct. I'm the most
equipped. Let's do it. All right. I love
your Hooter shirt, by the way, Nick.
Thank you. I love it. I'm equipped to
give advice, but I'm I'm going to joke
around today, so it's like it's okay.
You don't have to [ __ ] get your hand
off of me. Punched my knuckles, dude.
Literal knuckle sandwich. If you were to
be a straight man, Nick, would you
prefer Hooters? Like boobs or butt? What
What's What's your preferred? If you're
a guy,
what do you a guy? First of all, no. If
you're a straight, I'm a real authentic
normal guy is what he's trying to say,
man. If I was normal, if I was normal,
say that. That's what you're trying to
say. No, it's not. You're saying if I
was normal, what would I like on a girl?
Shut the [ __ ] up. You know, I made Pride
Month, Chris, you know, I made an error.
I don't know. I think it just shows
where your like mindset is at. You're
insane. Tits are ass. Nick,
what's your answer, gay boy? I genuinely
find zero like like I I don't have any
sexual interest in women at all. H,
boring answer. Oh. Oh. So, what what's
your
Did you hear that? Yeah. Who's here?
Creek upstairs or something? What the
heck? Creek and like water starts
bursting through the pipes. Okay, buddy.
I hope not. The plumber came today.
Classic Creek joke. You wouldn't get it.
What are you talking about? Before we
get into it, should we talk about Love
Island? Holy smokes. Talking about
should we break up or not. This show is
getting crazy. It is. That's what
inspired the video is Nick's love for
Love Island right now. I'm not even
really like aggressive. Stayed on the
island. No, like he got his passport for
that. Dude, I'm like really heartbroken
for Jaylen leaving. Like Jaylen leaving
was just sad cuz he just like he looks
like such a kind guy. I really really
love him. Would you couple up with him?
Can you stop? I just don't understand
how someone's like family could watch
it. Like if I was like imagine if you
went on Love Island, I I'm not watching
that season. I can't. Well, I'm not
going on that show. Yeah, but it's okay.
Whatever. If I was normal, I might. But
chill out, Nick. You're so hot. I'm
kidding. Anyways, let's get into some of
these responses. Way too I can't film.
It's not hot. It's I'm sweating. Get an
ice pack and fill your boots. Like, I'm
sweating. I don't know what to tell you.
I saw someone post a [ __ ] idiotic Tik
Tok the other day. Putting ice in your
belly button helps cool you down while
you tan. I'm like, no [ __ ] [ __ ]
You're putting a frozen ice cubes on
your body. It'll cool you down. It's
like, do we need TikTok to tell us this?
All right, let's go. Let me get my
laptop. Let me get my laptop. Someone
said, "We've been together for almost a
year and he has been living with me in
my house during our entire relationship.
My boyfriend went to a party where his
ex was invited over and he knew she
would be there. I wasn't invited because
his friend was the one hosting it and
his friend's girlfriend, my ex best
friend, wouldn't like me there. They
spent two hours talking, my boyfriend
and his ex, all while I was trying to
call him because I'm balling my eyes out
at home alone having a hard night.
And now his ex is ex invited him over to
her apartment, said that she preferred
that I wasn't there. And when I asked
him if he couldn't go or if he could
bring me, he left my house, shut his
location off, and went.
That is not your man's. Yeah, that's not
your man. That's not a good situation
for you. If I If I had a girlfriend and
she wasn't allowed at a party I was
going to, I'd be like I would not go.
I'm not going to. Yeah, I'm not going to
go. Wow, that's amazing. That's good.
That's good points for you guys. I feel
like that's I'm not saying anything for
points. No, I think that that's No, but
that's serious. Like, why would I go
somewhere where like the person I should
care about most is unwanted? Oh my
goodness. Like, is that not is that like
I get it. I get it. That's like if I was
going somewhere and they're like, "No,
like your brothers can't come." I'd be
I'd equally be like, "All right, well
then guess who's not." See you. Now,
when you get into a relationship, are
you going to like me more than this
person?
I think I'll like you in a different
way.
Really?
I think he meant the other way around.
No, I'm excited. What do you mean? Um,
please help.
So, the person I shouldn't have done.
So, I've been dating this guy for almost
a year. At first, it was great. He was
funny, charming, and always made time
for me. But now, it feels like I'm
constantly walking on eggshells. Uhoh.
Anytime I try to talk about something
that bothers me, he says I'm too
sensitive or overreacting.
Damn. Yikes. I've cried in front of him
about Oh, I'm getting texts.
I've cried. I've cried. Okay. I've cried
in front of him about it more than once
and he just kind of rolls his eyes or
gets annoyed.
I'm like really scared. We don't really
go on dates anymore unless I plan them.
And I feel like I'm the only one trying
to keep this relationship fun or
meaningful. But every time I think about
breaking up, I get scared that I'm
giving up on someone who just has a
different way of expressing love. Am I
being dramatic? You're not. I I just
don't think that there is any love
there. It doesn't sound like It sounds
like It sounds like the I think that the
issue is you took our prompt of should
we break up or not to vent about your
problems, which is completely valid, but
I think I'm missing the remotely
positive thing about this man. Can you
tell me like give me give me some stats.
Is he like is he at least hot? Is he
like like tell me anything about this
guy? Because right now this guy sounds
completely useless. Correct. Should I
break up or not? Yeah. You're telling me
he's a you guys met and had like a
magical moment and like fell in love.
This magic moment and then my boyfriend
ghosts me and only talks to me whenever
I post something. He replies to my
stories. He's active and yet still never
talks to me. Should I leave him or talk
it out with him? I love you guys. By the
way, that's not a boyfriend, bro. I
about to say it doesn't sound like you
have the ball in your court to be making
any decisions to be honest. Someone that
only a boyfriend ghosting you is not
your boyfriend. Yeah. Yeah.
Is straight. Should I talk to him? Yeah.
He listens. It sounds like he ain't
there.
Is that [ __ ] up? No, I mean I agree
with you. Yeah. No, I mean if if you get
a hold of him
I got to stop. It's true though. How can
you say like should I talk it through
with him? I don't think he wants to
talk. It's awful. Oh, my leg's numb.
What? Oh my god, my leg's completely
numb.
They always got girls somehow making out
on that show. Can we get two of the guys
to be making out with each other? Has
that happened? Yes. How do we end up
with two girls always making out on Love
Island? Let's see big men kiss each
other.
That's Am I crazy? No, you're just gay.
I'm not. I'll tell you one thing, I'm
not normal. Stop.
I wish I wasn't gay for the sole purpose
of having like a bombshell walk out to
on Love Island. Like, you have to be
good looking for those.
Maybe one day, champ. I I couldn't be
one either.
Well, not because you're not
good-looking, but because you're a
[ __ ]
That did not. The plate is full, boy.
The plate is full. Get out of here. And
you're a [ __ ] loser, too. Okay. Do
you want to hear the saddest news ever?
Saddest news ever? No. Never. I hate sad
news. Oh, I thought you was going to
jump. Something about Royal Kingdom. I'm
going to lose. I'm going to throw my mic
at his head. I think that we are the
last generation to witness fireflies in
real life.
I don't think I ever have to be honest.
Oh my god. Remember the golf course? I
like to make myself believe. Remember
the golf course? What about the golf
course that we were at that had
fireflies and when we went down the hill
at one time in the valley thing? So
they're gonzo. They are done. What
happened? What do you mean? Wait, what
do you mean? How do you I just all the
actual lights like street lights and
lampost and all the light pollution. No,
it's it's confusing them and they're
just like, "We don't need to glow
anymore.
Oh my god, I'm actually really upset."
And without mating, the lights go out.
No.
Seven. I've genuinely never been so
shook in my life. Yeah, they're fading
away. I'm shaken up.
They mate and they lost their [ __ ]
magic. They flirt with like lights, but
they can't. They don't know how to light
anymore. Get them all Viagra.
Stupid joke. This is a bad joke for
sure. I try to make myself believe
it was. It's crazy to think that
technology is a baby. It's like a little
infant. That's what scares me about the
world. Technology is brand new and look
how much tech has taken over.
Absolutely. They don't like
shopping at like Black Friday. Never
will be the same. Get out there and dig
for the sales. Like it's like what?
We're waiting till Cyber Monday. Black
Friday comes. What? We're We're on our
phones. Go [ __ ] shop. Wait in line.
It's It's the digital. You don't know
[ __ ] about a Furby. Talking about Laboo.
Do you know who Furby is? No, for real.
You don't need a Lubu. You need a Furby
or a Beanie Baby and you need to grind
for it. You have to wake up and go to
the [ __ ] store. Dead ass, bro. The
internet is taking away the magic of
like life. I'm so happy I don't want a
Laboo. Me, too. If I wanted a [ __ ]
Laboo, I'd be pissed. Laboo is giving
silly bands. Like, we're we're done.
We're done. I just when I see this much
craze on the internet regarding an an
item, I'm like, I don't need that [ __ ]
Sometimes you need it. No, I do. I
agree. Yeah, but for if there was like a
viral pasta strainer, I'd buy it. Call
me crazy. I just feel like that's
something I'm always not doing right.
Like a there needs to be like a better
strainer.
Something that's getting the job more
done. This is like a very thing to be
upset about. Like we have a good
strainer.
been holding on to that all day and
trying to like find a way to navigate it
into our Don't get me wrong, we have a
good strainer, but I just don't think
it's the best. I get it. And that's why
when I see a little boo boo, I'm like,
it's not the best, but it's like
literally, Nick, it sounds like you got
dared by someone like backstage. 500
bucks if you bring up like strainers
tonight. Like, that's literally how it
how it feels you're talking about. I
can't with the little boooos, though.
It's like it's it's genuinely like I
hate to let [ __ ] like this affect me.
It's pissing me off. Like I couldn't
agree more. And it's like can we get a
more realistic strainer involved like
like you know that's not what I meant.
Like you know that's not what I meant.
No like I get it. It's like the Le Boooo
craze is just making me think like how
can I drain the water from my pasta?
You're not you're making a fool of me
right now. No, I'm I'm thinking more
like I've like seen some people like who
cook or cooking videos or been at
friends houses where they have like a
more functional strainer than I do.
Somebody once you get think all the
water's out. Do you like I don't know.
Am I someone you've seen cook? [ __ ] no.
[ __ ] no. I'm talking about
what happened to all the horny Matt
edits.
[Laughter]
I was think that was the craziest thing
you could have like casually said ever.
It's kind of true. What happened to all
the horny Nick edits? Like I want to see
more. Nick, you are ridiculous. That's
the thing though, too, is like we talk
we're talking about all this thing about
like living Matt, don't shut that off.
We're talking all these things about
like living in the wrong generation or
like being like happy with the year we
were born. Like the universe knew that I
needed to at some point be in a position
to consume edits of myself. Like edit
culture is like my favorite thing ever.
Like like these slow-mo like dips,
twists, little after effects [ __ ] Like
you guys go hard. No, it's legendary for
sure. Like seeing an edit of myself, I I
genuinely do feel like a level of
unstoppable. But I think I just don't
think I was ever supposed to feel as
cool as I do when I see like a good
myself. I think that the internet is a
beautiful place and it's obviously given
us like the platform we have today. But
I think that like let me give you an
example of times I think the internet
ruined a weekend getaway to like a cabin
with friends. There should be no
internet. There shouldn't be anything.
And then like I also think of like
school. Do you know how many kids are
like scared every day to go to school
because of like cyber bullies and being
like recorded? And this is no listen I
like let me actually speak here because
I'm so passionate about this [ __ ] It's
like it's so aggravating to me to
witness like the life get drained out of
like real life human beings because of
the internet. It's so [ __ ] up. Like
literally cyber bullying is like the
worst. I I'm not trying to sound like a
Disney Channel like don't cyber bully.
It's genuinely like there are people
there are people out there that are so
affected by the internet. And I think
that it's only it's only going to get
worse as like the the rise of Tik Tok
and the rise of girls growing up with
like [ __ ] this these examples on the
internet of girls that are supposed to
be like this perfect thing. And it's
it's so [ __ ] up. It's so so so [ __ ]
up. And social media is genuinely the
scariest thing that that that Carly
Granted we do it as a job so it sounds
hypocritical. We're sitting on our couch
at home with each other talking with the
microphones. I'm aware of how hip
hypocritical I sound and how crazy I
look, but
I'm aware of how hypocritical I sound
and how crazy I look. But it's true.
What is this? That's That's a VHS tape.
I'll do you one better. What is this?
What is this? If if I'm in an argument
with someone, right, or if someone's
like trying to like if someone is
speaking to me and they can't tell me
what this is, I'm not listening to you
anymore. And that's fine if you didn't
grow up with this, but learn about it.
I can't I can't talk to someone who
doesn't know what I'm like. I can't I
can't enter like a I can't enter like a
friendship with someone if like if I
gave you this and you were like, "What
is that? How do you use that? And it's
crazy too because like cyber bullying
even was different in like 2016, 2015
cuz it's like cyber bullying was like
people still had like public profiles
when they were cyber bullying or like
they were texting you from like their
thing. Whereas now cyber bullying is
Gollum troll number 44 with no profile
photo and like they might not even go to
your school. You might not even know
this person in real life. Imagine
getting cyberbullied by someone who's
never met you in real life. You think I
give a [ __ ] You think I give a [ __ ]
about you cyberbullying me? I I've never
seen you with my eyes. I've never seen
you with my two eyes. I've never seen
you with my two eyes. You're going to
cyber bully me? You're going to
cyberbully me? I've never seen you with
the eyes in my skull.
A hate comment from an account with a
profile photo of someone who does not
exist. I'm like, who are who are you
talking to? Genuinely, this isn't Nick
saying this to a direct person. It's
saying it I'm talking like a girl that
is sitting at home. I'm talking to a
girl someone who's sitting at home and
scrolling and they feel like really
upset about a comment 330 said and it's
like who are you? Who genuinely you're a
gray person like this? That's their
profile. That's the profile photo.
That's genuinely and that's not even
this. I'm not speaking on behalf of me.
Like I don't care about hate comments.
I'm speaking on behalf of a girl that's
at home that's 14 years old that's upset
because someone commented on a post
something negative about her. We I feel
a little crazy that we posted a Google
form and asked people their thoughts and
fully got we gave them a little bit of a
Are you one is he What is he does he is
he doing what I think he's doing? You
stop. Yo, Chris. Yo, it's so out of
hand. So bad. Like this isn't even a bit
anymore. No, it's not. It's out of hand.
Um, I feel bad that we asked you guys
for responses cuz like honest to God, we
haven't read them. No, we haven't. Guys,
so today I wanted a chocolate chip
muffin from Dunkin' Donuts. And I go to
Door Dash it and it only says coffee
cake and blueberry. Nick goes, "Get a
fourack of blueberry muffins and I
promise you'll get a chocolate chip
muffin." So I did that. I I wanted a
blueberry muffin once and I ordered a
blueberry muffin and got a chocolate
chip one. So, I did that and we got
three blueberry muffins and one
chocolate chip. I knew I knew they'd
[ __ ] it up. But it's like, imagine Matt
wanted a chocolate chip muffin. I told
him to order the wrong thing to get what
he wants. It blew my mind a little bit.
And it worked. It did work. Why are we
all wearing green? Matt in particular is
wearing like Wall-E the green giant.
Let's call the police and ask them.
Let's ask the green green patrol. What
would you do if like a green person
walked in and was like, "Ah, it's all
right." Like an actual green patrol
showed up.
I don't know how to answer that. What is
that? Blueberry. Blueberry muffin. Can I
have some? Of course. Just falling into
my What's your favorite part of the
muffin? The top or the bottom? Top.
You're a top guy.
I wouldn't say all that. You're not a
top guy.
What are you asking me? I'm asking you
if you like the top of a muffin.
Not my fault where your head goes. Like
you're just always you're just always in
the gutter with the questions me and
Chris are asking. You asked if I'm a top
guy. Yeah. After clearly talking about a
muffin. No. Fenway. Legendary stadium.
So proud to be a part of it. How many
Fenway Franks do you think you've had in
your life? Not enough. Do you know who
Matt literally kind of looks like? Don't
say this. The hashing slasher. Like when
he gets to the front and they realize
he's like a dork instead of a scary guy
and he's like with the spatula. Like he
reminds me of Matt.
Cool. Double microphone.
I'm now realizing scared the [ __ ] out of
me. Take a chunk out of your knee. I
should have eaten the muffin before we
filmed. Dude, I really missed the
Cumberland Farms Chug Jug thoughts.
Dude, they had the chug jug before
Fortnite. I know. I was with my
boyfriend at his house and I wanted to
go buy myself some cinnamon rolls. I was
also on my period and I was really
hungry. I told my boyfriend this and he
just said, "Don't you think you need to
ease up on the sweets lately?" Oh no.
Someone said that to me, I would
literally pile drive my fist into their
face. Matt literally said that to me
yesterday. Well, you're his brother.
Well, I did not. Yes, you did. You're
his brother. You guys aren't like
romantically charged toward one another.
I hated that. Unless Are you? No, we're
not charged up at all. Okay, tell me if
I'm being dramatic. My boyfriend says he
loves me, but he never texts back unless
I double text. He always says he's too
busy to hang out, but somehow he's
posting from rooftop bars three nights a
week with last weekend he borrowed my
car, said he needed to run errands, and
I tracked the location. Tell me why his
car was parked outside his ex's
apartment for 3 hours. When I confronted
him, he said, "Babe, you seriously need
to trust me more." Like, am I crazy or
is this actually insane? I don't know. I
love him, but I also want to kind of
throw his Xbox off the balcony.
Thoughts? I don't think you have to
throw this man doesn't like you. Like,
this is what blows my mind when people
like are like like you're telling if you
if somebody gave you that sentence,
you'd be like, "Girl, leave the
relationship." Like, there's not one
positive attribute it sounds like this
man has. Yeah. What? Yo, I saw a Tik Tok
the other day and it was about it was
this girl saying that her exboyfriend's
mom had her son like flexing shirtless
as her background on her phone,
dude. That is awful. That is terrible.
That really scares me. Yeah, that really
really like I know that like like that
makes me feel such a level of discomfort
that I can't even portray or explain.
Yeah. Can I have a photo of you flexing
for my wallpaper? It's been over a year
and I honestly feel more drained now
than I ever have in my entire life. Yo,
the thing is when it's good, it feels
really good. Like euphoric. We laugh, we
click, the chemistry is off the charts,
but those moments are getting shorter
and farther apart. He constantly makes
me feel like I'm the problem. I'll bring
up how he made me feel and the time he
ignored me all night at a party and
flirted with someone else. And somehow
it turns me into being too sensitive or
overreacting. Every single argument ends
with me apologizing even when I know
deep down I didn't do anything wrong. He
keeps score like emotionally. If I mess
up even slightly, he brings it up for
weeks. But when he crosses a line and
like calling me names or gaslighting me
or even straight up disappearing for a
day, it's always you're being dramatic
or I just need space. And if I push that
sounds a lot like Nick me. Yeah. What?
Yeah.
Read it again. Read it from the top.
What? Read it. Read it from the
beginning. What? Read it from the
beginning. I wasn't getting Nick vibes
at all. Read it from the beginning.
What? Go ahead and read it. What is
wrong with you? Like what is actually
wrong? Read it from the beginning. No,
it's I've already read three passages.
Read it from like the middle. Then I'll
tell you when it's like just like
disappears for emotionally. It even if I
mess up slightly, he brings it up for
weeks. But when he crosses a line like
calling me names or gaslighting me or
even straight up disappearing for a day,
it's always you're being dramatic or I
just need space. He kind of just like
me. And if I push back too hard, he
suddenly gets cold or distant, like
punishing me with his silence until I
cave. Oh, wow. This girl, you are like
ripping me right now. Yeah, you're If
you guys could create a dating app based
off of any theme, what would it be? Like
like the qualifications like you know
like Christian Mingle. I would probably
do like level 300 plus on Royal Kingdom
only.
What level are you? Um I don't know. I
have to beat this one first to check.
All right. Out of the three of us, who's
most likely to fall in love after one
conversation? Don't ask weird I don't
like weird questions like this. You. Me?
Clearly. Yeah. 100% you. Actually, you
want me to bring up?
Oh my god. Turned around. I always
forget when people say like my dog like
they could be talking about their
friend. Like I was talking to someone
the other day and they're like, "Oh, my
dog." And I was like, "Oh, like show me
a picture." And then they showed me a
photo of them with their friend. No way.
Like I thought you were talking about a
creature. Are you actually serious?
That's insane. They're like, "Oh, my dog
and I." And I was like, "Oh, like let me
see your dog." Like like I said it like
cutely like, "Oh, let me see your dog."
And they were like, "Okay." And then
showing a photo of them with their
friend. No, that's really bizarre.
That's funny cuz like if you're talking
to a person that's like it's like my
dog. Like you say it like differently.
Like it's like oh my dog. Like that's an
actual that's a dog. Ask for a photo of
this person's friend. Like that's weird.
Yeah. That is weird. And I didn't know.
No, it's weird on their half that they
didn't put those pieces together. Yeah.
What's the most disgusting experience
you've had like witnessing PDA? No.
Stop. Last night. Really? Last night me
and Matt were at a burger place and we
were sitting so good.
We're sitting at a burger place. How did
I just uncover this? Sitting at a burger
place last night and well, first I said
to Chris, we got one burger and cut it
in half. I said, "Do you think people
think twins are gay couple right now?
Cuz this is crazy." Yeah. We were like
with people would think we're a gay
couple. I'm like we love We were like
sharing fries and like like splitting a
cheeseburger. No, we were just eating
lunch but or dinner. This couple came
over and they're like leaning against
like a brick wall and they were like
talking to each other. I've I've never
seen people talk so close like f like my
where this mic is is where the girl was
and he was like talking to her like this
like like to the point where like if
they looked at each other in the eyes I
know it was like blurry like I know it
was like crosseyed like that's how close
they you know what I like you know like
look at your mic right now it's kind of
like it's hard to see it cuz of how
[ __ ] close it is to your face that's
how close they were like talking and
then they just like started making
making up. It was like 10 minutes before
that in the same area where they were
like kissing on this bench, there was
this dude and I don't know if he was
like hurt or like what happened, but he
went
and me and Chris were talking about how
we thought there was like a pirate
nearby. So, it literally it was so
perfect of sounding like a pirate. We
both went, "Is there a pirate?" Like at
the same time we asked for people don't
use their free will like I want to go
out and just make pirate noises. No. So
then they started they started kissing
in the same area and I and I said to
Chris I was like I feel like we should
tell them to get a room before the
pirate comes over. It was crazy. It was
really funny. They were like making out
with each other. It was most likely the
three of us to get matching tattoos with
someone they just met. You obviously
that is true. All right. Thank you guys
so much for watching this week's video.
Hit that subscribe button so that you
can subscribe to us because you should
want to subscribe to us if you made it
to this point in the video and that so
that you never miss a video and so that
we have more subscribers and then so
that you get to just watch our videos
and enjoy our videos. That subscribing
would then be the goal. Smash that
subscribe button if you want to sub. If
you want to like I think you should like
I I would Can you stop? Smash or pass
the subscribe button. Smash. Pass.
Say smash. No.
All right everyone. See you guys next
Friday 5:30. We appreciate you all.
Later. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
[Music]