Hello, my name is Roy. I founded this
company called Cluey and I just got
kicked out of Columbia for uh building
this tool called interview coder. It's
like a cheating tool for software
engineering technical interviews. I use
the technology to build a much bigger
company, the desktop app that lets you
cheat on everything. Right now, we just
launched about a month ago, closing in
on $5 million in annually recurring
revenue. And we also just closed a $5.3
million seed round led by Abstract
Ventures and SUSA Ventures.
I I was a pretty I was pretty wild kid.
I got in a lot of trouble. I was pretty
smart. I think I was pretty good at
math. I did a bit of math competition
when I was younger. I was on like the
debate team. I played some cello. I love
girls, you know. I every year I had a
new girlfriend. Yeah. My mom made me do
a lot of studying, but I hated studying.
I was always trying to go out and like
like like like like have fun, play with
my friends. I've always been very
competitive when I was a kid. I had a I
have an older brother who was 2 years
older than me. I always wanted to be
like smarter than him. I always wanted
to do better in great at school than
him. I I'm always trying to win. I'm
trying to be chongu at everything, you
know, like top of the class. In the
world of software engineering, if you
want to get a job at a big tech company,
you have to answer these sort of
riddlelesque questions that are called
code questions. And pretty much every
developer you know at a big company has
gone through the gauntlet of memorizing
600 300 riddles and just sort of like
memorizing the solutions and
regurgitating them in interviews. I'm
very very competitive. So, the second I
knew that there was like a a ranking on
League Code, like a global ranking, I
knew I had to be like one of the best.
So, I uh I spent hundreds of hours
studying Grinding the Riddles, even
though I like I don't care about League
Code. I didn't enjoy it. I didn't really
have a good time, but I was just
competitive. So, I thought like there's
a ranking, then I got to be on the top
of the ranking. But, I mean, it just
ended up with me wasting a bunch of
hours. Le code just has nothing to do
with what you do on the job. It's like
the modern-day equivalent of asking how
many balloons fit in the Empire State
Building. It's supposed to test your
critical thinking, but the questions are
online to the extent that rather than
practicing critical thinking, you just
practice memorizing the riddles. You're
going to sit through and memorize all
the 10,000 questions cuz it means you
get a 200k a year job. This is not good
for anybody. You don't you don't learn
anything from practicing these riddles
and you just end up wasting time when
you should be programming. I thought
this was pretty stupid and this has been
going on for around 20 years. Right now,
the technology was there to sort of
develop this tool that would invisibly
let you use AI to cheat on these
interviews. So, I built the tool. I
publicly recorded myself using it on the
Amazon interview. I got the job and I I
posted this everywhere saying, "Look how
easy it is to hack these interviews."
Eventually, this this this got me in
some trouble. But, uh, the impetus of
everything was when I decided that it's
just a stupid industry practice and I
wanted to change
it. A lot of people think it was
explosive from the start, but it it took
about a month before it really started
to take off. And for a month I posted
everything Amazon saw was getting mad at
me and Colombia saw and was getting mad
at me and everyone was just upset and it
didn't really go that viral for about a
month. And during that time I was really
stressed. I just gave up my entire
career and my entire education for the
hope of a company. But it didn't even go
viral. Like I did all this for like
15,000 views. And I was really worried.
Everybody in my life including even my
co-founders were telling me like, "Hey,
we should probably stop. We should
probably shut this down." But I don't
know. There was just a voice in my head
that said like this is something this
has potential. Like I have to keep
going. And I did keep going. And then at
at one point it did go viral, like super
viral, and everybody on tech saw it. At
that point, I was safe. Virality
protected me from further punishment
from Colombia. It made the path to
entrepreneurship a lot easier and
clearer. I've sort of like committed my
life to building companies. Once I made
that decision, it was it was very easy
for me to decide to leave Colombia. And
once I did leave Colombia, like I knew
I'm going to do the only thing that I
can do now, which is build companies.
Uh, I think it also helps position me
like I I'm a I'm a very unique person
now who got kicked out of an Ivy League
and as a result there there's a lot of
interest from from Silicon Valley about
what I'm going to do next. To me at the
time it felt like things were moving
really slow. As soon as interview coder
went viral I knew that I had to
capitalize on the moment cuz the
attention wasn't going to be there for
long. The product was a product designed
to die. It's a product to cheat on
technical interviews. So the second
companies change technical interviews,
the product dies. meaning I have a few
short moments before uh my my spot in
the limelight dies and I thought I have
to raise around. I have to start a
bigger company that's more sustainable
and defensible longterm. So it for me it
felt like things were moving so slow. I
had to push back my fund raise like 2
weeks. I was going to fund raise 2 weeks
earlier than I did. To me at the time I
felt like I was in such a time crunch
and I and I had I had to uh I had to
wrap things up and and do the next thing
and it felt like things were moving
super slow. But uh I guess I I was under
the pressure of the situation.
Yeah, I mean we planned for me to use
interview coder to like cheat on a bunch
of big tech interviews and and get the
jobs and we thought that was going to be
a viral moment. So in that sense we
planned it, but the last 3 months I've
made probably like maybe like a thousand
tweets and since then like I figured out
how to make tweets that will go viral,
how to make tweets that will be more
controversial and and and get more
engagement. I think for X especially,
well I've only really cracked X. Uh I
think because I think people on Twitter
are a very unique type of people. Um,
they love controversy, they love drama,
they love attention, and they love to
either dog on people or watch people get
dogged on. I think every single time you
tweet something, if you don't think half
the people in the world would feel very
negative about this, then it's probably
not going to be viral as a tweet. All of
your tweets that will are you're
planning on making go viral, they need
to have a very strong controversial
twist that makes people pause and be
like, "What the fuck?" And this is not
the case for Instagram, Tik Tok, or
LinkedIn or whatever, but it is the case
for Twitter. And yeah, I think I think
Twitter Next, the more controversial
you're willing to make your tweet, the
better and the more viral you will go.
Interview coder on Twitter was received
so positively. It was just like this
scrappy young kid who was trying to
fight back against big industry, big
tech. And uh everyone on Twitter was
very supportive. I think as I got bigger
and my account grew, people grew less
supportive, which is like to be
expected. I'm generally very good at
receiving hate and criticism. I' I'm a
very polarizing personality and I do a
lot of crazy stuff. Throughout my life,
I've always had people like giving me
hate. None of the negative comments
really stood out, but I was very
surprised to see how positively
Interview Coder was received on Twitter
when I first launched it. I think people
are often so worried that they're going
to say something bad online and it's
just going to get back to them and their
their their reputation is over. And I
don't know, like it's it's going to bury
them. But I think in reality, all press
is good press. I say a ton of super
controversial stuff. And in every video
I'm in, there's like a bunch of comments
saying, "Oh, this guy's evil. This guy's
like like this, this, and that." And
there's always some hate, but it's like
like this stuff really doesn't matter.
Yeah. I mean, like I I've learned that
it really doesn't matter if if if
everybody in the world just doesn't like
you. Well, actually, it's it's done
pretty much the opposite. I've realized
that even if I say extremely crazy
online, it will just make people more
interested in me and the company, and
it'll just drive more downloads and
conversions and get more eyeballs onto
Clue. If anything, I've learned that I
need to become crazier online so that
people will keep funneling attention
towards the core product. I think uh
there's it's very very rare that you
will say something online that
translates to something negative
happening in the real world. Like online
is not real life. I'm a pretty chill
person in real life, but online I'm
crazy because uh it gets it gets me
engagement and attention. When you are
so polarizing and controversial online,
you need to very clearly distinguish
this is my real world life and this is
the online life. And in my real world
life, there are very few people who I I
trust fully and who I think I love and
love me. My parents will always be on my
side no matter what crazy I do
online. And my wife and kids, they will
always be on my side no matter what
crazy I do online. And I think it
is very very important to distinguish
this is my real life uh family and
friends and they love me unconditionally
and I love them and everything online is
just noise. Even if everyone online or
everyone outside this box hates me, it
doesn't matter because uh the most
important people are in this box and
they're people that I love and love me
back. Interview coder is a tool designed
to let you treat on technical
interviews. But what we realized as we
built interview coder is that the idea
of an AI that sees your screen and hears
your audio sort of shows itself as this
translucent screen overlay. This has
never really been attempted before. This
is a completely novel user experience
and it's very shortsighted to think that
this is only good for cheating.
Ultimately, what we're building is we're
building for a future where models are
multimodal and the models are not there
yet and they're probably not going to be
there yet for another 3 years. Nobody's
really thought of what happens when chat
bots are no longer relevant. What
happens when you don't want to prompt
GPT anymore and AI just knows what you
want? Then how will you interact with
AI? Nobody's really attempted this
before. And I think um interview coder
was the first proof of concept of a user
experience that could work in this
world. So we realized that and that's
that's that's what we're building
clearly off and clearly is the new way
you will use AI in um in 5 years
hopefully if we do things right then in
2 years. The phrase cheat on everything
is intentionally ambiguous like what is
cheat on like I know what cheat on test
means but I don't know what cheat on
everything means. It's left to be sort
of confusing and make you sit on it and
reflect for a moment. When you see
someone using AI for everything, it
makes you think this is unfair. They're
not supposed to be doing that. They're
cheating. In reality, like if you can
use this for everything, like what does
cheating on a meeting look like? It's
not really a thing. It's just our gut
human reaction to think this is so
different. This is such a big advantage
that it's unfair. And what we hope to do
is we hope to give everyone this
advantage. When every single person is
using AI to cheat on meetings, then it's
not that you're using you're cheating
anymore. You're just this is just how
humans will operate and think in the
future. I think when you can use AI, you
should use AI. If it helps you, then you
should use it. If if using a calculator
will help you, then you should use it.
If using spell check will help you, then
you will use it. Eventually, the spell
check will teach you how to spell the
right words cuz you'll get used to it so
much. Or you just won't need to know how
to spell anymore. You'll just need to
know what the word is. If you can use AI
to help, then you should. And if it can
already do the job, then you'll never
need to do the job in the future,
assuming AI is everywhere, which it will
be. All of technical interviews need to
change. Not just in software engineering
but everywhere in the world. If you get
asked a question and AI can answer the
question then you should probably get
that out of your interview. I think
interviews will be a lot more holistic
and I really question whether we even
need job interviews at all in the
future. If there is an AI that knows
everything about you, everything you're
good at. Why do you need a 1-hour
interview to assess anything other than
culture fit? I already know all the work
you've done or at least the AI already
knows the work you've done. It knows how
good it is. It knows what skills you're
good at. Um, and if there is a skill
match, then AI should just be able to
match you directly to the job, assuming
that we get along after like a 30-minute
conversation. I really don't know that
there is a need for interviews in
today's age. But, but right now, what we
use is uh it's really just a
conversation. Uh, we check if you're a
culture fit. We talk about past work
you've done and um that's pretty much
it. The whole point of Clo is to get
everybody used to or used to a life
where they use AI for everything. Once
everybody uses AI in every instance
possible, there's going to be a lot of
jobs that get replaced and there's going
to be a lot of people who are able to do
so much more than they previously were.
If every scientist decided one day, like
today, I'm going to start using AI as
much as possible. They will be 100 times
more productive. When scientists are 100
times more productive, we cure cancer 10
years earlier. We cure Alzheimer's 10
years earlier. Everyone lives to 400
years old, and we're on the next flight
to to Mars in like 2 years. the
rate of societal progression will just
expand and exponentiate significantly
once everyone gets gets along to the
fact that um we're all using AI now and
and and that's what clearly hopes to
achieve is to get everybody used to
we're all using AI
now. I think the the user experience I I
spent a lot of time making the user
experience very seamless. It's less of a
technical challenge I think and more of
a taste challenge. uh the the concept of
an a translucent screen overlay,
something that really has never been
attempted before and it's something that
that I tried and I think I only got to
it after like dozens of iterations of
different tools that would be a more
seamless use of AI in your life. Yeah, I
think that was the pro probably the
biggest technical challenge was just
figuring out like what exactly is the
best user experience for someone using
this tool. I mean I mean latency,
response speed and um accuracy are like
the the two biggest things. This is what
every model, every like open AAI is
working to improve latency and and
accuracy. There there's ways that we can
get to a much faster response. For
example, if we host models on our own
servers, uh this eliminates a lot of the
latency that comes from the the load
balancing and request uh request
handling that that is just inherent in
OpenAI servers. That's probably what we
will end up doing. There's ways that we
can cache the input and um sort of like
uh parameterize the input so that um
they you get the same condensed same
same information but just condensed in a
smaller way and the smaller the input
size the faster the time to first token.
Also generally accuracy can be improved
by specific system prompts. We're
developing custom evals in house uh
based on a lot of the analytics and
usage that we're seeing and like
everything is getting better like every
single day the model of the clue gets
more accurate and faster. At a certain
point, we're going to know uh exactly
what type of responses you prefer as an
individual. Um what sort of
conversations that you're in and we can
use all that data to generate a very
very hyperspecific personalized
fine-tuned model for you that knows that
hey I'm a media reporter. I conduct
these sorts of interviews and I
generally want these types of responses.
The tonality of my emails is this. So I
would like you to respond in this way.
And we can just get the most
personalized model in the world. And um
once we have that data as like a a moat
defending us from the other big tech
companies, then we'll pretty much be
unstoppable. More so than the data, I
think the the user experience is just
interesting, untapped, and novel. Uh if
we're correct about this, then we'll be
the first to market. And there's a huge
first mover advantage when you're when
you're trying a new form of UX. And as
if we can capture the market quickly
enough by going viral enough
sufficiently, then uh I think there will
be it will be very hard to compete with
us.
the entire way we're going to think will
be changed. Every single one of my
thoughts is formulated by the
information I have uh at this moment.
But what happens when that information I
have isn't just what's in my brain, but
it's everything that humanity has ever
collected and put online ever. What
happens when AI literally helps me think
in real time? The entire way that humans
will interact with each other, with the
world, all of our thoughts will be
changed. like like what what happens
when I know about every single post
you've made online ever and I I I use
that to distill down into like a like a
condensed blurb of everything about you
ever what does our interaction look like
then it's it's really hard to say but I
think this is a turning point for
humanity and it it will fundamentally
change the way that we think and the way
that we behave as humans well if you're
not building a company in AI right now
then you're probably not doing the right
thing just enables you to build such
cool stuff and it's such a new
technology that even If you're 19 and
you've been playing with it for 2
months, you are one of the the brightest
minds. You are one of the pioneers of
the field. It's not like biology where
if you haven't studied for 10, 20 years,
then you don't then you're not an expert
in biology. You can study AI for 2
months and you'll be an expert in AI.
This technology is so gigantic and it's
so new that you can be really really
young and you can you can know it more
deeply than anyone else and you you'll
have the opportunity to build like a
billion10 billion company out of it. I
would say take bigger risks. This is the
only advice I have for anyone really.
You are smart enough, you're capable
enough, you're hardworking enough, just
take bigger risks. If you take bigger
risks and force yourself into positions
where you have to make it, you'll find
that you're a lot more hardworking than
you thought you were. And you'll also
find that life gets a lot more
interesting and very often the downside
of risk is much smaller than you think
and the upside of risk is much bigger
than you think. I wasn't really like
this 5 months ago. I mean, literally
like like half a year ago, I was
thinking I just want to get a job at a
big tech company. That's all I want to
do. And it wasn't until very recently
that I thought like, oh, I actually want
to build companies and go all in on
this. Taking risks initially, it means
being willing to uh get rid of the
constructs and limiting beliefs in your
mind that make you think, hey, when I
graduate, I have to be an engineer,
lawyer, a doctor, or whatever. Just
being willing to see what would happen
if you didn't do it. Every risk starts
very small. Right now, I think people
look at me and think I'm a crazy risk
taker. But it didn't start like this.
Started with me taking smaller risks.
Like the first risk I took was, hey,
what if I what if I built this tool and
told nobody about it? Then the next risk
I took was what if I posted online but
made it free and didn't really associate
with it so that people more people would
see it. And eventually the risk just
snowballed and snowballed until now I'm
like fully posting whatever confidential
document Columbia gives me because like
I don't care like the risk is not it's
not that much of a risk anymore and I've
grown used to it. So grow used to taking
bigger
risks. I feel like my life is very easy.
My life has been very easy. I mean my
mom I've got loving parents. my mom, she
made me study. Uh even when I didn't
want to, she would just say, "Well, you
should go study." So, I studied and and
as a result, I did well in school and I
hung out with smart kids and uh they
they helped me do better in life. Like,
I have two amazing great parents and I
come from a great family. I don't really
feel like my life has been all that
challenging. Getting kicked out of
Colombia, it's not that challenging when
you're out there building companies and
I was going to drop out anyways. Getting
rescended from Harvard is also not that
challenging when you have a loving
family at home. There's kids like out
there who are starving in like Uganda
and like my life is not that hard
really. A lot of everything that you
should think is you should just try and
think more positively about life and be
more optimistic about things. It's very
rare that you're going to be in America.
You're going to have the opportunity to
go to college and you're really in like
an actually challenging situation. In
reality, we're in the most interesting
time in history. If you live in America
and you're not like in poverty and your
parents aren't crackheads, you have the
the opportunity to make billions of
dollars and and make generational wealth
and do the most interesting thing ever.
There's very few challenging situations
that are so challenging that you're just
like limited. Right now, anybody can do
anything and you should just try and
take risks and be bold because uh you're
very privileged right now to be living
in this
world. Success is having a wife, having
12 kids, and having people remember me.
I think Steve Jobs and Elon Musk are
very cool in that everyone has a strong
opinion about them. Whether it's good or
bad, everyone has something to say about
Elon Musk and I think that's really
cool. We're all going to die eventually
and nobody's going to remember us in a
thousand years. I might as well be
remembered as strongly as possible for
for the time that I'm here. I think the
biggest thing is confidence. Like truly,
you hear all the time that um the people
that build big companies are not
geniuses. They're not smarter than you.
They're just um they take more risks
than you and they're hard work harder
workers than you. And I think this is
generally true. 5 months ago, I was just
some random student at some random
school and I didn't really have anything
going for me. And now I just raised $5
million and I'm in this giant office and
I'm building a company that I hope will
change the world one day. And very
little has changed about me except the
fact that I took a risk. Even moving
forward, if I do end up becoming like
the next trillionaire, like as as as big
as Mark Zuckerberg, there will be
nothing about me that changed. It'll
just be a series of well-calulated risks
that I took that will lead me there. And
I think the gap between Mark Zuckerberg
and your average human, it's it's really
not that big. And if you just have the
confidence to take bigger risks, then
very often you will win.