do you ever feel like mischievous that
Matt does know about a film no he has no
clue he definitely does know what about
let's prank him say something that it's
not okay what do you mean what you me we
know what we're filming but tell him a
completely different idea you have to
think okay yeah yeah yeah
um good yeah word all right guys today
we're going to rate vegetables and see
which one is most like Christmas
time we're not just ranking vegetables
Chris thought of it inside like it was
the best idea like what vegetable most
reminds you of like Christmas we're
going to go through a list of jez wait
really carrot one well don't move too
quick yeah we have to film this whole
video we're not filming a whole video on
vegetables I know you guys have a better
idea we that we were like cuz we were
thinking what you parrots is like
probably number one cuz it eats the
reindeer but we're like which ones else
reminds you of Christmas time and if we
take easy praner and you take it easy if
we ran out of um if you ran out of
vegetables we're going to switch to
fruit but we didn't want to we wanted to
try to I'm not I don't know why you're
joking around this I know you're joking
can I have a piece of that chocolate no
why cuz you're not telling me the truth
I feel like no one buys just a Hershey
bar it's always like Hershey with almond
or something can I have a piece of
chocolate let me have a piece come on
give us a piece we're lying can I have a
piece of chocolate come on Matt what's
the
topic come on Matt just give us
some please
okay thank you mhm all right carrot
number one what's number two broccoli
cuz it's like Christmas tree but smaller
hold on eat that chocolate and then
talk it ate you up and broccoli being a
small Christmas tree is
crazy I got it thank you Nick I didn't
like broccoli is just a mini little tree
so it's like oh it's a Christmas tree
like if ants were having Christmas I
feel like they'd want a broccoli to be
their
tree I feel like sweet potatoes cuz
that's that's like two for sure Nick you
look like Rudolph right now just cuz of
how bright you are like you would be the
and with your nose so bright won't you
guide
my jingle bell jingle bell jingle bell
rock two Christmas saell
to Nick no I just tring to rip it do
it this kid no Nick why you actually do
it Nick
don't how's it still glowing I ripped it
in half the safety yellow lenses as well
you look like the the Christmas
protector right now well you guys always
call me a big yellow Beast so I thought
today I would really just Zone that in I
love it why are these lights out maybe
cuz you ripped the necklace apart Nick
it's okay I have a backup oh my God all
right let's get into it today what we're
actually going to be doing is we're
going to be playing smash or pass with
Christmas characters
good video idea thank you yeah let's
start off strong really strong really
strong Santa Claus himself Santa himself
he's so strong he has to carry that big
sack around shimmy down that chimney
let's see like smash her pass Santa
Claus I need images like I need to see
what Santa Claus looks like come on Nick
no Santa's a pass for sure really for
sure he's yeah he's just too old he's
definitely like sweating delivering all
those presents like he's big and stinky
I know it like I like don't know where
to add like look this is Santa no yeah
no it's just like dude you're wearing
the same outfit every day I'm sorry
Santa pass yeah I agree pass I love you
though with my whole heart pass I agree
all right next we got two of the same
character but we have two different
versions We Got The Grinch okay live
action and we got the Grinch not live
action Grinch liveaction pass biggest
probably Smash in the Christmas movies
franchise and I think of iconic
Christmas smashes the Grinch is number
one you're tripping the Grinch is number
one How the Grinch is number one smash
he's a big Grump like smash he doesn't
even like Christmas smash you're insane
the Grinch smash no questions asked you
guys can disagree you don't understand
no he's a pass Grinch ad don't up there
for top three most iconic smashable
Christmas characters your Insanity ni
liveaction Grinch I he gets points
knocked off he's less fun oh animated
one yeah he's the OG smash no the OG
smash is liveaction Grinch oh so you
like Jim Carrey no I like the
Grinch okay I don't know what you're I
just think those big toes the big curly
feet he's all gross and green and big
and I love him his breath smells his
teeth are up I love the Grinch do
you see baby Grinch is so ugly as well
like a little kid when he's a little
baby he's ugly as no offense Frosty
the Snowman
smash smash his lights
out but he's more cute than he is like
smashable why just like his little
jacket have a jacket yes he does he does
not have Frosty the Snowman have a
jacket Nick Nick I don't know guys
Google it Google Google Google it Frosty
the Snowman has to have a jacket you're
like dead wrong I feel like Frosty the
Snowman has to have a jacket or I'm
losing my mind what world would
he have a jacket um snowman yeah
he has a jacket on noad
Chris he does not have a search up
Frosty stowman with jacket okay he looks
he's kind of valid like I kind of love
him I just like his little hat save that
photo wait save that photo good yes
smash Frosty easily I feel like Frosty's
a pck me though like he's I'm melting
the whole time like
help no cuz he needs help and I love him
no he is melting it's it's like a real
problem he has I haven't seen Frosty the
Snowman in actual years that's a red
flag though that you're melting the
whole time hold on correct get out but I
love hold on I can't even say this but
Matt get off your phone get off your
phone that was ugly Martha may
from hille from the Grinch oh smash
without a doubt oh wow Martha um she's
president's or the mayor's way better
than the first picture look Martha yeah
she looks good yeah okay Martha I
actually with Martha a lot I like
her hair Mara May is the most OG smash
she's a classic smash come on she's the
hottest who in hille no doubt about it
no doubt bro no doubt about it Sydney
Lou's dad is so ugly okay Sydney yeah
yeah not as big as fan yeah he's hideous
the male dude the mailman he's not the
mailman Cindy Lou's dad's the mailman
know they're bringing to the post
office at the beginning of the movie
he's just a family dad oh I want to know
who's so hot actually oh God Rudolph's
dad I was about to say that I know you
would like Rudolph's dad is so valid
honor oh oh wait that's his dad yes
donor is Rudolph's dad I did not know
that oh my god oh I looked up Don I got
photos of an instrument that's not an
instrument Rudolph's mom
is
back yeah he look oh my God the coach
the
coach Rudolph's dad is the most valid oh
my God oh my God he looks so good here
okay that's Rudolph's Mom oh yeah yeah
Rudolph's mom is OG smash yep oh my god
oh what's the name of that movie what's
the name of that movie what's the name
of that movie what about airbud
Christmas edition what's the airbud no
Rise of the Guardians wait wait wait
guys guys guys would you consider this
movie a Christmas movie yeah would you
consider this movie A Christmas yes of
course the Easter Bunny is so
hot in this movie what Easter Bunny is
he not like a little bunny rabbit no
he's not he's a big bunny
rabbit
oh my god oh yeah he does yeah I can see
it's like the fog Utopia Vibe guys I
don't get why we do fictional character
smash or pass like this is a weird topic
no it's not no it's not cuz I found
several smashes you just got to think a
little bit okay what about oh my god do
you guys see the new Christmas movie
with um um Hopper yes with um David
Harbor yes yes oh my God you love that
guy don't you yes bro I no he's not
doing it for me me in violent and he's
not doing it for me in violent night as
much as he is as hopper in stranger
things yeah okay speaking of stranger
things shout out Joy's buyers oh my god
oh I love wona Rider yeah she's the goat
speaking of would you consider the
characters in The Edward Scissor Hands
movie Christmas characters no it's not a
Christmas movie well some would argue it
is really well some would argue that are
Jack scullton holy oh my God he's ugly
as oh he's B my he tall he's like
bald and pale God he's so attractive
Nick you're losing your mind
dude oh my God he's so attractive it's
actually terrifying you're insane oh my
God oh my God my God insane oh Nick I
think you got lucky because this is
mostly male characters I know I'm having
the time of my life right now the yeti
yes I was going the yeti is kind of hot
for I was going to pull up both of them
oh the Abominable Snowman actually hot
see he's just like goofy like he's like
no like he's actually hot you're insane
you're insane he's just a goofball you
know this is hard to do cuz you guys
just don't get if you can make them
laugh and
giggle you can make that booty shake and
jiggle
what who said that it's just an Infamous
quote from who just the people who's the
people you're the people I'm not the
people guys Sally from The Nightmare
Before Christmas she's bad um yeah Matt
come on I don't like that dress but what
she's rocking I love the dress it's like
passwor vintage okay sure she put that
on for real shout out Sally guys
what would you do if I feel like there
has to be some what would you do if
Christmas just came to life and then
like do you know how f is Christmas how
can he come to life no I'm not talking
about like I'm talking about like do you
know in the movie pixels when all the
like video games come to life what if
all just like movie and Christmas
characters came to life it be hot and
heavy Nick come on you ass we're playing
smash or pass with the characters I'd be
flirting with every character that comes
here come on
hello oh speaking of speaking of
smash your pass out of here he says
hello what world come on dude how I grab
you guys know what the like the myth
like the mistletoe myth is the whole
mistletoe like thing is what if you get
caught under the mistletoe of someone
you have to kiss them oh yeah we knew
that I know all about that I just
thought like what's the origin of that
no I'm just Nick stop you weird
put this really affect you cuz
you're weird as a fake
missl toe come on I can't believe
neither of us have grabbed it yet I'm
it's like slipped right through my hand
every time o Nick what about Ebony's
your Scrooge pass what he's so hideous
it hurts he looks good
no no I know Nick Nick told me one day
he loves Eben screws I did not say I
liked Eben yes you have the
snower oh his name's the snower the
heater is way more attractive than wait
what is that from wait actually the
snower is kind of bad when was where is
this from they call me
Heatmiser do you remember that wait what
is this from snower washes the Heat
Miser easy I forget what that's from
Snow Miser is 10 times more attractive I
like his little hat guys what is that
from they call me heat m
the oh my God oh my God the train
conductor Polar Express you're Nick Nick
this is getting
too you're so smash you're so weird off
topic from a video but I feel like Matt
looks like the nerdy kid with the
glasses on the Polar
Express well I feel like Christmas is
just like the time of cheer We Made It
Dirty by doing this yeah but like it's
all good though if they don't want us to
play smash or pass with Christmas
characters why is every male Christmas
character hot as come
on riddle me a come on come on I I don't
know Nick I can't like Rudolph's dad
smash guys what about let's do Christmas
activities what about sledding smash
smash sledding sledding is I can't do
that mat it's just like yes or no yay or
nay yes or no I don't like sledding that
much you don't like sledding it's
dangerous danger you're a loser
I'm so mad I've never ski or snowboarded
in my life like I feel like I'm wasting
so much time Matt's the type to like
hang 10 you know what I mean oh my God
what oh my God another one oh my God oh
my God what dude oh my God I feel like
Master's the type to like hang loose on
the snowboard God no you're wrong how am
I wrong cuz I'm not going to hang loose
yes you would Matt that's more you be
like this you be like this hey that's
more surfing and I wouldn't do that oh
my
God who remembers Arthur Christmas I
love Arthur Christmas his
brother holy hold on let me see
this kid is searching bro
like oh my God okay dude hold on
look
wait
what that's crazy dude hold up on who is
making that notoriously hot obviously
something like that is popping up who is
making that hold on come
on you let him jingle your
bells oh man lots of just Mariah Carey
she doesn't count character I'm not
saying that I'm just saying that song's
like kind of
mid going to get hate I'll get ha agree
that that's a very mid Christmas song my
number one every year I don't want a l
for Christmas there is just one I need I
just I don't get is like no matter what
no matter how in love I am I still going
to care about the the Christmas I cannot
I I really can't like she saying she
doesn't care about the Christmas under
the tree cuz all she wants is you but
it's like come on bro if you got someone
specially then you should have presents
under the tree real we set ourselves up
for me to just go feral over Christmas
yeah like what are we doing minutes C
themed adults you're funny hold on
they're all hot though Nick come on like
it is crazy that almost every male
Christmas character is hot it's just so
funny to me cuz like we never make
videos like this and then when we do
it's about cartoon characters it's
hilarious I've never gotten like the
door wreaths like what's the
point of those I don't know dude collect
snow I might have to give Arthur
Christmas every you come on I seriously
might you're a sicko wait does he have
to like become Santa the whole time
right he wants to be like real bad he
wants to be Santa that's such a like oh
big task popular Christmas movies Edward
Scissor Hands pops up that's not a
Christmas movie it just snows no cuz it
is a Christmas movie doesn't count Nick
um the mother in The Grinch the animated
Grinch from
2018 ooh for sure yeah um for sure so
bad actually I don't write the rules I
don't write the rules but I do not Nick
I agree with you I don't write the rules
I just follow them correct what about
the two Robbers from home alone too Nick
they're both hideous you talking about I
was just asking I didn't say anything
what you talk yes you did I did not say
yes you did you weird what about the
lady who feeds the pigeons Matt Nick
what would you do if Arthur's Christmas
brother said hop on my
sleigh literally float onto the sleigh
yeah you're a sicko like literally like
levitate over you're a sicko I would
actually levitate over not yet what
about the Narwhal from Elf pass what
Matt Nick whatever the your name is
like what was that what was that dude
like how does he get a full back profile
of that was just weird dude who is Mr
poppy Nick what are you doing what is
wrong with you Steve Claus absolutely by
far Takes the Cake hottest Christmas
character number one who is it Arthur
Christmas's brother oh my God you sicko
Nick you're weird are you guys like
Notre can we agree on this the photo
Nick God of him was insane it popped up
all I had to do search for his character
I did not search anything else Matt what
are you doing I was just looking for the
character fully
closed that's all I was looking for what
come on I was Nick what's your favorite
Christmas activity
watching Arthur Christmas oh my God I'm
kidding I like frosting
cookies and eating cookies would you
like snowball fights I like getting
people's gifts that's a good one um I
like sledding I love sledding I just
want you for my own me singing to Steve
Claus Nick come
on more than you what's your favorite
Christmas movie favorite Christmas movie
is probably I haven't like I feel like I
haven't watched enough Christmas movies
Nick what are you doing um I've got to
say my favorite Christmas movie is
easily the Grinch yeah what did Tyler
the Creator R did the song I was me one
I'll watch it Grinch you really are a
you oh Nick you felt cool doing that as
a cactus as
a that was today's Christmas video smash
or pass with Christmas characters that
was an interesting one for sure let us
know if you agree with me down below or
if you think I'm a psychopath yeah um I
need to hear everyone's opinion on Steve
Claus Nick everyone's I hate him I think
he's ugly and gross wrong he's hideous
wrong Arthur's better looking wrong so
wrong but it's fine Santa himself is
better
looking wrong no the spaceship in that
one or what's it called the sleigh they
go crazy the slay is it
slaying did the Slay Slay
you were a sick of this video yeah
you're sorry this is
predominantly a male category no you
need to like yeah you need this is like
just caught 4K the whole time are you
guys serious you look like a school
bus dumb
Matt you look like the cutest
reindeer in the bunch right now so
adorable all right guys we'll see you
next Friday and Wednesday when the
Christmas aolo Christmas continues
thanks for watching this
week sorry about that whatever that
was and what you saying how you miss me
yeah you miss me and all the things that
we did we we going to travel from the
island to Madrid we had a lot of plans
but they
all why all because of someid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
saying nothing when I'm my
brothers