go
oh my God
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
busted the glass on us like I just said
don't do that no way yeah who the guy
the scary man yeah he said don't do it
he said what
what
not a nibble dude people don't believe
us now like when we film these videos
people don't with all due respect
because I am an avid customer I gotta
read y'all this McDonald's sign that was
just there when we went through the
drive through try our new cheesy
jalapenos already
cheesy I'm out anything cheesy from
McDonald's I'm good it sounds like a
heart attack in 20 years of cholesterol
I'm good
good I'm good
good try our new cheesy jalapeno bacon
quarter pounder with cheese so it's
cheesy and with cheese that's made me
laugh it's just like try our taste the
cheesy jalapeno bacon quarter powder
with cheese
like you you already addressed the
challenge that literally sounds like an
hour on the toilet and a lifetime of
regret like dude
we're playing smash or pass with
animated characters I love this [ __ ]
what like just good old videos you're
gonna have to bear with me because I'm
gonna have to see what people said to
smash or pass and I'm gonna have to
Google them so we can decide this yeah
so it's just gonna take you forever okay
not forever
literally a [ __ ] decade not forever
kid you look like a [ __ ] bacon cheesy
Quarter Pounder kid you smell like a
fart after a baking cheesy Quarter
Pounder like you're a [ __ ] take the
cheese threw you off the jalapenos threw
me off yeah jalapenos dude the first
time I ever threw up you say jalapeno
like you're gonna say jalapeno business
like you said would you say it like
that's what's gonna happen every time
you say it jalapeno how is the moon
yellow sometimes because the sun first
the Moon is a reflection of the sun no
it's not yes yeah it is the moon has no
light the Moon is no light it's just a
big mirror okay first smash or Moonlight
is
I'm gonna [ __ ] just throw a Haymaker
one day and knock your ass out and then
you're gonna be [ __ ] limp in the back
seat we're gonna have to drive to the
emergency room because you're gonna be
dead first smash [ __ ] both you guys
pause pause down pause down both of you
Betty boot like that's the OG smash the
OG smash is crazy yes bro like I know OG
OG OG people that one's too easy like
all the old heads like love her that's
what someone said too I didn't even like
look it up I love Betty Boop bruh
she's lit I like her little leg man me
too
her what the little like leg thing she
got
I like her dog
Casper
that's crazy Casper got too big of a
head for me like homie's gonna walk
around that head looks like it's
carrying so much dead Casper got a lot
on his mind bro you gotta figure out how
to haunt some people yeah he got [ __ ]
he's trying to I don't really like the
concept of like a Friendly Ghost like
yeah bored of this yeah I haven't seen
Casper in I really want to watch it
actually me too until he becomes a boy
like Casper becomes a boy no in the show
yeah like Casper becomes a human
can I want to see Casper I think his
head's so big because he's trying to
think of where that fifth finger went
bro walking around here with four
fingers on each end that's actually so
creative that you just came up with that
that quickly props to you like laugh
instead is some Cornish weird [ __ ] I
don't want to say something but I'm not
gonna say it Matt no go man I can't say
it can I whisper it to you then yeah
okay
[Laughter]
say that
you're so weird you're so you're so
strange
not even that bad he said Casper looks
like a sperm cell he does he does
Smurfette pass bro you have to smash
he's the only Smurf like there's no
other Smurf options I'm putting myself
in the Smurf camera like I'm not gonna
like as me but if I was like if you're
clumsy you're falling into that wow
sorry
sorry sorry too much too much too much
too much we're just gonna move on too
much okay
Lola Bunny is the OG smash like with
Betty
how many OG smashes you got like that's
crazy
like a ton like if it's old it's an OG
Smith Danny Phantom no
that was too quick his hair is too
pointy bruh I like his hair I think it's
ugly Danny Phantom's a cutie patootie
bro and he looks like lanky and Tall
yeah you got a big ass hand too bro he
said
Popeye the Sailor yeah I love Popeye am
I putting myself yeah but he looks
Heavenly that is true bruh dilf
[Music]
what's his wife's name olive oil olive
oil she bad dude let me pull her off
okay olive oil from Papa bro she also oh
what about Judy Jetson
um she bad
I don't like her hair bro I love her
hair bro very stylish and unique I like
her y'all gonna call me crazy for this
one what because this is an ultimate
Smash but no one's gonna hear me out the
Grinch
okay bro he got that beer belly I know
Grinch like he's he's like he's got a
gut on him yeah he'd be drinking
I think the Grinch an alcoholic the
Grinch is so bad actually like in the
live action Jim Carrey yeah
you're weird as [ __ ] dude
you know I have no idea you know what
he's talking you better go to the camera
like that okay I think so
I'm a psycho
[Applause]
hmm
that's insane holy [ __ ] that's right
you've never seen that Nick Wilde yeah
go hook crazy neck go ahead
what
talk or talk for a second I have nothing
to say bro you just made it like so
weird no it's funny no because you've
talked about Nick Wilde off camera
before you have I will I'll say it
that's unreal like yeah you recalled me
really preaching my love for Nick Wilde
off camera no but Judy Hopps is bad
it must take people to make animated
characters it must take them so long ew
bro she's nasty
that's mean bro I feel like animated
characters like to create your own is so
such such talent I don't think so to be
the artist of an animated character I
think like coming up with a concept of
one is like no bro like coming up with
like an animated television
ew bro sure I got big ears
I love Shrek's is like Shrek the first
ogre like what was an ogre before Shrek
let's look it up ogre Nick you're an
ogre you're an idiot you remind me of an
oath these are ogres ew oh wow so they
really like dull down Shrek when they
made an ogre
that's actually crazy we should do
um top three animated TV shows
I'm down
Simpsons goaded SpongeBob goated
SpongeBob's good there's so many what
are your favorite moments from SpongeBob
actually biggest red flag in a human
being is if they're wow he's flying
people that don't [ __ ] with SpongeBob no
biggest red flags is people whose
parents wouldn't let them watch
SpongeBob like you're weird what was in
SpongeBob grow the [ __ ] up dude like any
animated [ __ ] like you're dude your
kid's gonna watch it my kid at least
there's there's nothing in SpongeBob
that like harmed me I get like animated
[ __ ] that's totally targeted toward
adults like Simpsons and Family Guy but
my kid can watch whatever the [ __ ] he
wants I don't care well it's just
SpongeBob what's in SpongeBob that's a
negative thing bro what's that Adam
Sandler movie that says douchebag
no it's a different one but I went into
school one day after watching that movie
and I called someone a douchebag cause I
didn't know what it meant and like well
I don't know what I think it's a crazy
concept I flipped off our kindergarten
teacher why
um two kids that we used to at school
that were we're not friends with anymore
used to like it was Kindergarten
and I didn't know what I want a piece of
ice Matt relax I didn't know what it
meant and they were like never stick up
your middle finger alone so I thought
that I'd like explode if I did it so I
put I was sitting crisscross applesauce
like this in kindergarten and I put my
hand like on like in my lap like this
and I did the middle finger at the
ground and I was like okay I'm safe like
it can't be that bad of a thing and they
were like we never do it like it's a bad
thing I'm like okay like it can't be
that bad and then I said
the do it to
um Miss so and so like it's if you if
you're like so brave and so I thought I
was cool so I was a teacher I went like
this
is happening to her face and they're
like why'd you she yelled at me and of
course I was like I don't know what this
means yeah
they were mean like for setting me I
think it's crazy you can tell a kid
anything and they'll believe it
speaking of I saw Tick Tock and this
lady was at like a train station with
her kids and she she told her kids I
don't know if they'd like never been to
a train station or if they're like in a
different like country yeah she told
them that the train never stops and like
to get ready when it comes they have to
like jump jump on that's [ __ ] up dude
is crying freaking out I saw a tick tock
of a New York Subway dude saying that he
saw a pigeon get on one the on the train
at one stop and get off the other one
like not real Bros are so scary pigeons
are
what pigeons are really scary I don't
like that group of people walking
through this parking lot
okay I'm about to go home and do their
calculus project we're fine
damn get [ __ ]
um what about Gaston
what nothing just thinking about him
who what what'd you say what are you
guys talking about
okay I think let's play a game of
witch's character reminds you of the
other one the most Nick's [ __ ]
Patrick Star bro I was gonna say Lumiere
from Beauty and the Beast he's gonna
love that I do like that yeah a little
candle let's walk around with that he
was like dropping crazy poses because he
had like the nice like arms okay
good for his arms what about you Chris
Chris is giving Matt you're getting Mr
cogsworth oh cogsworth Clockwork oh I
think he said [ __ ] worth let's say that
it's the clown say what dude I thought
he said cockworth is there a problem
don't say that my counterpart Matt oh
the the [ __ ] the clock
Bros kettleton with chip not miss
kettleton it's not miss Kettle [ __ ] you
you do look like [ __ ] don't [ __ ]
yourself buddy
okay
it's like hooting and Hauling Nick you
look like the [ __ ] Mama pot then what
the [ __ ] her name is it's not miss
kettleton who is it what's your name
it's not miss kettleton I don't give a
[ __ ] you look just like her with your
big nose
that guy's still saying full sentences
to himself I feel bad it's terrible I
feel like blackberries need to go [ __ ]
themselves I hate black bears get up out
of here not a big fan dude my allergies
are so awful right now and I don't know
what it is
and I still don't know why
Nick reminds me of watch where you go
here me and Nick are like
um I like the fair warning yeah
literally me and Nick are like Shaggy
and Scooby
what what
Matt [ __ ] are you doing sit get get [ __ ]
up and sit down
babies
yeah dude
it should be them for Halloween no dude
about being a [ __ ] weird I just want
to paint myself green and run around
like a chicken strike baby
God that's they're so awesome Matt's
picking his nose okay I just made myself
the one with a bow okay
um
Matt not just because you don't really
talk much I feel like you'd like really
successfully be a good mime
I feel like he'd be Ferb
from Phineas
don't break your neck on me [ __ ] kid
just whipping it around what's your
opinion on those things whatever y'all
want to call it that's fine
this verb like is just quiet as [ __ ] oh
he's back
good to see you huh Ferb's just quiet as
[ __ ] and then he comes in with like like
one day he'll just like oh actually then
they say like a [ __ ] like a big Goofy
sentence and then I was like firm shut
the [ __ ] up like you know all right verb
you look like what's the what's the
dude's name not Bell G but his friend
along with the black shirt
Rufus no it's like is it not Rufus no we
gotta bring up the little kids
what about them you look just like them
no it's like a million times I know but
come on videos about cartoon characters
yeah but we get it do about the [ __ ]
little kid from The Lorax yeah you look
like [ __ ]
you look like the grandma that's all
nosy and [ __ ] in Ned's business and [ __ ]
like now he's trying to go about his day
and be with Shorty go get a seed and
[ __ ] she wasn't no G though no she's
nosy as [ __ ] no no the mom's nosy the
grandma the Grandma's nosy but with good
intentions no the Grandma's chilling
she's actually lit I feel like I'm like
the bear that stuffs his face with the
marshmallows and he's like that oh yeah
yeah that's a good one and you're like
the fish in the bowl complaining a lot
and you just jump out and you're like oh
that's the thing it makes like the Cat
in the Hat oh I love it look there's a
fish
there is it's the same type of fish
they're both Dr Seuss books but doctors
did you hear that theory
did you guys hear this oh my God I'm so
excited to tell you guys stop listen go
listen what color is the Grinch green
green what color is the mayor of
Whoville like [ __ ] purple or
something whitish and blue right
whitish and blue yeah yeah what color
when he's like at the council meeting
are all the people on the council
like green like greenish blue lavender
almost the Grinch is the only green who
in the Grinch's Whoville spec now in
Horton here's a who we learned that the
speck lives on a truffle a tree correct
same universe right I think that the
Grinch was supposed to be or it's like a
Theory online that the Grinch was put on
the wrong Speck and he was supposed to
go to Whoville in Horton Hears a Who
because he would match the rest of the
who's there you know there's green who's
in Horton Hears a Who you just told me
that oh yeah there is on the council is
that not crazy yeah that is Grinch is on
the wrong spec so it's Becca Zion
the one with the Grinch with Cindy Lou
and yes and the Gang we just haven't
learned about his spec without his whoa
why did he do that we haven't learned
about the Grinch's perspective we
haven't learned about the Grinch's
background no baby Grinch was ugly are
you all done no so for real what do you
mean I don't want to catch more Pokemon
okay we can be done what favorite
Pokemon [ __ ] yourself Cubone and what
was my other one Haunter oh you're tough
what about you what favorite Pokemon I'm
not answering that goofy garbage
question why because he's a [ __ ]
lackluster content maker get in this
[ __ ] he wants to know your favorite
Pokemon I don't care anything you remind
me of [ __ ] like the Cyber Chase dude
in the movie The Annoying [ __ ] that
like cheats the game and he's like I
tried to hack it and like send the
Mystery Machine gang into the thing you
know the goofy dude a goofy what are you
even saying you look like a baseball
dude though
the villain that's what I just said
Nicholas yeah oh you called him
like get out of here
I love [ __ ] um Velma no you don't yes
I do bro why because she's the baddest
Daphne Velma why because what a change
of heart what led to this I don't know
but also Daphne had a bad dude I love
Daphne so much yeah definitely bad for
sure what are you gonna say
that was so crazy
matters
oh my god look what I just found oh my
God oh my God you know Patrick Star's
sister Patricia yeah Nick oh that's you
Nick Patricia Starr for sure guaranteed
that's you bro you look like SpongeBob
no that's cool like also what are
SpongeBob's parents old sponges not
cookies we get it we've seen it we've
heard it oh yeah that's right is that
not crazy you love that don't you well
they just look like cookies Nick loves
like parallel [ __ ] like little like oh
like yeah Nick's like the type of guy to
watch like 25 times Toy Story was
mentioned in other Disney movies and
then he watches it like this and then he
sees the ball and he's like it's a good
guard like the [ __ ] whatever movies
and he gets all excited about it you
know way too much
you're watching watch whatever that
whole thing that whole thing that's Nick
looks out the window in despair
why do you always do that I don't know
because sometimes you're just feeling
the Nature real quick I'm like wow
you'd be blown away oh
yeah
I know what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things