there's a lot of things that should be
that isn't correct there's a lot of
things that should be that aren't but
they shall be or else they will not
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you
yeah
[Music]
okay but come whatever that I didn't get
a drink you should go get a drink
no yeah well do you have a drink your
mom
okay today we're going to be playing
smash or pass
with random objects that you guys give
us
what do you mean go ahead I have nothing
to say how did kovid make the gas prices
go up
like if you can't use your [ __ ] hands
pick them up yourself you didn't place
it in my hand once
just literally on camera okay correct no
you didn't put in my hands
classic
what Nick I'm just scared of people
really bad okay uh
nope we're good we're good let me know
see how's that gas 347.
but that one's 360
63. it's about like where they get it
from where anyways we moved over like
six spots so hopefully we can be
Incognito over here but yeah like I said
we're filming smash or pass
oh
we're the random objects what about
funions Funyuns Funyuns are like kind of
like
delicious can we do overrated underrated
and perfectly rated instead
perfectly rated
I don't know what you mean by that
okay I don't know how you don't know
what I mean
I don't know what you mean because it
doesn't make sense or you just said it
makes perfect sense
does it though
absolutely a grand scheme of things in
the grand scheme of things it makes
sense in what world does it make sense
and according to you okay whatever
okay ready I'm ready
Rachel said a lamp
overrated
oh I'm playing my own little game here
what are your thoughts on a lamp
how dull is it I hate how loud you've
been chewing recently it really bothers
me because like you gained this new
passion to like not shut your mouth and
it's yeah it's a real big passion of
mine I don't know well I don't know it's
like brand new this little stupid thing
you're doing
it's brand new
I only want to be in here
I can't listen to this like I actually
can't do it stop I can't do it like I
literally cannot do it and I will not do
it so saying something to then laying
your hands on me is two very different
things okay so I'm never gonna do what
the [ __ ] you just did again oh okay or
what I'll [ __ ] knock your teeth to
your [ __ ] throat [ __ ]
I'll knock your teeth
just don't [ __ ] hit me first
now it's hot so good luck I'm turning
the AC on I'm turning the AC on I'm
itchy I got a long sleeve shirt on itchy
itchy I'll knock your feet to your
throat [ __ ]
he sounded like the [ __ ]
okay what are you doing like throwing
your arms when you're done
how about you finish that bag and then
we'll do the video I'll knock your teeth
get out of here it smells like skunk
dude I've seen roadkill two times today
it's so scary to me why is roadkill
scary to you I my biggest fear is dead
things I love the museum with all like
the taxider meat animals in it uh-huh
can you go there I could but it's like
my biggest nightmare
can I tell you what I think my fear is
of like dead animals go ahead my you
guys are gonna be really gross out
though okay like my fear of dead can I
eat this first
yeah let's let's you eat that whole
thing and then we'll and then yeah
and you've been chewing like you can
shut the camera off and redo it when
you're done
oh your beard is bad oh my God but no
what I was saying is
a grand ordeal
what's shaking up there
punch the front I bet you'll fix it
and it did that's my go-to solution
but whatever doesn't work
my biggest fear when it comes to dead
animals is one of them like jumping up
and getting me or like pranking that
they were alive and fighting back the
only one or I have such a big fear such
such a big fear of like stepping on it
oh my God because when I was little
this is where my fear rooted from
genuinely Miracles ran apart is that
like the endless bag it's like I feel
like Mary Poppins yeah sold them the bag
of Funyuns no but actually we were
playing at a park and my sandals were
too big for me I have sandals you said
the story a thousand times okay then I
won't good I'm gonna say oh I don't want
people aren't gonna be able to find it
and then you're like oh I wish Nick told
a little swords like I can't remember go
ahead
and look so when I was little when I was
little like I was like 10 remember what
are you rolling your sleeves up for and
I had short sandals on I had short
sandals on so my feet sandals yes what
do you mean shorts I'm trying to get
that let me speak shorts and sandals
short sandals like sandals that did not
fit my feet and my foot was longer than
the short sandals
sure whatever you want to call it potato
potato
I have sandals on so do you want me to
just show you this way that's length it
was like this and my toes my toes were
above the sandals Nick get your foot so
my feet didn't fit and we were playing
tennis so I was like oh let me just take
my sandals off I took my sandals off and
I ran to the tennis court and I was
playing basketball or tennis with one of
you somewhere it was like a multi-court
like it was Tennessee it's not not
important I stepped on a dead bird
and it was like mushy and it was like
feathers and blood on my feet oh my
oh my fear you have shoes on though no
it doesn't matter I could be [ __ ] put
in a [ __ ] titanium suit I could be in
a [ __ ] hazmat suit and be too afraid
to watch what if you were in a big metal
box and then you just knew we were all
throwing dead birds at you oh my god
there were these crazy psycho [ __ ]
that we went to school with and one of
them picked up a dead pigeon I remember
that and was carrying it around and like
throwing it at people and like put it in
her backpack I'm like you need to be
evaluated and sent to the psychord ASAP
yeah no one should be playing around
with the dead animals okay no one should
be playing with dead animals that girl's
a [ __ ] creeper right here like I'm
not sorry not gonna see her again I'm
running man the lamps how do we feel
about them
I think a good tinted
um like a good like not too bright
doesn't sell all this that's all bulb
s
it's bulb
does it sound or anything I was trying
to like really tell him how it's
pronounced say it again bulb bulb
we're talking the lamp part
like the like the lamp itself the lamp
or the lamp shade
have you guys seen that season American
Horror Story
which one there's like 11. about the
lampshade the haunted yeah there's
another one that's like a lampshade is a
very critical part
IES
in asylum in Asylum I'm pretty sure the
season like Sarah Paulson's character
finds out that she's with the bad guy
because he like killed people and like
made [ __ ] out of their skin and the way
she figured out that he was like the
killer was she she was there and his
lampshade was like made out of human
skin and she was like oh my God but then
like she got kidnapped was like crazy
I wish you never told me that no but
yeah okay no but yeah lamps I can pass
on a lamp [ __ ] a lamp bro well I gotta
say it a good slash
a good like small
kind of dull bedside lamp would do the
trick reading light but it has to have a
cool design I'm not going with them I
want like a lamp that's like a character
like I want it to be like Goofy
now
no like the goofy like a Disneyland
oh goofy [ __ ] buck teeth build a
dog the dog it's not a dog it's goofy
Goofy's a dog Goofy's not a dog Goofy's
a dog he's a goofy stupid [ __ ] is that
for real yes are you trying to tell me
Goofy's a goof yes and that's who's like
definition
like what is Goofy's breed he's a goof
like he's a goof and then Pluto is a dog
no it's a [ __ ] Goofy Movie and
they're they're all Goofs that's the
whole point of the [ __ ] movie so as
his name Goofy
because that's what he wanted to be no
because did you want to be Christopher
no mother name
where am I mother what am I
no he's not it says he is a tall dog who
typically wears a turtleneck and a vest
with pants shoes white gloves and a tall
hat originally designed as a Okay blah
blah blah is a close friend of Mickey
Mouse and Donald Duck and his Mac Max
goof's father but his name is he's a dog
and he's goofy [ __ ] stupid thing
who's lying to me saying he's a goof I I
cannot believe you thought that he was a
goof do you have a drink back there no
you got nothing to drink
no nothing I have a coffee We're not
gonna drink it it's 1 30 in the morning
okay so just drink it
um why do you want me to drink a drink
what are you gonna is it osmosis you're
gonna have some too based on me drinking
my drink no I'm just really thirsty shut
the [ __ ] up
it's not how it works at all you wash
your hair recently it looks terrible
that's it doesn't look bad
you know I'm not gonna like it no I
think I think it was good
fixed it it looks better than it just
did nice yep I love you Nick come on go
buy a drink for yourself no bring it in
don't I don't see enough Nick at it no
for real I want to see them all day I
can't I really can't not like the good
looking ooh I'm Nick but like just the
funny ones you're a funny guy I know
thank you
God he's so funny ah God why don't we
just I think for this video we should
all go back there and just tickle each
other that's insane
get off me Matt you guys like ah
a really good car video would be if we
talked about everything we hated yeah
I think we should do a video where we
just compliment everything about each
other
I'm just such a oh wow huge bug rare
right right where no you're good it's
not anywhere oh you guys are playing me
no there's a button we're not at all
there's a big moth
yeah get the [ __ ] off me [ __ ] that was
crazy that was like instinct I don't
know okay OtterBox phone case smash or
pass pass I say smash way too boxy super
strong no
strong durable there to support you too
much too much what else could you you
know what I'm gonna say I have no idea
what that is
a brick I don't know what that is get
some words out use the [ __ ] vocal
thing I don't know what the [ __ ]
OtterBox phone cases yes you do no I
don't
they ran those [ __ ] ran 2016. not a
clue what the [ __ ] it is an OtterBox
phone case is like a super secure one so
like dads have like on their Clips oh
yeah
oh wait their new stuff's not bad
they're just all simple like tough are
we talking like generic OtterBox
just know what it is you're the one that
said OtterBox a sword sword smash no
absolutely that would hurt
well I wasn't it's all metaphorical okay
obviously no I think I think you should
talk about how kind you are why
why
are we looking over my shoulder I think
like if Nick was a chocolate he'd be
like a Kit Kat like the big cat like the
three the row of three of them boom boom
boom yeah like I feel like that'd be us
three not even just Nick like the big
cat where it's like you know a normal
kit kat is for us this way hey big cat
is three that way that'd be us yeah
that's hard
and then if Nick wasn't there and he
doesn't want to be a part of like the
whole chocolate reference we'll just be
Reese's like a pack okay smash or
passing piano
yes I hate pianos I can't believe kids
actually took piano lessons oh don't be
mean
a little someone's gonna ask for aspirin
that's totally fine
did I say my contacts please go ahead
there was this kid that I was friends
with
no listen he didn't enjoy playing the
piano he hated it but his mom had him
signed up for piano classes and me and
him wanted to always hang out like after
like school after the third fourth grade
but he couldn't because I can't yeah I
think parents have forced their kids to
do like extracurricular activities like
Chuck if you're a parent force you to do
something like that like an activity
that like really that you don't want to
do I say punch him in the face okay
don't don't do all that dude like the
kid's mom would always make him go home
and play the piano when he wanted to
like hang out if you can play the piano
you could probably play numerous other
instruments yeah because it's the same
like it's like chords bro it's like okay
you guys are boring someone said smash
or pass chimney dust oh my God chimney
dust yeah next question you look like
chimney dust next question pass and what
does that make you how does Santa not
get his coat that dirty
I played a live studio audience we
should do a VR video with a studio
audience one day
I said too many crazy things
I know I know it's just sometimes in the
middle of a car video we'll randomly
talk about like our life and obviously
we're not gonna put it in
resume
the [ __ ] was that yeah it was like oh
hey where the [ __ ] did this guy just
come from
why why does he already have a
Cumberland Farms cup and why is his
posture insane dude dude
exact thing happened last time we were
that's so true the posture too there's
got to be a portal somewhere bro
literally this dude
no because that lady went by the fence
last time this dude just
oh my God last time we were in this
exact same parking lot some dude from a
[ __ ] there's got to be something
that's like a trail that way
who's walking on a train
in the [ __ ] morning either serial
killers or those who want to be a victim
of a serial killing there's the only two
people walking on I don't think anyone
ever really wants to be so stay off the
[ __ ] Trails okay that's my whole
point of the goddamn sentence dude next
word doesn't like I don't like what
grout
that's not a word
incorrect what the [ __ ] does a word It's
gotta be grout is when you're like a a
lining tile or like brick or like
something that's like in many pieces
grout is like the inside of it that just
[ __ ] up the camera for sure when you
somebody's just out there whistling like
I just hear
and it's really scaring me are you dead
ass I'm so for real are you dead ass I'm
so excited that's so scared like I I
think there's just somebody right over
there whistling what I'm adding that's
my list of biggest fear you have an
active list of that oh yeah no way can
you read a couple
no dude not yet like what is this plan a
fresheners how do we feel love it I hate
air fresheners I feel like they don't
keep the air fresh yeah it's like a
momentarily smell yeah actually perfume
works better as an air freshener than
air fresheners I agree like when someone
sprays a perfume that [ __ ] stays
forever forever dude if like if you have
a cologne or perfume in a car with you
or something it's Never Gonna Leave
that's why I love when I when we go back
from LA and to Boston and back and forth
because whenever I walk back into my
bedroom did I tell you my plan
like dude what you've interrupted me
no but my plan but I love walking into
my room and smelling it I get that on my
plan yeah yes
I want so badly to have like a body wash
a conditioner I've heard this telling
you again
I want like a bunch of different like a
soap a body wash uh all at all products
I want like candles everything yeah in
like a specific scent and then every
like
3.5 months I want to change them out
no 3.4 isn't divisible Seasons Seasons
yeah oh my God hurry up Nick wants to
have every single season I want to like
switch them all out so that way when
like a full year goes by and I'm back to
that scent it will remind me of
nostalgia I'd be like oh my God remember
that one time
so you basically want to create all your
scents for one season for all four
seasons so that you can like Circle back
to all of them with memories yeah
because then like the first day I used
those scent from a year ago to bring me
Vibes like oh what was I doing a year
ago I think there should be a car video
where we each really try on a poem okay
I'm down like really hardcore yes like
wait can we do a fan submitted talent
show where they do their talents and
send in videos oh I have a gorilla
really good
really good idea whatever a fan submits
us them doing we have to recreate
because I know some of these little
girls can do some crazy [ __ ] like like
say that one of the girls fills up her
tub with like ketchup and jumps in I
don't even have to do I'm not doing that
no like I think it's a challenge because
that's also that just invokes them to do
like violent things like we're not gonna
recreate it okay I think we could have a
talent show though where they already
know what they're doing a little bit we
should play the extreme game and we each
take turns doing something until we're
at like extreme levels and then no like
I'm good
[ __ ]
[ __ ] like drink more water I don't
need something like that you want to
feel extreme no at all no I'm extremely
[ __ ] okay with not doing that I like
a good tall glass of water and uh my
feet up and a bag of goddamn chips
you're funny
but the type of guy that'd be really
good at speaking malarkey
[Laughter]
notice how I just made you laugh harder
than you ever made me laugh I didn't
even say words nothing left my mouth and
you laughed harder at a joke I didn't
make than I've ever laughed at you or
matt
like let's be absolutely for real oh you
just chuckled I hear it no you hurt me
you didn't hear [ __ ] play it back you
chuckled you did I will put this
album
the bush
the bush Transformers oh he has a
king-sized re-seasona
oh wow
he went that way my heart he went down
he went down my heart is actually racing
he went down like I would never walk
into the a [ __ ] abyss of nothingness
we should do like a 12 a.m midnight
walking in the wilderness video no no
yes no hazards all right everybody thank
you so much for watching this Friday's
video we appreciate and love each and
every single one of you guys
looks for the lights behind them he just
reaches cause I know where they [ __ ]
are
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things