oh it's a chilly one right now why are
you actively so hot because we went to
the dentist today we went to the dentist
today guess how many cavities I have
don't don't even tell them I'm barely on
one hand
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
this is their toothbrush yeah why is it
like halfway open why are you touching
it I don't know two good questions two
great questions yeah but I have to quit
soda and [ __ ] because I'm like about I
have like a ton of cash I really feel
like the whole car like yeah right now
put the floss down Nick We're not gonna
like take care of our dental hygiene
right now yes I absolutely
I don't know who you think you are
like that I said weird like I know we're
not I am for sure I don't know who you
think you are speaking for me like
you're the pope I'm absolutely this is a
pope like resonate with you a lot you
often bring him up another rats resonate
isn't a word so he doesn't resonate with
me it resonate what's the word I don't
know he just seems like I'm already at
two mice no more can you stop looking at
the [ __ ] mice like why do you why'd
you say Mike yeah because there's one
rat one mice and I feel like mice you
can tell the difference from this far
I have a mouse in this hand and a rat in
the other and I would not oh you would
know I can't okay you can't tell no a
mouse is this [ __ ] big a rat is like
that big
then it's like that big it's like a
little bit bigger okay and mouse is like
that [ __ ] Chris okay
anyways today we're going to be playing
smash Mary kill with different things
the reason I said smash is because I
just believe the word like like I know
we say the F-bomb a lot but I feel like
in this F bomb in this tense
the F word's really strong okay like I
feel like the action of it is way more
stronger than just using the word so
we're going to use the word smash so
smash Mary kill with three random
objects that you guys helped us Supply I
did have Smashburger too you guys helped
us Supply with it yeah we had
Smashburger yes we had surgery yeah
today so that actually kind of just
really that's why I'm really feeling
this it resonated with you I resonate it
resonated with me what y'all farted bro
it smells so stinky I did not fart I
don't fart I didn't fart either I don't
fart I'm gonna go first I have like
three really I have a couple good ones
that's freaking me out they say I'm the
goat okay first one mop Robot vacuum
cleaner and a rag Robot vacuum cleaner
isn't hitting the spots wow I feel like
that's a smash really I agree you said
you don't like robots though but it's a
vacuum cleaner yeah but it's like dude
for me I'm a more of like get my hands
dirty type of guy so your rag
no a mop
that's not getting my hands dirty
smashing the mop no marrying them up me
and the mop go way back
Fork spoon and knife classic oh I kept
it simple
a spoon's just so particular
spoon I [ __ ] hate spoons spoons oh
and knife is more particular I think I'm
killing the knife I think honestly but
what are you gonna cut with only a fork
and a spoon okay but the second the
forks the fork can do it no the Mary we
want to cook love and keep that by our
side yes
yeah he can be put in any single
situation he's battling his other side
soup but guess what I can just sip it
correct and then use the fork Force left
in there low-key exactly like if I have
ramen noodles I only use a fork me too
okay hey
listen
times in your life say let's use Kraft
macaroni okay all right hit right and
you're like oh do I use a fork or a
knife like I don't really know no never
ever that's never happening
sorry sorry yeah I was like
mind error
yeah sometimes where you're like oh like
I don't know fork or spoon like I don't
really know I'm a fork guy okay I don't
care there's has there been [ __ ] day
shut the [ __ ] up there's been a time
yes with a knife how many times have you
second guess grabbing a knife zero
it gets the job OH police Nick what are
they gonna do arrest us for oh two good
content take me in pool hot tub and bath
pool hot tub and bath they didn't throw
shower in there therefore I feel like
the bath isn't important because we're
not talking bathing I agree so bath is
gonna be my cat that's my kill as well
why because we're not talking bathing
shower wasn't inclusive Smash in the hot
tub if it was like bath shower wash your
hands I'd second guess but as of like
pool I agree Chris yes pool hot tub bath
is getting killed well bath is just a
more personal hot tub correct for me and
it's a lot less hotter I kind of enjoy
the bathtub more than I enjoy going to a
hot tub
Insanity to get clean though yeah but
you can't bathe with friends we're
talking we're talking just Chill Vibes
you can't bathe with friends why are we
talking Chill Vibes because showers not
included oh my God I have to say it
again if we're talking cleaning and
showering the pool and hot tub would not
be included the fact that pool and hot
tub isn't included therefore they mean a
relaxing bath because a pool hot tub or
relaxing bath let's reword it killing
the bath kill the bath smash the pool
marry the hot tub got it on okay I'm
down you can't no okay I'm down you can
hot tub the friends let's hear your
answer Nick I don't have an answer okay
well you find one do you agree with us
sure no no no no yes I agree fully
wholeheartedly yes I fully
wholeheartedly agree you read the next
one all right Santa or a leprechaun kill
the leprechaun [ __ ] the LeBron I gotta
say kill him like yeah kill Santa yeah
and the reason I say is he's too goddamn
busy
if he's bringing gifts to all these kids
on Christmas Eve have a good Christmas
day what do you think he's doing all
year he don't have time for you ever how
many times you've seen a leprechaun
never that's it hold on what is it Tooth
Fairy leprechaun no sandster Bunny
Easter Bunny
Easter Bunny's less busy than Santa I
agree that's my point is bringing me a
few eggs
the Easter Bunny supposed to come and
hide eggs and he really doesn't do a
good job because everyone ends up
finding all of them so well so you think
think about it I've never read you
haven't found what you never found
or you don't know that you haven't found
something if you never found it yeah but
like every time these hid eggs I've seen
a ton huh so it's like if I if you if
you're hiding eggs and I see as many as
I do unless he's hiding double then it's
really not but also what I'm saying is
Santa's the most busy as if he does not
have time for the two other things
the smash and Mary
you're so weird like Santa has no time
it's not like you're he's building toys
with these elves like and he's got Miss
Claus you're wrong you know what I'm
saying oh what's it what's Miss bunny
the L's building what does that have to
do is the Easter Bunny or the leprechaun
already co-tied what does the leprechaun
do exactly you don't know so kill the
leprechaun oh
Easter Bunny
completely disagree Santa's one taken
and I'm not a homewrecker okay
goddamn busy okay
honestly he's the opposite I don't
understand how Santa can even manage if
he's only working one night and he's not
even making the toys he's just dropping
them off he's actually not busy at all
he has 364 days to prep for the next
Christmas yes there's no way that he's
sitting around doing nothing he's
organizing the timeline he's mapping his
route he's feeding and handling the
reindeer Nick Nick listen obviously he's
doing the same route every year you
idiot you don't know
what are you one of the elves
think about it you don't know he has to
why would it no he does not have to it's
[ __ ] Santa Claus he works by Magic
and it does ruler hammer stapler marry
the hammer really I love a hammer you
love a good Hammer I'm deeply devoted to
a knife
I'm like what no
um I just like the camera you're sick I
just like a hammer shape
I thought you were gonna be
gonna be a fan kill the stapler
I'm killing the ruler if I have a tape
measure around no a ruler how old like
with a stapler it's like yeah
okay I go back to it I go back once
again how often are you using a stapler
not very often but when I do need it
something stapled what else am I going
to use
it there's not many times where a
Staples the way that I look at addition
to like oh like a folder Chris what hey
yeah Hey listen the way that I look at
interrupt Nick correct okay the way that
I look at it I can use anything to
hammer something in I could use a
baseball bat but it's the perfect shape
it's the perfect I get it I get it if
you're if you're gonna do something like
hammer in the nail there's nothing
not only that but the hammer yeah it has
substitutes so doesn't everything else
in the world a stapler if I if stapler's
not working kill the ruler
listen if the staple is not working I'm
just not gonna staple it it's not that
crucial to me if the [ __ ]
doesn't work it jams it gets done it's
done what if it jams I don't need it
staple that bad there's nothing I've
Ever Needed stapled
I've never needed to stability I'm
killing the stapler ruler how often do
you have to like oh how you don't know
how big something important ruler it
really doesn't get used much when tame
measures around okay but that's what
well I'm I'm grouping them for the
situation well well you're wrong Mick
you still have a tape measure yeah if
you kill the ruler I don't like that the
one way too like like I don't like that
any measuring device should be grouped
in for the city no no no and that's like
saying if we don't have a hammer we have
a drill that's wrong because the hammer
and a drill are two different names no
because if you can call a ruler in a in
a tape measure both measuring devices
then a hammer and a ruler clip paperclip
binder clip anything that holds pieces
pieces of paper together is also with
the stapler I don't like this at all I
don't like this one bit
kill the ruler
smash this up
marry the hammer
do you hear
okay we're just blowing and burping at
people here for some reason regardless I
[ __ ] hate staplers they're useless
they've been done before would you love
getting Amber okay
oh man
I feel like there's no world where you
should be in the fetal position it is
markers oh a record player an iPhone 3.
record player just reminds me of every
single basic person ever that just
record players in vinyls and leaves them
in their room and doesn't actually use
them I'll be the first to say it it's a
little no there's two types of vinyl
vinyl Keepers and it's people who like
dust them weekly have a beautiful
collection constantly
wasted their money yes
we've seen you
you've been here before we all know what
you are we know what you're capable of
and we've had enough see you later
you're done you've been seen before
you're done
wow gone gone out of here no need for
you anymore see you later adios amigos
toodaloo you're not being said moving
forward Scented Markers or Mary on top
absolutely Scented Markers you know what
that thing is at the end I ask plural
correct yeah you have the [ __ ]
Universe of Scented Markers you are sick
and tired of one put it away for a week
go sniff the black chair sniff another
you know you have a fridge microwave
oven what fridge microwave oven now this
is fridge
don't call me that
this is where things really
elevate gotta have the friends I'm
filling the microwave Hill microwave
kill microwave because an oven is much
more like things to things that you
could do in the microwave that you could
also
we're not even not until the same
ballpark kill microwave smash oven merry
fridge absolutely okay I'm with that you
can't put anything in the oven if you
don't have a fridge to keep it and store
it until it goes oh great really good
point Thank you really good point
because how are you going to use your
oven to cook frozen pizza where's your
frozen pizza correct in the microwave I
doubt it no let's eat real come on okay
YouTube Tick Tock or Instagram whatever
oh look at that oh oh my God it's a
paper bag I thought it was a big animal
my heart what what were you today
talk or Instagram kill Tech talk Mary
Instagram I [ __ ] hate Tick Tock I
think that Tick Tock allows way too many
people like anybody can like open their
mouth like yeah that was crazy open
their mouths Wild
it's kind of boring I loved when people
would just shut the [ __ ] up and my point
is on Tick Tock they've made it so easy
to like just comment and keep scrolling
or duet or Stitch a video and there's
way or Stitch there's way too much
opportunity to just never shut up kill
Tick Tock marry you you know what I mean
smashing I was literally in the middle
of a sentence
I'm just talking that's the whole point
I'm trying to like debrief on all of
them I love YouTube you're watching a
video you're enjoying it you throw a
comment if you feel sometimes you can
move forward with your life if you don't
you know yeah I feel like I got it take
a party and you're just keep on because
it's the point I wanted to get out there
okay but it's fine
not gonna work no I did see a car drive
but I [ __ ] hate Tick Tock that's
awesome I love Tick Tock so good I I'd
like to talk about making tick tocks no
I hate whole different balls favorite
platform by far
I'll just never spend my thoughts on
anything again awesome
Velma Daphne and Fred smash Daphne Mary
Fred no kill well I'm guessing
I forgot yeah that's fine okay move on
move on
either
move on I don't care I didn't answer
last time move on kill Fred move on or
I've had a sneeze in my throat for like
oh my God no one gives a [ __ ]
literally no one gets a single [ __ ] okay
next one oh morning midday and night
I hate the Sun and I love the night I
hate sunlight okay I've been saying it a
lot recently like when the sun rays are
on me until midday wait what is it
midday midday morning I hate midday
I mean kill morning no no morning no no
oh my God I feel like there's something
about the morning that sometimes just
feels good midday is just such a midday
the night in the day like it's like
midday and you're like oh good morning
it's not the morning anymore like [ __ ]
yourself
you have a terrible night I hope you
have a terrible afternoon and I hope you
had a bad morning since we're using past
tense now [ __ ] yourself look when I say
good morning at least at least respect
the thought that I attempted to wish you
a good morning now that you're all mad
that I said morning I hope your morning
was [ __ ] miserable [ __ ] on by a bird
I hope your car was locked you forgot
your keys I hope you're dropped and
crack phone I hope your kids [ __ ]
tripped on the way to school I hope your
day was [ __ ] terrible so far how
about that
good morning oh it's actually afternoon
oh [ __ ] yourself I don't care at all
the attempt was there it was made clear
and it's not that detrimental of a
[ __ ] difference at all between
morning and afternoon but if it means
that much to you I hope you have a
terrible all three
how do you feel about people that will
say that was actually yesterday at like
1201. oh
even worse
than worse when you're trying to like
talk about a plan it's like midnight and
you're like oh tomorrow morning actually
you mean today it's like no [ __ ] I
count nicely I don't count past midnight
and it's always the [ __ ] that
correct you were like 1205 like they
catch you so off guard because they'll
be like you mean today and you're just
like what the [ __ ] are you even talking
about you're gonna check the time and
you're like oh you're one of those
[ __ ] weirdos that are like using it
completely correct like you're right but
it's like you're a loser you know what I
mean I hate that I hate dogs oh I can't
even explain how much that anger I have
like a headache I haven't stopped
laughing I'm like you know how
aggravating that is he clearly does next
topic
Pepsi Vaseline stuffed animals
Vaseline stuffed animals Vaseline oh
we're not really really weird thought in
my head I was like why are we that's
even weirder I know what he was thinking
okay I just like um we're killing
Vaseline Mary supplements supplements
substitutes
isn't a substitute wait
absolutely there's just so many
substitutes to vaseline
[Music]
that's another thing in the SpongeBob
movie when Plankton's like I need the
petroleum he's just talking about
Vaseline essentially
plutonium plutonium
there's not one moment where I thought
oh Plankton just really wants [ __ ]
Vaseline what would he do with Vaseline
just tubs and
actually I'm like 95 sure Vaseline is
completely hydrophobic
[Laughter]
like you would never need it because it
wouldn't do anything underwater I'm like
95 sure
so that's all the word hydrophobic
really got me
oh yeah just because I know it like
hydrophobic
waterproof that you just made it way
bigger of a deal than you had to yeah
and I knew your finger was up
you were like it's actually hydrophobic
dogs like such a nerd like literally oh
yeah so Vaseline useless Plankton wasn't
looking for it you were wrong oh [ __ ]
I've had to sneeze for this whole video
I'd assume it's in your throat somewhere
is that our vehicle
no that's not a vehicle
all right
really really really strange noises just
occurred over there on the ground oh
welcome to Boston well I think we were
done anyway yeah I agree so goodbye I
love you all
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
[Music]