Afternoon,
dragons.
My name's Christian.
What's
Hi, my name is Natalie.
And together we are
Stand Out.
And we're here today to pitch for
£30,000 for 25% equity in our company,
Standout Enterprises Limited.
In the UK, there's approximately 1.5
million adults with a learning
disability. Now, as it stands today,
there is little as 5.1% of adults with a
learning disability in England known to
be in paid employment.
Unfortunately, my little brother here,
Ross, was part of that statistic.
Frustrated at that fact, myself, Ross,
and Natalie got together and thought,
why don't we create a job for him? And
that was the day Standout Socks was
born. Our mission for Standout is to
become the leading employer for people
with learning disabilities in the UK.
Thank you very much for listening. I'm
going to pass you over to Ross now who's
going to hand you all a sample. I hope
we hope you really enjoy it. Thank you.
A business with the purpose of providing
jobs to people with learning
disabilities.
My eye
is the brainchild of brothers Ross and
Christian Lane and Natalie Dixon.
Spot on.
Thank you. M pay for it.
They're seeking £30,000 in exchange for
25% of their sock making company.
Who's your favorite guy? My favorite
girl.
All of you.
Diplomatic catastrophe narrowly avoided.
Thank you, sir.
Steven Bartlett is first to kick off
with the questions.
They're like Manchester United colors.
So they they were sold in the Manchester
United mega store.
Who do you support?
Manchester United.
I've now got the best socks in the den.
It looks good.
Um the most compelling thing you said
when we're thinking about the story here
was giving people jobs who have kind of
been left out of the workforce to some
degree. Yeah.
Can you speak from your experience about
how transformative that is as a value
proposition or a value ad to the
individuals that are getting jobs
because of Standout?
Yeah. So, for example, Stand Out was
born out of COVID really. Ross moved in
with my mom and dad
um and was shielded um for pretty much
12 months back after that.
Now, Ross struggled with after all that
time away. He struggled with social
skills. Is that all right for me to say?
Yeah,
sure. Uh confidence
always.
Yeah.
You don't strike as someone lacking in
confidence. Ross,
you got bit of confidence.
And then just giving anybody the value
of having a job and and the purpose to
go and do something is good for anybody,
not just somebody with a learning
disability.
So, how long has the business been
going?
So, we now just finished year one at the
end of January and we're now in year
two. So, what was your full year's
trading on that first year?
So, our first year's trading, we turned
over um £36,158.
We had a gross profit of 22,245
with a pre-tax profit of £5,186.
Someone spent a lot of time learning
them figures to the pound right there.
Oh, well done, Natalie. And are you
fulltime on this, Ross?
is together is Tuesday
on a Tuesday. So on a Tuesday and a
Sunday we we do like
videos for our social medias and post
our social medias and then Ross will
pack all the socks.
Oh, so you're the social media superstar
Ross
as well as Chief Packer.
I love it.
Do
you know what? It's really interesting
because I must admit, as you can tell, I
love socks.
But is this and can this be a business
or could anybody do this? I mean the
answer for me is that anybody could
could do this. So I need to find what
your real unique selling point is that
as a consumer when I'm buying this I
know. So for example there are very very
famous sock business in the states and
their whole premise was that if you buy
one pair of socks another pair of socks
goes to somebody that's homeless. Yeah.
Yeah.
I want to know what's your unique
message and how do you get it across?
So our our unique selling point is we we
we're using the socks to create
conversations around disability
inclusion and down syndrome awareness.
But looking at that, I wouldn't say
that.
That's my point. So I want you to tell
me how are you doing this?
So Standout, the brand Standout will be
known as an employer of people with
learning disabilities.
Brilliant. Now tell me about that
because that's what I'm interested in.
How are you going to do that? So we've
been working with a national um charity
and then as we build through from there
our our main ethos is to give people
like
above who have struggled to get work.
Jobs.
Right. Okay. And how are you going to
get there so that I know about it?
So imagine you're every retailer.
Yeah.
What one strap line would you give this
business that when I'm walking past that
end aisle, I'm going I'm going to buy
those socks.
So
by these socks, help us change the
world.
One pair of socks does what?
Makes a makes a a ripple.
Makes a ripple in the the world,
you know. It's
No, no. I I appreciate
Are you getting what I'm saying?
Yeah. Yeah. I I I I appreciate what
you're saying.
This is a brutal world to make money in
business and I don't believe you're
going to get there unless you're
absolutely laserike focused in how
you're going to get there and how you
are going to do exactly what your brand
says, which is to stand out.
Why stand out, not stand up?
Stand up kind of feels a lot more about
what you're doing. You're standing up
for people. You're you're including
people into So So did you think about
those choices?
Yes, sure. We we thought, well, why fit
in when you're born to stand out? Why?
It's not telling your story,
right? So, for us, it's it it's hard to
get across. It's just like, don't don't
hide in the background. Stand out. Be
Natalie, that's the problem.
It's hard to tell your story.
But I sit here looking as an investor.
And I think there's a lot an awful lot
that needs to be done to tell your
particular story. And that does make it
hard for an investor.
So, I'm really sorry, guys. And I mean
that. I won't be investing. I won't.
Christian Ross Natalie.
Yay.
How big can
these socks get? And I'm not talking
like extra large, extra large. I mean
like how big can this business be?
We It's going to get massive because
we want to become a global leader. want
to become a so we want stores in each
capital city and people to you know help
people not just in the UK but worldwide
to get there cuz obviously socks are
quite
I'd say quite easy to make these are
very good quality but obviously the
thing that's going to help you penetrate
such a saturated market is an
impenetrable mission and it's really
telling the story of the mission here
um
and I know how to tell a good story
so I'm going to make you an offer
back in me.
I love the business. The very core of
this business is allowing people to have
opportunities who wouldn't otherwise
have opportunities. That's the bit that
got me. So my offer is going to be for
all of the money
for 25% of the business.
And listen, we'll go to Manchester
United together.
Why are you wearing city colors? Why are
you wearing city colors? Miss
didn't
think of that.
Wow. Okay,
guys. I want to know what you want a
dragon for.
Yeah. Watch
dancing.
Ross wants someone from to come dancing.
You want someone to dance with? I'd be
perfect. Ross,
may I?
talking.
The first time I've had that answer.
Excellent. It's looking promising here.
How about you, Natalie?
Yeah. So, obviously we we've got we've
got a really varied skill set between
us, but there are some gaps where we
could just do with a a kind of helping
hand along the way.
And the big thing I've heard that you
need help with in a big way is
storytelling.
Yeah.
And I would say the the unique skill
that I have in my business is
storytelling.
So, I'm going to take Bartlett on.
Good luck.
So, I'm going to match his offer and I
would also give you all of the money for
25% of the business.
And I've got something he hasn't got.
I'm a way better dancer.
I'll be shove.
[Music]
Look, you've got two great offers.
individual offers,
but maybe there's another offer because
I because I think that you might need
more than one dragon on this.
Open door. It's all about opening doors
here.
[Music]
So, my offer really is is very simple is
I would offer you half the money for 12%
if the dragons wanted to do it cuz I
think I think it needs more than one
dragon here.
Thank you.
Yeah, I think that's a nice offer. You
can tell you can you can see the
situation here, can't you? It's it's a
tough one.
No, no, I would push it.
I really wanted to push you today as
hard as I could to try and get this
answer to this question, though.
Mhm.
Because I don't believe that you're
going to have a chance in hell of making
this a successful business until you get
that right.
Okay.
And that's why I think I'm the right
partner for you.
So, I'm going to make you an offer for
all of the money um for 20%.
The old undercut.
Okay. Should we go in?
You can speak to them all.
Thank you guys. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Peter Jones with the undercut.
A plethora of offers for the
entrepreneurial philanthropists. All
right, going to do now.
Steven Bartlett and Sar Davies have
agreed to pay the asking price of
£30,000 for 25%.
Got a choice.
Steven
Tuka Sullyman has offered to team up
with another dragon at the same
valuation.
I really don't know what to do. What do
you think? do this now.
But sock supreo Peter Jones has undercut
them all with a pledge of 20%.
Let's do this. Let's stand out. Come on.
Who will they pick to pair up with?
Okay. Um,
obviously thank you very much for all
your input. We really, really appreciate
it. But we wondered
guys
if you two can could work together on
this.
[Music]
I have to say um Peter is the only
dragon that's ever spoken to me about
socks. Literally sat in this chair over
maybe a bit too much.
So if we do at the 25% level then I'm
I'm happy to partner if Peter is
Wow. Oh, I think that's that'll be for
me. That I think that's that will be
amazing.
Ross, what you think?
Do this.
I'd like to do it. Let's do it.
Success for Ross and his team as they
secure the backing they came for, which
will undoubtedly turbocharge their
business and their cause.
Well done. Well done.
What about me dance? Go on then.
Yeah.
Do you know how you do it around here?
One, two, three. One, two, three. Yeah,
good. And a spa.
Oh, he's sipping the pel. I like it.
You're a good sir.
Yeah. Thank you very much, honestly. We
really appreciate it.
Brilliant.
Ecstatic. and shock.
Yeah, it was uh it was it was
unbelievable to get four offers for
starters. That was amazing.
Oh, it was so brilliant. I actually
think it could be a really really great
business
with the right story.
That's the thing we got to work on is
get that messaging that
it's not there yet, but we'll we'll make
that happen.
We did it, guys.