all right I'm going to a concert Matt
and Chris are leaving for Vegas in like
an hour or two but I'm leaving before
I'll see you guys in 3 days again yep
last time me and Matt just went to
Chicago for summer Smash and spent 5
days away from Nick and now we're going
to Vegas and we're spending another 3
days without Nick so excited I don't
know what I'm wearing in the concert I'm
bringing an entire duffel bag to my
friend's house so we'll see how that
goes I'm so excited I'm going to this
concert have fun Nick I'm going have a
blast is your Uber already here I can't
believe you're going to see people like
literally slap each other across the
face like for fun I saw a video of like
the them edit the lady hold on me and
Matt got invited well all three of us
got invited Nick just isn't going to
like the power slap thing I don't need
to see that I think after when we get
back we should do it here I I don't
think we need to do that at all I don't
think that's going to happen but we're
bringing Justin my driver can't pick me
up faster this is so awkward I hate
being around here you can just go
outside that's a duffel bag I'm bringing
with all of my stuff in it for one day
for one day I don't know what I'm
wearing yet so I brought like you
couldn't decide at home no there's a
bunch of [ __ ] in there I'll figure it
out when I get there that's a delusion
are you going to have a blast with him
me and Matt always have a good time he
does the speaking for me and then I just
walk around I can't believe you guys are
going to Vegas I can't either in a month
before we're 21 you can't even do
anything there I know well we're it's we
can go watch the Power slab thing that's
why we're going Chris we'll be right
back when next we were driver's here
ready
yeah he thinks that that's hilarious you
think that's
funny oh my God mad as anxiety yeah all
right Nick your Uber's here yes goodbye
don't touch me give me a goodbye be fun
have safe goodbye did you hear what I
just said yeah be fun have safe you're
funny you're the funniest ever I'll walk
you through the door all right come on
don't have too much fun Chris be fun
have safe you better sing at the concert
I want to see a clip of you sing it
thank God right Matt now it's our
turn now it's power
SL I'm excited to see Justin I'm excited
to see people slap each other and I'm
excited to it's not funny CH yes it is
Nick is disgust mad as anxiety guess who
I am anger nope Joy oh God you're stupid
hello everyone we are in Vegas right now
and we are in what it's a whopping like
109° literally I'm sweating my ass off
right now but we are in a very big rush
right now to check in turn in our bags
and then we are going straight to a
casino that our older brother is playing
poker in right now and right now he's in
a heads up position which means it's him
and one other guy we're trying to get
there so that when he possibly wins this
we are in there or loses we are there to
celebrate the crazy second place cuz
there's there was 11,000 people in this
tournament this is uh definitely the
craziest Hotel Hotel I've definitely
ever stayed in in my life and probably
will forever be the craziest Hotel
what's up yeah we were going to run up
here drop our bags off and leave to meet
up with Justin at his final table but he
just came in second place unfortunately
yeah his friend just texted us he didn't
get the bracelet which would have been
first place but he did get a slight one1
million grand for second place so very
proud of him we're going to go and hang
out with Justin tonight and Uber to them
probably in the next 10 minutes but
let's show them the room and
you want to drink all this and get
hammered for sure let's do it oh my God
peanuts no way yeah how much if I open
this probably like they're probably
going to charge the room like a million
dollars kitchen dining room living room
kit what is this what the
[ __ ] what is this I have no idea what is
is there a doctor office oh what what
does it say am I going to get a flu shot
are they going to come up here and give
me a vacine it's like a Massage Wellness
what theow is going
on
yeah I feel like SpongeBob and jelly
when he has all the jellyfish over at
his house and it's like and they got
like the Hella speakers yeah tear the
pineapple up to this all right we're
going to see Justin we're how far away
are we Matt 16 let me check 9:43 drop
off 13 minute drive how are you good
what's up dude that was the worst
[ __ ] beat I've ever seen that was
that was so sick though V dude that was
[ __ ] so cool to watch I wanted to get
in on the action and put a bucket hat
[Music]
on see a lot of bricks not going to
lie holy [ __ ] here do some [ __ ]
trivia on the way yeah do some trivia
Uber trivia here yep
oh dude you what the two bro Justin told
me it was one who the hell's on the $1
bill you should came withg New Jersey
Maryland Maryland Maryland Maryland what
do we get four points what's the what's
wow we almost won our own is there like
a water fountain in the middle of the
[ __ ] rumors no but it's I to find a
place to go on all hang out me and Matt
are the only two that are under 21 so
it's like annoying cuz we don't want to
drink and we don't want to gamble we
just want to be able to freely be
everywhere um
no one's ided us yet but we're facing
that challenge cuz it's like if we walk
all the way somewhere with Justin and
all his friends and then we get ided
then we have to leave I shut my eyes and
we're getting on a party bus can I get
on off I don't got to flip it in take a
look at that
waterfall we're still just me and Chris
aren't let in anywhere cuz we're 20 so
we're just walking around having fun
they're getting their drinks we're
observing that's about it we're having a
good time I can't believe I'm walking
the Las Vegas Strip I was walking in
this Las Vegas trip when I was 14 years
old right here's the the picture to
prove it I'll put the picture in there
it was a lot more different when I was
that age than it is right now and I
can't believe how far we've come in
YouTube and how far Justin has come
playing poker out here it's crazy to
think 5 years ago how different the
position
was once you get that kid talking he
doesn't shut up all day all night he
good
[Music]
want are the drinks in the fridge look
me and Matt didn't even know we had a
fridge in here until last night what
would you like I want a
Coke
nice all right take those socks off and
really feel the slippers no look at me
I'm I'm barefooting these I did that I
did have it like that and then I was
like I'm not taking my socks off to then
put the slippers like you know what I
mean yeah it was too much I don't know
that kind of just came oh that's the
that's the ters that's the breakfast
potatoes yes it's one order of of
breakfast potatoes we should sit sit
closer to me Matt I was sitting in front
of the waffle on no you have to sit in
front of the plate
oh oh wow they did like they like plated
this yes they did you think I did that
they came in here with the whole thing
and they open the
lids how do you feel this this is pretty
insane all right let's share two pieces
two
pieces I don't like tomato so this is
getting to plop off yep breakfast
sausage or breakfast potatoes we'll do
this hold
on there we go [ __ ] one and a half each
right
yeah hold on hold on Chris yeah I can't
get this what is that the mashed
potatoes yes half
oh I love potatoes half come on now took
the small half that's the way I roll and
I'm taking the Big Slice all right
should we recap our night absolutely we
should what do we do we went to like
four different casinos randomly and then
we just like walked around we tried to
find a place where we could we could go
sit and me and Chris could chill with
them while they drank but it was near
impossible
because we're not 21 we're not on it was
just like very difficult yeah so we went
to like some convenience store and they
bought a bunch of high noons this
alcoholic beverage and they all came
back to our room and they just all had a
good time me Matt and Justin Justin
spent the night with us last night and
it's so weird like being in Vegas with
Justin cuz we used to visit Justin when
we were like like freshman and
sophomores in high school and we would
visit him on his poker trips to Vegas
and this time like with us being
full-blown YouTubers he obviously had a
very successful full win last night it
just was like really like it's just
crazy how different this time was
compared to the last times true dude you
want to know what I was really impressed
by what whenever I'm at like a high
floor in a hotel I'm like oh the water
pressure to the shower is going to be
super weak dude I felt like I was in the
rainforest it was beautiful like it was
like warm uh hardcore water almost
instantly I was like that's hard for a
hotel to achieve felt very nice I was
impressed yeah I can't believe the room
we're in this is like ridiculous this
will forever be the fanciest I can't
believe we're both in Rogues in ordered
room service yeah like who who are we
right now that's what I did for the
first time ever today what I used a
bedan there no you didn't no you didn't
no you [ __ ] did not tell me
everything about it how it go not to get
super like yeah no that's fine in detail
but we're you know we're normally uh wet
wipe users yes we we love dude wipes of
course dude wipes were in the other
bathroom I was in there with just toilet
paper like you want know what I'm going
to [ __ ] around no you're not IIT there
was like a iwe no you didn't I swear to
God I didn't even know there was one in
there dude crazy okay yeah I hit like
like medium soft or like low soft
something like I wanted to be timid for
my first time you're not going to
[ __ ] put it on power washer at the
first go dude I'd be scared that super
warm and I was like this I was like like
I was actually genuinely like in shock
wow yeah I would be scared like if I
stand up it would just shoot out of the
toilet oh
definitely really yeah so you got to
like stay there you got to try it I'm
not trying try before we leave there's a
stop button that stops right away
really air dryer I hit no it's
not here you're making [ __ ]
up I dry it like comes in it was like sh
you're lying crazy mm-m I swear to God
Matt okay it was crazy it's literally
crazy I can't believe it yep you should
definitely try it so would you do it
again I
would on so you would right you feel
like wa wait what oh there's no NS no
look it these waffles are like big and
these ones are like like look there's 1
2 3 4 5 6 7 eight holes in that one and
there's 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 holes
in this one kid you're making [ __ ] up
again no I'm not look at the difference
oh yeah well maybe we I have your other
half maybe I don't know if that's like a
if that's a plating if that's like a PL
but here's here's the other question
that I had yeah do you feel like that
experience oh is look at this I love
little spoons just to get some butter is
equal to or less
than your usual experience like do you
think that will outweigh I did feel a
little like iffy about it m but I think
if it was like a regular
motion for me I could get up and walk
about my day just
fine okay yeah definitely something that
would need so like it it could it could
become the daily occurrence 100% yeah
but the thing is I really think that the
world needs to invest in higher class
and fancier toilets in public restrooms
and just more public restrooms MH
everywhere cuz I feel like some of the
most uncomforting feeling is like having
to use a bathroom like somewhere super
public mhm the ladies get it all figured
out oh yeah with all the Stalls get rid
of urals guys can pee in toilets why do
we
got seven rows just piss yeah you're
right make that four extra stalls you
got to walk into a stall to pee your
[ __ ] figure it out this is unbelievable
you got have to Waffle really yeah cuz I
feel like part of it's like a walk of
shame walking to the walk to the stall
in public especially when you can see in
the stall like through the crack yeah I
hate it tonight we're going to go to
Power slap
yep the the reason why we're here
actually is the power slap event they
got they put us on to everything that's
why we're in the room we in everything
is because of them so shout out power
slot it was just very convenient timing
that Justin also was placed at a final
table in his poker game the day and like
the LA flight to Vegas is nothing it's
literally like 30 minutes yeah so if
Justin was playing at a final table in
Vegas I would fly out here to support
him anyway for sure it just happens to
be it was like outstand standing timing
yeah it was awesome all right guys we're
in the elevator going down to the lobby
it's power slap day boom we're about to
go meet up with Justin Justin just got
here hate that that's at like the 83rd
floor too it's making all that noise is
going to be right here going to the
event and then you'll see our reactions
to people getting smacked across the
[ __ ] SL is the whole reason we're
here man you got to get hyp I'm going to
smack the first person I see out yeah
okay imagine like a receptionist at the
hotel
J what up buddy what up up what's going
on we're going to the power slap we have
to find the the north elevator Meemo
knows
where all right everyone we got Justin
and we will see you at the event excited
awesome thank you allow to get fre free
food and drinks all night wow SS good
dial in perfect there you are awesome
and you can take a
shirt take one take a shirt all right
[ __ ] it I'll take a shirt maybe Nick
wants one all right locked in locked in
let's do this that way this way awesome
we're going this way free t-shirts free
food and drinks all night we're vibing
let's do this no problem I feel I feel
way too important right now love it
though this is great
wow how many
knockouts it over under yeah over under
on Knockouts I feel like how many matchs
are I think there's like I think there's
like six matchups I think we got one the
overun has to be two there's definitely
at least two Knockouts has to be two so
you can take the under okay how many
times do they slap each other I think
three I think two works yeah three
rounds and you have 60 seconds after the
slap to recover from it I think two
Knockouts two Knockouts I'm I'm could
you could you recover from a big slap in
60 seconds [ __ ] no no guy just out like
a
light he's ready to go it's about to get
real they're getting the Hawaiian Hitman
he's going to [ __ ] saw some smack
it's a crazy Hawaiian in the Hawaiian
Hitman you got to love it's a crazy
Hawaiian and the Hawaiian Hitman are
brothers there two of them slap the dog
one's going out now the one's going out
next the crazy Hawaiian versus Ben
hen this match is three rounds in the
power slap super heavyweight division
wow he ate that [ __ ] holy
[ __ ] don't kill
[Music]
him
oh oh my
god
[Applause]
wow he's eating them he doesn't even
he's fine it's like he just woke up like
he's totally okay okay he's Stone Cold
this is crazy
one that was a bad that was a bad one I
don't know what that was what was that
one
[Applause]
about he would just smack you out of the
[ __ ] Arena guys 100,000 likes and I'm
doing it you just smacked you out of the
[ __ ] Fountain Blue buddy right out of
the
you'd be back you'd be back you'd be
back in your Delta youd wake up at the
with a [ __ ] back in your Delta plane
heading back to [ __ ]
LX oh she say she's going to cry she got
shook wow she she she's shaking
up oh she sh referee good slap Prett
good wow shaking up off the first slap
is not a good sign God you hate to see
that oh I feel bad she actually going
like cry
D oh she's CH yeah she's I don't know if
she can hit
though St
everything all neck all neck she didn't
like that one all
neck what she turned into a fist that's
a foul not allow did she really yeah
that's why she was mad okay oh little
foul not looking good here oh yeah TR
that needs a knock up if I see a knock
out today I'm going to freak out dude
dude if I whole place go crazy it's
going to be
nuts what's this guy I don't know he's
got a [ __ ] he's got a movie theater emo
this is what you need yeah look at this
guy look at record his camera look how
big it is dude's got a movie theater
camera got to attach to his back up who
knows what's going on take off it's
actually insane
oh she's not dud she's about to get
rocked on three she wants
three
one
two three oh that was nothing kind of
Dusty that was nothing this ref takes it
serious dude the girl like she was like
nothing like it looked like like tears
in her eyes she's like yeah cuz you're
getting the tears smacked out of you you
you're not actually feeling that emotion
you know yeah you're
right I like her coach she's got to
coach over here on the Seline dude they
both they both clubs so now it's even
playing oh it's fair game dude next time
we come here I'm going to like read up
on the rules and I'm going to come like
as a pro I'm like oh of course she
clubbed like you TR R yeah
absolutely clearly clubbing clearly
clubbing you fouled this that was a semi
Flinch like deductive Point
whatever oh she's loading up oh my
wait what was that foul what was that
what was that foul she hit her with her
cor
[Music]
elbow what a terrible hit slapping the
back of her neck terrible shot did you
forget where she was one two here it
is his hand for on his face
what yeah that's the most shaking up
someone's been getting
absolute what
ising when someone gets a foul they get
longer recovery time but they're about
to go again this dude in the blue is on
fire right on three two
dude is hold hand Fair blow Fair blow
blow Fair blow mat wait we have an
incoming caller yeah incoming caller on
the phone Nick watch this dude there
it's it's about to be is Nick Frozen or
is he just standing like he's stuck like
that hold on hold on we're at
it oh [ __ ] here it comes right on two
uhoh right on Two on Two on Two two
oh
oh they don't like the
call they don't like the call at all bad
call oh this is brutal oh there should
be clean up
crew I would love an elderly matchup how
sick would that be like a
seven-year-old invite and do this there
should be like an elderly match up and
it's like just two old [ __ ] going after
he's not going to like it one bit he
hates it oh the cut man he's the he's
legit cut
man the dude he has a shirt that says
the cut man and he helps out with the
cuts no no no he's good we're
recovered why is he get another one he
flinched no two for flinching dud that
that wasn't a Flinch dude oh he flinched
again did he not I think he just
flinched again fairow that was more of a
Flinch than the other one that one was
more Flinch than the first
Flinch
oh he's right out he can't get up oh my
God I told you oh my
God he's done he's
wobbling oh my God sh off shirt off get
this guy
dude he got his shirt
on he he deserves it absolutely deserves
it get the
[Applause]
replay oh my god wow his mouth got
rearranged his teeth he needs to go to
the dentist you see the blood come out
oh my God triplet bro that's my other
one you a trip oh [ __ ] oh wait God
damn Y at the same
time 2 minutes
apart 2 minutes apart bro when's our
match up we're going to hey hold on
y'all both single huh y both single so
y'all be hitting the same girls on an
accident never no no oh wow bro we got a
match up power SL me vers you oh me and
you yeah who's winning me and him me and
you yeah he got the beard hey you got
the beard for protection so you're good
I think I'm the favor in the look I got
to arm vle you before I do I think I'm
done I beat you and they here [ __ ]
around and beat me exactly oh my God
this is insane
bro all right what up Matt Matt this guy
in the gray highest knockout rate in the
whole thing no yeah we're about to
witness something big I
[Applause]
hope oh Flinch that was a
Flinch that was a Flinch for
[Applause]
[Music]
sure oh
[Applause]
oh
you he's good he's good no he's not oh
my god oh my
god dude he's just a
[Applause]
CRA dumpling oh [ __ ] dumpling's on first
shout out dumpling I see this dude on my
[ __ ] phone all the time he's just
smacking the [ __ ] out of people insane
it's me nervous I would never I would
never be able to run it back like if I
was a slap boxer if I was did this [ __ ]
I'd do like one round I'm never doing it
again dude I get nervous and I'm not
even like getting remotely close
to off
of oh my
God lights out lights out he's out he's
[Applause]
out he's absolutely out one [ __ ] hit
one out oh my God oh my God we got a one
holy we got a one hitter quitter
on SLAP look at
him he he doesn't know where he is no
idea what
IDE that's it the dude didn't even get
smacked look look look
[Music]
look that was the fast that was the
craziest [ __ ] I've ever seen he doesn't
know what planet he's on he's still on
the ground
that dude's still on the ground can't
believe this ladies and
[Music]
gentlemen one one
and did you see it yeah watch
it Wow way to go that's that's why the
coin toss the coin toss matters matters
this guy's still on the ground he's
still on the ground he's like done he
doesn't know where he is this dude flew
from Russia to smack somebody for 10
seconds playing him out is he going to
get up oh he's up okay he's up he's in a
chair I feel the cut man working on him
huh the cut man working on him yeah get
the cut man to that guy right now Lefty
Lefty Lefty watch out on three she
said one oh this girl Stone Cold
[Applause]
two she said thank you no way she said
thank you she said thank you she said
thank you oh my God I can't
no way she said Thank you thank you no
[ __ ] I swear to God no way she said
thank you
100% she did oh she's already back oh
she doesn't give a [ __ ] Jay she did say
thank you I know she did I know she did
can't believe
it one and done one and done Justin's
predicting a knockout oh oh she ate it
that was nothing
that was
nothing
one two here it
is
[Applause]
oh oh she's good she's
good oh my God she's dizzy take the full
minute of recovery she's dizzy
absolutely relax clean she's done one
D someone goes night
night
oh she can't get up get
up at least hit her with one more she's
good lock in eat it
again hey just is dust she's hungry give
it to her she wants to [ __ ] smack the
face this does she doesn't knock her out
she wins done walk off
see you
[Applause]
later she said go figure it
out mouth guard W mouth guard mouth
guard she's on her mouth guard the kid
with the red hair is
[Applause]
[Music]
disgusting oh he's talking [ __ ]
[Applause]
oh chalky
mouth oh my god dude that was the
firstect a mouth full of chalk you just
hate to
see looks like he put white lipstick on
him oh
oh oh my god oh
he's dizzy
Justin he's good he's good he's good
he's back in it he's back just hurry up
what are you reading kab I don't know
I'm opening books I'm [ __ ] unfolding
books here let's see it there are like
balls that's what I'm
reading this about balls just he reads
it's about every ball Chris goes what
are you reading I got go not too sure
I'm just kind of unfolding books here
and I look at it and I go huh
balls that's what I'm reading about you
guys were like eight years old Justin
tell Matt what you just did I didn't
well I didn't do it I asked Chris I I
went to take a piss I said like said
Chris have we ever taken up on the
amenities of the toilet have we ever
have we ever do did you did he tell you
about this thing today did you do it
have you done it no I'm never watching
it are you scared to do it no I think
there's a couple of things that we can
keep oldfashioned that being one of them
you know what you want to do it don't
you talking about I think we should do I
think Matt should do it like up a day in
general like are we are we taking it
into the toilet hands [ __ ]
no I will leave it right here you know
I'm good oh it freaks me out but it was
fine for you man you should do it hello
everyone we're back with cheeseburgers
and french fries we're at our house it's
good to be back yeah when we come back
there's like we got popcorn popcorn
funion the bowl look at all this [ __ ] A
Sni A Snickers bar une what is he doing
une is that a word [ __ ] everywhere but
me and Chris are going to eat this in
and out and then chill out and then when
we should play a game how many packages
did Nick get while we were gone for 3
days well there was one on the stairs
when I walked in one is this him
oh no it's stuff for memo it's film
stuff oh camera stuff okay that he has a
valid excuse I just looked in my
room oh my God I got a big box I don't
know what this is is it a gift
from oh it's a gift I'm proud of you
bro we're going to have to open that one
word play joke word play joke hello
everybody my minions my we're stealing
the moon
today God if you don't know what I'm
talking about that was a reference to
Despicable Me speaking of Despicable Me
4 came
out and they got me m and Chris this big
box who's your Daddy give me an
KNE
scapp God you're insane what if a minion
jumps out and attacks us oh my God wait
what if we get a minion yeah that's what
I'm saying what if we open it and it's a
minion look at the line i
c oh my [ __ ]
God only in
theaters I used to think when I was a
kid that when I said only in theaters
I'd never be able to see the movie If I
didn't go to the theater like I used to
be like no CU I couldn't go there bro
what do you think is like the history or
the pointedness between like oneeyed
minion and two eyes minion do you think
it's like in their DNA um what a twoed
minion and a Oney minion like Nick that
this is too much another Fork gun
yes maybe I move the other stuff in the
way yeah okay wait I need that bucket
hat give me
that all the minion fun what is this can
you take your F gun and go play and get
away from me no it's a real
blast these are nail
polishes I think I'm good no you should
do it sorry sorry you would look cute in
these I love to see you with these on
just look at you like touch stuff ASMR
with Matt The Perfect manicure I'm
throwing these on whoa is that a Lego
set no way I almost bought this at the
store the other day oh my God we have to
do it that's so Me minion let's do it
right now that's Me minion and that no
that's Me minion the popsicle and the
what are you saying that's Me minion I
saw the Hat that's me for sure no this
is Nick with the microphone and the
pointed
head that's
Nick what's a box bag oh my God it's a
punching
sack strong lungs I might pass out when
I was a kid I blew up an entire pool
floating with my mouth and there was a
pump for it like it was like the [ __ ]
big like 6 feet on how am I supposed to
blow this get a breath get a breath get
a breath this is fun for like the the
summer the the pool party with the kids
you know you thank King Bob thanks King
Bob don't I to like break it open Nick
you're not gluing Minion nails to
anybody here so put that [ __ ] away yes I
am give me your thumb nope come on I'll
just do one minion you're pinky you're
pinky look no look not with the real
nail glut can be stuck forever no this
is semi-permanent I don't care
semi-permanent means like 2 weeks you're
not gluing this on to me by the way yeah
this is cute yeah not happening come on
nope it's not permanent like I don't I
know it's not Perman I know I'm not
going to die with the minion nail on
Nick I know that I'm just saying I'm not
putting it on for like a week girls have
to like bite their nails off after they
do this it's not going to last a week
just give me your [ __ ] finger no I'm
not give your finger nope I refuse for
the Vlog you won't put a minion nail on
I'm not having a minion nail for over a
week and why are we YouTubers if we
don't take risks if we don't I would if
I didn't have my nails painted if I
didn't already have [ __ ] on my nail I
would I'll do it right now all right
it's not permanent I don't know why
you're
tripping the the minion thany come on
Chris let's match I'm not putting that
on it's not permanent I can peel it off
do it
yep you have it it's stuck for like a
week now not true yeah it is no this
will come off with acetone no it won't
Nick oh my God I told you that's why I'm
not letting you do it to
me I told you like what do you expect
you get anything off of the pair of
pliers it won't come off yeah go ahead
and just wash it off right
he won't come off yeah you have Minion
nails for at least a week is that glue
on the table Nick yeah maybe get that
off clean your mess you did the mess you
make the clean how do I get this off of
me you did the mess you make the
clean and that's a quote how do I get
this off of
me put the [ __ ] nail I'm trying to
read how to
get yes this is so hype keep
going my
God now that is RZ
[Music]
a