hey guys welcome back stop it stop it um
we did not film a proper intro to this
video but we went to we went on a road
trip we went to our first wedding and
our first fashion show and we went to
Europe for the first time so this Vlog
is what we've been doing for the past
like 3 weeks so 2025 essentially let me
try this 40 short is that what you got
on too yeah this is definitely my size
let me try this
on I could just be like hello everyone
here at the party you look good man feel
like girls what do you think I can need
a bigger one though
reallyy what do you think I don't know
Chris I lowkey have pants just like
these already so then don't get them no
cuz I got to get the exact match oh yeah
yeah Matt you like this song love it
really are
you wait Chris I got to see
you got the shoes too he got the shoes
on too loners Chris wait do we
match those pants Oh Nick you look
spiffy crazy head to toe you look spiffy
stupid though Chris looks dumb cuz he
has a baseball hat on but I like it this
jacket doesn't seem too long for these
pants no not at all no I'm just
imagining that I'd also have like dress
shoes and like are these pants tight on
me he kind of so here where's my main
man no no that's what I was saying so
they they come on F
come around the corner over so they're
unfinished so if you notice there's
no Just sh up when you go to the
tailor there you go and this Jack
doesn't seem too long for these pants no
okay yeah that fit this is a regular fit
okay so it's going to have like that
length got it that's your Vibe you're a
regular guy you know regular fit guy
okay cool good to know Nick do you want
to you want to take a picture so you
yeah I'm I'm I'm recording for the
Taylor our mom's going to want to see it
as well too so she definitely is all
right y'all Chris is going home with Sam
we just ate we me and Chris got our
suits online cuz they didn't have our
suit size in the store Nick got his we
still have to go get dress shirts and
ties and stuff like that and whatnot but
overall a very ex ex uh what's it called
successful successful
uh trip trip and the guy there was super
nice and super helpful super helpful
coolest dude ever see you at
home in the Royal Roy
truck Nick where'd you go are you using
the potty run out no Chris Chris park
the
car oh my God look at this what if I
killed a my first road trip on your
first road trip oh yeah this is my first
road trip I thought you meant the first
road kill was like a Poss like I thought
I was just confused on why you were
keeping stats can I get seven impossible
I can't do the joking I'm fing oh one
second okay yeah sorry no
problem oh one second okay I want a
shroom and swiss patty melt Nick so
Chris you want Matt you want two plain
cheeseburgers Nate you want two plain
cheeseburgers with Pickles Chris you
want one plain cheeseburger and you all
want french fries Chris you want a Dr
Pepper Nathan you want root beer mattt
you don't want a soda they have churo
fries Nick instead of like chicken fries
care so it's just a churro I guess so
I was the night and shining armor in
your can you shut your gay mouth please
Nick don't call me that with your gay
mouth before I kiss you in that gay
mouth let me get five Whoppers and five
more Whoppers I actually want the fiery
Royal crispy you're not funny you know
what I actually got before for the Royal
crispy no like a a chicken parm thing in
here before yeah that's what the Royal
Krispy is no it's not oh they might not
have it no I think it's a royal Krispy
wrap deal where you can get two
sandwiches for like cheap and then
that'll be all thank
you bless you can you not touch like my
keys and stuff and my legs I want to
touch more than that okay wow I'm a new
driver I want my meal this is like my
third drive-thru everever isn't that a
rare
stat yeah it's only going to go
up unless I die tonight this is like the
biggest drink I've ever seen like holy
[ __ ] it doesn't even fit in the cup
holder like a mega
pint remember when Nick threw that Wing
soop drink at the window yes I'm just a
freak
yeah I want it bad okay there's nothing
here so we're starting from Ground Zero
LEL one no food in the house there we go
all we need to think of is what we're
eating tonight and then we're leaving
tomorrow so we're leaving tomorrow yeah
Saturday already is breakfast lunch and
like maybe dinner depending how late we
leave so literally like three meals okay
okay sing Oh my God oh my God look look
look Chris stop stop stop I think we
should get like powdered Donuts or
something cuz you guys like those and
then we should get milk and cereal yeah
yes and then T tonight are we going to
make pasta I'm down to make pasta sauce
I want mac and cheese we can make you
can get mac and cheese eat it tomorrow
if we don't eat it today and that's
really it yeah have
butter sweet orange
marmalade please this pattern is like
the vibe the Smuckers the goober you're
a CER you need should we get
condoms what is wrong with with you kid
why you hit
me anyone want
juice I love ju lemonade get a
lemonade lemonade come drink it Nate
dude you're
sick you want some lemonade put it down
okay do you guys want any like ice cream
or something ice cream oh look oh we can
get those popsicles we like let's go
unfrosted strawberry that's the disg
thing ever get out fruit Loops rainbow
Sher looks horrible and it's not even
correct it's like circular what's the
point cools your mouth
awful what Y what they do to my
boys oh my God I remember the old
cinnamon like it was yesterday vaton and
vodka sauce and then do you want to get
a different pasta shape and I want cream
sauce no I'm kidding Nate will you eat
this and if you won't that's fine we can
get something El no do you know I [ __ ]
with that I'm also
you guys like Tony right yeah
okay oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my kids losing it over apple cider I
thought it wasn't the time of year
anymore jeez P am I a man or am I a
muppet it's a good question for
you oh this is Nick this is actually
like the intro to like your documentary
like your movie The Scene go hold on
yes that's it that's the money
shot baby can we watch you get dressed
sure I'm already doing
[Laughter]
it you're so funny that tie doesn't read
Brown on the Vlog but it's a nice brown
color I just saw you like zip your thing
like on the camera like in the mirror
cuz that's what I was doing right just
like he's so shocked that he's like
recording what's on video right now
Chris has made he can't believe he's
living this Chris has made horrible
decision since he woke up this
morning de you guys look like two
vampires like this is what you look like
30 seconds
ago how in Japan I love it do you want
to wear it yeah put it on is it really
expensive though no I had it love how
she wouldn't take it off like Mom is
what I I would be extra careful I feel
like I'm going to the prom with Nick am
I ever going to get in the Vlog when do
I show off my suit here let's see should
I feel like if I if I wanted to I could
rip these pants tonight I did the same
thing earlier I feel completely immobile
I said I'm ripping the shoulders off of
this thing soon yeah if I really wanted
to like bust the crazy move these pants
would split in two dud in half right
right on the GU it is to tell the time
no it's not to tell what time it is it's
to let everyone else know what time it
is you get it it's time it's time it's
our time it's like it's like it's like
it's our time oh oh it's our time yay
we're going out yay what is this ugly
dude doing
here like what the [ __ ] is this you need
to stop yeah I'm going sure run I'm
going to lose my mind look at the snow
mom do you have any snow songs in Your
Arsenal that we can sing she's got
plenty let I got but
Frosty no no you got to
Goa is hey
Matt what do you
[Music]
think M Matt and Chris are headed to
Milan Italy it is not my first time out
of the country but Matt and Chris have
never left the country
before all thanks to Prada we're going
so Shadow Prada we are going to our
first fashion show ever and no before
you ask we are not walking in it but we
are going to go observe have a blast
Vlog our entire trip to Italy and we are
going to bring you guys with us for this
entire trip and I'm so excited but we'll
see you guys we're going to bring you
with this whole trip so see you at the
airport
probably like
gross hey guys we're at Boston Logan
we're
boarding the
[Music]
plane back up where in the
thing pull the handle I'm going to put
you in first class I'm watching your The
Joker I didn't even see your camera like
in my face and that's really like
frightening to me you had that excited
for the flight get off me with that 5x
[ __ ] look at my seat dude I can
like where's my um where your where you
going to put your shoes I wonder if
they're going to take off using the
tarmac or going your forehead I going to
say some dumb sh Nick's editing like a
good boy never St good boy edit that
video I I want to play hide I want to
play hide and seek like playing hide and
why' you stop recording I don't know cuz
you're recording me
telling no one walked
by you like a
[Applause]
raccoon the only thing that's even equal
to Pepsi in my eyes did you put that in
there yourself the lime yeah no Matt God
came down and did it for me of course I
put it in there myself I don't know I
just didn't think that was like a you
maneuver I had at the other night we
went out to E and who are you fooling it
in one of those small cans go back up
there and grab two more right now thank
you guys so much thank you thank
you I
love why is this not a us thing imagine
car videos but we put the camera like in
the middle it's a
conversation they do this in
La like why can't they do this
everywhere ask driver it's like the
coolest thing ever literally the coolest
thing
ever did have the real camera so I don't
have to Vlog on my phone anymore my
backpack wait Matt you have a letter
this is Matt's room he's in a different
room me and Chris are staying in a cuz
I'm special you are can you fix your
hair my hair's messed up cuz I had a
hood on the plane I'm not trying let me
show you guys all the things my room
first of all gorgeous yeah really nice
room second of all Matthew sto there's a
letter here there's a letter for me and
Chris in the other room fruit chocolate
you can click these buttons and it just
shuts the blinds and it just
who and you can control like most of the
lights what if I turn around and my nose
was gushing blood like 11 like I did it
okay can you guys stop [ __ ] with my
[ __ ] please Chris Chris I'm going to
write you if you're going to make a fool
of yourself do it in your own room
please I'm going to write you need a
note I don't want a note just tell I'm
right here say it out loud please okay
it was for later but whatever a note for
later yeah like that's the whole point
want do open
it these are so nice so nice these are
so nice I tried these on in the store a
they they saw you try them on in the
store you look at
these oh my God these are so fire those
are ni nice shout out the Prada family
for real thank you everyone all right
guys well we're so happy to be here see
you soon fig chocolate I don't know the
other at the other room door I'm sorry I
have to like this is just me this is
cyber I've already yelled at Matt 100
times he goes like this scans the thing
goes Nick Nick and he's going that that
dead ass and he's doing that for 10
minutes I go Matt it's a push door and
he was trying for 5 minutes and never
thought to push it I don't know why I
didn't it can we talk about how fragrant
it is in here and how amazing it smells
smells like a rich grandmother this is
where the real party starts me and Nick
okay Chris let's try our
chocolates good um not to be weird this
is like the most creamy chocolate I've
ever had that's nice oh wow this is like
mov Are We Stand
Together can we go down there we have to
figure it out I'd love to go down there
it's really gorgeous I feel like
everybody in Italy are babies if they
think it's cold it's a very nice it's
not that cold at all not at all it's
very comfortable yellow shoes they know
that I'm gay should I do a grand
reveal I'm going to feel the
color
M black okay dude oh my God I seriously
didn't look I swear to God there's a
good guess from the see-through black
bag I I seriously I seriously didn't
even know you're so weird no when I said
like you love lying no I no I swear to
God I hate lying I'm serious I guess
that Chris obviously you're looking
through your see- through black bag to
see more black it's going to be black oh
my God these are so nice thank you Prada
they know me so
[Music]
well I
got I'm not going to embarrass myself
and try to say the name of this building
me and Chris are enjoying it from far
off I like that I really like that lean
look at this guy in the bike onehanded
oh my God oneand biker he's a natural
that man is a stone cold killer on the
bicycle how are you feeling today I feel
good man guys we just went out to eat
yeah and we literally were all falling
asleep at the table no we're all so
tired cuz we've all been up for like
over 24 hours so we're all like just
like this like fading away literally I
was almost KO at the dinner table
tonight I was literally scoop the only
thing that kept me alive was the ice
cream at the end of it not hold you so
true W wa looks like she got ET in the
front of that bike oh here here's one W
wo whoa whoa whoa right at
us I really wanted to like stick my ass
out not that tire over Dude waa I feel
like I need a
bike might just need
one dude Nick some guy tried to get get
me to buy roses is for like Laura he saw
me and Laura and he like get her Rose
like this is my manager you didn't get
her one no no and then he she was like
taking a photo with both hands and he
like rested it over her arms I was like
give me money for this we're like
no that's we should go ask him for a
rose and steal it how
crazy mat just said he was talking about
how you were like doing back flips at
dinner back flips at dinner I was
falling asleep eating my meal all right
let's
go where are the gay Italian
men I don't know dude where are they
all okay post your address and room
number and maybe they'll all
come
what hold on should we say good night
Nick like they do in the books I don't
really I don't read really and I don't
think I'll do it I'll do it close your
head or close your eyes and bow your
head I'm not doing that good night Italy
good night Moon good night
Prada good night good night Prada good
night good night pasta airport I'm going
to my am I going to bed yeah I am like
so delusional say good night me cuz I'm
leaving good night Matt thank you bye no
no no what okay end of day one I had I
was trying my very hardest to stay awake
I had half a Red Bull in like 30 Cokes
today trying to like boost the energy 30
Cokes no I'm not even exaggerating I
think I had I had a hot chocolate on the
plane and then I had like you had like
four mini Cokes in London during The
Layover and then I had two at dinner now
two at dinner I think I'm at 7 today you
just said you had dinner twice so you're
clearly tired I don't know good
morning good morning get that camera out
of my face good morning get out of here
good
morning I still can't believe how just
close we are to buildings when we're
driving anybody that it's
cold and they're not from Boston
Massachusetts i m that lady where right
there she got that black C going to
breakfast I picked the place with
immense amounts of pressure on hopefully
it being good I hate being the one to
pick I wanted I wanted to walk there's
only one person that hates it more and
it's you correct Nathan do Nathan do
wait I got you that bug's bunny statue
behind you mat is the coolest thing I've
ever seen what's the coolest thing youve
ever seen that statue
Matt record it Chris record
[Music]
it thank you does my heart immediately
go to this sweet treats tab no literally
but it's okay Matt had a Matt had a bad
night's sleep and he's a big baby and he
woke up in the middle of the night he
said he did this he did that he's been
[ __ ] he's been pissing he's been
bleeding out of his nose this morning
Matt blows his nose and he like he shows
Chris the tissue like oh God I just cuz
they whenever I say super
sou waffles are like my favorite thing
in the world need this this looks really
good e what is that chocolate chocolate
syrup dude thank you wow thank you thank
you so much thank you I hate Tik Tok
truly but it is a really crazy loss like
it's one of those Monumental things
aren't they so cute like they're like in
love I kind of want to be in love so I
can give this to someone yeah I always
think of that when I'm in like gift
shops I'm like I wish I could care I
just said to I said I wish I cared about
someone enough to buy them anything did
just say that off C low key No Cap yeah
look at this tea party they're having
definitely a major conversation like
what do you think the topic is hello
other rabbit and he's like I killed that
boy this guy looks like he killed some
they look like Mobsters making decisions
mobster rabbit he's like who look at him
he's happy I'm loving the red no they
look really cute that water actually to
that cafe and here's everything that we
got look at this triplet Chris Chris can
you take the lid off and give it to me
we already showed them in a little bit
but this is so cute they're so cute it's
Nick Matt and Nick Matt and Chris I
don't I don't want to be that one I got
I have no idea what I'm going to put in
this but I saw the owls and I was like
oh my God wait wait Nick got this one I
inspired Nick to get it I got the bunny
10 got the bunny one I don't know what
I'm going to put in mine I'm going to
put drugs in mine next time this for
Chris because he wouldn't buy it for
himself and I bought it for him because
I'm like you need to do nice things for
yourself and it bothered me that he saw
this and liked it wouldn't buy it for
himself I just don't like spending money
yeah but this is such a nice thing for
you and I just like picture I picture
when you get like I know you want to get
a new bed frame when your bed's all nice
you have a nice night thing he'll he'll
live so happily in there and you weren't
going to get him have so many cool stuff
in like he's so cute and and you get to
remember like oh it's from Italy I got
this it's like an ornament and I love
bunnies wow this I got this for myself
because I wasn't going to get it and I
was like I don't need that wait the
firefighters have peaked my interest
you're insane and then
I can you focus Nick I was going to I
wasn't going to buy this for myself and
then I saw the keychain strap and I was
like oh I'm throwing that on my bag so I
got this for
myself that's everything it says please
ring but I think we're good so pretty
this is like really is nice we do in the
jacket or is it like a little bit it's
got to be in here
okay I really like that actually one of
us should definitely own
this this is ugly but I kind of like it
cuz that's who I am Christopher
Christopher christop fur boots with a
fur hey first
left excuse me
everyone oh my God everything's falling
over my God have to find a sweet spot I
bought a jacket I'm wearing who let me
be cameraman bro I got a fuzzy jacket I
got I like it me you look like prim and
proper why am I proper cuz I'm Prim I
feel like I'd be goofy and You' be fancy
I need to put lip on
hello she was not talking to you yes
yeah we're about to experience real
Italian pizza we're getting a big
pepperoni pizza correct homemade is
everything but I'm like is that is
everything that's made not eventually
homemade and especially if you're in a
restaurant you can't really say homemade
cuz that's wrong my favorite songs keep
playing in places that I go okay I'm
coming back okay no
rush R uh any starter bua garlic bread
Pacha cheese garlic bread we at garlic
he loves garlic garlic or cheese garlic
what you like garlic that's it extra
parmesan cheese
slices yeah why not one fries one fries
in the middle one salad in need
though not s I'm okay with the okay
let's go with and can we do a big uh
pepperoni big diaa extra parmesan Cheesa
yes one big gabala with Parmesan
gentlemen oh that's for all of us that
our you share yes do you think that's
good thank you thank you great I feel
like maybe not enough food yeah I feel
like we let her down with how little be
ordered I think she was expecting you to
eat it alone Nick that makes me sick too
I was like I'll get garlic bread and the
baked pizza and she goes very cool right
look at C's hat Matt give me that she
had the hat and the coat and the bag and
the boots I snip by Le pants I want to
go to that gelato place after too the
gelato the G gelateria it's like
cafeteria for ice cream it's my business
you smiled a little too hard I don't
like not know I love that guy in the
green jacket over there yeah of course
you do he walked into the Vintage store
all right man all right
you're um what was I saying before you
rudely interrupted me holding gloves car
serial killer no one cares I care gloves
are normal in cold areas by the
way what was I going to say I don't like
this wearing a scarf though it's like
kind of like a turn off oh selfie STI
selfie stick in action wow all right how
would you guys rate your how would you
guys rate your first Italian pizza was
so no fire actually it was
phenomenal I love garlic bread oh my God
I just I killed about six of these
little piggies Mario and Luigi are from
here dude they might be around the
corner we should get gelato I [ __ ]
love garlic bread it might she's did you
hear her I it's on camera I don't have
to say another words you saw me you saw
what I thought I think it's crazy like
we're in the position to do this this
stuff together as triplets like who if
you told no seriously as like if you
told me a couple years ago that we would
be in Italy together I'd be like you're
lying what do you keep jumping for see
that's
up see that's how I am I didn't even
know you were recording and I'm jumping
at the
wall need to see what I saw I've seen
some girl talking about the craziest
[ __ ] about Matt and I almost blocked her
I'm like I just don't want to see this
you know yeah like it was like I like oh
was like dirty yeah tomorrow we're going
to the show just ordered room service
and we're going to get our hair
done
wa this is fire wow oh this is you right
here wow look at those three little
sausage links me Matt and Chris cute
that's your omelette but
rather obviously wa my God it's barely
on the table neck so put it up
more neck no I put that chair there for
myself we are here at the round table to
discuss the ban of Tik Tok and how it's
going to affect our career can I have
the Coca-Cola in your fridge mat sure
can I have the other why
[Music]
not we're watching r's Grace I'm in the
mirror this is
terrible well you don't have to like
whatever you look
good we just I just hang we finish going
to the fashion show let me just say what
an experience man I didn't think we were
going to have fans in Italy at all I
know and then we laughed and people were
screaming I looked behind me I was like
who the [ __ ] are you young who's the
where are the cool people com out bro I
think I've had 40 of these things yeah
wouldn't be shocked it's like a POV
you're eating as Chris right now okay we
had like a Fashion Stylist not Fashion
Stylist like a fashion like a
hairdresser and she was so sweet so nice
I talked to her for like two hours this
morning J has been a smashing success
yeah it's been so fun here I'll smash
you to success chip
chip they're not like babies all right
bye guys goodbye Nick and Chris's room
me and Nick have we you have to
understand right we were just in Boston
from Christmas Eve all the way
till today which is January
20th why are you waving your arm up and
down nothing okay that was weird from
Christmas Eve all the way to January
20th what are you doing nothing you can
see that reflection oh my God I'm like
stop raising your hand raise
your hey guys Matt's asleep we just
finished editing this video we hope you
really really enjoyed it I loved that it
was like Italy it was the wedding it was
like our little boy trip like it was
such like a yes it was a very intricate
video and I loved it I love when we make
a vlog cuz I'm going to be able to watch
this when I'm like 30 yeah we are back
in La we're safe because of the fires
it's still crazy but it's not nearly as
bad as when we weren't here which is
great um but obviously something to
think about we're going to go ham we
have so much coming we hope you enjoy
this week's Friday video and we will see
you guys next Friday of course so true I
don't know sorry sorry our Vlogs have
been all over the place we we I thought
this was a solid vog no it's a good Vlog
but we were just everywhere we were
literally in Boston for like a month
which is like we haven't done that since
we were like 19 years old so it was love
you all thank you so much for watching
and we'll see you next Friday y
[Music]