hello everyone we just edited the entire
2024 recap and we think it's amazing and
reflecting on all of these amazing
things we did this year and we can't
believe it and we appreciate all of you
guys that have been here since before
2024 all of you guys that have joined
this year and all of you guys that are
carrying over into the new year and we
hope that you have an amazing year and
we appreciate you guys so much thank you
for everything and enjoy we celebrated 6
million we celebrated seven million Nick
got his wisdom teeth out we went to the
zoo we so many fun things this year so
many achievements I'm really really
really happy like putting it together
and like looking back at everything is
like like like it's just crazy cuz
anytime we felt down about ourselves
this year it's like you look at
everything we've done and it's like oh
my God
there's launch this year too yes so many
crazy things um but thank you guys so
much and we will well I just hope you
enjoy and laugh a lot while you watch
this next two and a half hours cheers to
an amazing successful productive fun
entertaining loved healthy
2025 yes see you guys next Friday at
5:30 be safe be yourself be
easy stay awesome and the rest is
barbecue that's kind of
rude back up a little
bit a lot the ca camera can't even see
you at this point you're just locking
eyes on me it's freaking me out I just
love you Nick I'm enchanted by
you here goes the sties here they
go oh my God can you take those yellow
glasses off so I can see your big blue
eyes take that hat off and give the
world the void of that
forehead I know isn't going to happen so
yes did you just blow your nose and your
hands I blew up I blew I sucked up you
blew up
yeah that wasn't even
funny wasn't even
funny hey blew up hey I blew up Melody
pops little suies let's do the little
suies I got us each one they're only a
dollar each if we like them buy them
that's a lot of money that's a lot the
dollar lollipop wait is it a
whistle that just came out of the sucker
wow
wow that's
good you're
good what is this like to extend it just
like you can really push it back oh
maybe it's a slide
whistle of course [ __ ] this
maybe it's a slide whistle first thought
that would be the last thought I
had I'm never eating this it's a slide
whistle
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait what car
[ __ ] we got to
move
there it's like I
slipped oh this is [ __ ]
amazing if I woke up as one of you guys
I feel like I wouldn't know right away
until I like look in the mirror i' know
immediately no just cuz of how similar
we are you're an idiot I know if I woke
up as you Matt I'd be like wo why do I
have like Matt's tattoos what the [ __ ]
and then you wouldn't think I wouldn't
think I'm in your body okay like and
then I'd look in the mirror and be like
wait it's really me then I go like that
like that and I'd look and I'd be like
oh my God Nick do you have answer to
this question that makes sense I'm just
a little confused I don't think I'd feel
this way at all I kind of agree I think
I'd be shocked yeah I agree I
would I didn't even mean to hit you I
just like instinctively was like that
was me being like stop making this noise
like I tried to put my hand up or
something all right so what would you do
with if you were me a propeller hat I
like that nickname come on P put it on
oh that was Noble very curious look as
no Noble it's like very h define Noble
you define it no I didn't use it nothing
defines me I Define myself I make my own
destiny what would you do if you
realized your whole YouTube Carew was a
dream and you woke up um better go back
to bed
oh that's a good answer go back to sleep
mhm um I would probably well you could
say we're living the
dream good joke good joke good joke all
right let's each before we finish this
video like each of maybe like five
things we just love about Matt um I love
your your determination to get things
done when you want to your blue eyes
absolutely your silky soft beautiful
skin your nice hair your nice flopy
fluffy hair when you walk around that
cute little sheer night
gown get
it everyone pray for Nick he has a
stuffy nose pray for Nick he has a
stuffy nose I think I'll make it the
[ __ ] pray for neck what I'm totally
fine like everybody Nick has
allergies report to the media we need
you all to reach out Nick has allergies
report to all the tissue Brands make
sure they know good guys I'm going to do
one full day of updating the people on
Nick every move Nick just grabbed a
drink from the fridge Chris I think I'd
actually cut your arm off Nick why would
you do that so you can stop touching
your phone if you did that that's sayte
Nick just woke up in like a photo Nick's
allergies are not getting better and I'm
going to post it well guys sorry I was
clearly sick in this video I don't feel
good but it's okay The Show Must Go
On okay the greatest
show got David Blaine over here I feel
like I could sing a song in
here it's like a little Echo chamber as
I was cleaning my [ __ ] room I was
just um texting Nick and Matt and I
decided to dance like really really fast
and send them like a funny video of me
dancing and
um I literally got ahead cuz of it like
really bad cuz I was like moving around
and I was like I texted them I said one
of two things just happened I either
danced too hard or just got
Co yeah yeah yeah you
[Music]
make oh my God I just like two lights in
here there's not just one there's two
light bulbs y'all this thing of
cheeseburgers and french fries has been
on my floor for like 4 days in a row not
lying all right
y'all salt bur is being continued right
now first note I want to take if I ever
got called
a a boot
licker it's going down it's going down
immediately I'd be like Mr nuts and
bolts oh gross that be me freaky as [ __ ]
no it's not nut like you would be Mr
nuts and bolts like you're just weird no
i' and I'd be like handy like I'd be a
handy robot yeah I'm pretty sure you'd
be pretty handy with a name like nuts
I'd be like the Auto Body service robot
i' be the Matt shut the [ __ ] up you
screen I'd be the burger bot and I just
[Music]
get mat did you just hear Nick mat let's
repeat the same joke so many times Matt
did you just hear what Nick said his
name would be no I'd be the burger
bot okay dude and I'd just get everybody
whatever meal they want hey it's the
burger bot what's the word Burger bot we
need to trademark Burger bot no we need
to trademark Burger bot I wouldn't be
surprised if a couple years we go in a
[ __ ] fast food place and you get a
burger and the [ __ ] Burger brought to
you the burger bought is going to exist
and we need to just prepare for burer br
do you guys remember when we went to uh
oh my God salmon cat no CP CK CPK and
the [ __ ] little [ __ ] yes the robot
puppy came over and gave us our food it
was I thought it was going to bark who's
there salad salad l
[Laughter]
in 1 minute I already know which
question all right we got it CH all
right you're getting a two for one lucky
you when in your life were you the
happiest and when in your life were you
the saddest
I say so hard to say when in your life
were you the happiest cuz the true
answer is probably when I was like eight
or something oh my
god when I was like a little kid I was a
very happy little kid yeah like I loved
being a little kid y I loveed hang out
with Mom and doing with stuff with Mom
all the time like going to the zoo with
Mom or go shopping with Mom so probably
when I was eight but I'm
like no I'm so
upset oh my God yeah probably I was 8
years old a loaded
question
crying that's so crazy I instantly
started crying talking about being 8
years
old I did not accept I just got really
emotional cuz I really agreed with you
oh my God like I really just like felt
that was the first time I think that was
the first time I think emotion has ever
just like come up to me like that choked
me out I fully agree I BR I think it's
the vulnerable state of
it I'm literally right there with you
like it's you this is the first time I'm
like crying in content this is soar that
was a lot I lit like my ey that was that
was a lot my eyes started like watering
and [ __ ] like that was cuz I have like
baby photos in my head yeah like dude
Mom it's like funny but it's not you
know you're the cutest kid ever I know I
was adorable oh my god dude that's
crazy that was
shocking I wrote that question down
earlier
too oh
my oh my God so w dude I'm going to
leave the CERN triplets behind and join
the circus great it's a great little job
for you wait I'll tell you all about I'm
not even going to tell you guys what I
would do at the circus I'm just going to
pretend I'm I'm already there and I'm
putting on my show okay I already know
what you'd do I'm going to say or I have
an opinion on what I think you'd be
doing at the circus come on come all
welcome I can't have this video of me on
the internet I'm screaming I'm yelling
can't do that I just literally was going
to act a fool for another 30 seconds and
I thought digital footprint Nicholas Ser
what about in 5 years you're trying to
be taken more seriously and this video
comes up of you [ __ ] hooting and
hollering about what you're going to do
at the circus come one come all to the
Nick stolo show take your seats you're
going to want to sit right there it's
the best seat in the house I'm going to
get where where I want to go
there I'm going to put up my little ring
and I'm going to say I'm going to jump
through this ring right in front of you
you jump through that i' give you
billions just going to jump through this
ring okay no what this ring is on
fire and I'm going to light this ring of
Blaze
Blaze you're insane dude and I'm going
to head to the back of the room and you
may say Nick are you are you yeah thank
you don't hold it too far up I you know
they're going to say Nick are you going
to go to the back of the room and get
like an oil or a soap to through the
hole oh my
God I'm going to say no pass me the
gasoline just dip myself in gasoline on
fire yes right we need that element of
risk oh he has a talent he can jump
through a tiny ring yes but can he risk
it
all question so I'm gonna dump myself in
gasoline my hair is dripping I'm
covering gasoline and I'm going
Toom pop through the ring come out the
other side a blaze a blaze okay and then
they're going to have the the the there
should be a kitty pool that you got to
like land no sh I'm going to land in the
middle of a sand pit it's going to look
like it's the end of me everyone's going
be like no he's gone forever no do you
know what they're going to do when
everyone's worried about me what roll
out the tarps cover me in the blanket
I'm going to hit a button fall through
the Trap floor Underground follow the
Trap underground I'm underground now
these people don't know they're worried
about me oh should I come back up onto
the tarp and like at be like Oh I'm fine
everyone no you dropped down from the
ceiling no oh [ __ ] for 5 years that's
when we cue the elephants Matt they come
in run around Tiger's whole Show's going
on where did that guy go next show I do
the same thing ready really weird
sock those are my hands oh yeah that's a
nervous mat Moment Like This notice how
you haven't said someone oh Nick what
Chris Chris it's
Chris
Grandma yes I love grandma me too I miss
you Grandma that's a nervous mad hand is
like the craziest like this like you
were scared yeah it did look like a
nervous mad hand that's why I did it so
like bro you guys off you guys literally
were standing there not guessing me for
like 10 minutes to be fair I did say
that's a me hand immediately okay this
one is crazy
I don't even is I'm going to go with me
I'm going to go with me I'm going to go
with
Nick oh my God that's the that's the
monster from a quiet place he like runs
in like that oh God if that was in like
black and white that'd be like one of
those like unsettling moments on Tik Tok
that you see luckily for you what's up
Sneezy can you you f take a th
disgusting bug you doing get out get out
isue look at your allergies rub your
eyes a little bit can you do it dude I
can't even look at you it's making you
feel a little SC you ever just spank
your ice cream like I'm about to eat you
okay that's crazy that's
insane
Chris at your grown age he just airplane
himself at I've never seen somebody like
M I've never seen a 20-year-old man
sneeze with both hands by his side and
just go like that and sneeze yeah just
like out and about for anyone to enjoy
my name's Chris don't wear it out no
one's going to wear it
out not even remotely close what was
that what did I just Nick did you just
see that I need Adil wait we should have
like a boy Valentine's day trip this
hold on here's my thing no no hold the
[ __ ] okay this is my plan oh God I'm
so scared we all go somewhere cool that
has some nice things going on yeah
bowling bowling Adventure Trail zoo park
water slide whatever just something fun
and we all spend the night together as
boys and we do it for for Valentine's
Day for the boys like like that's how I
like just us
three I don't know I just want to spend
Valentine's Day with like
there's no girls out there that I'm like
that I don't have a valentine this year
you don't have a valentine this year you
don't have a valentine this year let's
just have a boy's Valentine
moment I wish there was a button right
here that erase the last 2 minutes and
just go Bo I hit it really fast I wish
there's a button right here that erased
the last 20 years of my life that's
good I just kidding take I wish I could
stick my eyes with toothpicks and eat
them off like a kebab what why come on
Chris it's weird no it's not weird just
call it a trip it's a trip Bros trip
sure it could be a Bros trip well it's
the same way girls have like gallentine
look you be my bro brotin is
crazy is insane bye
everyone holy [ __ ] look you would to be
my bro in time stop talking bro it's
like a dinosaur like bronchitis like all
right that's not a
dinosaur that's like an illness right o
oh look at the lap pool wao wait that's
a really cool deck that's a really cool
deck you sound like an observation like
a like a murder mystery sh I actually
really like that's a really cool deck
like the layout and design of that deck
is nice that pool is nice Definitely
probably a little Frosty right now
Chris do you want to sit
Chris do you want to sitp or
no do you want to sitp of what Nick it's
like
lemonade are you [ __ ] stupid want me
a pizzeria [ __ ] you forget about it come
on we're about to eat some nice Austin
Texas Pizza look at that building yeah
so we're eating pizza we've had barbecue
twice when we were filming with S mobe I
was like admiring their equipment they
had a nice light yeah they were do okay
um that's not weird oh my hands are cold
we've eaten barbecue twice we haven't
documented at all but we're at an
Italian place to bring it back to you
know the stern Yola shum buoy Roots
we're going to go eat pizza we're in
Austin Texas still only time you'll ever
catch me my lips trat I'm in the [ __ ]
Tundra right now and I don't have my
[ __ ]
yet I can't eat in here scent is high
Chris has eaten the whole thing they
don't call me meatball mat for a reason
all right for no reason yeah they
definitely call you it for a reason
that's what I'm saying
10 out of 10 ball 10 out of 10 ball mat
meatball
mat sace good amount of flavor no no no
I'd say eight out of
10 what a tricky little laugh that
was um I'd
say oh my
god
get I got to [ __ ] Wicked Witch of the
West rude it you late [ __ ] meatball
eight out of 10 cuz nothing can beat my
grandmother's rest in peace rest her
soul oh this is feeling just how
Grandma's balls
fell 10 is crazy that's all I'll say no
I was I was factoring every every detail
yeah but I'd agree 10 is insane you're
insane it's like a seven he's suing
little
Donuts I'm the toughest [ __ ] in
the
city oh my God I'm really embarrassed
yeah this is so
embarrassing D my car super
fast I can't take you seriously these
glasses I keep foret I have him on this
is so embarrassing what if he's like
trying to like impress his friend dude
if he's with a girl right now I hope
that she makes it home safe and never
goes to hang out with this [ __ ] idiot
again oh my God okay you're on a first
date right oh brother you're on a first
date scenario so Nick you get picked up
on a date and the guy has like a super
cool truck dude I already don't give a
[ __ ] okay me up in Santa SLE you could
tell me to take public transportation
you could pick me up at a Target cart
I'd be fine I'd be happy with anything
okay so you get picked up in a nice big
truck a super cool truck and he's like
he he goes into the parking lot you guys
are just talking blah blah blah you're
having a good night date's going well
right he says hey sugar lips you like my
big
truck oh my God shh you get you're on
timeout for the next minute no words
better leave that [ __ ] trap of yours
seriously no Nick the next minute if you
speak I'm punching you he goes like this
he doesn't he doesn't like direct the
fact that he's going to do it all right
sweet shut up you you're on timeout for
real Nick he just I'm actually setting a
timer you shut the [ __ ] up Nick he just
goes like this he just goes watch this
oh watch this is brutal shut
up Matt can I tell you my actual thing
yeah I'm screaming bloody murder as if
this [ __ ] is trying to kill me
scrolling down the window I'm going let
me
out let me out that's you asked that's
what I'm doing if I'm in a car and the
person's like look at this I'm going to
rev my engine drive you around like a
[ __ ] Maniac psychopath and annoy the
whole [ __ ] neighborhood and wake up
Auntie Sue down the street that's just
trying to go to bed cuz she has a
[ __ ] actual day job to hit tomorrow
morning you're like annoying the
neighborhood yeah shut the [ __ ] up I'm
genuinely doing that I'm screaming let
me out of this [ __ ] ass car bring me
home I'll walk I'll call the storks come
pick me up fly me home I'll do anything
to get out of I'll roll home I'll
somersault home literally get me into a
hill I'll barrel roll down I'm not going
home in your car I'd rather literally
step on glass and drag my feet
home
actually they're working on the Mammoth
I think okay undisclosed information
they're working on the woolly mammoth
it's unreleased no I think they're
unreleased it okay so the bathroom it's
in cry sleep right now or something this
tent this tent according to my map is oh
brother is tent number oh Joseph I see
him that's our guy get down there that
one's 1038 by the way any questions
before we uh continue
[Music]
on no questions no questions that was a
lot of excitement morning campers this
is your wakeup
call breakfast is served at 700 a.m.
please have your personal items packed
up you can leave those items right
inside your tent door as to avoid them
getting
wet good morning world good morning
friends we're going to get ready ready
for today yeah we just got wake up
called at the zoo literally we woke up
she's like good morning sound like me
starting a podcast she said good morning
campers and I instantly thought I was on
camera like no I was like hello
podcast good morning
campers lady say we unzip this we could
see an elephant don't unzip it I need to
change my underwear okay I'll zip it
back up dramatic [ __ ] move out of my way
oh my goodness get out of the way man
was at the zoo experiencing aggression
this morning no elepants it was no no
elephants I fell asleep pretty early no
it took me a while I lied he gave us
these bracelets
yesterday oh my God found out today I
can't sleep with them it's like one of
the sensory things I was like rubbing my
arm I I ripped it off in the middle of
the night I was like I was freeing
myself from shackles I ripped it off my
body I said
free me I think the first thing we do
today is like get real up close with an
animal let's find
out this kid's using a
[ __ ] finger to brush his teeth how
gross who we're going to Flame me for
that so or not Nick you got to do what
you got to do and you're
glamping
yes I woke up like this wait where'd you
get that cool shirt next trip.com no um
stting on clothing.com
wa it makes you really look cool and
your outfit fully I woke up like this
flowless I woke up like this flowless
okay dude I woke up all right all right
you're freaking everyone you keep making
me think that there's someone that
embarassing I'm recording you well cuz
you're saying all right all right like
as if like there's a crowd well it's
just like all right settle down let me
take you out go I can't believe we woke
at the [ __ ] zoo I thought I was in a
pychard like I woke up and I'm like no
way I'm actually with animals in the zoo
[Laughter]
today thank
you nice you're not real
breakfast what was that two Advil and a
yeah I don't even know headache yet I
just know that's coming yeah I have a
headache every
morning elephant neck up way up here oh
Chris always says that a fun fact that
he loves but I don't even know if he's
right or not but he likes that what is
it baby elephants like can't control
their trunk that is true it takes them 5
years to figure it out oh my God our
friends just figured it out yeah they
just figured it out that's crazy yeah
Chris always like he'll randomly tell me
that I'm like I don't know how true that
is but very very true wow so wherever
you got your information it's accur
amazing good to know now I can say it
fully and yeah proudly he'll like tell
people that all the time how big is a
baby elephant born so they're usually
born between 200 and 250 lb wow uh their
moms are pregnant for about 22 months W
20 to 22 months is the average so
they're pregnant for almost 2 years
that's crazy I I just started saying I'm
two right when I'm born if I was like
I'm two that's so long oh my God Nick
you are too baby elepant you two of you
is one baby elephant isn't that crazy
what do you mean they're 300 lb or or
200 300 was that true at Birth yeah May
was an extra big baby she was born at
281 lbs the largest calf ever born here
at the safari park wow d p that's crazy
she was born early too yeah it's
literally you twice this is how big she
was let say like two and a two and a
third and a half
maybe I'll give you some wiggle room
just half maybe never I'd never want to
think about my weight being that close
to an elephant ever again but baby yeah
baby baby baby
elephant even know both around 4,000 lb
oh my God I'm not
there got right here the maple long oh
no no get away from me Long John why do
you look so tall it's maybe how
professional you're saying wait how
would you put that in your pocket how
about you Mr Bap bone
worse than the maple donnut mm-m yeahuh
that's where I'm putting it no yeah wait
is that a little cream just [ __ ] eat
it why is it like a little doughy okay
inspector eat it they just atat the same
it's it's definitely a little less
because hey let's think about it if we
don't like that that much then this is
more of it so technically we like it
less cuz i' rather eat
less I'm okay with that thought process
cuz I oh you got it what you understood
what I said no I just don't care I want
to put that's where i' put it no right
there all right okay all right next up
we have Matt's Long
John why would you ever Supply the
internet with that sentence coming out
of your mouth are you [ __ ] actually
delusional are you [ __ ] mentally
ill good good idea incoming uhoh o I
think we rent a retro pickup truck for
the whole summer wo love that idea like
a vintage one yeah of course you can and
we just ride around in our truck as
three Bros all in M can you stop saying
[ __ ] Nick I was threw up that's gross
what did I use for dinner pizza Buffalo
you're lucky it's not on Buffalo a
you're lucky it's not oh my God how is
it every single time we're in the car I
just ate Buffalo that's happened the
last like four car videos I'm a big
buffalo wing guy just recently found
this out when I was a kid I didn't love
buffalo wings but I grew up and I love
them dude I don't know that's a [ __ ]
very frequent experience right last time
I burped you were like hold you eat
buffalo wings I was like yeah I ate
buffalo wings that's crazy yeah that is
pretty wild the odds are with you
Buffalo Wild somebody got
shot someone recently just got shot at
our local buffalo wings crazy pray up
oh
prank um so yeah we're going to call
Nick in and then have him start sipping
all right I saw I saw what are you doing
what did you just do I like clearly saw
him do that what are you do it I didn't
he went to sip it and he fully leans I
didn't mean to see it I just was like
going to like that's how I take a sip of
a drink I got to like shut your eyes and
take sit we have to mix these up just
the first three first three serious
you're an idiot the um y strawberryish
sunkiss 21 get in frame
[Applause]
is it coconut water yeah where did you
get coconut water oh
look we there's the cocon all right you
have to go back in bathroom cuz we have
to put you have shut Your Eyes Nick Nick
we put that there as a prank yeah I
[ __ ] P obviously Chris real you're
I'll do vocal exercise I'm not doing
this I'm not doing
that you can't do anything fun Matt I
can I do okay do the craziest thing you
could think of like just like a physical
Outburst like your dog you got the
Zoomies what's going to be your first
move oh he's driving Matt Matt oops guys
like what are you doing M like you just
like fu
[Music]
that was that was the craziest thing I
could think I L it now you have to go
recheck the camera I wouldn't be
surprised if the camera's [ __ ] broken
after that that was insane all right
moving forward into the topic cuz Matt
didn't hear I'm going to say it one more
time what would you like shut the [ __ ]
up I something it's not going to I have
something good I have something good
what you cookies cookies something
you're interupting me to say have
something good if there's not a baked
treat under your ass I don't want to
hear it if I'm not getting rice krispy a
[ __ ] two for one on [ __ ] cake pops
shut the [ __ ] up it's not worth cutting
off my sentence it's good it's good then
you're baking me a treat when we get
home my hair looks fine thank you b
Smurf in the car with us today veiny
Smurf goog Vey isn't it VY veiny I don't
think it's veiny
whatever VY Smurf is crazy
whoa next thing you know they're going
to bring out girthy Smurf
shut the [ __ ] up that's terrible it's a
kids show it's a kids show it's a kids
show what would be like the craziest
Smurf dude everyone think of one what is
actually the craziest Smurf what are
they named off of adjectives what's the
yeah clumsy Smurf like he's [ __ ]
idiot no what would be like the craziest
Smurf the actual craziest Smurf road
rage Smurf he's like [ __ ] you and he's
like always in his little onion onion
yeah his little mushroom mushroom no not
even the same family girl we're not even
in the same produce section oh it is
mushroom correct he's little mushroom
car like I think like just like Papa
Smur like Papa Smurf's making his new
spell in the woods he's like [ __ ] you
papa [ __ ] give me a mixing
bowl lose your [ __ ] attitude please
get my patties what are you saying get
your patties your patties aren't made
yet or get my
buns and I gave Matt that job on purpose
to get your buns
yep guys are we ser
this doesn't seem too smart it doesn't
we have look at this is how we have the
thing plugged in give me a spatula
actually you need to say please and
thank you get it your mother did not
raise you get it where are your manners
please and thank a head shf doesn't have
time for manners he has time for
Perfection I'll thank you at the end of
the night get my spatula get my spatula
I'm looking for a wow you think you're
talking yeah you feel tough and
major and I'm listen you I'll thank you
guys once I have a good Creation in
front of my eyes going in your mouth now
get my spatula
what I'm dead ass I have literally zero
clue I've never cooked in my life like
why why are you just like the whole are
you [ __ ]
kidding the whole dinner almost just are
you [ __ ] kidding I got the meat all
over me I have to pee really bad again
just started you need to go to the
doctor no I've been drinking a lot of
water I'm staying hydrated I bought a
new wottle water today a new water
bottle oh a new water bottle new water
bottle I don't talk like that that's
what you say like you you just said
water Bott your
words literally just said water replay
it I Ahad talking about Water Burger
your words are falling I did not say
Water Burger you said water I bought a
new water B
today like a kindergarten did just said
water you ran into the room with like if
you ran into the room and like just
underwear like held something up you
look just like a kindergarten what cut
that out cut that out cut that out you
know a little boy like I'm talking
clearly you like could have said like oh
if you ran up and I had my eyes shut I
would have thought you were like a
little kid I was going to say something
but then Nick fully interrupted me you
all you've done it you have to you have
to not be mad when you get interrupted
when you interrupt people to say stupid
the number
one number one yes no I was going to say
something but one of you guys like
screwed do you have to keep saying I'm
going to say something or what am I
going to say all right got sheep in the
back seat um
I my ears a I'm going to read oh shut up
I'm just going to hit you my ears at you
my [ __ ] ass at you shut up I'm just
going to read all mine cuz I Nick you're
just looking scre I'm going to just
start hitting you stop Chris stop God
that was insane I'm going to speak that
was a full array of several smacks to
the heck just like you need to stop
right you're just so fortunate we're
filming a video and I want it to go good
that's all I'll say let's carry on
sounds good you if I went up to you and
hit you as hard as I can in the back of
your head you'd have terminal [ __ ]
brain illness for like if I sucker punch
you in the back of the head in like the
kitchen one night you hitting the back
of my head stop you can hit me in the
face all you want the back of my I just
think Matt is like so X Games like
you're the type of kid like x what is an
X game it's like the BMX and like
snowboarding like I can just picture
Matt being like you
stop I'm like trying to listen are you
[ __ ] stupid now sounds like you have
a moraca
me if I ever [ __ ] your
[ __ ] like
what what are you talking about I had to
say something to break the I you guys
have been [ __ ] yapping and yelling at
each other I had to say something out of
pocket so I could regain focus and
Consciousness to
the do you like
that my
God I can't look
wait wait what happens if you do it on
the table wait it says wait wait wait it
says walking watch your lamb walk by
giving her a pat on the back hold on to
the leash and see where she takes you
let me wait let
meop you're going to Don't drop snowy oh
you got to turn her
[Laughter]
on I me like on the bottom dude the
actual power power button you guys are
sick okay snowy hold
on yeah you just got to hit it was in
try mode and you have to turn it
on oh God you got to turn it on did you
name it snowy or
is snow on the thing oh my God I thought
he wait can I have it can I have it hold
on I want play hold on hold on ready I
want to play turn it on let me see no so
the first I want to put the leash on
first I don't like
okay okay stop okay now you can feed
it
you you good sis okay that was a burp
[Music]
that's cute today I'm wearing my Hooter
shirt cuz I'm a big fan of
breasts I got good chicken too though
and I'm a big fan of tits and
chicken God you're insane
Nick breasts is probably my least
favorite term for boobies n boobies is
worse boobies is worse what's your
favorite I don't like this com ation
four hamsters could pick up a pound okay
you need like 3K
yeah let's not take guesses let's not
take guesses let's not take guesses
3,000 hamsters uh-uh girl like alcohol
consumers what would be your go-to my
go-to drink of choice would be a Pina
colato you know that for sure absolutely
I I don't know cuz I don't know what
they taste like but like off of like
just thought and like how was annoying
Beer Drinker you would yeah you would
like Miller li no i' I'd love a good
fruity drink we should bring back the no
what's the biggest thing you think you
can swallow in one
gun like dude I have no unable no idea
who asks that what's the biggest thing
you could swallow probably a sword
honestly ly I see sword swallowers I'm
like what I could do that
either sword swallowing takes no Talent
it just takes an oh my God I was going
to say throat I going to say an open
throat guys are like insane that's
terrible can we go home please if I was
like caught off guard and someone like
pushed me in the back or something I
could easily get like a Snickers bar
down there but it just needs to be like
a blind side your throat
[Music]
easy I said no onions and they're just
trying to get their check and no I said
three double doubles not two with extra
spread oh ordering spread angry is nasty
ordering I feel like wrong building I
feel like I'm going to be at like a
strip club or something yeah
like I don't know can I get a double
double and can I get some spread like n
that's crazy spread is crazy can I get
some spread a
style like that's insane do me favor
flip over and spread it animal style
this is top this is crazy flip over
spread it animal
style give me 20
minutes to pull on up to the next
window you guys are nuts we're
nuts you're you're going further into
the joke oh my God it's a seven what is
the what is think you're the toughest
cookies what is
38 off 10 I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
please don't hit me please don't hit me
please don't hit me I'm sorry I didn't
mean it you just God grace me with
patience I'm sorry Nick I'm sorry this
is going to be a funny one I love when
Nick has his glass how many syllables
are in the word RH know how many
syllables are in the word four Oh I
thought you were going to sounded out
for sure I did in my hands oh that us
three get to make decisions every day on
like what we want to do with our life
decid to be annoying [ __ ] you can you
[ __ ] actually stop dude I'm trying to be
sentimental right now you know those red
butt butt Apes I just like walk around
and go a baboon yeah baboon a red butt
ape a read 10 it's a
baboom why you that after you're like a
[ __ ] red ass baboon that's what you
are oh God you just monkey around all
the time I love monkeying around yeah I
know [ __ ] no can we actually be
sentimental and real with the viewers if
you got the [ __ ] point do you think
that aliens would just look like us but
be all robotic no that's probably robots
yeah thank you robotic would be the last
thing I'd expect aliens to look no I
feel like an alien could just look just
like us except have like a weird like
antenna like one little thing that
stands
out you blow my mind every day yeah I
can't
even oh God someone said favorite melon
melon your
mothers your
mother no what I was going to say is um
is cantaloupe or Melon yes of course
that's a main Melon No yeah
that's in the name though it doesn't
have melon in the name my main melon
someone said what this is going to sound
bizarre I like like licking the waffle
fry like my tongue goes between like
each
CR you could have totally kept that one
up yet I know that one was that's like
one of the crazier things I've ever
heard about no you know when you like
play with your food and you like stick
your tongue on it or something and it's
like yeah I poke my hole through one of
the holes of the waffle fry no never had
no one does that okay whatever I hate
the heel of a waffle fry the heel yes
like the edge of the potato oh [ __ ] I
did it to myself oh yes oh shut the [ __ ]
up we're talking no no we're not no
we're not we're moving on we're moving
on how how do potatoes get brought up so
often I don't know I don't know I don't
know people just constantly ask if I'm
actually gay like I need to just like
what do I have to do to prove
it what do I have to do to prove it my
God I'm like sweating like I'm like I'm
a disgusting beastly creature cuz it's
10 million de in here and in order for
my G not to be exposed on the camera I
have to wear sweatpants so I'm dying I'm
dying my God I can't do I feel like in
in another world a GU is like a nice
bag like I don't know I feel like it
really fits like if a designer brand
dropped a GU and it was like a pouch I
would be I wouldn't be surprised at all
oh stop talking Nick my wallet's
actually in your gu what
what give me paper towel on that I'm
just going to take over be head yeah no
[ __ ] mt's just nervous that we're not
going to enjoy I know you guys aren't
going to enjoy my food it's okay mat
shut the [ __ ] up [ __ ] baby I know
you're not going to like my
food yeah get that [ __ ] all oiled up
okay all right
let's K goes just kid just comes back
with a Crispy Cream
donut you're such a good Nick if you
were food I think you'd be a donut I'm
[ __ ]
starving that was the funniest thing
you've ever done in our entire YouTube
career I'm so w w this is a lot of
asparagus Matt asparagus I just said
that you're saying AR am I losing my
mind like you're saying I thought you
were going to yell at him for repeating
you not I might not be The Brightest
Bulb in in the in the ceiling I need
like an alter ego name cuz there's like
a part of me deep down that's just like
a Fearless monster keep that to yourself
actually no one needs to meet your
monster dud how often am I oh that's
such a good saying meet your maker
underrated saying how often am I you
stop talking I just really could fight
like if like I'm not a fighter at at
heart but I'm a fighter if I need to if
someone like made fun of like my Mom oh
they're oh my God if someone tried to
mess with Mary I think they'd be eating
cement in point I agree I would neuter
someone if they mess with Mom I would
take their ball sack who almost neutered
me the other day with a trunk you the
other day we were standing by a trunk
and someone
literally the other day someone we know
as like a newer car and it was like a I
don't even know where we were and the
trunk was like like they have like a
[ __ ] trunk instead it doesn't open it
it goes down so it's like it comes like
most of it goes up half goes up half
goes down yeah and it was like coming
down and I was putting stuff in the
trunk I click the down button like legit
like my height was perfect like like
like I don't know how to say this I'm
sounding like insane like my your dick
and balls my my you're [ __ ] balls
yeah yeah yeah I like they almost got
pinched in by the truck yeah like I
can like part of me cuz of my height
like when I was putting something in the
trunk like perfectly rested on the trunk
yeah and Chris went to close it so it's
like like I wasn't going anywhere my
balls were lifting it almost guillotined
like I almost got neutered the other day
that's a night yeah imag you going to
pay attention more dude to put him in a
situation like that almost neutered me
not that it matter it was was like it
was like an auto if any of us hads get
neutered I'd volunteer I'd volunteer cuz
I can't have kids anyway cuz I'm gay
shut up so it's like if one of us if we
were like at like a if we were at like a
um if we were like got kidnapped by
someone and they were like one of you b
b your balls are out of here you're
getting neutered I take you know what Ni
No ni I want to be a goodle take one of
mine no I want to be a good uncle like
if if someone had to lose the ability to
like don't all right done Nick I hope
you have a nice Bush one day in front of
your yard thank you yes of course thank
you I really want that I was really
uncomfortable when you were saying you
hope everybody's welcomed by your
Shrubbery I was like I really do I want
to walk and like the first compliment I
want about my house is like wow you have
amazing Shrubbery outside don't I'd love
to hear that no I wouldn't I oh imagine
someone goes up to you Mt oh your
brother's shrubber is unreal they
wouldn't know it's my Shrubbery yet I
have to tell them unless you [ __ ] be
like oh it's my
strawberry oh oh oh
your
hand yeah pull me
up believe you just fell it was so funny
what a good outro to that video it was
awful oh Matt you look so good
today I just love that shirt on you you
look so Dapper come on look at his ankle
look at his ankle oh are you like
limping bad head
up oh my God I was to hit him in the he
caught
it m was amazing thank you I'm I'm
highly impressed that was insane that I
went to hit him in like the head with it
and he [ __ ] Spider-Man grabbed it
here I don't want to hurt your ankle you
want me to help you down I can get down
get the
[ __ ] stop let me help you
down ow [ __ ]
you you're going to hurt your own ankle
dude no I'm not and if you're around bad
grapes you're a bad grape what true most
of the time you saying you get your
[ __ ] hand out of my face I want to
punch you in the mouth I'm going toch
the
mouth
feel I'm being I'm being verbally like
pressed by Mario right now yeah he's
like a yeah get your finger out of my
face din
Battalion dude I have a good arsenal of
like accents and like a great arsenal of
like correctly being able to say like a
sentence in another get in the car
listen I look like I I like listen you
stop talking I hate when you repeat
yourself they're screaming in the
[ __ ] yeah you're like mac it in Mac
it in Mac it in I feel like Lumiere from
[ __ ] Beauty and the Beast with these
[ __ ] lights on like this you need to
stay in the car I look like a [ __ ]
candleabra you're ruining my [ __ ]
Central piece ask ask the [ __ ]
woodpeckers if that's a relatable to
they don't do they don't look for
sap what what else are they [ __ ]
pecking the wood for let out go ahead
wood simply because it's their [ __ ]
purpose if a woodpecker was not pecking
wood get to [ __ ] work you have some
[ __ ] wood to Peck you little pecker
go peck wood what the [ __ ] else are you
doing imagine a woodpecker like flying
through the air it's like what the whoa
whoa go you have [ __ ] you have work
to do go peack wood are you [ __ ]
crazy or they're like peering through
wood and holes in the tree like little
berries and ants and stuff it's like uh
back to the tree the wood go PE you
[ __ ] pecker pecker is a great word
yeah ah the peck of at wood is to
establish
territory the
W
Grandma out a w they PE at wood to
establish territory find a mate um and
yeah and make a nest hole they Peck
Woods or they find little insects and
sometimes that wood is attached to the
building yeah they can relate they PE
woods so they can peck wood she needs
the real teeth not for WIS value for her
no it's not not for wisdom teeth wisdom
teeth is like a okay that's like the
last time you're going to see the tooth
fairy so it's not now
no it is it is unless you lose a tooth
in your adult life it is the last time
the toothberry is going to come there so
I'm going to start
so listen I'm going to start pulling my
teeth out so she doesn't care she
doesn't care to take the four fake
wisdom teeth that the denst gives you
because of the fact that it's her last
time taking the teeth and it's like it's
like a thank you the Tooth Fairy really
grows up with you man yeah she does that
Mak sad ni you're not even under
anesthesia yet let's keep our emotions
together just actually so sad think of
little kids who get their teeth taken
out yeah or they lose their teeth for
the first time
yeah and now he's actually crying now I
have no more teeth to K it's okay Nick
sad no it's not sad it's a part of life
and you do have yeah you're doing a the
tooth Fair a big favor Nick you want to
know what I
heard I heard I heard wisdom teeth are
20 bucks a pop
can't believe this don't be sad Nick
that's 80 bugs tonight
dud I'm so emotional recently what is
happening to me you might toss on the
extra 22 you might find a [ __ ]
Benjamin under your pillow tonight
Nick what are the odds man how crazy
would that be oh Nick you kill me I
haven't felt like this in so long what
do you feel like I can't believe this he
just feels sad
[Music]
F me
up I'm so
upset I wouldn't have brought up the
toothpick I brought her
up I wouldn't have talked about it I
just can't believe
this it's not even this that's making me
so upset I just I can't believe
it what the wizdom tee are gone oh hello
hi lady hi sweet lady hi sweet
lady I'm so
afraid
wa what a [ __ ] loser literally I was
talking about the Tooth Fairy as a joke
but now I'm seriously thinking about
like every single
time jumed up don't Nick
you're ni I'm thinking of every single
time oh wow
dude why am I so
upset what is going on I feel like I'm
in a dream I don't know I don't know I'm
think of every single time that one of
us got our teeth taken out as kids and
every single time any of our teeth fell
out which is so stupid and so I can't
believe I'm upset by it but it's just
sad you guys know I was the first one
out of us three to lose a
tooth yes that's that's what I'm
thinking of too and I had my little
envelope yes yeah oh my God Tooth Fairy
came you were so cute and little and I
no and I no [ __ ] front teeth dude at
least I have front teeth now they we're
going to goow back in and now they're in
and now you don't need
anymore I need to put the air
conditioning so good
nickis long has it been it's been like a
half hour they're all gone a half hour
yeah like it was like 8 minutes each too
they let me they let me take one of them
out yeah Matt did one of them I did the
bottom left one yes like I'm
noty oh I'm not lying Nick I swear to
God they let him do it oh I'm not a liar
they said we need a professional so they
called in
Matt
a CH to it
I don't believe you for a [ __ ] second
they almost called rup Paul to do
it don't
[ __ ] you are that's good I'm me
yeah I'm me
yeah who am I that's that yeah do you
have a favorite no no I love that oh I
love you too ni I love you so I love you
too do you leave that don't move your
finger you got to stay still don't you
can't move your finger no no no leave it
on leave it on Nick I'm actually going
to be mad at you Nick stop it leave it
on Nick what's the password to leave no
no do you want to take a selfie with me
let's do
it thumbnail thumbnail change post go
like this like you're
shocked Jing no don't move wants to show
the all right put your arm
down change your pose Nick ready one two
three change your pose all right we got
it we got it nice let's take a
[Laughter]
[Music]
selfie the S oh your hair your hair yeah
fix that it looks good do you want
I feel like I'm giving decup Hooters
girl in this shirt what did you just say
girl in this
shirt yeah you got some nice knockers
H all right guys status update we
finished eating pizza or Matt's about if
be finish eating pizza eating his crust
I'm making Matt drive me to the store
cuz the other day I got a is that a
orange poodle yep died ah I'm taking a
photo look at it my window hurry up Nick
hurry up hurry up hurry up Hur oh my God
hurry up [ __ ] Matt go upep up cre you
got to take it you got to take it I
can't see it [ __ ] [ __ ] dude we just
ruined it that would have been so was a
legit orange it was like Cliff you see
that you see that orange dog yeah that
was crazy like a clown I
know for real have a good one have a
beautiful day man oh my God that is
thank God you talk to a stranger because
that's the little we're like that's it
was a [ __ ] CL W he he gave you side I
was like I need to ask this dude if he
just saw that he thought I was thought
it was aown clown dog so cute a that I
love [ __ ] like that I love
it [ __ ] I love that [ __ ]
cute you guys look
great try again try
again it's too much to do
soaring mat Matt put you on the spot
crazy these people are taking photos
right here and Matt and I go look I
literally Matt Scrolls on you guys look
great I got zero response that was
ridiculous that was horrible that was
really funny anyway I don't know what
the past I should have been wearing
shorts today and I'm wearing a sweater
and pants I don't know what the past two
minutor that was a lot and very chaotic
hot that we drove by I knew you were
going to say that when I saw that dude
on oh the guy with the hat no oh I knew
you were going to say that too Nick you
can see you have to watch the footage
back it literally like my eyes jolted my
arms are I like the videos that we don't
have anything to talk about more okay
cuz then I get to say anything I want oh
no that's my least favorite thing ever I
have nothing to say so I don't know what
I don't know I don't want to
start I'm nervous to start um anyways
welcome back guys happy Friday today's
another car video we clearly have
absolutely no topic today we just's
really good can I have a bite let's go
what don't say anything nobody say word
nobody say a word this is before the car
video and before we leave and Chris
isn't in here yet okay million dooll bet
that he's going to ask me for either a
sip of my drink or a piece of my
chocolate
bar we are what 30 seconds
in here's your piece idiot you baited me
though you I know I was trying to no if
you didn't say that I would have no yeah
you would no I wouldn't have Chris you
shouldn't have said that we were in the
car for another 40 minutes with this
drink and this I guarantee there was
going to be a question one or the I
guarantee I guar you baited me you
baited me oh it tastes really
good if I ever need to laugh I just got
to look at
Mt I the laugh I'll just look at Mt cuz
Matt always makes these
faces I've never thought
this if I ever have to laugh I'll look
at the clothes you put on I'll look at
your haircut no it wasn't like a mean
thing it's just like you always give me
this look of like such
disappointment cuz I I genuinely am I'm
like oh my God here [ __ ] goes again
some stupid
[ __ ] like what is so funny what was the
look I'll see it okay awesome all right
I have like tears in my eyes that's good
do you have anything to
say yes I do
okay oh oh my god do we know where the
is oh nothing happened nothing bad
happened Mt
enough what is going on put this down
good yeah it's pretty good it's
like ooh the strawberry and watermelon
is like a little overpowering no dude
that's what it's that's the flavors that
tastes like
2006 [ __ ] you don't know what 2006
tastes like no it tasted like that 2006
tastes like breast milk Chris you were a
baby it tastes like 2016 you you were
off the tit at 3 no
way no way no that tasted like like good
like classic times like good classic
times no I felt like a kid right then
you should name like these like like
corny snacks like I feel like you'd like
Chris would Chris would be the type of
guy who owns like a little shop called
like good classic times and he just
sells like bizarre [ __ ] that reminds him
of like his kids life tastes like apple
juice low
key it's kind of good it's like
perfectly apply no it's like not good
but it's
like still it on myself I thought we
were about to get robbed and shot no I
still car look like it's gunning at me
where Matt why would you ever
ever I only say that when I think it
Nick so when you're like oh my God is
she likeing
handcuffs what she looked like handcuff
you looking at this is 3 weeks old
bottle
soda actually longer than that the whole
time you're in La this three weeks it's
not cheese [ __ ] it's not going
to get
better he thinks it's Pepsi's wine he's
putting in his wine are waiting for it
to get right let's do the fake yell like
blow out all your I saw this on Tik Tok
you blow out all your air also not doing
that and yes try
it now scream scream how do you have
that much air in
you
Jesus see if I if I blew out all my air
I'd still be able to scream I feel like
I would okay
go scream oh cuz that's that's coming in
right did I just breathe in more air is
that what I did is that wait how do you
do it he you thought you could do you
thought you could do it thought be so no
yeah you
can't you look [ __ ] stupid dude one
more time one more time
it's like it's easier to fall in a canoe
than a kayak I think okay than a kayak
you just can't shift your weight okay
like why you us if you have every answer
King kayak is asking me the question
it's like you you're clearly the
professional you need a job at the
[ __ ] bass pro shop selling kayaks if
you could go back to any point in your
life already lived where would you go
probably go back to like Cape Cod and I
would legit like eat bubbles after
really long wait we were talking
physical
location or a time period
wait what are you talking about
nothing n in the heart why
nothing Matt spoke to
me I felt it right here is that the
question yeah you hit the nail on the
head okay Matt likes to critique me cuz
I think I make him feel old like he's
just as immature as me but he's like a
slight variant you being in the car I
don't know guys are we not gumming
people eat probably a
90 oh my God Nick you just broke a
childhood Relic and it was mine donut
not bad oh it actually smells really
fruity not bad this might be the best
one smells kind of
fruity your face is gross okay it was
like a little no it was like a little
kid face you made that's what I meant is
everyone
ready what is going on in imagine you're
in the sea and there's like a 100 male
seahorses surrounding you and they're
sporadically giving birth because have
you seen a video of male seahorses they
just like out the
babies and they're like pushing babies
out like I'd freak out I'd freak out I'd
be like get the [ __ ] out of here it one
goes in your ear and it like stop yeah
like a [ __ ] family could grow up in my
[ __ ] like Canal yeah really Canal
[ __ ] hate that I would just try to
eat them all when something's in your
stomach it can't live it just dies to
the stomach acid what the [ __ ] camera
you're going to break your [ __ ]
window man
stop oh my God I just think it's no when
you chew teeth yeah he's tee no I'm not
when you chew it helps your teeth grow
as in baby cuz it rubs against your gums
and it helps the gum like it helps the
cute I could never breastfeed my I
literally just did
that I could never breastfeed my nipples
are way too sensitive to breastfeed way
to we're going to move on Trevor go peee
I like love his camo collar he's such a
tough guy do you want to take part in
the Vlog what do you want me to do twerk
no that's actually the last thing I'd
want your [ __ ] ugly ass to do he just
got back oh look at him he's kind of got
a Gallop to
him took him long enough I no that's
what I'm saying what is this Kong easy
treat gross terrible terrible you think
he'd enjoy that that's nasty all right
what's up you the dudes from YouTube yes
the D we're filming a video right now
how are you want to say hi yo say hi to
our dog he's trying we can take a photo
if you guys pet him 10 times because
today is all about him 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
10 all
something this is she said it wasn't you
I'm being no it's us we're taking our
we're taking our dog out on the town
today all right let's do that hold on
let me get him in the phot out here pick
him up man
ready oh he's squirming okay all right
watch tomorrow's video it's going to be
this so of course see you guys later
have a good one do you think when people
say wait hold on do you think people
that drive by like I always do they got
to like they got to look over and be
like why do those kids that whole car
fully illuminated yeah in the camera
yeah they got to know what we're doing
though right filming a por it is that
does do that he speaks if like super
provoked especially first thing in the
morning when we're getting ready to go
somewhere you're very limited on words I
get like Matt are you getting up
shower Matt what are you doing bathroom
shower bathroom no I think I got can we
go drive I think I have a total of car I
think okay this is probably why as well
you know what I mean
interrupt I I think I have all right are
we done
that was really good Matt I think we
have a to I have a total of like 15
words Max before my feed are outside for
the day kind of crazy sometimes I don't
even talk to Matt we get to the car and
we're already going somewhere I'm like
Hello nice to see you holy [ __ ] my goal
is had a turtle in my throat What's the
phrase can I speak it's like a my
goal no Matt you're just like you need
to talk with some compassion Matt I want
you to I want hear it from your the
second
there talk louder he like looks to can't
even do
it oh no oh no can you get to the front
of the car go go say what you were going
to no Matt if you pour this Matt no
don't pour don't mat and my Snapple is
gone that Snapple had nothing to do what
was going spray what the [ __ ] that snap
just got emptied that snap has nothing
to do what with happening right now buy
another
[Laughter]
one I didn't even [ __ ] want that that
bad a you didn't okay go ahead cuz
sipping it and making noise was a lot
more important than what
I am I
right am I right or am I
wrong am I right or am I wrong no that
was a good point that was a good point
okay go ahead you charg something no I
feel oh Jesus and I ate one look this
was me that doesn't count that's there
if there's still chocolate showing Was
Bitten It Was Bitten but like bro I
would oh my God it looks like
Batman feel like Batman like this is my
City Glass are you sweating I'm really
hot I don't know would you
trust yes I would actually you body slam
the I would do it for no money that's I
was going they didn't let me it would
not cherishes life there's no way don't
try
it no there's no way oh my
God May a body slam will do it a body
slam might do it [ __ ] imagine if
saying get out of here well that would
if Madison died on the's Vlog
that good
content kill you we're going to the
aquarium that's serious like I I like I
saw a turtle I'm like I know you she
that that big ass ass fish she was like
oh yeah he's been here since the'80s
8s like that fish could have bought a
Coke for five [ __ ] sents literally
that's sickening literally scare and
whoever is more
clothed and enough
Nick ow ow you think you can just run
upstairs and scare me like that tiptoe
like a [ __ ]
psychopath knock back up get away you're
lucky I have my [ __ ] belt in my hand
you're done that was perfect timing I
was I was worried I wasn't going to be
able to see either of you it was so
silent my room's right there no one's up
here I almost took my dick out cuz I had
to go in here and pee I literally said
that I was going to I was going to scare
whoever was more clothed and I saw you I
heard you start to turn the corner and I
knew putting a video I took a video not
of my penis of my face stop saying the
word penis so loud I was recording my
[Laughter]
penis no no
Matt just th the whole Woods I don't
even think I can speak that loud though
I think they heard you over there yeah
you're ruining the vibe come on he go
take he goes take the camera take the
camera he's like loading up the scen how
about Matt every single day we're in La
he's like oh I just want to be in the
wilderness I want to be outside in the
peace and quiet and then we get him to
the peace and quiet and he shouts penis
every time I'm just trying to show you
there's nothing to be scared of don't
you just feel like a free bird right now
think something this is how we should
pick oh my
God oh my God three left again it's got
to just come
down please him
again yeah this is rigged drink up o
yummy hey sound like a four-year-old
trying to say tomato the
Tomato it again I love
booies Gay
what
what put it down I
like Matt can I move it I'm trying to
put it back back he's like you got way
too much height on that get away from
me where wait I can't wait don't have a
oh he ran down quick I don't even know
where he is now I don't have a visual
look at this monkey praying for us on
the screen oh he's up
to where he's up the top he's going up
the top okay should I shake it again
he's on the side he's on the side mat
you got to just kill him through the
curtain onto the wall I can't kill this
dude through the Cur onto the wall Matt
you can easily kill it we all give the
door cuz Nate he's going to keep
climbing threw the curtain into the wall
yeah hit him out the wall give me this
you have this it's it's oh my god do we
see him cuz this push really push him oh
my
God kill switch do it
Nick where is he where he's dead he's
dead he's dead he's dead he's dead he's
dead he's got to be dead he's got to be
dead oh no
until your [ __ ] friends don't come
back take the
Vlog oh tears in my ass oh my god I've
never jumped up higher and faster in my
life shout out grandpa that was his Cane
mom literally said that when we were
kids me what what what you're earing
you're [ __ ] his earrings upside down
he's stoning Satan holy [ __ ] that's the
sign of the devil oh my god dude I
actually I actually was expecting
someone to be standing right there oh my
God in what world did that need to
happen you fixed your earring though we
good oh my God I was scared like a ghost
all that because I have a cross earring
and it was upside down by the way I
literally was expecting someone to be
right there covered in BL holding a
machete was I in the middle of say so
sorry just like like I said you guys
will always find into way in Matt
punched me or Matt slapped me those are
$100 glasses broke yeah don't do that
give them to me no give me them at you
Matt just slapped me and it hit the
bridge of the sunglasses right here into
my head and I have like I feel a little
C
awful it looks like slime is this
expired smells
[Music]
sweet I saw a little bit of relief in
your eyes he he's like smell smell sweet
SM sweet on
three oh
tastes better than it looks tastes
better than it looks tastes better than
it smells not number one three two
one not that bad I'm sure in high doses
it's
horrible come on
baby are you
joking what happened this is the drama
is crazy it's not that bad this is like
that was pretty good it's better than
it's
here it's here
oh it's not yeah know it's I think that
that's a safe rating if I were to take a
big keeping scoop of any it'd be that
dude so far yeah it like got stuck to my
throat like the whole slab of it it felt
like it felt like thick you know when
like the Habachi Chef put that slap of
butter on the rice that's what I just
felt like I ate like it was just like
like I felt
every moment of my throat o o gross
let's go let's go yeah there you go oh
my God I just got a [ __ ] piece of
that stench okay
ready it's on my teeth oh my God oh my
God oh my God it's like hot oh my God oh
my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my
God having a Dr Pepper is a cheat I'm
not trying to be dramatic I'm really not
and I've had a lot of bad things
this is this is the worst the worst Food
we've ever eaten for our Channel ever I
have kind of a funny question wait
answer or what would you play here's my
question do you want to hear my answer
yes A funny question go um a
sunflower that's so your Vibe I love it
your tattoo Oh I thought you were just
like
he yeah that's what I thought he just
did [ __ ] happened happens when you guys
let me speak but what should our what
should our Trio be name small medium and
large you're in the middle
idiot I'm shy yesterday I went to the
store and I [ __ ] your mother so yeah
it was like that today me and Christ was
to go get ice cream and we were in the
ice cream but how did they get there who
drove mind your business we got to the
ice cream place and this lady was like I
felt bad for her
um I was too busy [ __ ] [ __ ]
getting money I'm joking how about this
little how about this little interaction
I had with Chris the other day if we're
going to talk about people being stupid
we're we're driving by a semi-truck and
he looks gasps you were in the car looks
gasps points at it and I wrote down and
I quote he goes this looks just like
it's from the movie Cars and he's going
like this he's like pointing at the car
he goes this looks just like it's from
the movie Cars it was probably the scen
and then he goes he he goes look it's
Mac and it's a [ __ ] 18wheeler truck I
said Chris wait till you find out what
the movie Cars is based off of Just you
[ __ ] wait he literally points at an
18-wheeler with bolt his hands like this
like a like an animal
like like sh poting look it looks just
like it's from the movie Cars like he's
seeing like the real actor of the
[ __ ] movie it's a truck it was an
18wheeler truck
are you crazy of course it does and so
does the car you're in in every other
car on the [ __ ] road are you
unfamiliar with life is a [ __ ]
highway here we are Life is a Highway
we're here oh my God Nick you're too
funny can you grow up random hot take I
have seen The Nutcracker play like five
times no when in my whole life when you
where and when have you [ __ ] gone to
see The Nutcracker are you [ __ ] ser
have never gone to see ner I have been
yes I have absolutely not you've seen a
[ __ ] Nutcracker in play you have
never you're cracking my nuts right now
no I'm not we went for a school field
trip one year mom took us one year yes
absolutely I you can't even get to three
call Mom right now I went and watched
the [ __ ] Nutcracker play actually
call her actually call her no don't cuz
she's in a different time just call her
and see if she answers I'll call her hey
Mom mom random wait wait wait wait wait
wait is she
calling hi Nick hi hi Mom hi honey how
are you it's me Matt and Chris I have to
I have to go cuz we're filming a video
but we have a question for you if you
can answer it for our
viewers absolutely how many times and
did we ever go see the
Nutcracker in Boston like the Christmas
musical never you ever brought us to see
it no I think there was a field trip yes
that's Chris is claiming that he went
five times and me and Matt said no we've
been he's dreaming you saw Lily in the
Purple Plastic Purse I remember that
that was a good one you know I never
took you to The Nutcracker all right I
didn't think you guys are into it
yeah apparently Chris is a man yeah I
mean it's a ballet you guys didn't
strike me as the ballet kind of K I
didn't I'm not I'm think we are either
all right thank you so much for that
information I'll call you again
soon all right I'm going to bed good
night Mom love you love you m just
posted in his close friends on Instagram
and we can't stop laughing it's so look
at this video who the [ __ ] gives a
[ __ ] godamn Togo drink in a [ __ ]
bag
kid was so mad look at his tacos like
covered in soda ew that [ __ ] is so
disgusting who's thong was that under
your bed
[Laughter]
what
what enough of this time's up boys how
many uers did you buy too many too many
hundreds of dollars in Uber actually all
good songs my friend all good songs my
friend I need to learn how to drive all
right that's it put him in The
Slammer
okay and put turn around and pull your
pants down real slow I did for the first
time ever today what I used a bedan in
there no you didn't no you didn't no you
[ __ ] did not tell me everything about
it how' it go not to get super like yeah
no that's fine detail we're you know
we're normally uh wet wipe users we we
love dude wipes of course dude WIP for
in the other bathroom I was in there
with just toilet paper I was like you
want know what I'm going to [ __ ] around
no you're not I there was like a no you
didn't I swear to God I didn't even know
there was one in there dude crazy okay
yeah I hit like like medium soft or like
low soft something like I wanted to be
timid for my first time you're not going
to [ __ ] put it on power washer at the
first go dude I'd be scared that super
warm and I was like this I was like like
that was actually genuinely like in
shock wow yeah I would be scared like if
I stand up it would just shoot out of
the toilet oh
definitely really yeah so you got to
like stay there you got to try it I'm
not trying try before we leave I just
stop Buton it stops right away
really air dryer I hit no it's
not here you're making [ __ ]
up I it dry it like comes in it was like
sh you're lying crazy mm-m I swear to to
God Matt okay it was crazy it was
literally crazy I can't believe it yep
you should definitely try it so would
you do it again I
would on so you would right hurry up
what are you reading kid I don't know
I'm opening books I'm [ __ ] unfolding
books here let's see it these are like
balls that's what I'm
reading this about balls J he reads it's
about every ball Chris goes what are you
reading I go not too sure I'm just kind
of unfolding books here and I look at it
and I go huh
balls I'm reading about you guys were
like years old Justin tell Matt what you
just did I didn't well I didn't do it I
asked Chris I I went to take a piss I
said I so Chris have we ever taken up on
the amenities of the toilet have we ever
have we ever do did you did he tell you
about this thing today did you do it
have you done it no I'm never touching
it are you scared to do it no I think
there's a couple of things that we can
keep oldfashioned that being one of them
you know what you want to do it what are
you talking about I think we should do I
think Matt should do it like a a day in
general like are we are we taking it
into the toilet's hands [ __ ]
no I will leave it right here you know
I'm good a for freaks me out but it was
fine for you you should do it not going
to like it one bit he hates it dude oh
the cutman he's the he's legit
cutman the dude he has a shirt that says
the cut man and he helps out with the
cuts no no no it's good we're
recovered why does he get another one he
flinched no two for flinching dude that
that wasn't a Flinch dude oh he flinched
again did he not I think he just
flinched again blow Fair blow that was
more of a Flinch than the other one that
one was more Flinch than the first
[Music]
Flinch he's right out he can't get up oh
my God I told you oh my
[Applause]
God he's done he's
wobbling oh my God off shirt off get
this
guy dude he got his shirt
off he deserves it absolutely deserves
it get the
replay oh my God triplet bro that's my
other one you triplet oh [ __ ]
oh wait God damn there's a third one not
here the third one was boor at the same
time
Trip 2 minutes
apart 2 minutes apart bro when's our
match up we're going to first hey hold
on y'all both single huh y'all both
single so y'all be hitting the same
girls on an accident no oh wowo we got a
match up power me and you yeah who's
winning me and him me and you yeah he
got the beard hey you got the beard for
protection so you're good done the favor
in look I got to arm wrestle you before
I do that I think I'm done look I'll
beat you and then here [ __ ] around and
beat
me POV your brick in public but it's
only semi so it looks like you an
absolute
Shopper
what
oh instant headache oh I feel I got to
watch my Indian head massage my [ __ ]
head hurts that was bad instant P
pull [ __ ] God damn it watch it watch
imagine your mother does that to you
punch in the face watch [ __ ]
don't touch me like that
[Laughter]
idiot okay go go I need to shower just
yelled at me it looks like in like over
never yell at me again [ __ ]
[ __ ] like looked all around like weird
kid walking no I'm locked just watch it
B I didn't even he a noise listen just
listen oh my God just watch just watch
just watch please give him a
cookie
overnight ai's daughter
Kik had her first
cat this is
venty only a few hours old I don't know
it's just a story about baby elephant I
just thought the intro was insane I'm
ready to call CPS someone said oh that
was really sad the noise made it so much
worse it was funny at first and then
like the sh The Cry for
Help a few hours old right in this
oh you're a few hours old here this will
set you to [ __ ]
reality
no no does he
die
no I don't think we see anything happen
but
what it's just him like giving up and
like the you can see look look look you
can see the peacefulness in his eyelids
he's he's like he's just like yes I feel
bad for him cuz I've been there you know
you're just like you can literally see
all guys the allergies are so bad wait
Mt hold on wa can you is this like the
ones to collect or can you build all
three of these no that's all one and
then you build it and then this this
will sit like on a shelf the back to
thank you yeah that's how Legos work I
know that oh my God I just want to he
just said guys I can't I'm editing right
now and I can't stop laughing at why
does why does Chris go to grab a knife
when he disagrees with me why why does
he why is think to go pick up a knife
I'm playing that clip again look it he
he he yells at me and picks up a
knife
what look again and then you build it
and then this this will sit like on a
shelf the back you yeah that's how Legos
work I know that oh my God I just want
to he just said oh my God his like he
picks up his eyes like like like oh my
God God you'll build it and then this
will sit on a shelf you're not allowed
to partake it's me and Matt only right
Matt are you going to the Finish Line
yeah I'll meet you guys at the Finish
Line Matt first the winner bring my
shirt no you're not ready no no let me
let me let me you guys don't know what I
got USA
[Laughter]
where let's go I'm doing it for my
country oh my God there's no
way oh my god look so fun come here give
me my shirt
back Nick busted out the USA shirt for
the American Ninja Warrior obstacle
course just know Nick that's what I got
on under here and I'm ready to win
that's the craziest that's the funniest
thing you've ever done in my whole
career my a no Sheck she took my whole
swag the okay oh like the call me like
I'm texting new boys you're too yeah
like you're giving me like I'm scared
I'm scared of you gross mid Mega mid M
Mega mid get some shoes what was that
flip she said oh he just broke up hold
on
what she's out here they all took my
SWAT who is this ni Yello hello oh I
like that little goofy hat I hate it I
hate the flower in the Hat oh yes oh
yeah oh turn around yeah I [ __ ] with her
okay
bow [ __ ] hands up
said it's quiet yeah it's quiet it's
quiet for sure it's quiet I don't like
the bangs I don't like the necklace it's
quiet it's quiet I she kind of fly
what is this horny ass I can't believe
babies don't know anything until they're
taught like like a baby say the ABCs
[ __ ] it's like the easiest
things like all humans it's like AB B
why did I do it in Spanish first A B C D
I what am I doing I'm like mixing
between Spanish and English right now as
if I'm like tring um du lingo I mean
what's two what's two du lingo no it's
it's um dualing trilingual is too du B
bilingual bilingual dualingo is that the
app that's the [ __ ] app um no ABC
it's like you can't even say the ABCs
cuz no one taught you yet you're a
[ __ ] baby babies learn everything
from the adults around them and that's
crazy yeah it is crazy am I crazy for
thinking that the other day I think I
saw a baby and I wrote that down in my
phone I was like this little baby his
opinions exactly his mother and that's
why and I know I've said this I know
I've said this in a car video before the
other day during our photo shoot for the
let's trip [ __ ] where we did the polar
Ray and stuff the other day a month ago
stop stop saying the other day the other
day a month the other day a month ago
the other day like I can't even remember
how long ago the other when I say the
other
day the other day is the last like 90
days for me literally when Chris says
the other day can I no it doesn't shock
the other day it does mat look it
doesn't shock shut up shut don't ball
me when Chris says the other day I'm
going to put a visual on the
screen right after I explain it because
I need them to also see okay this is
what I see in my head I hear literally
it it can he can say the other day and
actually be talking I know it's going to
be on the screen no he can say the other
day and actually be talking about like
two days ago but no matter what the
second he says the other day close your
eyes I I see I see a book like a
vintagey book with like brown papers
shuffling quickly through the pages and
like a map with like red lines popping
out and then like it brings us over like
a traversal drone shot of like sea and
woods and then into like a little
village and then like an x on the ground
and then you meet like the main
characters like that's what I see
indefinitely side by side when Chris
says the other day I see a passage into
an otherworldly
Visage I just turned 21
today we should go to the liquor store
and get alcohol and drink until our
livers explode I want to wake up in a
[ __ ] Park tonight give it to
me somebody somebody go from this part
of the video right now what did you say
that's the scary scarest thing I've ever
seen in my life he's kind of ugly I kind
of want to kill him and try again no you
can't that's your kid I'd let it happen
if your kid was ugly would you kill it
and try
again I'm going to kill you I'm going to
kill you I'm going to kill you [ __ ] him
let's try again wait so Nick lost no
Chris don't that's just really like that
that one pissed me off why did you throw
Matt's egg cuz I wasn't going to like do
another one I won Nick
oh look look at look at the Yoke on my
oh I didn't think it would explode like
that I just had to get revenge Nick all
right so it looks like we're going to
try wait look at look at my get the
camera get the camera Matt get the
camera and it's like look it's dripping
off the table I if I I can't stand up
it's going to drip egg everywhere
[ __ ] broke yeah okay I just have
one question before we wrap up this
video uhhuh if we were to all crack our
eggs technically SC me I got to come
with listen listen is it technically you
lost of who's cracked first I don't know
please I'm going to need you guys to
both Focus up on this 4minute video what
what is going
on hello Nick hello Chris and hello
everybody watching this video I know
that you might be confused on why I am
playing you this video in the middle of
an egg dad video but there is very good
reason and it's going to start with the
second I knew we were filming this video
you look like a like like a
villain during the first drawing attempt
knew I was not going to play fair I was
going to win this Challenge and I was
going to be the best dad of my egg and I
was going to let check see my egg is a
phon be the bad dads that they are so
the second that they cracked the eggs I
went to the carton and I grabbed new
eggs but before that I also made sure
that there were two eggs that looked
extremely similar to theirs what I put
them at the bottom of the carton so I
knew which two to grab when I went into
my plan later in the day then
when we were taking the videos of the
eggs to put on the screen when Nick told
you whose egg was who I calculated that
I would be the one to record the eggs so
that I had an exact image of what their
eggs looked like at all
times shut
up quiet and watch I like quiet and
watch wait a second wait a second I am
like I am bam Bo this is the most Rogue
mat thing I've ever is so the most
effort he's ever put into
I culated that I would be the one to
record the eggs so that I had an exact
image of what their eggs look like at
all times the next thing I did was I am
always the one to clean up a mess so
when I picked up the Sharpies
and no quiet no
quiet I made sure to take the three that
I was going to need at the colors that
they used I brought them to my room and
I put them in my box lucky me I did not
do this on purpose but got caught by a
pretty easy distraction of his wallet
being in the washing machine roll the
clip what i is in my short your wallet
is in your shorts I have a fear that it
is no I'll just leave it wow
wow
cooked with this now new knowledge I
knew that Chris would be way too focused
on his wallet and not on his egg while
me and Nick already had our eggs in our
pocket ready to go for the rest of the
challenge Chris was too busy seeing if
the track and his wallet got ruined by
the washing machine or not so he was on
his phone with him being on his phone it
struck the perfect opportunity bring in
myly
drunk toet simply see that they were a
carbon copy and switch them out and put
the real egg in my pocket Chris's egg
was very easy to draw I just had to make
sure that the lines did not pass the red
line of his head and make sure that his
eyes
[Applause]
watch
it watch shut up Nick was a good egg dad
he sat there and held his egg while
watching TV and doing everything that he
was doing I knew that he was going to be
the problem and he was going to be my
biggest competition Not only was Nick a
very attentive father to his egg but he
did a good drawing but the only thing
that he was missing was the fact that he
was smudging it all day long in the
pocket out of the pocket so what did I
do I drew his egg perfectly carbon copy
then I went to my bathroom and grabbed a
face cloth and I simulated the motion of
taking the egg out of the pocket over
and over and over again until I realized
that the smudges will match and mine is
honestly a little more bold than his
then as we were eating dinner and
cleaning the table we decided to put all
of our eggs on the same plate Nick went
upstairs before dinner and that was the
perfect opportunity to go back into the
room compare the eggs make sure they
were close enough and take his and put
it in my pocket and walk back to my room
now the hard part was done the false
eggs were put out into the world and the
real ones were in my possession there
were only two more things that I had to
do one of them it was gruesome it was
evil but your eggs were my breakfast
continue no way continue watching after
eating them they were very delicious but
the hardest part after that was just
making sure that you didn't fall for the
Trap and realize that your egg was a
phony and you guys were too CAU shut up
most important part when you guys were
too caught up to even think about the
fact that I was smart enough to do this
but thank you you have lost this
challenge you have lost this
challenge case in point don't [ __ ] with
me
I someone please Photoshop the word
Security on Chris's shirt cuz why the
[ __ ] he standing like he's the
[ __ ] security like this is a secret
service cake Secret Service cake [ __ ]
take a breath before you speak
idiot
oh I work best with communication with
eye contact so if you'd look at me
that'd be wonderful
I just got literally punched in the jaw
on my YouTube channel and I edit every
video I to see that again I just got
punched in the jaw and I have to witness
it today tomorrow and every time you
[ __ ] clip it
how he can't even see I'm getting
punched to the
[Applause]
jaw you feel the presence of the Whisk
like less than a [ __ ] centimeter from
your your lip no I
don't
oh get this good job Matt you're a great
listener that you [ __ ] ster Olo I
will rip your eyes out of your head so
you can experience what I experienced
for one [ __ ] minute
who is it who the [ __ ] is it own up to
it
now ow [ __ ] cuz you're an idiot
St my shoulder stop I didn't even hit
you once [ __ ] off me mushroom um I I
have to confess this for a very long
time I've been confused about the
difference between Chicken Little and
Stuart
Little and one is a chicken and one is a
rat and they're both little there's no
they are not the same and I've just
figured this out cuz Stuart Little has
those big ugly red [ __ ] shoes
on and Chicken Little got that crazy
looking friend that girl but what's the
point of both of those I need to I need
to up my knowledge on the littles I am
un okay do you think oh my God New Shout
Out cement new you're doing your thing
new conspiracy theory chicken and Stuart
Little are long lost
brothers and they they are both little
and they need to find each other to stop
the sky from falling I'm going home I
think that's it being a sports player
and they're like an athlete
whatever and having like a designated
why he correct himself cuz it's like
sport player I don't know I felt like I
was going to be made fun of no you
weren't
I imagine having like a Gatorade flavor
like i r blue like I'm a blue oh I can't
say that
what were you going to say like like oh
like I rep like this color Gator this
guy's swing in a nice bag I just think
laugh this guy's literally like what did
you mean by that no like he's swinging
in a bag yeah that guy's swinging a good
bag no but this guy's like the
definition of like moseying around right
now like no he's so chill car oh my God
he just
looked he just looked at that car guy
just looked looked at that car up and
down and he went
yeah I we all can't be caught looking
that's why I'm looking this way dude why
I'm kind of
scared what are you just checking out
every car for oh this makes me sad what
he's at the bus
stop after looking at all the
cars that's why he was checking out the
cars I'm so grateful that we have a car
and I'm so grateful that Matt can
drive I love pool Flags what's a pool
flag like a rainbow array of flags
crossing the pool no oh they're like oh
I multicol they're like the triangles
love love those they're such a Vibe
catcher just like wow we were at a pool
but now put on the screen now we're at
The Vibes and at a picnic table in a hot
dog friends yeah cuz those kind of
just whoa Ben cut me
off should I get Road Rage or what what
the [ __ ] you look so good on a horse
like I never thought you'd look this
great what I knew it I foresaw it I
don't know why I just looked back
expecting to see like 10 more horses
kick them dude I'm
like I've never practiced my inward
kicks so they're so they're not good
today yeah out and then
Chris maybe we run through canes yeah
yeah I'm
done get a little canak combo yeah real
quick just eat it in the car imagine
going through a drive-thru with this
thing welcome to the joke Matt that was
that that just would be so fun welcome
to the joke no cuz I heard I just thing
I've ever heard I just heard bless you
rusty rusty good sneeze it's like that
that'll be that'll be$ 1297 at the next
window yeah yeah this whole time I've
been trying to mentally figure out the
name of Woody's horse or Jesse's horse
in Toy Story um what's his name [ __ ] who
the horse and Toy Story um bullseye
bullseye if I say something right now
like the most random thing ever could
you make a joke out of it you think like
it depends if you volley me if you don't
[ __ ] volley me I'm not going to be
able to do
it can you
stop like it hurts you just punched my
and balls what would you do Nick what
would you do Nick if
um hold on let me think let me think
what would you do if do you know how
like at a store they have like washer
and dryers there to like sell sometimes
like like a Staples or like a home like
a Best Buy yeah what would you do if
someone went in and just started like
doing like washing their clothes I
wouldn't do anything it has nothing to
do with me unless I work at Best Buy
then i' be like hey maybe
chill maybe buy that or go to the laundr
mat and use a [ __ ] quarter or
nickel like is that funny to you like
that's not like a fast quick answer like
that that could have gone better in my
opinion like that was that was perfect
like for what I wanted to happen it just
happened flawlessly like I said if I
think of something random could you make
me like laugh and giggle off of a
response and you just perfectly executed
it Nick thank you time to build and and
and come release
know that's not how this one
goes that's
not you sick [ __ ] dog get off that's
not a this one what do you want to watch
it again maybe you sick dog why did I
think I said that I just be I'm a I'm a
goofball and I can't contain my
goofiness making the kangaroo twerk give
me him no give me him leave him be what
is this oh $30 Chris $30 oh my God oh my
God you don't know [ __ ] about the
game what you don't know what it [ __ ]
takes kid stop flinging the dust at me
seriously ni
[Music]
stop get away 24
nothing
winner 25 [ __ ]
bucks get the [ __ ] off get the [ __ ] away
from
me no way you H for 25 yeah let's see if
I got more actually
yeah there's no way we can empty out
every [ __ ] lottery machine in the
[ __ ] Los Angeles County and we can't
[ __ ] hit big like actually what are
you doing it's dark in here what are you
you have a penny I'm about to hit a
million dollar you're not going to get a
million dollar I swear to God I am Matt
are you ready to be a millionaire
billion dollars give me a kabillion
dollars give me a cab billion dollars
give me a kabillion dollars 33 three I
hit no what you get us my God where'd
you get us wait we have to get hype if I
hit it okay are you ready I'm
scared oh no de breath breath oh my God
I'm going to jump on the table if we hit
it Chris what if it's like just $2 no if
it's if it's over two bucks watch me
jump like I'm going to literally hit
Saturn what is it what is it
$4 show me the money oh God that's a
good one that's a good name all right
guys what's up um so we're I know we're
in the middle of doing the scratch
ticket video right now so it's weird
that I just popped up in the middle of
the car but the other day I said like oh
if we film this video if one of you
[ __ ] idiots get
one of those fake scratch tickets I'm
going to be so mad and they were like oh
that's such a good idea blah blah blah
you should have done should have done
that and I was like wait that was a good
idea I should have done that but now
that I said it out loud and they think
like oh like I wouldn't do it I think
now it would be more believable
especially with this one cuz all the
other ones like like the $2 ones and
everything came in the size but this is
a $5 one and it's literally a checked
the exact same size as the other one and
I said that I I was not going to get a
fake ticket yes yesterday and I
overnighted this and it came today so I
think that this could fool them so I'm
going to do my best attempt this is a $5
ticket and it's going to
show that we won $100,000 so 7 30 11 and
9 I like this one it's very simple we
should keep this
one
65 12
can't do this near you guys cuz I just
want to watch you do
it
19 32 did you lose I'm losing so far
248 one last chance 30 no oh we got a
winner Nick no way it's going to be a
ticket watch don't say winner anymore
unless it's [ __ ] all right we got to
pray it's not a ticket guys come on show
me the money
oh what
100 is that 100 or a
th000
100,000 what the [ __ ] this is a fake
ticket this is a fake like one of you
guys bought this one is a fake no oh my
God one of you bought this as a
fake one of you bought this as a fake oh
my God I bought that on Amazon this
morning did you fake yeah and I put it
in that pile I knew it right away I knew
it right away God I knew it
that I knew it right away yes I knew
going to work do that was
good what's up everybody it's Matt and
Bucky here and we're here to tell you
some good news for those of you who are
confused by the Bucky that's in our
living room right now us and our tour
driver have built a very fond
relationship and he is driving another
artist around La right now for their
tour but they had to stop where there
was a Bucky so he bought this and
surprised us and put this in our living
room and it works perfectly because now
not only do we have party time Bucky we
also
have this which is a giant welcome home
we missed you
sign and we also have six confetti
cannons we also have five people from a
mariachi band coming to our house at
7:00 in the morning
tomorrow all right guys we have some
friends with us now and they're here to
help us welcome Nick on this beautiful
what time is it on this beautiful
Tuesday morning at 6:43 in the
morning guys I can't include the audio
to this clip but I we had to include
this moment in our 2024 recap because it
was amazing and it was so fun and
awesome but it would get copyrighted so
I can't keep the the audio but now I'm
going to cut the clip right here but it
it we couldn't do this video without
it I go I look at the menu and it says
beef burger brisket Patty aged cheddar
Smoky tomato relish pickle and tomato
with fries great I love cheeseburgers
but I am a 21y old baby so I like my
burgers with just meat and cheese in a
bun because I'm a simple man plain as
can be plain plain burger that's all I
[ __ ] want and dream of I'm starving
so I pick up the phone and I'm you guys
know I'm if I'm if I'm patient the
person I'm most patient with on Earth is
a customer service worker I will work
through this with you I will speak to
you for 20 minutes I will encourage you
you have my time yeah no worries no
worries at all can I get a cheeseburger
to my room and he goes
I'm sorry at this time we don't have
cheeseburgers available and I'm starving
so I'm like I H I usually be like oh
okay and just hang up but I'm like I
need to eat so I instantly tell this guy
I'm like oh like I checked the menu and
there was like the the the Burger on the
menu and that's like what I want to he
goes oh yeah we don't have a
cheeseburger but we have the beef
burger and I said
okay I'll get that but take everything
off but the cheese
he goes let me check with the chef
please if we can do this I'm like okay
he goes I'll call you back I hang up I
sit literally like this not moving for 5
minutes at the edge of my bed waiting
for the phone to ring phone rings ring
ring ring ring ring ring I answer the
phone yeah so I spoke to the chef and it
at these hours of the night because
we're down to the nighttime menu we can
only do the beef burger and I said no
totally fine completely understand I'll
do the beef burger I don't need
cheeseburger I'll do the beef burger but
I'll just take everything off it but the
cheese yeah and he's like yes so sir we
can't add cheese to the Burger we can't
do a
cheeseburger and I said sir the beef
burger comes with
cheese I'm not asking for something you
don't have I'm asking for a [ __ ] beef
burger keep the cheese on it I'm making
your life easier you don't have to get
the [ __ ] pickles out and the tomato
and the jelly and all this [ __ ] all I
want is cheese okay so then what so I
ask again I say I'm like yes sir the the
beef Burger's to I literally being so
nice I was like the beef I understand
like I understand the beef burger is
totally fine like don't worry about it
like I don't I feel bad like I don't
want you to stress out like the beef
burger is fine I just only want cheese
on it and he goes give me a second hangs
up on me again I sit down I wait for a
call back the manager calls me and she's
like hi um so I I hear you on a
cheeseburger no the beef burger I'm like
yes if you can do that she goes yes so
we can't do a cheeseburger because it's
not on the menu right now but we can do
the beef
burger and this goes on for like 30
minutes I literally dropped to my knees
alone in my room I literally was sitting
there and I dropped to my knees in shock
I'm like I
understand that I can only get the beef
burger but the beef burger comes with
cheese on it so just leave the cheese on
the beef burger what's the difference
between cheeseburger and beef burger
nothing Wait nothing and meanwhile
meanwhile no no meanwhile the day prior
during the day I ordered hey can I get a
beef burger with just the cheese on it
and they're like yeah of course and they
sent it to my room so I'm like what is
the issue now listen isn't a beef
burger like the American hamburger so
it's like cheese I telling yeah I'll
take the beef burger with just cheese on
it yeah but that's not but Chris the
beef burger comes with cheese I'll show
you on the menu it says beef burger
brisket Patty aged cheddar yes got it so
I'm like oh maybe they're getting
confused with the cheese and the cheddar
yes even though cheddar cheese is
[ __ ] cheese I'm like I'm so sorry for
the confusion I hate I like hate being
this guy yeah it's totally fine I just
want a beef burger with cheese and the
lady goes okay okay we can we we
understand you want so you want the beef
burger and you want everything on it but
cheese I said no reverse that keep the
cheese and remove everything else yes
she goes okay so a beef burger with just
cheese anything else and I'm like a
Pepsi yeah and she's like okay and for
the trouble that like All the Troubles
will take off the Pepsi charge I'm like
no you guys can charge me for the Pepsi
you can charge me a 10 million more
dollars just bring me the cheeseburger
just bring me the cheeseburger okay and
they finally they finally bring me my
burger and I ate
it and it was a [ __ ] beef burger with
cheese that's it and a side of fries and
a Pepsi and I had dinner wow but I'm
like the fact that I had to have this
conversation 35 times that's insane blew
my mind blew my mind when I said can I
get the beef burger with nothing on it
but cheese and they're like we can't do
the beef burger no we can't we can't do
a cheeseburger we can only do the beef
burger I said the beefburger is fine so
what is the cheeseburger there the che
the cheeseburger is the same [ __ ]
thing so they have a cheeseburger and a
beef burger on the men there's no
cheeseburger on the menu if you at all
if you ask for ask for a cheeseburger
they just don't understand what's going
on you need to ask for the beef burger
be rid me of this pumpkin
flavor this is a
lot oh my God I thought herge was
falling Nick
really in the mouth I just you took our
fridge Off the Wall no I
didn't thought it was going to fall Nick
goes oh I thought our fridge was falling
ow and just hit me you're insane
[Laughter]
my
goodness what were you
saying let me see let me see let me see
it just show me I will take it just show
me it just show me oh never mind oh my
God I thought it had black licorice but
it's wild berry if you speak it out loud
then your body starts to like react to
that and then like that's why even if I
said like oh something like
I'm not going to say it no stop you
speak that haircut out
loud really
Matt I feel bad so
rude he had nothing to say he said
really
Matt I feel so bad that a mean l that
was a mean
line feel so bad but that was good it's
okay Chris I like your
he's not going to say something stupid
this video that's free money for me
million dollars I'm not I'm an adult I'm
shake my hand on yeah I did wait do you
want me to sit in the middle I know
you're probably going to have like good
no I sit in the middle in the car can
sit in the middle here I just want you
to get your hand off me like get the
[ __ ] you see that he's like this I feel
like this like I feel like four fingers
touching me you're spin that and see if
you you can all be seen you need Elbow
Room get the [ __ ] out of here with that
[ __ ]
Bro she's in Chris's room bro
[Laughter]
yeah you [ __ ]
up wait I he said yeah you [ __ ] up cuz
seriously guess what what you're going
to start having terrible days look at
this search how to summon are you
[ __ ] serious you guys are sick
of like goodby should we start should we
just you guys actually pissed me
off that's so cute he was going like
[Music]
do hey Nick hey what you're up to hold
on F ignore the thing blocking the you
got to what the [ __ ] is going on come
here what the [ __ ] is happening
don't be too loud you're going to disrup
the animal like I'm never leaving the
house again I'm never leaving the house
again I'm seriously
over hi you're so pretty nice to meet
you of course oh that's a turtle this
Buster Buster hi Buster Buster don't
leave like I can't leave the house
anymore I think that us being triplets
but also becoming adults right now we
are realizing so much about each other
in such a good way nothing you have to
share yeah what I'm just a psychopath
what why the other night Nick said you
pick one night a year to be loud and
annoying and Loud how did that make you
feel what what night was this oh I I
have video evidence I can bring it up oh
no no no we don't need the video
evidence no I I love the video evidence
so are you quiet and what's the time at
I'm a very quiet guy yeah I can redirect
everyone's attention
T Jesus what is this this is a video
from the other night when Nick said I
quote you one night a year to be loud
and annoying to
Matt why so that was the other
night Matt was being loud and
dramatic and so you kind of stepped out
play it again I'll
again can we make sure we got a good we
got a good angle that oh my goodness
brother swag need a diploma getting sick
to your stomach going to put down the
soda and I'll switch the language so you
understand [ __ ] shut your [ __ ] I didn't
get it
right I was going to say the last one
wait tough tough tough mat I can't lie
so good
mat ask me if I love the kid I
know what ask me if I love the kid I
hardly Noah am I her yeah okay that was
so good Matt Noah open your put it on my
balls
[Music]
[ __ ] oh my God
dude you're
sick open your boa put it on my balls
[ __ ] I
[Music]
think four seasons is a hotel by the way
in studio eating
pizza yeah I'm just
practicing sitting in the
studio looking at M
he's so
sexy I want to rub his
back yeah he got me
breed like what of These Bars why' you
kind of hit that on
on first time Chris has ever wrapped in
key yeah yeah yeah yeah he got me breed
up hard [ __ ] yeah I don't know I'm
freestyling I don't know I'm just saying
whatever comes to my head that spre was
Elite you must have forgot you Che what
did he say Elite all right I said that
shopping spree was a leap you must have
forgot you
cheap that's crazy that's czy czy true
wow it's actually good it is good I am
cheap you are cheap he got me
bro you Che out of all of us the black
sheep stop talking about that jeep
he just my favorite a Jeep he just my
favorite car
bro
asleep I'm I'm not done I'm not done get
up I'm no
[Music]
way d That's crazy oh my God easy I got
he's out for blood I got to cook I got
to cook he's out for blood hold I have
to cook I was just I wasn't even
bro I wasn't even
dis
that he's he's murmuring right now it's
not even good all right we're do like
the little basic tricks first so I think
you try to go like
this all right just make sure you don't
hit your eye right here okay so show you
just like this you're going just toss it
and just let oh my God all right
don't drop in the floor cuz we going use
this to eat oh God okay yeah a tiny and
then it's going to flip and
then I'm going to do it like play bypl
here like Red Zone like that and then
it's going to spin yeah but don't do it
too hard cuz it will either go that way
right in the middle or right towards you
I'll do it gentle yeah so have it like
this the goal and like a gentle is it
better if it falls on the stove like on
the on the make sure you don't grab it
I'll grab it if it falls on the stove
got don't burn yourself
oh that I can barely Shake someone's
hand let alone flip a [ __ ] saucer I
don't know what that is go try it let's
go yeah whoever's in the middle watch
out cuz I see I got you and you know and
you know my capability level so you got
to really just like that first time all
right so we're going here all the way
up you come do that again I can't you
can do that that was really good someone
does a banger you if you just do exactly
what he says it's easy just show you got
a little classic we got some egg rolls
for you guys
only okay and you get one chance to look
at it yeah if you didn't see it just get
me back tomorrow cuz I'm always here all
right all right here you go got you guys
and now one you guys got to hold it so
here you're going to hold this real
quick for me but don't throw that one I
want to go blind to yeah just hold it
real quick here show here show you a
little bit all right you ready yeah yeah
you know what to do I think so no you're
not ready let me tell you you're going
to this three times okay tap it three
times here you go one two
three can all see it here you go we got
two yeah I'm parttime magician cookies
that was crazy there just thought I used
to do magic when I was a young kid wait
wait
okay all right all right all right
ladies and gentlemen welcome I have an
empty bowl here sure you do
[Laughter]
you
do tell me more about the ball
whatever go I want to see you do it it
would have been I want to see you do it
I want to see you do it let's see it no
you were doing CHR come on I'll pretend
I didn't see it I such a good what a
great fun dinner that we got to have
together for con such an amazing dinner
thumbnail thumbnail
thumbnail I'm eating it put the Pepsi in
my mouth Matt like I got you I got you
thumbnail Habachi dinner gone
wrong I got stuck in Habachi din get the
[ __ ] okay that was the Su video I feel
very very successful and then she's done
we're like thank God already took 20
[ __ ] minutes and then she's like oh I
I wanted to buy cigarettes and I I need
like money back so she starts trying to
make a return at the thing like you need
to bring your [ __ ] to the service desk
she decided she decided that she didn't
want like four of the items that she
already purchased and instantly tried to
but instead instead of also instead of
also buying cigarettes she was trying to
make like a trade like here's the four
items that I accidentally bought that
don't want anymore I want my two back
two boxes of cigarettes that's the
that's what she want she wanted she
wanted to barter instead of like return
she thought she was a [ __ ] pirate oh
I'm bringing two cannonballs in a Year's
worth of py to your ship if you give me
your [ __ ] yeah two goats and some
[ __ ] maze I don't know corn yeah yeah
maze is
corn
and so he refunds her $9 onto her card
at the thing which I'm already like dude
you shouldn't have done that should have
sent her to the service desk your job
was done and he's like he refunds her $9
she puts her card in gets the $9 on her
card and literally takes her card out
and doesn't she goes where are the
cigarettes he's like I gave you $9 on
your go where's the cash he goes go you
just put your card on in the machine so
she's like in her brain she deserves $9
like looking around out like in the
world I pull a 20 from my bag I'm like
if this takes another goddamn minute I'm
going to buy this lady cigarettes and
smoke one with her cuz I'm losing my
[ __ ] mind I'm losing it I'm going to
become a nicotine addict so I'm looking
at her so hold
on so it doesn't end there it doesn't
end there it's do end there commercial
break commercial
break so it's been at least
not joking dude you have literal tear
you need it's been it's been not joking
anywhere from 18 to 23 minutes that's
where we're at dude you look like you're
crying cuz I just not kidding that's how
long it's taken 18 to 23 minutes not
kidding now round three the lady the
lady in front of us turns around and she
goes I don't know if you boys are too
young Margarita KN yes no she didn't
invite us to the margarita night I'm
asking for
clarification are you drinking are you
drinking I need it dring her wine and
then I got 36 of these 36 of these I
think you 36 left they not your dentures
out you hippie hippie freak Chris I
think if you went back to this store my
feet would be like the [ __ ] TSA x-ray
you'd see my [ __ ] feet on the ground
where Nix stolo lost his [ __ ] mind
Isle eight dead serious there better be
a placard next time I go there and a
[ __ ] Express G
pass give me the [ __ ] Genie the lady
in front of us turns around not the one
that's like causing all the problem the
one I got it she turns around and she
goes I don't know if you boys are too
young but I feel like I'm on punked
right
nowz I'm waiting for John I literally
looked up I go where's the film
C I'm going to go first with my ranking
and I'm not going to be biased and I'm
going to be honest okay I put Matt
number one because I think it is
he is like if I was walking on the beach
I would think that I'd see someone dress
like Matt first out of all three of us I
agree and that's why he's getting my
number one vote for this round I agree
thank you so much yep who so you lost
your mind so number two vote Chris I'd
give number two to Nick and i' I'd take
the third place I have the I agree with
the same standards and you're and I'm
being fair as well thank you yes of
course Matt is clearly Matt is clearly
like going to the beach like it's a good
second place you look horrible okay so
so so first round I didn't say you look
iist you oh I'm telling the truth though
first round I didn't dis you be quiet be
quiet first round I am first you are
second you are third that's the average
yeah unfortunately and what you guys and
contrary to popular belief they can vote
going to vote I'm not left I know that
they're going to vote that mine's the
best okay put on the unless these girls
want to sleep with Matt vote for him him
cuz he's got the straight man's
Advantage because you guys are going to
discriminate against me cuz I'm gay and
you I don't like you
back clock that that's a lot so if I get
third it's cuz I know people are
sympathy voting for ma okay but you're
gay wouldn't that make them vote for you
out of guilt
corre poor little gay poor this is I'm
gay
but STP
sign okay I'm feeling it uh how do you
feel about the Elder Wand is this is
that crazy of me sorry the Elder Wand oh
my God if I can if I can wield its magic
I'm totally it's the most you it's the
most magical wand in all Hogwarts oh
Matt why do you want to play with the
most magical wand and Hogwart I do I do
I'm just saying hear me out no I
whoever's got whoever whoever's got this
it's going to be a little bit harder for
me to agree with this one Chris it's not
about the wand's shape it's about the
wand's power
are we ready Judy hops
of that photo is cool what is what's the
photo oh wait my bad wrong
photo J my God y'all didn't see the
first photo oh
you like it's obvious a little
Shrine this you got to show the camera
that one I put the Beast before he turns
into a person of course we can't have
so the Beast is the Beast yes okay
what's the beast's name Beast it's
Beauty and the Beast Beauty and the
Beast yeah him and The Riddler okay um
him and The Riddler at the same
time dude what I'm saying you expect me
to have my Factbook of turkey knowledge
no I expected you to shut he expected
silence and unfortunately he was gret
with gret GRE describe it
okay I'm going to bleed out my hand
you're going to [ __ ] hit my my hand
my hand my buck crack's not out I saw it
you're going to smack he just L like
this like that oh yeah you want now do
you look like under under
show get out of here I don't have my
butt crack up yeah you do then what's
that us what else Chris I'm thankful for
I'm thankful for a lot of things ah
I'm thankful for I'm thankful for my
sweatshirt cuz Matt bought me the
sweatshirt I bought you this sweatshirt
Chris I did right Chris Chris's eyes are
like I'm thankful for my under bite of
thanful that I
get it's funny doesn't have under I a
perect I'm thankful that I get to scream
and yell at car videos all the time
and I'm thankful that I get to go
whatever
[Laughter]
thanks and I hate it I hate
it I hate it cuz I end up making I end
up making fun of you in the clips that I
see of myself of the things that you do
all the time I'm thankful for sports I'm
thankful for soup I'm thankful
for [ __ ] you eat soup you always eat
soup I you've eat just as much as soup
as I uh I'm thankful for stuffy I'm
thankful for stuffy stuff like stuffed
animal pug I'm thankful for Derek white
I'm thankful for I'm thankful for soda
I I Tock H sodas a day I'm thankful for
restaurants cuz I get french fries and
soda you're
thankful you're thankful for I'm
thankful for my Baga boots and my CR
Parts earring what's his name I'm
thankful for Carl Jun I'm thankful for
Walter White I'm thankful for MTH
because we can make a whole TV
show Carl
junor oh my
God my God for car I'll kill you Carl
God my [ __ ] God I'm thankful I'm
thankful for car Jun you're not that
serious
I I meant Walter what makes it so much
funnier is that he said Walter right
after the funniest thing is I said I'm
thankful for meth because they can make
a whole TV show about
it that
way just disbelieve you see it was that
way can't do nothing about it it's human
rights
man you rather sleep on bricks or
concrete someone asked same thing yeah
like you're not giving us much much
diversity here literally maybe the
bricks I can like caress the little
crease as I fall asleep for like some
comfort some Edge yeah literally there's
a little bit of like there's a little
edge of some texture to it but better
tactile experience I actually really I
[ __ ] with like when ow
what what it just scared the [ __ ] out of
me imagine how I feel what happened this
bow just fell off my head and grazed my
face I thought I was being attacked by
like a [ __ ] bug I thought you just
touched this I'm going to go like this
and you guys can see how whoever catch
whoever catches more wins are you guys
ready instantly got ready he's going
[ __ ] oh I way more way more way more
count count 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
13 14 15
my let's
go 1 2
3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13
oh [ __ ] go with my bare hands I like
this like I was [ __ ] praying to God
they all landed in my hands [ __ ] you
Matt
[ __ ] we need to eat those sight on
the table they're all over the place
let's give it a
rating she tasting a
peep yeah okay well you're going to die
yeah like like like like what do I
do how does one bounce back from
marshmallow
bitching
seriously
ohud
FU oh my God I got it I got it the
reflexes Prevail once again that was the
best catch I ever made
it the in I feel like that's kind like
okay get
[Music]
don't that was like kind of weird right
was that kind of weird Nick or or am I
losing it what that kind of weird hello
how are you good how are you I'm so
sorry about oh don't worry what you
sorry about I have no idea I'm great
thank you
okay sorry thank you no problem you like
any catch up today by any um I'm okay no
okay thank you I almost said Yes again
you are those two Burger plane here
those three thank you so much than you
how thank you
to I like thought she was tripping but
oh look at this hat on this lady she
look like she going to explore the wi
CHR goes how are you she goes I'm okay
that's no she said I'm sorry no she said
she came back over she said I'm good and
then one hour Chris goes okay yeah I was
just like confused I was like okay buddy
well I was just confused by what she was
telling me I'm good he go this lady look
at this look at this bow on the license
plate gay I I don't know what I used to
be such a bold person like I'm bold on
in terms of us yes like in like our
vicinity but I would never just go up to
someone and say something like rude or
F there's a photo of me in my Snapchat
memories and they're slow dancing at the
school dance and I'm like gagging myself
with my finger and pointing at them like
like throwing up yes they're right
behind me in it's a flash photo of me of
them slow dancing right behind me you
have the photo yes dude we have to put
it in the video no no just blur them out
it's literally me being like disgusted
by theming each other I'm like that's
ter I think the craziest like slow or
school dance memory that I have is like
just like kids that I thought like
presuming that they were just like
innocent kids sh like deliver like just
delivering like back shots to somebody
at prom like like that's crazy what's
good [ __ ] gang [ __ ] gang I thought
that was a test for the mic like I
didn't think that was a straight
video that was pure honest
reaction wow I'm surprised that
those Merry Christmas Christmas I wanted
this Donut for far too long we caught
your hand in the cookie jar
[Laughter]
terrifying pornographic I know it's not
shirtless Cowboys 2025 we have a
collection we to Countdown the days with
you wait is this
firefighters this one's
exciting oh my God A Firefighter
Calendar a cowboy calendar and hunks and
Trunks we can eat which what's your pick
Chris I'm good you don't want one no I
like the shortless Cowboys one the most
sorry sorry sorry sorry I murder
him hey Merry
Christmas did I get the same thing open
it
[Music]
up oh my God Mt I don't want any nieces
or nephews anytime soon I'd rather you
have these then and do I hear you're
welcome thank you man thanks man
[Music]