oh then you don't get any of my Twisters
Point yet well that's crazy cuz I have
them right
here you could say you got those pulled
and Beed away
from that was chaos Matt is when we when
he shuts the [ __ ] up in car videos and
doesn't speak and then we leave the
house and then you're interrupting him
and and in reality in real world Matt
speaks the most out of all of us yes
once the cameras are off this kid
doesn't well no Matt it's just he takes
you'll never understand the real me then
you're oh my God no listen to me why
what I hate why when Matt asks me for
directions cuz I'm have my phone plugged
in uh I literally get in the car I'll be
like this I'll sit down close my door
for reversing instantly like I need to
buckle I need to [ __ ] buckle up I
need to take my jacket off I need to
take my phone out CE a few grab my
drink next thing you know I'm in I'm
moving already so I'm like wow on the
and then you want to know something
Chris and and then and then and then we
don't even know where we're going oh I'm
kind of hungry what do you guys want to
eat what do you guys want to eat so we
don't have a location to we're like a
minute away from the house oh let's go
to let's go to Canes let's go to Cavo
let's go to Taco Bell and I'm like okay
I don't know where we're going oh Taco
Bell I put it in it's like Taco Bell
[ __ ] this Taco Bell [ __ ] Taco Bell
[ __ ] this Taco Bell I'm like there's
80 different Taco Bells I get yelled at
if I put in the directions wrong so I
have to like look and pick which one and
for some reason the first one that
always pops up on my ways is 397,000 M
away like oh hey head to this one it's
only in [ __ ] guom Canada like I've
never even seen that place in my life
why is that the first you want to know
what really pisses me off Chris blows my
mind come on guys I don't know how to
get there and then we're like pulling
out of the [ __ ] you want to know what
really aggravates me with this whole
driving debacle nope when I you have to
do this you have to do that and I have
my backpack I what's in what's in in the
backpack all of the [ __ ] [ __ ] for
your job my camera my Vlog camera the
battery chargers everything everything
that makes you mat stolo makes your job
your job is in my
backpack what
about and the batter's dead what about
we go to film and the battery's dead
when we go to film any Cravings right
now like what are you a soft pretzel
with a Sal on it
with
cheese cheese can it come go yeah it can
stay on the counter chro from Costco
listen poor design listen listening how
much wood could a wood chuck chuck if a
wood chuck could chuck wood I feel like
a woodchuck doesn't even chuck wood and
I I feel like it should be called
question isn't a woodchuck in
otter can you sit down are you for real
why are you what's a wood chuck that's a
real animal agree with you I'm thinking
it's just water are they are they no cuz
now since I'm the odd one out I'm
thinking can you sit the [ __ ] down sorry
I'm like the the seat warmers on and it
feels really nice I want you can spin
around you know like I got enough of it
on my back so now I'm just really
feeling it on it's not really on my back
it's on my leg like on my ass no like
your lower back like right here feels
really I don't really feel warmth right
there really cuz I'm kind of like
getting like I don't know I don't know I
don't feel it feels
okay no not for me okay now it's her
well is oh mine's on yeah yeah that's
what I'm saying yeah mine's mostly on my
ass yeah same what are we doing sorry I
just get what are we doing what are we
doing we're so we're so weird what are
we
doings oh my
God record record where did they all go
they're on the side of the sidewalk on
the curb that's a funny thing it too a
curb rat at the dumpster ratty ratat
record r r rat there's like seven of
them there's none no we need to bring
cheese one day how think that actually
works ni would all yes I'm not that's
cap oh like your fit is e like lingo yes
like oh your fit's eating up like you're
slaying right now they'd be like they'd
be like what the [ __ ] did you just call
me I'm not slaying I'm not I'm not on
the battlefield great Heavens great
Heavens great my great bippy was slain 3
weeks ago correct they get all defensive
I feel like oh so you're eating is gross
they'd be like what no they'd be like oh
we already got this oh my God that's a
big chunker a big chunker really correct
like a tissue could be a disposable an
[ __ ] how do you think they felt about
an [ __ ] dis disregard how do you
think they felt disregard what are you
saying disregard ungard [ __ ] I'm
on that same [ __ ] thing fencing can
we fence for a video oh my God yeah okay
why why isn't fencing more known I saw
that [ __ ] in Wednesday and I was like
damn I need to get a piece of
that ching
like it's so like ug like it's like a
good old classic sword fight but no harm
can we fence like absolutely I would
mess you up let's find legit fencing
place and try to do it we should fence
in a room full of fences and make it
like a cage so we're fencing through the
fences the fencing fencers okay no the
real my burp smells
spicy over there the wall oh my God let
me lo my
[Laughter]
mus aim
[Music]
steady I said it smells like that they
put a [ __ ] onion ring in my French
fries and it's a mystery and like I'm
like eating like all these fries and
they all taste like onions I'm like
what's going on and I get to the bottom
of it literally I got to the bottom of
it and it was an onion ring oh my god
get rid of it like you're waving it
around
you're going to die I was about to throw
it outside but now that makes me want to
keep it in here for a little bit
longer it's not that Chris that was just
unnecessary
Nick now you got hit with an onion ring
you stupid
kid I bet you there are more people that
care about my fries having an onion ring
than you not wanting that onion ring in
the car now they will and now they'll go
back and talk about it what do you think
people care about more me having an
onion ring in my fries or him not
wanting they were both forgettable
experiences they were both forgettable
I'm not saying that
my fries is far far more rememberable
than not
true why smelling onion I'm not helping
out anyone cuz you why would first of
all people don't care about your you're
arguing like I think people give a [ __ ]
that I smelt it I don't I don't think
people care that I smelled the onion
ring I'm arguing that from one it's
one-sided no one I don't think people
care about my onion ring and the fries
but you were talking about it and I said
get rid of it and then you're like
you're just you wouldn't stop you're
like holding on to it naming it dressing
it it's fine it's an onion R you go why
don't you go outside I just didn't care
you go outside your [ __ ] onion rings
out there go get him my God you didn't
take his clothes off he's probably
lonely and take a walk I'm good I'm
surpris you eat yeah leaving that in I
just got body sham by CH fat phobic no
I'm not I'm just surprising yes you are
you just body sham me I'm keeping in it
has nothing to do with your size I just
know your big
appetite
I'm sweat
here I don't look good in hats but I'm
buying this [ __ ] hat 758 you guys could
call me a [ __ ] head seven bro they don't
have my size I'm getting this hat
oh you liking that you want to see me
hit the
gritty you think you can do better
what is this conv what is this
conversation we're
having that's true cuz people have
confirmed it that work there you ready
jelly beans what I thought you were
going to talk about like a candy factory
for some go ahead go ahead just go I'm
gone no mine would be last name Ender
first name Cal
calender oh my God
I calendar oh my God yes yes cuz you can
end that's here oh my
godal Cal St I don't think I'll be
eating this it looks so sweet oh [ __ ]
what's in the middle wow oh it smells
like yeah that smells so good oh my
[Laughter]
God y are all
moaning
um
ice Frozone Frozone froz like imagine
like he needs water like there's too
much requirement got it right there no
there's too much of a requirement I feel
like there it's just you got to get
lubed up like he doesn't got to
like no why he's just got to get a
little wet
like
Christopher goodness that out yeah for
real like he just got like he doesn't
need water the whole time like say he
has a glass he just has to get started
he go let me get my drink and then he go
like then he refes correct like he
he h flying boring I must be a pirate
cuz I'm looking for some
[Laughter]
[Music]
booty you must be
jelly cuz Jam don't shake like
that that it's dishes cuz I want you to
get me wet and do me
that's foul wait o what Nick my neck's
like
cracking this is cute yeah yeah I feel
like a little like I was going to say
something crazy yeah don't do you know
when no it's not crazy like bad it's
crazy I was going to say something it's
crazy just like super bizarre what you
go first I was going to say something
really weird go see I was going to say I
feel like a little lion cuup like when
the mom yeah that's Weir like when the
mom like licks it a lot to get it clean
like I feel like I'm just like being
like cleaned by my Mama C okay by the M
okay I think you're good it's a little
messy but whatever no matter what we
were doing everything was getting
dropped running at it ready to go also I
remember wiping my ass once and J like
beat up J time I was
like as much wiped his ass on me did
what did I say hold on I'm
confused yeah out oh word all right
gotcha what is this no
idea I'm very we just got kicked out by
[ __ ] Mall
[Applause]
Cop
I couldn't have said that any more clear
lukewarm hot fudge you don't think
there's anything worse yeah why would
they make hot fudge what about
kidnapping I think that's worse than it
should be warm fudge then if they're
going to [ __ ] like if they're going to
lie and say hot fudge make it hot at
least kidnapping no one's lying to you
you straight up getting stolen yeah
you're getting kid
Penny cuz the penny costs like more than
a penny to make it cost like a penny and
a half let's what yeah that's why the
penny was extinct how much does it cost
so for real you really care about the
penny no it's just I I remember this the
penny was it cost 2.1
cents I told you this Penny was in
danger cuz you got to double down in the
penny so who's doing it like the
government that's why we're in so much
debt we keep making pennies so oh my God
so if we stop making pennies it'd solve
a lot of problems but I love
pennies isn't Abraham Lincoln on the
penny yeah I love Abraham Lincoln I just
love I love Abraham Lincoln Matt what do
you turn I like top hat like his beard
Matt what are you doing look I don't
remember why is he laughing it's funny
cuz I know the only reason Nick likes
Abraham linoln is cuz of his [ __ ] top
F true Nick loves Nick said he wanted
the same top hatat as abam loln I feel
like I've always ever since I was young
like just resonated really well
with like since I was like five I
remember just loving Abraham
Lincoln but not in like a weird way of
like oh I love Abraham Lincoln I just
love the guy he just I just had this
weird connection like kind of like when
kind of like when people are like
reincarnated I just guy I know like do
you guys remember that show Ghost Inside
My
Child and like the kids used to tell
stories to their parents about like you
know a like didn't wear the hat all the
time
yeah yes he did no he didn't he did it
hard
e
m it ain't no way
brother here you can even dull The Taste
here's a bigger french fry that you can
like put with it you know I feel like I
feel like I'm going pale like come on
here this will make it better I swear to
God the more food you add the less
ketchup you taste you have to go quick
the camera's going to die I'm I have to
hold my nose do
it you got this mat it's literally I
can't it's just a wet french fry 10 9 8
7 6
it's going to get on your finger so
hurry can you get me a cup of mouth wash
for after it's right there I'm not you
put that in your mouth hurry up we're at
10 we're the camera's going to
die swallow it swallow it swallow it
swallow it swallow it swallow it swallow
it yummy
ketchup I'm going to go cry I cannot
believe that the tears oh each person me
it has to be kind of spontaneous though
so don't think too much okay but
describe yourself in one
word I'm the biggest hater ever a that's
not good I plot on 90% of people's
downfall wow Nick ni that's so untrue
you bring joy to so many people's lives
that's good Matt one word to describe
you that and you know what the ants is
going to change next week going to
change I know it's going to change the
ant change tomorrow nervous is a good
one but I can't make that my whole thing
one word that pops in what are you what
isolo all about um one word delicious is
mine that's that's disgusting word to
describe czy um delicious is wild for me
I'd say right now delicious is just
right now I want you guys to think back
when you were little like I mean like in
your pajamas like com coming downstairs
why wouldn't you say like diapers sorry
pajamas like your footsy pajamas you I
wear pajamas like to this day
that's oh wow what avocado
creaming pretty fresh avocado that wow
that's like magazine avocado thank you
that's like the meme get thank you not
near my other half and it's like the
avocado no this is definitely like the
avocado meme where it's like me and you
I didn't know there was an avocado meme
on wa I know exctly you guys are like
that's like the meme of like no you know
like the good old I know Matt had a few
meme account mhm you'll find it
somewhere match my chocolate yeah
choking guys
bro all right french fries in Ready set
go what's the noise
for it wasn't that bad I give it like a
6 out of 10 never doing it again but 6
out of 10 see this is my weird [ __ ] bro
I really [ __ ] with
this very very mixed reviews across the
board I really [ __ ] with this we have
whimpering and pain tolerable and you
really [ __ ] with it what a crazy olive
oil and vanilla ice
cream
oh the oil's not hitting for me the oil
hit for me and it's not I hope it never
hits again oh it's kind of good you're
and they don't actually get hurt like
you know little kids are like made of
[ __ ] foam I think it's so funny that
little kidre how little kids physically
feel after like a tumble or something is
solely off of other people's reaction
yeah like if you go oh they're going to
cry for years but if you're like you're
fine they could be gushing blood out of
their head and they will fully just c
yeah like if a baby gets you could punch
a baby like a you're good
like like you second cry especially when
like a baby falls and kind of like face
plants and they're still okay everyone
around
like and then the baby's
like every single person looked at the
baby so he you have to assume the baby's
a okay until you until you further you
got to it's like a fake until you make
it situation for sure cuz then the kid
thinks it's like way more serious that's
what me and Matt used to do with
you he's hiding it's a guy with a dog
exactly what's he going to do fall I
just don't like
men is he gone no
no Nick lock the door lock the door you
said that was such a good word bro how
much money to eat a whole bin of potato
salad yourself I never what potato
potato salad oh my God what's a bin and
what you just literally added something
to my [ __ ] list of top 10 fears
literally you could put me on fear fact
in that like I could be on the season
finale of [ __ ] Fear Factor already
suffered through a pile of grasshoppers
10 stinging scorpions a bat last thing
eat a bucket of potato salad count me
the [ __ ] out I'm done I'm tapping out
put me with like a 100 African bullfrogs
I'd rather survive that you put me with
poisonous spiders and I'd be like okay
this is good like a little [ __ ] oh my
God over the rainbow I tried to type in
potato salad it
oh oh my God that's so
terrifying s a l I literally rather
I you could jump scare me better you
could jump scare me better in like a
[ __ ] horror movie like imagine they
put like a sharp tune like it could
either be the babadook or the potato
salad the babad I wouldn't Flinch at all
potato salad I'm running and pissing oh
my God it's like a chunky Cole SLA
potato salad is a salad that's the
funniest T well explain it it and then
I'll throw a clip the guy goes up to
random people and he goes hey and then
ask him a question and as soon as he
answer go all right all right all right
like is invested when he asks gives him
Absol zero he makes him seem like he
wants to listen but then he just doesn't
do that
exactly hey is a highlight yeah really
wow yeah this was the only one they had
in all right that's enough that's enough
thanks you Mt I feel like we just share
like if you get ripped up by someone you
rip them back up that's how we sure go
ahead
the one of Matts is he sleeps with a
stuffed animal that's that's not the red
flag though the red flag is that the
stuffed animal has severe privileges
over the spot on his bed and the rules
of the bed so if you sit in the bed but
the stuffed animal Falls you have to
like pick him up apologize put him back
if you want to lay on the left side with
his stuffed animals there Mr puckington
has to tell you oh Mr wrinkles has to
tell you whether or not you're allowed
to sit there so the red flag is not the
stuffed animal itself it's the fact that
the S animal is literally a tyrant of
the B that's the problem that was great
okay I have I have one combo one though
like a group one okay go ahead you guys
both ask me questions as if I work for
the brand and then you're asking
questions like that are ridiculous like
you you guys be asking like the warranty
and like the [ __ ] Apple care and I'm
like I do not know I do not work there
I've never worked there and I don't
[ __ ] know the answer to your
questions Chris is like like why is that
WiFi out and I'm like I don't know cuz I
also don't have Wi-Fi then I use my
critical thinking skills and I go to the
living room where the Wi-Fi router is
and Chris unplugged it so I plug it back
in and I'm like oh maybe that's the
solution to your Wi-Fi problem or we
could be like eating and mt's like
what's in this like the restaurant I'm
like I don't work here I don't know the
ingredients I'd tell you if I did but I
don't and it's questions that are so
specific like you literally have to work
at The Establishment or for the company
of the question question you guys are
asking me also I'm I actually named
Chris's brand but he's not going to say
that that's not true no you like are the
first person to okay it that's not true
no he was the first person to say it out
loud cuz what happened
was listen
listen list a little bit of fork in the
road listen listen listen listen he
really come up with it but we can't it
was more it more like a duel like
togetherness cuz I was like Matt my two
logos are like a heart and orange like
what what's the
first I like what's the first word that
comes to mind when you think of orange
he was like oh fresh I was like what
about a heart he's like love and I was
like oh fresh love and he's like oh yeah
it's like works out well and I was like
okay word like it was more of like a
teen thing like he was like hey your
name should be this that and I was like
okay yeah it wasn't like pitched to you
correct was for who we are
anyway bro so weird I kind of love this
cuz sometimes like I want a tattoo but
my heart hardest decision is what it's
going to
be that should be the hardest decision
that should be like the most like
thought out decision but that's not for
me he's Carlos the magic rabbit no he
was
thought I love this is this on my leg
Yeah Trident nice Trident I love that
Poseidon I love posidon I know it's nice
and small too or like thin thin thin
thin there's so much room for play down
there
what play for other
tattoos you what I meant insane man no
you're just ridiculous W I love it I
have the saved as an idea that's awesome
thank you Matt yep you did good you
listen like so annoy no it's like you
did good you like knew that that'd be
something I liked
next disco ball yes I love that idea too
he looks so good at the Snowman the
Snowman doesn't have a name though I got
to name him like that okay they attemp
but they talk with a baby voice I say
zero that [ __ ] really scares me that's
the most foul thing in the world I
especially like imagine imagine cuz like
nobody should be talking like that no
one like even being unless you're
talking to a baby I still I don't get
it's still corny I love when people just
straight up talk to kids like they're
like grown yeah what up bro and like
fish bum I love when it's like a kid
like oh you like that and the kid's like
sucking on like a pacifier or something
oh like you know I you know I that was
insane you know what I meant thate like
the kids like eating an app sace you
like the applesauce you know what I mean
you guys are insane that was awful you
took that out of context
insane you
don't it's not that funny stay in the
video
please dick that was you know how poor
your
word I know but what I meant was like
when a kid's like eating like a food or
like has like you know what I mean how's
your meal that's yummy car video cuz I
always feel like I have to lean in to be
in the frame but then I feel like my
like like can I speak man
turt go ahead I forgot what I was saying
you interrupted me there's no way why
inter me so [ __ ] you [ __ ] I forget
yeah you look like a forget you
look was really close to something that
was
crazy I meant to say you look like you
forget like you like I saw the that was
crazy what was I saying I don't know you
l i don't I just it's like it's nothing
could happen in which my body has a
physical reaction of excitement like
like I just don't Nick that's just a
personal preference that's not you can't
it's a personal experience not
preference it it never happens okay okay
what I'm saying is you can't like hate
on people for showing they're excited
about things I can okay yeah oh let's go
I'm like oh my God that's insane no but
also I I've seen you do that I've seen
you me so for real and instacart got to
the house and I like no it was it so
beyond for real never
Che let's go it's not that exactly but
I've seen you get like excited that's
not true there was an instaart you
ordered an insta car to the house I
forget what you got it was like you
needed like batteries or something and
like I'm saying let's go cuz two Double
A's got on my doorstep with no [ __ ]
chance I'm like I notoriously sound
sarcastic in every circumstance like
that's why I
felt
oh my I was FaceTiming the group
chat this is the prank Liam
n all over my bedroom is the
prank oh my God you didn't even see that
I didn't even see that
one take a look where's my one take a
look around I'm sure you'll find more by
Magic ruler hammer stapler marry the
hammer really I love a hammer you love a
good Hammer I'm deeply devoted to a nice
Hammer like I'm like what no um I just
like Hammer you're sick I just like a
hammer
shape de do a stapler I feel like a
stapler specific it's it gets jammed I
thought you were going to be a big
stapler fan kill the stapler no kill the
stap I'm killing the ruler if I have a
tape measure around no a ruler how
people here for some reason regardless I
[ __ ] hate staplers they're useless
they've been done before but you love
getting
Hammer okay we're going to move on I'm
just going to read the next
one oh
man I feel like there's no world where
you should be in the feto position
W the first time you see someone like
2:30 it's not the morning anymore it's
like [ __ ] yourself I hope be have a
terrible week I hope be have a terrible
night I hope you have a terrible
afternoon and I hope you had a bad
morning since we're using past tense now
[ __ ] yourself like when I say good
morning you at least at least respect
the thought that I attempted to wish you
a good morning now that you're all mad
that I said morning I hope your morning
was [ __ ] miserable I hope you got
[ __ ] on by a bird I hope your car was
locked you forgot your keys I hope you
rocked and cracked your phone I hope
your kids [ __ ] tripped on the way to
school I hope your day was [ __ ]
terrible so far how about that good
morning oh it's actually afternoon oh
[ __ ] yourself I don't care at all the
attempt was there it was made clear and
it's not that detrimental of a [ __ ]
difference at all between morning and
afternoon oh my and if it means that
much to you I hope you have a terrible
all
three how do you feel about people that
will say that was actually yesterday at
like 12:01 oh even worse even worse even
worse when you're trying to like talk
about a plan it's like midnight and
you're like oh tomorrow morning you mean
today it's like no [ __ ] I count night
sleep I don't count past midnight and
it's the always the [ __ ] that
correct you at like 12:05 like they
catch you so off guard cuz they'll be
like you mean today and you're just like
what the [ __ ] are you even talking about
then you check the time and you're like
oh you're one of those [ __ ] weirdos
that like using it completely correct
like you're right but it's like you're a
loser you know what I mean what is it
don't worry about it what is it couple
100 miles from Japan
tonight that one almost stayed trapped
inside all right what are your top three
meats I think top meat for me and I
think that this can be spoken for for a
lot
wrong top meat and it's in the name it's
the meat man meatball number one in my
opinion we got meatball coming in on top
then chicken two reliable good constant
consistent we love them chicken we got
meatball number one chicken number two
number three I'm not a steak fan so hear
me out I'm going Che
hamburger
slap some cheese on it so hamburgers
made of ground beef you want to else
made of ground beef tacos ground beef is
three I'm not going to say it cuz I
can't speak Spanish but there's some
Spanish meat that I love that I refuse
to say CU I sound white as [ __ ] but we
got
honestly I might like top three hangout
spots it's all stupid dummy top three
hangout spots none of your business I
see your strategy with asking us that oh
you know where do they hang out I want
to their top three so I can maybe the
park I like hanging out sketchy alleys
at 4:00 a.m. go find
me do you
see that was a joke um joke he said
friends how last one to three pastas are
we going sauce included or just pasta
shape that's really important really
really dude I don't let's figure it out
let's do both okay sauce top three
pastas no sauce no sauce I got to go fet
angel hair fet wa angel hair
insane
literally F FY Penny Penny Penny
whatever did I say it wrong got to go
rare pick for number one coming from me
Ron incorrect
rigon top three ways you want to die oh
my God probably blunt force trauma to
the
he driving over that bridge I see
them I see someone right there right in
front of
me knocked them DJ honey but see you
later oh my dear great Heavens I'm
behind them right in front of
you 50 white pushing I'm getting in on
this kid I'm getting in on
him who who's your Daddy come here buddy
what he's so yes I got him I'm stuck
like in a tree that isn't actually there
okay other kid near me 50 he's a baby
I'm on his ass like [ __ ] ants on a
picnic I'm coming after you get I'm
trying to become a fortnite YouTube
channel [ __ ] car videos I was going to
say to lay an egg but that's
cool oh buddy oh don't you regret that
decision oh [ __ ] I'm dead
Chris fall damage fall damage fall
damage fall damage fall damage mat I'm
down here on the
balcony oh my God who's your daddy Matt
come on bro don't say weird
[ __ ] we should be a good boy and let me
revive you all right what are you saying
right
there okay who's most likely to walk in
on someone in the
bathroom Matt me my personal opinion is
mad I Tri you how do you talk so quiet
but like say loud stuff you know what I
mean what if that was me I would have
said me and he goes me like it's so
quiet but he wants to be loud just let
it out man okay I got you say it again
me it felt too forced okay okay okay it
felt too forced I need you to bring it
he said okay open up me yeah that was
more like it you have a beast inside let
him
out okay I feel like you don't really
let out your true like umph sometimes
and I just need to see it CU I save my
um up like to anime things God you have
too much ump bro your ump is [ __ ] you
need less ump as well whatever bro I
can't talk anym whatever bro whatever
bro I just talk too much and I feel like
an idiot bro you guys got to help me out
here what the [ __ ] I just said oh [ __ ]
respectful I really like when I have
this hat on it's hot take the [ __ ]
hat off you want the wig nope I'll take
it my hair's probably even more [ __ ]
up cute so weird on you it's like double
it's like a layer like an
Oreo ah it's in my eye [ __ ] I feel like
I just got pepper sprayed look like NE I
get it out get it out get it
out oh my god do you have water it was
like dust it was dust it was
dust
oh it's in my eye Matt your forehead now
you can move it what am I a plant get
out of
here I thought you were going to get out
I need I needed to stand up but my foot
couldn't extend what's wrong I got dust
in my eye jackass what the [ __ ] do you
think is wrong I just said it literally
stated what was wrong three times said
there something in my eye oh it was dust
you're you're like oh wow you're
helpless and I don't mean wow that was
rude low low blow low blow low blow low
blow I don't mean help you're helpless
Ian you're not you're
pathetic [ __ ] you go [ __ ] yourself let
me speak I don't mean helpless in like
the term of like the word helpless
usually I mean help look now without hat
listen I mean oh my God Nick look at
that oh my God there's millions of them
Chris there's hundreds of them I'm not
as scared of big birds like this this is
why look how cool that bird telling that
tell me that first bird isn't any ones
that one is cool as hell you look ripped
bro You' been H in the gym dog you're in
people's way by the way am I
yes I thought you were I don't know oh
my God you guys have churros no oh
that's okay you have so many other
options flavor sh where did you see
watermelon on that that oh I'm looking
at the wrong
thing what's your favorite favorite
for for the shaved
ice really but our best seller is tiger
oh oh Tiger's blood what is that
strawberry strawberry COC oh strawberry
COC strawberry
coconut I was hoping you were gone
actually get the [ __ ] away from me
nickola it seems that you oh [ __ ] no
play the ra stop bro he left that
restaurant like he had somewhere to be
Nick Turnell Nick hey Nick Nick Nick hey
Nick you're in Maui Hawaii how does it
feel how's your Hawaii experience so far
Nick stolo Nick stolo Nick we want to
hear the new Nick we want to hear what
it's wonderful I'm an open book for lack
of a better term
lifechanging Matt how are some ways
you'd explain You' describe your P pork
sandwich good that's all I got there you
go that's all I got that's [ __ ]
boring I'm not going to be dramatic
about it I'm not going to I'm not being
dramatic I'm being realistic I'm not
going to say it's life changing I'm not
going to do any of the theatrics that
you're going to do it's pretty good it's
all
right mid wow you guys are
F huh it's just funny it's funny
watching your reaction like I bet your
pause after I said that is going to make
people
laugh that's what I'm here for Vlog they
gave me an extra because it was broke
YouTube Ramona positions her camera in
front of her face before clicking the
record button hi and she speaks it says
like as if we're like in shock that
Ramona can use her words hi she speaks I
was going to say hi first Matt wines too
bad so sad
suck
she that's what she that's what she says
to you off rip on camera yeah you said I
was going to say hi first and she goes
too bad so sad
suck my all right relax Dr Seuss take it
easy like that's insane that's actually
give you 10 bucks each I will get to the
bonfire I'll give you 10 bucks each if
you guess Chris's Snapchat username oh
no no Chris Chris it's Chris please
[ __ ] it's Crispy
Cream
bro that was most defeated I've seen you
that nickname makes you want to do a
headstand in the five gallon bucket like
legit oh you're the one Matt can't stop
talking about Chris says Crispy Cream
related
that that said it's okay I love my fans
bro chill you put my
cover [ __ ] Bro now she knows I like her
needed in the pain and sleep Department
pain and sleep two things that happen to
me very
often in the pain and
sleepious kid practically
Home Police
Department yeah can I can I get to to
that I don't see it Nick here I don't
actually like
there it is they definitely do
right damn that shit's expensive as [ __ ]
right like what am I going to do like
like that little thing is $24
$23 better also end world hunger like
yeah it was not going to happen again
what she guilted me into a $5 donation
the other day she looked at me today and
I know that she knew that it was me
again and she asked me for another G cuz
the other day she goes oh can I get you
to donate and I'm all like I'm like oh
sure like like you know like hold on
I'll tell you she's like oh can I get
you a donate beeps to focus you [ __ ]
idiot you suck she asked me the other
day to donate and I was like you suck
[ __ ] you she asked me to donate the
other day and I'm like oh yeah sure and
I'm thinking she's going to be like
round up or like a dollar or something
and she's like can I get you to donate
$5 and like I'm not going to be the guy
be like no like three
like I'm not going to demote the
donation like that's embarrassing so I
donated $5 the other day and then she
saw me and asked me again it's like what
do you want to [ __ ] run my bank
account down to zero after donating over
and
over
ready I don't know who you think I am I
don't know if I
[Music]
got literally nothing there literally
sensing car SP out for no reason okay
time to open open my
[ __ ] amulet price this cost I almost
[ __ ] I'm surprised they didn't make
me fight Captain Hook to get
it actually lay low actually lay low
actually lay low actually lay low
actually lay low camera Nick lights off
our parking lot got infiltrated so we're
going to the next area move move move
roll out the bottle of Don Julio on the
ground should have been a red flag at
the start of this video I love it
honestly it shows characterism okay you
don't even know what that word means
yeah Nei no I don't I was going to say
neither do you but you might it depends
on like character like I could picture
someone that emoji it totally depends
who you are as a person when that [ __ ]
that scared the [ __ ] out
of I've never got scar got scared of
me I've never got scared I never in my
whole life got scared by the [ __ ]
alarm and that one didn't it I think
like us switching parking lots I wasn't
expecting it it's just funny cuz like
this is what 2 like 20th car video in
and what 220 like be real I don't know
what are
you help me help help Nick stop why cuz
bro you look like a strawberry okay I
actually get scared when you're like
vein pops out of your neck like I think
we were going to die when I get angry my
forehead vein goes nutty no Rel your
neck is the worst dude I get angry way
too easily my God thank God you finally
realized the [ __ ] are you doing you
[ __ ] I felt the wet like Splash
on my lip when I put that popcorn in my
mouth it was like perfectly circular
that my immediate bodily response was
like it felt like a ping pong oh yeah
let me spit on my [ __ ] brother and
make it feel all wet and sloppy like you
[ __ ] serious I feel gross now oh are
you going to cry about it you little
baby the only thing you're you're going
to cry about is my fist in your
mouth got him got that was
awful that love when M laughs yeah laugh
laugh some more laugh some more okay he
literally spit on me and
called the whole car is
shaking my my fingers are actually I
can't I can't your head is yeah let go
let go
let I actually you let I will [ __ ] Ru
the de you will Ru it I will I will make
this the hardest living life on Earth
you've ever had in your life get the
F you're a crazy little nut what look
you're is a crazy little fruit loop
don't [ __ ] call me a nut or a
loop what are you going to do about it
you nutty Loop Sprinkles Cupcakes
reveal yay sprinkles movie coming out
I'm really like interested in going to
watch the movie but I don't know [ __ ]
about it and I I don't want to be one of
those posers like I want to I want to
watch and like devote my life to it for
the next month I hate when you do this
[ __ ] well it's also a game and we don't
know the format of the game that's my
[ __ ] point I want to know
what's going on before I go to the
theater okay the game and the thing is
different the movie the
movie the game in the movie can't be
that I have a bright idea can we start
before watching stranger things did you
play a [ __ ] whole trailer of Dungeons
and Dragons no but there's like a
storyline a plot character it really
really really think about it it has to
do with Dungeons and Dragons but it
really minimally like relates it's a
whole did you play Dungeons and Dragons
before going to the Dungeons and Dragons
Premiere no and I wished I did that's
true you wish you did [ __ ] you I really
wish I didn't I don't understand what
you mean you're like actually validating
what I'm saying more and more as you
speak so keep going
oh my God we literally have a place
called Plymouth obviously the pilgrims
went there first why would the Pilgrims
go to Plymouth first they both start
with a pee oh my God I love Cape C
Plymouth Plantation is where the pilgrim
that's like why no the Plymouth
Plantation that thing beat when we used
to go to Plymouth Plantation with like
our school and it was like in Plymouth
and it was about like the pilgrims oh my
God it was like the most like surreal
thing ever no I remember we used to go
in the a I'm me so for acts that were
there should have won like [ __ ] Emmys
like I'd go in and talk to the lady and
I was a little kid and I'd be like what
are you doing here and she' be like Oh
churning butter for my family this week
and do that don't do that no she was
like okay she was churning butter for
her family like the butter churning
station I'm going to be totally honest
with you I had no idea they were actors
so you just said that you thought they
were pilgrims I thought they were like
living in Plymouth Plantation I just
realized like fully in my head that
those were all faks they're all phonies
y obviously they got high like I
genuinely think one of hold on one of
the most mindblowing experiences of my
whole life was seeing Plymouth Rock with
my own
eyes just a chunk of rock like but it
was surreal cuz I felt like the moment
like I it's like dude when you go to
places that's in history you don't even
have to really know what's going on you
know it's deep like you know like oh my
God like I'm being for
real what did you say said [ __ ]
blanket hoger cut me up all night yeah
this is crazy the lack of blanket in
this area look go to that side of the
bed just record
it yeah this is pretty wild
oh
wow woke up cold Matt you want to know
what's crazy too what I'm really
hot yeah just walk in my
blank Chris holding
is this good or bad yeah like what does
this noise mean is he afraid of him or
does he like
him oh yeah
that's yeah oh that's my stomach yeah he
probably isn't feeling supported Matt
I'm trying my best bar goes walk into
that building next thing you know I'm
ping a baby raccoon yeah like that was
insane you say that that right there is
the scratch of a baby raccoon I hope it
scars that would be so cool want to go
in that store those girls oh my God it's
a Pokemon oh no it's not it's Luigi I'm
sorry you have chocolate on your
lip I can feel where it is yeah there
you
go oh my God
match we're going to be discussing
discussing things that we just cannot
grasp things that we cannot understand
things that are just truly make no to
understand who wants to kick us off I
will let's hear it Matt all right I got
four that are very like similar so I
kind of want to read all of them before
we like yeah yeah yeah just go okay I
didn't need that whatever it Tes Nick's
style Nick's haircut Nick's
attitude and everything that comes out
of Nick's mouth oh my God those are my
first four you couldn't wait for wow I
thought for sure it was going to like it
ended at Nick style and then he never
stopped no well let me just read my
first one then if you wanted your joke
to be Nick's still editing on Thursday
nights that's a good one too they should
have an ETA and a PTA like oh this was
your ETA but your PTA is now but they
don't know the PTA that's
what I thought there was a bug on me but
it was just like a little like it was a
charger that was actual I don't no cuz
you can't have PTA and ETA because we
don't know the PTA that's why we have an
ETA what's up with miles per hour too we
don't have a PTA that's why what I don't
get Chris you want to know what I don't
get
you what you say Easter I say Easter egg
you're listen listen I said PT listen if
it's estimated time of arrival that's no
I'm not I'm just saying that version of
you I know you got a pink Drink I put it
it's made with coconut milk and [ __ ] and
I like have never had that you had a
[ __ ] Nick why is it made with coconut
like your dead cuz I don't like coconut
milk I wouldn't like to drink that's why
I keep saying like oh I haven't had one
cuz I don't like coconut milk and that's
what it's made of so I was like oh I
don't like the [ __ ] drink so I know I
didn't get one that's why why I keep no
I did I'll call them right now what time
is it on the East Coast I've never had
one I'll
they're all as [ __ ] I've never I am
so confident you're Googling the lyri
the lyrics the ingredients and you're
like oh it has coconut milk I'd never
have it I what you check before you got
it in eth grade you dummy ni yeah but I
wouldn't like it like I never ordered
one yes you would Nick something shut up
cuz you listen listen you same reason
like oh when you're you don't like a
food you're like oh I don't like it
because of blah blah blah and you
explain like one of the ingredients in
it that you don't like so I'm here
saying like oh I've never had it cuz it
has pokut milk in it and you're this
confused it's like insane to me don't
have [ __ ] they're allergic to oh because
they don't want it because it has
something they're allergic to in it like
I don't know why you need more of a
further explanation other than they
don't [ __ ] want it I've never had a
pink Drink ever in my life in my whole
you
should life know in my whole life I'll
[ __ ] when we die in what whatever we
go to in the universe gives us our
replay of like oh this is what happened
during your life and then we can both
stand there dead together I'll wait in
heaven for you for God to give us our
replay that says I've never had a
[ __ ] darker that light shut off okay
no Nick hold on in the okay in the legit
darkness of this video you're telling me
you haven't had enough [ __ ] pink
drink in your life to fill up a [ __ ]
Trent guaranteed shake my [ __ ] when we
die and go to heaven we can ask God
together I'll wait for you at the Gat I
guarantee I I swear to God he's had a
dragon fruit for fresher though I that
for sure had that okay so either way
that means I wasn't with you when you
when you had I've never [ __ ] had one
you were not with me because no one was
with me cuz it didn't happen I have one
that's once it goes to the laundry it's
like it's like a stamp like you would
need to be a legit Mastermind to pull
this one off okay okay but it's like
replaced so s
it let get
there start with like a weird item of
clothing like underwear or socks I'm
hooked right and then start just making
them
Smalling theming making
them shut the [ __ ] up making them
smaller every time they wear it so like
they wear socks and like would you put
them in the laundry like say like you're
in the perfect Ro to do
this like no don't even shrink them but
it it'll fully replace them with like a
size down so like if the underwear is
like an extra large buy them large and
then just replace it oh here you go and
like but scrape off the L so they can't
tell and then they wear it again oh it
was a little tighter that time replace
it with a medium and then by the they're
going to get to like all their clothes
is just like dumo this actually works
better every time they wear it like that
would freak me the [ __ ] out this works
better this works better if that
person's one who does the laundry cuz
then they can't blame it on like oh I'm
like if my clothes were like rapidly
like lowering inside eyes like all of
them like every time I wore it it was
just coming I'd like get so mad at who's
doing my laundry it's like
a rub Cube like if you're an elevator
with some p a Rubik's Cube and start
like solving it in front of you like
that's weirder than a hot dog that's
cool as
[ __ ] Sol no no like a food what was it
called it was like a Zoe 101 it was on
Nickelodeon in like 2010 like during the
commercials and it was like a that was
funny it was like a what was it called
like the fu Jami ball and it was like
the
fagi it's like it's best friends it's
it's awesome it's cool it will make you
a lot of friends there's nothing like it
what are you talking about the ball and
they're like this they're like fagi the
coolest mind mending ball ever and
they're just like imagine if you're in
an elevator some they blow like AI I
can't remember you remember the name
what it's a literally a
ball
okay fushi like I don't know
coolest thing ever and I can do it hi
I'm timy and this what a promotion I
don't know what the [ __ ] it is it's cool
as [ __ ] I do it fushiki like I don't
know what it is it's the coolest thing
ever and I can do it gravity ball magic
gravity ball magic maybe an illusion you
decide this looks like exactly what they
were promoting in the Power Rangers that
got all the people to turn bad you
could god dude he's running all over
skipping down the I was sing I'm the man
I'm the man I'm the man me too I was
singing too trying to catch up where's
my Takis at what's going on holy [ __ ]
where's the
ice I need your finest batch of
ice oh fiction neck something just told
me it was that way
what something inside of me I don't know
could have been the cooler too oh wait
it might be that no it definitely is
hold on you think
so yeah it's got to be this one let's
Che it oh yeah it says ice
May what corn dogs I have to pretend
that I'm a can of
[Laughter]
Pepsi cooler
okay are you ready on get in there like
my fingertips ice cold like right
[Music]
now I can't do it I can't do that I can
do it somebody's got to do it oh my
[ __ ] God it's like worse than like
when when you go to the beach in the
winter I have to come on Nick you got
this [ __ ] try it oh
man yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes stay
stay oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
God oh my God oh my
God what is he doing what the [ __ ] oh my
God oh my God what is going on what is
going on I gummy ball no it's a gumball
not gummy
ball oh oh oh it's
overflowing wow someone's if someone's
just watching that's
crazy
W I don't even know if we can keep that
in a while that's how it started you
want a a suy gumball
no the [ __ ] is s you need I brought two
hoping gummy gummy ball Gumball want to
s a gummy ball it's super sour going to
blow your face
up
your like 12-year-old little boy lisp is
crazy
accurate this will really put some hair
on your
chest how long would you have to be
dating somebody to just drop a [ __ ]
right in front of them in front forever
I don't think I could I don't think my
body would let me like they're in the
bathroom with you and you dro the stinky
like wait like in a relationship wise is
that what you're saying so I didn't get
the be the whole question yeah ah God oh
man e Chris that's such a mad thing oh
man scratching his head I'm just
thinking about
the crazy
one great idea we should get an ASL
transl stop touching my
nipples God I [ __ ] hate when you poke
my underarm bro you know like bro I'm
going to actually rock your [ __ ] I'm
going to actually [ __ ] knck your
[ __ ] ass do you want to know what's
something important to me is my vital
organs so I hate when people or this is
all what you need to protect do you know
why hey stop you know when people fight
hey
stop hey stop ow okay buddy okay we're
going to actually get demonetized please
don't hit each other do you know when
most of the time when something crazy is
about to go down most people go like
this because they're protecting their
vital organs everything you need in Love
Is Right in here I just do that cuz I
don't like they don't they can't hit my
arm if I do that
either okay let's test it out get off sh
vital add carbonated drinks to this mhm
yeah cuz I think the second you suck on
the straw it's going to be it's going to
squ out yeah no I don't think that's
like what happens with carbonation I
think that like you just never get the
taste out of like anything but water out
of the thermos well guess what I don't
drink water cheers to
that you're supposed to use the thermos
[ __ ] be saying anything but
thermos the Theros Theros the Theros the
Theros in the forest where is the thas
the third
toas my face I told you I told you what
did you do that it's what's your
favorite summertime
activity probably [ __ ] [ __ ] how
much of the GL you think you can eat in
one
bite okay are the rest of us I we get
the old Liz I told you had her for
years sick she never let me down
marshmallow I trust this more' cooker
more than I trust most of the women I've
been with okay that's like always the
old timey line you know what I mean yeah
like she doesn't fail me like your will
never run
out easy should tell the tetanus shot
story no why that's giving away my
secrets it's not it's funny I don't want
people people to know that just tell
them no cuz one day if I like become
really strong and powerful that's why
and I don't want chis has two no don't
tell them I'm actually for real why I
don't want the internet to know okay
about your tetanus shots mhm doctor's
going to show up right made me feel
really funny okay like not the actual
shot but like just the knowing of the
amount of do you feel like you're like a
little bit more immune to like
rust I'm not WD40 I'm just a [ __ ]
human well that's what the tenis shot is
for are you to get out of not just
[ __ ] fart at me I didn't fart I hate
that that's called blowing raspberries
it makes you really
uncomfortable you didn't have to bring
its formal title in here no like yard
sales are such like an
amazing what I
hate why holy [ __ ] why I hate him were
you were talking to me about yard sales
nothing good all shabby junk Chris
shabby junk that's crazy where have you
ever telling me about yard sales the
other day when you bought a piggy bank
for $3 and there was a $20 bill in it
and you made 17 correct there's a good
come up was the piggy bank worth it nope
why were you even at this [ __ ] place
but the $17 for free probably it wasn't
a yard sale was it was a flea market oh
flea markets and they charge you like
$50 I kick the table over and I say
buddy find a new you're if this is your
life of business you're going to need to
find a new route wow so you're just
going to I'm going to give it to you
straight up kid I'm going to say buddy
you got your you got high hopes ahead of
you if you think somebody's just going
to walk by and spend $50 on your
lemonade at the end of your driveway I
tell them his profit margins are out I'm
saying somebody's got like you're
averaging $59 a cup D somebody's got to
teach him
if I'd probably just pay the
$50 take a sip of the lemonade spit it
out and say that's not worth 5 cents you
little dump figure it out it's time to
figure it out really yeah it's time to
really think about it and figure it cuz
what you're doing right now is not going
to cut
it tasted like gold that tasted like ass
with chunky lemonade powder at the
bottom do you even stir the [ __ ]
picture idiot I know this is made with
real squeeze lemons the [ __ ]
flavoring inside dummy your mom's making
this and run it out you haven't done a
single thing to help all right dude what
you do pitch the table oh one leg oh you
could you just pitch one leg up cuz your
dad had to do the rest cuz you you have
muscles you have no strength to put the
table out here yourself you want to I'd
say pick up that picture lemonade you
probably can't even pick it up pick it
up and I'll give you 50 bucks pour me
the glass yourself I'll give you $50
he's like both hands shaking lemon thing
it's like all right you're
12 like what a fool you're crazy dude
what if he does 50 plus t like he makes
you get like you're like he like $50
you're like what that's crazy you give
him 50 he like oh it's actually like
5027 until you're lucky I don't take 27
cents and throw it at your forehead you
ugly little
kid I want 1 billion Grimace shakes
you're saying Grimace wrong Grimace I
want every Grimace Shake on the menu I
want the person behind me to not be able
to
even um can I do you guys have a Grimace
shakes we need 1 million can I five of
them what size all medium please no
small small small um and then can I get
a medium fry
God would happen if Grimace did
Shake he definitely got some jiggle to
him I hope he doesn't steal our shakes
hold
on imagine it I don't know about that
it's definitely not deep Bro he's big
and purple he's got to sound like a
little baby no in my head he sounds like
Barney it's my 52nd birthday in my head
sounds
like in my head he sounds like Barney
Barney why' you say Barney The Bee was
Heavy He's a Barney he are really hot I
feel like I might [ __ ] [ __ ]
immediately ew dude I'm kind of scared
honestly what flavor is grim do you
think I'll [ __ ] purple um no thanks I
mean I'll take
three thank you here you go Chris Grim
Grim [ __ ] underneath I'm really sweating
someone's dog fudge e e a is fudge
missing a leg no oh no he's just running
oh God Action Shot fudge fudge he looks
so cute look at fudge fudge is on the
move oh fudge is actually so cute fudge
is a calendar dog if I had a dog like
he's
January fudge if I had a if I had a dog
just belongs on the headliner of a Pet
Smart yeah if on a dog food this is like
the benefit
oh my God yeah he's eating carrots and
peas every night I know it no if I was
wild cut sandwich no he's eating
fudge so true no if I had to own a dog
like tomorrow I'd buy fudge like fudge
is so cute his little tail he got one of
those retractable leashes too which is
crazy I I hate
I hate I hate hate hate [ __ ]
with a retractable leash let their dog
roam around yeah no they let the dog
roam like 20 ft it's like reel the
[ __ ] in he's not a fish like
what are you going to let him trip wire
the elderly like pull that [ __ ] back
especially with the name like fudge you
know where the [ __ ] that fucker's going
at all and you got to call them over I
can tell by looking I can tell by
looking in fudge's eyes the owner's got
no control over what fudge is doing he's
living like he's running around fudge is
a beast all right angle through us both
it looks
like
[ __ ] oh my God what is this
Stu bring that [ __ ] to the
dentist holy
[ __ ]
holy bella bella bella bella H
Jesus dude Bella needs to get those
teeth fixed dude Bella needs something
oh
I feel so
bad that you can't attack the dog's
hygiene I feel terrible dud brush your
teeth I swear to God I saw
him
hey
[Applause]
I made you a
sign
yay hurry up we miss
you
we miss you you are my sunshine you're
not real like you're not real because so
next I was alone but no multiple stories
so you know when like you scan your
ticket for like the plane and it like
beeps bright red if you're in an exit
row and they're like oh are you willing
and able to help in case of an emergency
due to like [ __ ] plane crashing and
you're supposed to say yes I'm willing
en aable and that's all they need like
they're never going to get in a plane
crash but you just have to say like oh
I'm willing enable like you have to say
yes yeah well they're like any handicapp
Personnel can board the plane first and
this [ __ ] crutches up there the slowest
I've ever seen anyone on crutches ever
like I'm talking like I've seen people
on crutches and be kind of mobile with
it like moving at a decent pace this
[ __ ] crutched like if she didn't have
those crutches she was getting nowhere I
kid you not okay she gets to the front
and scans her thing beeps bright red of
course and the lady's like are you
willing and able to help in case of an
emergency and I'm like why' you even ask
the goddamn question first of all second
of all she may be willing but she is far
far far far the [ __ ] away from AEL like
if she says yes like there is concrete
proof in front of my eyes denying this
like you are not able girl at all um but
gladly she says no I said correct like
absolutely imagine though she's like
yeah I'm willing en able it's like girl
there's proof in front of my eyes that
you are not God but she was dude I was
just a little in shock she got a first
class ticket and like the plane was
supposed to like like her seat was
supposed to fully flatten out and she
was like oh I just had back surgery like
giving the flight attendant her whole
Saab story and she's like my my seat
isn't like going all the way down and
I'm like you
know this is the one time I wish I was
one of those [ __ ] that could
say no or like was a bad person cuz the
flight attendant comes out to me gives
me the girl soab story and is like do
you mind like if you switch seats with
her and I'm like you know what I'm
probably going to pull in all night you
have to you have to say that she was
also first class but her chair just yeah
she was also first class her seat just
wouldn't lay down mine would lay down
but the reason he asked me is cuz I
wasn't laying down yet because my seat
belt sign was on so I'm like there's no
way like like I didn't know I could go
into laying
position why I was sitting up obviously
so he asks me and while he's asking me
the girl's looking at me like Matt right
now like looking over her seat
like with her [ __ ] holding back in
her [ __ ] stupid face mask like not
the mask the mask the eye mask like okay
all right all right Princess and the P
you crazy [ __ ] get out of here Princess
and the what the P what's that it's the
book with the girl she's got like 100
mattresses gole gole it was a really
good reference for this story
Google it Google it Google it for sure
Google it Princess and the P the book
Princess and the p i remember read holy
[ __ ] you
just I don't know how you have like that
book I haven't seen that book since
fourth grade what is it we read in oh my
[ __ ] got the big ass bed and the PE
bothering her on like the first one
goofy [ __ ] you don't haven't seen the
book Princess and the PE look it up
Google it that was a good refence good I
don't know where I I pulled that [ __ ]
from
I was I don't know how you remember I
think I remember to they did some sort
of like super Y episode with it when I
was a kid and I loved it but anyways
princess princess in the pee anyways
she's looking at me with her sleep mask
yeah and I was watching RuPaul's Drag
Race I'm 30 minutes into an episode my w
my ffi is going great I'm like okay I
got Wi-Fi this is awesome I'm like oh
yeah of course like let me grab all my
[ __ ] [ __ ] I unplug my charger I get
all my [ __ ] together and then I switch
seats with her she's like oh thank you
I'm like yes of course just take my seat
and then I get into my seat and bro the
problem was not that it did not lie all
the way flat the problem was it was
positioned if I was a [ __ ]
contortionist like the back was arched
the feet were up I felt like a kangaroo
on the Frogger you know what I'm talking
about the ride that goes up and down I
felt like I was at Star blast at canaby
Lake it was Unreal I was like what
coaster did I just get on I felt like
they put me up like like I've never had
this happen to me cuz I'm I don't have
female genitalia but like when you're
giving birth like your feet are up on
things so that they can get a good look
for the delivery I felt like I was just
up in the air like weirdest position
I've ever been in in my life for five
[ __ ] hours and then I tried to like
lay it down and the problem was that the
thing didn't go flat it was just like
stuck in that position and then I'm like
okay like whatever RuPaul will get me
through this so I go I go to my TV show
and it's like oh not loading and then my
Wi-Fi did not work for the rest of the
flight I'm like what songs do I have
downloaded I'll just listen to my
downloaded music and try and sleep as if
I'm [ __ ] delivering a child and I hit
Shuffle on my music silence the whole
plan silence silence so I spent the
whole flight sitting there in despair no
music we literally gave you I give you
I'll give you a a little cheat right now
you ready you can ask for a shuffle and
I'll pick one of another two words that
I have except one of them is more
difficult and one of them is easier but
I'll rock paper scissors Nick for harder
or easier words I don't know what you
should have said okay it's like a
shuffle like do you want to
take okay
minuscule sounds like mini
stool okay perfect can you say it in a
sentence the amount of water they had
was
minuscule where I don't know bad example
bad example whatever Nick can you get
Nick I want Nick's example this should
be taking a minuscule amount of time but
it is taking you far longer for no
[ __ ]
reason m
i yep n yep I
no
[Laughter]
just
relax h
blo can I hear it in a
sentence can I hear that's a whole lot
ofo balloon
yeah hu l l yep a yep B yep a yep l
o u l o o l o oh I should have H okay
close same day
remember remember you got the goofy that
Salon won't leave me the [ __ ] alone
actually email email email we're open
for another cut if you want one I'm like
[ __ ] off you [ __ ] my [ __ ] up bad they
have DM me every day I showed the lady
oh my God can you talk about this the
story there the lady cutting your
hair okay I don't remember it at all she
said that she was like this Brazilian
lady oh my God no it was this woman the
woman who cut my hair there like I try
to be like I'm all for women I love them
this woman
had breast implants for sure not that
this is like a bad thing it's just
critical to the story so that's why I'm
bringing it up but usually I wouldn't
talk about a woman's breast but it has
to go to story so I have to bring it up
but because she had breast implants her
boobs were obviously huge so she was
cutting my hair she was cutting my hair
and as was cutting my hair she was
getting so close to me while cutting my
hair that like her boobs were like
resting on my neck and back and
shoulders and head and like she just
kept going around me cutting parts of my
hair and I'm just like I'm happy I was
like gay because otherwise like like I
was just scared cuz I'm like if I was
anyone else I'd feel very violated like
I was very comfortable but her boobs
were everywhere around me like my back
my shoulder like if you're if you're a
straight man you're getting the wrong
impression no absolutely like I'm just
like like it was I just tried to forget
it and that's why it took me so long to
remember that cuz I was so like just in
shock cuz it's not something I ever want
but there was boobs all over me oh true
St that story killed me and I got a bad
haircut out of it so that's awesome
that's so funny that [ __ ] I cannot
believe you thought that he was a goof
do you have a drink back there no you
got nothing to
drink no nothing at all I have a coffee
but I not going to drink it it's 1:30 in
the morning okay so just drink it
I'm why do you want me to drink a drink
this I want a sip of it what are you
going to is it osmosis you're going to
have some too based on me drinking my
drink no I'm just really thirsty shut
the [ __ ] up yeah this is not how it
works at all you wash your hair recently
looks
terrible does it does it look bad you
know how much I don't like no I think it
looks good you fixed it it looks better
than it just did thanks yep I love you
Nick come on go buy a drink for yourself
no bring it in don't I don't see enough
Nick edits no for real I want to see
them all day I can't I really can't like
the good looking oo I'm Nick but like
just the funny ones you're a funny guy I
know thank
you God he's so funny God why don't we
just I think I think for this video we
should all go back there and just tickle
each other that's insane tickle tickle
get off me Matt you guys
like I think a really good Hard video
would be if we talked about everything
we hated get big bug trying to get
in like the type of guy that'd be really
good at speaking
Malarkey notice how I just made you
laugh harder than you ever made me laugh
I didn't even say words nothing left my
mouth and you laughed harder at a joke I
didn't make then I've ever laughed at
you or
matt
like let's be absolutely for real I lit
you just chuckled I heard it no you
heard nothing heard you Chuck you didn't
hear [ __ ] play it back you chuckled you
did Chuck I will
put I'll
put I have a lucky Tor chick the grow no
you catch the Tulip is it man tulips on
his dick oh Chris come on sorry that was
that yeah
we're love pizza really good pizza my
least favorite part of the pizza is like
right here the crust no not the crust
pre crust like the in between the crust
and the
cheese well okay oh yikes I almost made
a SP who does that and it's like okay
with
themselves that's what I you act like
I'd be really traumatized with what I
just it's just lame like you're just
weird it's good look at it no Matt would
be the goofy dude that like does a trick
and lands or something and then like
does like like
that like the loud thing yeah and like
makes everyone i' be the person in the
crowd just throwing popcorn they're like
wow Nick would be the popcorn seller no
Nick would be the the the guy feeding
the elephant peanuts have you seen that
guy oh my God this is a viral clip on
Tik Tok this guy goes it's like dead
silent like an arena and he
goes oh he screams hot dog hot
dogs get your hot dogs get hot dogs here
like he goes like that's how he does it
that was insane it I think that was the
loudest you've ever screamed in
extremely hot take you ready some
soundtracks spicy I got to get out of
here I got to get out of here some
soundtrack albums and like some
soundtrack albums and albums for like
Disney movies and [ __ ] are harder than
some projects that people have put out I
disagree
completely there there's not one movie
soundtrack I could ever hit Shuffle play
on ever in the world of the world
Lemonade Mouth that's
true I wasn't thinking of it like that
cuz that's a show where there's songs
Incorporated I was thinking for like
when normally I couldn't turn your head
that's why I had to write this instead
let's be friends start out slow get to
know you beyond your glow would you
rather meets to ey girl you're terod Fly
can I tell you guys a crazy fact you
hate can I tell you guys a crazy fact
let me tell you guys a crazy
fact
honeysuckles I think those are a goddamn
scam I think you're a
scam Nick you look like the type of guy
to like thaw out food's favor what's
your favorite fruit like first of all I
don't cook second of all that's
literally what 90% of people who cook do
sawing is ridiculous though just put in
the oven to warm up imagine thawing
something out before you yet a good meal
get it nice and hot if you don't let
Matthew Sero talk right now I'm going to
lit really cut your hair off no it's
fine I'm good I'm really one what I'm
tired of what the [ __ ] corny [ __ ] I
trapped my door bro oh yeah awesome
close it no look pick it up what are you
doing Chris you're going to [ __ ] rip
the door off got stuck in the dirt how
do you fix this I don't know I opened
the door now why are you guys swinging
your doors like you got to get a [ __ ]
whale out of the way you need to stop
yelling and all you have to do is walk
like bro it's like in the dirt [ __ ]
dig a hole let's go little rabbit
like it's in the [ __ ] I think you
have to move the car forward like I
legit can't close it yeah drive the car
awesome one you grab the camera I'm not
going to I can't drive the car and stand
here Chris if you break the [ __ ] door
I'll kill you I got it I got it I got it
oh my God you're not real how did that
happen I don't know how I did that okay
wait pause
ow I got like are you 12 Anonymous
confession time oh god that hurt when we
first came to LA and we drove around
this area for the first time I for for L
to bring me to team 10 house to like get
the Vibes of like being in La I actually
remember that cuz I took a I have a
couple other things that I've written
down that are just like goofy um my
least favorite words when people are
like oh it's ethereal or eal like [ __ ]
shut the [ __ ] up what does that mean
shut up what does that mean it's like oh
like like I look e ethereal or eal like
they think they're like a fairy princess
it's like you look uh a little a little
better than mid
ethereal ethereal ain't the word to use
like at all oh my
God I just hate that word my God I hate
that word that was the best that was the
most you've ever flamed like something I
was that he said you look a smidge
better than mid oh I love that word smid
thank
you no but it is true I really just
don't think that that word's ever
suitable for like a human being is that
a real word let's Google it that word is
good to use if you enter Narnia you can
be like oh this place
if if you're living out of fable then go
for it but you're it is extremely
delicate and light in a way that seems
too perfect for this
world what and if you're if you're
calling yourself that you're a God
you're goofy you're goofy you're so
goofy I feel like youd do that though
that was that was so that's like even
like like only way I would use that is
if I was
like I wouldn't use it yeah maybe
entering Narnia or like visiting
Tinkerbell but those are like seem to be
the only two occasions also another
occasion is if I was in Smurf Village
for sure oh yeah you have no question
about it damn bro Smurf at low key she
got to
be damn bro Smurf at lowkey she got to
be she got no she got to
be
birthday
Vlog it's our birthday today look at how
happy Nick
is yaho happy birthday Matt we just ate
celebratory hey it's your birthday too
yay oh my God hey it's your birthday too
this year I know we have a podcast
coming out soon about birthday so I
don't want to say too much about it but
now sorry the washing machine what's in
there did you put a brick in it it
should be it shouldn't be making this
much
noise is that did you leave your wallet
in
there that's got to be a brick that
ain't a wallet that's something heavier
whatever anyways can I talk about our
podcast it it's doing the next thing can
I talk about our podcast about Monday
yeah I don't care that you'd approach
you would be the most intimidating to me
yes cuz you just look like you're going
to like rip my [ __ ] like a ravaging
mutant yes you look you look angry that
was so funny no it's more of like you
just have the most like like you like
I'll stand there and I'll be like this I
got the most grit and you're just like
this you'll be standing there like like
all miserable and angry okay so I have
bad posture and a broken bottom lip as
well that's [ __ ] great just keep
adding on just let me know God what else
I do wrong imagine you meet someone and
they go up to you and they go hey what's
up yeah no it's not like a salute like
I'm in the Navy it's like it's two
fingers usually it's two fingers usually
like that outro Trend like where like
the people like play their outro and
then leave the room and then go like
that and then like walk up
Nick does that before it's simply to
break the awkwardness of like they
looked at Matt said hi looked at you
said hi I'm just like oh like it's like
a it's like in addition to like what
honey what producer do you think has the
best producer to
have I don't know any producers you know
how like at the beginning like Metro
booming you know how at like the
beginning of songs like rap songs and
stuff there's always like that little
message at the start message like um or
like a little saying like C that DJ
Yes actually that's a good one I like
him I like the way they shout out for
him in every song that's not oh he just
yells his own name yeah that's a good
one you don't like Metro booming Metro
boomman make it
boom heard metro metro don't trust you
he's going to shoot you oh then I like
Metro The
Best [ __ ] Matt tell him about Pikachu
what do you
mean how much how many things could you
tell about Pikachu and it also tracks
sleep but you got to set it to track
Sleep
p is his voice copyright I don't know I
hope not well he's singing Twinkle
Twinkle Too Sing Twinkle Twinkle Little
Star that's beautiful right shout out to
fall asleep in five seconds if that was
on in my bed all right we're playing
poker they make a if they make a
live W my nose is bleeding now oh good I
hope it does bleed bleed bleed like how
disrespectful is this motion
that oh that drives you crazy I know it
did like that oh well how many how many
times did you stop talking to I'll break
your goddamn see how angry you
are gra
I'm this
s
pull your pants up pull your pants up
you guys see it now see it now oh my God
what happened oh my God what did you why
did you do that you're a [ __ ] idiot
give me my hat is it the drink oh my God
everywhere Matt I'm soaked are you I'm
literally fell down his arm it's funny
cuz there's Skittles all over that seat
and then snap
such a State of Shock right
now and how about
that and now what would you do now that
you're equally as shocked as I am we
have like not even started the intro of
this video and you guys have both dumped
your [ __ ] drink on each other well
I'm just curious how shocked you are now
since you just did that to me so now you
can feel exactly how I do this is
Chris's villain backstory
oh
God ow
ow we're going to get demonetized I
don't
care going to choke skill who's going to
win tour who's going to win it who's
going to win it who's going to win it
all the guilt tripping in the W who's
going to win it look it this kid [ __ ]
soaked my
panties panties that's crazy panties is
wild like I do hope that that stain
comes out those are expensive sweats
yeah I think I'm putting I think they're
better than the might take that yeah
they're moving into first place this is
going number one for me okay that's good
well it was very light to
eat oh this one can't go wrong here Matt
what is it looks like a pretzel yeah
they look like little gr crackers it
just say cracker wheat
cracker get your whole hand
on someone's invisaline is in that water
did you take the cup that my invisaline
okay well that's
awesome you're enjo that oh my God you
didn't look in the
cup she's giving me like sips like she
like wor glass I drank it but that's
fine why why do you not get a new C I
did no you didn't wait Chris if you were
to compare Matt's head to one fruit what
would would you compare it to like shape
color size probably a warped dirty
watermelon dirty is crazy dude people
are going to think that this is scripted
why people are going to start to think
our content why because I have a dirty
warped watermelon
why cuz I thought that that's what you
were going to say so I was like or Nick
if you actually have that that's [ __ ]
crazy Chris no [ __ ] way dirty warped
watermelon
it's about the that's actually that's
like the most that was the weirdest [ __ ]
ever that's the most triplet connection
like like an apple or like a cantaloup
and I was like I was going to say I was
going to say like oh I think it looks
like a watermelon and pull this out a
joke it's the witch from o why was he
just
what Nick recreate that terrible
recreate what he I don't know if you
could see him through the back window
but that guy just went by on a bike and
was like like he never stopped looking
at our car that big G that was
terrifying but look yeah Matt no Nick
literally said he guys he goes you guys
go to the car early cuz I'm going to
grab something I don't want you to see
there so many and then and then he said
that I didn't even know what he meant
for me to say but that's crazy that I
these [ __ ] are in bad moods
yeah that's a good one that's on my nerv
when Chris is in a bad mood when Chris
is in a bad mood he makes it I think
everyone's problem no I don't bro y'all
all just raise some pants for if you
agree with
me that's crazy it's true I didn't want
to say it that's crazy I had to it's
true ra your hands if Nick has more
frequent bad problems than my God that
was
insane that was
[ __ ] feel like Spiderman that was
crazy what were you saying I feel like
Nick has more frequent like outbursts
than I literally urged out when you ate
it well cuz it shocked me I kind of like
this a little bit more than I think this
one is legit
plain uh take a bite
it goe I'm serious this
time Hur Hur I'll let you hold it
no he angled it like this you like that
my mouth
go all right come on come on it scar bro
chill all right I'll look this way
telling him to be for real is
crazy tell me that doesn't taste like
that's play M all right so does that
mean I have to have that one yep no I
want to say something but I'm not going
to say it Matt no go Matt I can't say it
can I whisper it to you
yeah M want the [ __ ]
C I didn't say that you're so weird
you're so you're so
strange that's like not even that bad he
said Casper looks like a sperm cell he
does at pass bro you have to smash he's
the only Smurf like there's no other
Smurf options I'm putting myself in a
Smurf car like I'm not going to like as
me but if I was like if you're clumsy
you're falling into that
waor Sor sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry oh my God sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry too much too mucho too much too
much we're just going to move on too
much we're just going to move
Ono popey the Sailor yeah he's strong I
love papy am I putting myself in looks
70 that is true bro D sorry sorry sorry
sorry oh my God oh my God what am I
saying oh what's his what's his wife's
name olive oil olive oil she bad dude
let me pull her up okay olive oil from
poy bro she also an she got a hat
haircut bro she got the Uggs on though
she not got the boots on N she's ugly as
[ __ ] that's ugly oh my God what does
that smell what does that smell I don't
smell anything shh there's a car right
there my God what smells like dead well
this is probably a dumpster this and
gross oh get me out of here okay I guess
we didn't find a park we can take them
there's someone right here there's
someone right here we take we have to
just go fast cuz I can't my god well
you're making it a bigger deal let's
just go it smells like the zoo with poop
it smells like the zoo with what were
you going to say about that song what
song you made us wait until the camera
was up so you could talk about it cuz it
was funny what's but I don't think it's
funny that song's like a sad emot no we
were just jamming out to James Arthur
say you won't let go say you won't and
Nick said ask me about that song see
I've been so like I have been fighting
this knowledge in my brain for so long
like having this story story not telling
anyone because of how like the sheer
embarrassment that it brings me to okay
so it's really difficult for me I have
an embarrassing story to this song too
but yeah I'll let you say it first it
was like the first guy I had ever like
romantically hung out with ever and this
song was on and I think we were on like
part two of hanging out like ever and
full
tears yeah no way I like kid you were
him right oh sorry sorry sorry sorry
Matt full eruption into tears no and it
was like the second time and I was just
in such a State of
Shock and that's when I knew that it was
not going to work at all that's crazy I
never knew that I'm like so that's why I
can never listen to that song Seriously
again cuz it's such an emotional good
song about someone you'd like loved for
years you know what I mean we were on
like hang out number two no that that's
my biggest my embarrassing story was I
just that's crazy I'm pretty sure I
danced to that song in my eighth grade
uh at eighth grade dance with that girl
that I liked you know you know who I'm
talking about gross yeah really
disgusting gross but then no I'm not
going to say what I was going to say
weird [ __ ] say it no I can't I can't I
mat no cuz then I I think our I think
after that's for some reason that when
they do that song it's normally supposed
to Yo Diamond's blinging okay
a normally normally when they do that
song it's normally like you kind of like
gradually get back into the other music
you know what I mean but I just remember
like the girl that I didn't get I didn't
hit puberty until like the latest out of
all three of us but we were still all
but we were still all like four [ __ ]
10 in like eth grade seventh e8th grade
but I was in eighth grade I think I was
like 5 foot 51 Maybe Max and the girl
that I had a crush on was like 58
towering over you towering over me still
liked me though don't know why don't
know how that added up I was also in
eighth grade really strange but that
song plays danc into that song right and
then I'm expecting like like a clean
transition into like another kind of
lovey song but like upbeat a little more
you know what I mean it went straight
into [ __ ] what was it I think it was
like a mamore song straight into a
mammore song and then our eighth grade
math teacher was break dancing seconds
after me and her St that's crazy I want
a large Pepsi and like a bunch of those
Cinnabon things with the cream in
itun um can I get
um six crunchy tacos with just meat and
cheese no lettuce I want a two tacos and
I want a Pepsi and I want you want two
of those
tacos yeah yeah yeah yeah can I get two
more of those I'm sorry large Pepsi
yeah [ __ ] speak um and can I get two
large Pepsis and then the cream things
like the cream like like eight like
eight creams 12 12 cream things and then
can I do a 12pack of the Cinnabon
Delights M do you want anything else
nope I love the cream things um and then
I'll just get do you like them Matt H
the cream things hey can I get a medium
wild I call them little cream little
cream balls what did he just get yeah
regular I'll do ordering too much food
this
is thank you so much what did you even
just order bro yeah that's all take one
article of clothing off
maybe if I can take off one article
clothing I'll go in for 100
bucks
uh-oh someone's unlacing their
pants Matt 100 bucks on the line if you
jump in like that
150 $3
million I'm
[Laughter]
kidding I kissed a worm for a quarter on
a dare kissed a worm no you didn't you
like you're reciting juny B Jones book
you didn't [ __ ] I I feel there was way
too children's books I feel there was
way too many children's books about like
worms and dirt and like sludge and gross
[ __ ] you know me a say who just came
inside you to say
slge like that wasn't Nick who just said
sludge someone just took over his body
he said SL he said no but I do feel like
there like there's way too many there's
way too many children's stories that are
like about like frogs and swamps and
dirt toads dude it's crazy that like a
toad is just like in my eyes a toad is
just a filthier FR take your crew next
one Nick what's the next one I have oh
no that's why I said I I was if you
[ __ ] ever hit me again I'm going to
knock your [ __ ] teeth out literally
that's why I was saying I was comt oh my
godou I just bit my lip [ __ ] dumb B
don't [ __ ] hit my mouth [ __ ] face I'm
going to just start sitting here in the
videos it's like what you did wasn't
funny what you did wasn't funny either
oh my God yeah like I'm bleeding right
Chris what did you do Matt get out of
here God I'll just never be excited to
tell you anything again cuz I know that
now it leads to perfusive blood in my
mouth blood blood blood in my mouth if I
just want to taste blood then I'll touch
you I'm sorry I made you bleed you're
not sorry about it yes I am I'm sorry I
made you bleed I want to taste my own
blood eat the jelly eat the jelly you
eat the jelly
M it's it's good
right do you like it yummy here's the
bag see it's like the fun like the
sensation is good like the tactile part
of the experience is good but the taste
is a whole another demon it's all gone I
ate
it you're
disgusting oh it's on my arm e the jelly
okay we're just going to put it right in
the back it's like a poop
bag
my I can't believe this to room it's
like the scariest place ever like what
is going on this Vlog look like Weir
nightmare Hotel jelly
experience nightmare Hotel jelly bites
what are you a Munch don't try to bite
it at me got a Munch is crazy don't try
to bite it at me I see you
yeah I saw you look I should have the
that you thought ho oh my goodness at
least I got to walk who went to the moon
Buzz Aldren as well Google that that's
what Buzz Light your is based off of is
Buzz Aldren is
B is Buzz Aldren alive said
balls said balls Buzz Aldren oh he's
alive
uh-uh there's no there's only a date of
birth there in a date of death I'm just
happy I got
[Music]
to what' you do I spilled water all over
my feet and legs by accident that was
[Laughter]
freezing oh my God I totally got excited
that me and me and Neil Armstrong were
alive at the same time and just poured
water out on my oh my God that was crazy
it's a wet back here just the FY the wet
sandals is crazy like why do you put
them up here
like my are so dirty I'm just
guessing ghost spooky ghost stories
Halloween time who the Happy Ghost The
Friendly Casper the Friendly Ghost
that's four words Casper Friendly Ghost
whatever I didn't even see you get that
sheep prepared chicken monkey monkey ow
just I'm going to wake up the neighbors
chimpanzee
attack monkey bite monkey
attack gorill
attack first
word second word attack gorilla
monkey angry
monkey ferocious monkey violent
monkey enraged monkey
vicious monkey sporadic monkey dangerous
monkey there it is dangerous
monkey thank you everybody all right I
liked it that was my performance a
dangerous monkey squirt squad or cream
team
what there's no one there's no way
someone spoke that into the world
someone literally said would you rather
be on squirt squad or cream good off
that heard it favorite place to go on
vacation what dog I don't know vacation
Malibu oh there you go Malibu yes man go
why did the scuba diver fall backwards
out of the boat why why cuz if you fell
forward you'd still be in the
boat what is sweet potatoes wear to bed
what
yammies what does sweet potatoes wear to
bed
yammies what do you call an angry carrot
what a steam veggie oh
have seven skip it they got webbed feet
honestly 10 I bet they can swim crazy
nope zero yes chis
z0 I bet they can't if you have webbed
feet you literally have flippers on your
own bare skin get out of here don't say
that [ __ ] webbed feet fun oh I just want
to cut the web
off oh my
God leral Panic just like actually fled
my body with this comfort same reaction
oh my God I felt my feet and hands get
so in pain right away yeah no that would
that oh my God next their room is always
untiy untiy untiy oh my God that
person's a zero they drink it might have
to take apple cider donuts holy [ __ ] I
just get so like warm inside I just want
to rub the cinnamon sugar all over my
body okay oh my god did like go just go
weird about it all right guys eat it or
delete it
that's so weird that's so Str I had to
make that joke good job I'm glad you
made it now that you're done with that
let's proceed let's proceed make the
type of gu to say let's proceed go idiot
you don't even know what the [ __ ] you're
saying half the time you just speaking
oh that looks nasty Mt I don't know what
what if it's almost like homemade
favorite meal you can tell it's homemade
yeah I can tell it's homemade for sure I
don't even want to click on that one
know
[Music]
that's the least scary Halloween
decoration I've ever seen in my life and
then okay next one Dusty black white and
ginger yeah you're looking Dusty you
need a duster
just Dusty actually looks really Co
that's the most unique looking animal
I've seen in like my life I think the
giant slug has him little beat but I
mean yeah I'll give no this one's cute I
think Dusty's cute I like Dusty
Dusty's Chris don't be rude he's Dusty
this is my dog named Bruce oh he's cute
what Bruth is just such a oh yeah it's
just like a
toy sh it shake it shake it shake it
shake it shake it shake it shake
it no
no what guys guys I get away don't throw
it away from the car you're going to get
me
[Laughter]
soaked dude like a n that was a terrible
oh God I want to be like Mike for
Halloween you're nothing like
Mike that's not good I hate you
you're nothing like mikee at all oh
that's a really cool concept of a movie
that was a really good joke Matt made a
good joke oh my God bring out the
[ __ ] cookies and start the parade I
want po twinky Winky and at the front of
it
like have PO on the float with sun when
when sun babies in it's okay Nick build
Nick Nick build build build build what
the [ __ ] are you doing get on a gun
shoot him Nick give me the remote give
me the remote give me the remote give
me go charge the camera being realistic
what would the I want M to speak [ __ ]
shut up every time his mouth is open
you've interrupted him basically what
the first thing I'm doing is probably
dude you can't catch a goddamn
braak don't [ __ ] touch
no [ __ ]
tou why is he so
mad SW seats what
what I'm going to die can you stop
burping you remind me one CHR reminds me
of and you'll agree I retired that seat
from here on out for the rest of our
YouTube career I will hereby hereby what
do you want a [ __ ] crown and a big
staff if this is me I'm diving over the
table oh
no
no don't have to
have oh my
[Laughter]
[Music]
God yes oh my
God if you piss yourself in a classroom
and then say hey Miss dummy [ __ ] didn't
let me use the bathroom she should be
arrested I mean she should be if you
piss or Shake Yourself that's kind of a
boss move cuz it forces your teacher in
a way more uncomfortable position one
time I threatened my chemistry teacher I
was if I was back in high school I just
whip my [ __ ] out and piss on the floor
don't use the word [ __ ] I hate that with
my [ __ ] out and piss on
the what is M again
he's he can't have to cheat come on
there's no what he not allowed to do
talk
oh what just
happened are you gross [ __ ] ow I
can't what's going on stop yelling at me
[ __ ] you doing don't run by me like a
[ __ ] tornado what's going on get out
who rolling stuff what's going on he
just bent over in front of me what are
you doing Matt was yelling at me and now
I'm covered in baby chicken what can
Titanium fishing rod I feel like I'd be
way more you're the weirdest
[ __ ] ever you don't fish yeah
but if I did didn't I a titanium rod you
don't need a titanium
rod you look like a titanium rod Matt
has a titanium rod
what Mr I have an idea idea dude you
know me and Chris were watching
SpongeBob last night and that was the
episode yeah that was the episode I
don't know Mr Crabs I think it's season
two something I have an
idea candle popped in your teeth I
walked in on Santa giving my dad head on
Christmas
Eve that's a real confession that wasn't
Santa no way that probably your
mother even if it was Santa I feel like
he would have sprinkled some magic like
dust so you didn't see him do it you
know no way Santa's letting you he's
delivering presents all these [ __ ]
years but someone's going to catch him
giving someone like no if we're catching
Santa it's in the act of dipped under a
tree I was giving
anyway oh no well I'm definitely not
going to help clean that he missed me
hold on it would have been way funnier
if I got hit with it stay over
[Laughter]
[Music]
there
what are you serious than you ni I'm
going to take a shower cuz of how much
[ __ ] [ __ ] are you guys for real oh
let's do how he added the [ __ ]
sprinkles
to are you stupid get away from me it's
just a goofball you know this is hard to
do cuz you guys just don't if you can
make them laugh and
giggle you can make that booty shake and
jiggle
what who said that it's just an Infamous
quote from who just the people who's the
people you're the people I'm not the
people there you go yes I'm okay fast I
was showing you the bite good bite thank
you no stuck my teeth can I put it in a
cup
sure okay you don't have to do that that
was terrible shocked no let's move
on this is all right you're making me
sick I'm scaring you yeah all right
sorry I just heard an amazing joke from
Shannon over there my ear
don't tell my
wife this kid is insane oh this has to
be a fake story I and I liked
it what after I attended his funeral and
I and now I can't stop thinking about
him either I volunteered in a dog
shelter and I donated to poor people and
babies they're
good like I don't know what that even is