Nick picked out a fan fiction we're
filming fan fiction today okay we took
the pressure off of you man I know you
really enjoy picking them but we figured
you'd already read them all so we were
just like let's have Nick pick them ah
feared Chris
but it's okay
and I had to also have to download the
app I didn't have it on my phone already
but I downloaded that yeah I got logged
out anyway okay closer to the name of
the fan fiction wins
um tripler Brothers triple love no well
no obviously I'm not gonna guess the
title not even close 3x the Heartbreak
that was done also not close yeah
because Matt knows what an average title
okay come on like it's gone for the
summer
in which Ramona Logan's best friend
plans a vacation along with his brothers
to take her and her friend to Hawaii for
the summer
wow very convenient timing because we're
just in Hawaii nothing I'm just ready we
got our characters Ramona Logan
one person one person Oh I thought
Ramona Logan
I thought it was Ivory Logan was
Ramona's sister well no I took terrible
like last name and name combo you're
already characters L Ramona Logan can we
just call them Ramona I'm just letting
you know that in case they refer to her
as Logan
okay Miss Logan or Miss Ramona match
it's Ramona Logan just both ones Ivory
Scott is the name of another girl okay
that's a better name that's a little
better Ivory is crazy Matthew cernyella
Christopher attorney Nicholas cerno and
they're just they're us
we are them rock and roll
I love hearing the things that people
write about come on let me eat like
Purdue you know see that sauce I love
being a homosexual because I'm just the
best friend in all these so do you think
she's gonna like you more Matt I don't
there's different segments and they're
called YouTube and IRL so some things
are like on camera and some things are
like in real life you know what I mean
oh it's already gonna be really bad
really corny already like off the bat
okay YouTube Ramona positions her camera
in front of her face before clicking the
record button hi
and she speaks it says like as if we're
like in shock that Ramona can use her
words
why she speaks I was gonna say hi first
Matt wines too bad so sad suck
that's what she says to you off rip on
camera yeah you said I was gonna say hi
first and she was too bad so sad
okay all right relax Dr Seuss take it
easy like that's insane yeah that's
actually getting crazy I don't know who
Ramona thinks she is but if someone
spoke to Mali that I'd put them in check
faster than I've done anything in my
life anyway cornball's rhyming too bad
so sad like you too bad so you think
she's hyping up like a like a okay third
grader yeah remote replies Nick and
Chris laugh at her laugh at the girl's
reply Matt even lets out a soft giggle
while attempting to maintain a pout it's
like he's trying to be upset but he's
like can't keep it in that's so corny
bro did you just come up with that on
the spot Chris laughs yes she says
um Ramona answers before focusing her
eyes on the camera bro you know where
you came over that on the spot like that
was so fire so we're gonna go on a
little we're going on a little trip said
Ramona
um now you guys be asked now you guys
may oh now you guys may be asking where
are we going for the summer trip well
it's Hawaii we're spending the summer in
Hawaii you
[Music]
seem disappointed Nick comments no I'm
not disappointed tired yes disappointed
never yeah
so never Scott just texted me and said
she's ready for us to pick her up
God oh it's the girl that's her last
name
just let her know when we're on our way
Chris States stop calling Ivory by her
last name it's weird Ramona replies
he responds biodegradable salt litter go
ahead see that's what I don't like we're
calling people by their last name
whatever I warned you by her last name
it's weird Ramona replies never Logan he
responds Ramona rolls her eyes as she
flips the camera and shows Chris putting
on his socks look at this
Ramona says hey stop they're gonna see
my dogs Chris squeals curling his toes
they're curling his toes and hiding them
in his hands Ramona Giggles happens what
are you doing giggles at the boy as she
Zooms in on his feet she giggles at the
boy remote
Ramona Camilla Logan Chris shouts
jokingly Christopher Owen sterniola
Ramona reply bro Ramona the corniest
like this this girl sounds like the last
person I'd ever be friends with on the
face of this Earth so it's funny that
it's like our best friend Roberta
willing to go on a trip with in this
store yeah right now this is so toxic to
be around and both of you Matt and Chris
that's what it stands for both of you
it's too early for shouting man whoa I
thought you were talking to us like
actively you're just jealous Ramona
claims yeah that Chris is flirting with
you and not me he States wow I see how
it is she replies rolling her eyes in
what world girl this is not even close
to reality yarn I mentioned 977 because
I am so confused where you pull this
[ __ ] I don't get where people writing
fan fictions like you can't copy a story
that exists you can't be even remotely
creative like that was really bad but
twin siblings I don't get like there's
no world in which twins are like okay
with being in a constant love triangle
friendship
I wonder what people like
think like happens with like you and me
I don't really get it I really I don't
either
guys I'm gonna tell you a story Ramona
says to the camera the triplets all
grown and roll their eyes as we shut
honestly this girl should stop talking
but don't stop Ramona from continuing
her story oh it doesn't stop her good
she's persistent
she has to be dude like that because
everyone's gonna be shooting down ideas
left and right
so in eighth grade math Chris and Nick
this other guy named Lucas we're all in
a big friend group well and me of course
because I'm better but whatever so
so Chris and Lucas were like really good
friends and they like they were like the
best friends of the group I guess and
they both liked me but I liked maths
like it was a whole thing because Matt
kind of liked my best friend and she
liked him back and yeah it was a huge
thing because like my best friend at the
time got really upset whenever me and
Matt were close and it started to hold
them so everybody likes Ramona now
apparently but what was the big prize
she's the big cookie she's dead she's
been [ __ ] we're over it now and I
learned to never be close friends with
your best friend's crushes and yeah
that's my story Ramona shares oh my God
I totally forgot about all that drama
bro Liz was such in eighth grade like
I'm sorry I know she was your best
friend but like she really ruined every
friendship you had
like she was such a bad friend Nick
States I honestly think Ramona is the
problem so it's crazy that they paint my
picture to be her best friend I can't
stand her I think who's who's it Liz I
think Liz was probably completely in the
right unfortunately for unfortunately
for Ramona and the story she's trying to
tell like this is the most fiction fan
fiction I've ever read in my life to be
quite honest because this is just
unrealistic after unrealistic after
unrealistic I feel like I'm in a dream
like this is unrealistic written in a
realistic way it was fan fiction no what
I mean is like it's it's realistic just
like it's unrealistic to us but it's
like a realistic thing like but in my
head in my head it's so unrealistic she
could be like a dragon and wizard pull
up in the room and cast a magic spell on
everyone and that would be the least
bizarre thing if I'm being quite honest
she could say bragging comes in and eats
her dog and I'd be like oh okay that
makes a whole lot more sense than
whatever the he's already on this paper
because right now I'm just reading a
bunch of [ __ ] like over and over hello
okay I'm done we can go pick up Ivory
now
I hate the name Ivory because I just
think of rhinos
what it's not what dragons have
I feel like you're right but I don't
know how like I've heard that but I
don't know like isn't they poached
rhinos for ifrey like that's the magic
maybe in there that's what I'm talking
about Okay Google it hold on I don't
even know okay I'm done we can go pick
up Ivory Now Matt says okay antsy pants
Ramona replies shut up you probably want
to see her more than all of us combined
so I don't got Shame about that she
states whatever let's go okay I'm done
with this story if you guys are done I'm
done okay is the hard white material
from the Tusk and Teeth of animals oh so
you ate yeah yeah wow
but that's so sad that's why they
poached them for the horns because
that's like the most valuable part yeah
um walrus hippopotamus narwhals sperm
whale warthog
no it's definitely rhinos too elephants
dude animal poaching is so sad like they
just really just kill animals for their
Ivory Rhino yeah they do oh this breaks
my heart I can't talk about this right
now
oh no rhino horns are made of
catch something
I can't pronounce it the same substance
found in human hair and nails new story
we're done with gone for the summer I
don't actually care how this goes
it just pisses me off when there's too
many people and then my head gets all
scrambled with Who's Who and this
person's in that it was Lucas's summer
bro and then and then basically what
happened was wait um
like Ramona but so did Matt but then Liz
like Matt okay there's so many people
this part's like the IRL do we want to
read that yeah sure yeah sure in real
life like after the YouTube Ivory Ramona
shouts in a deep and grumbly voice what
was that Nick exclaims is everyone
including Ivory folds over in hard
laughter how the [ __ ] wait so that was
all YouTube a YouTube video yeah like on
camera
this is terrible go ahead Chris and Matt
tried to imitate Ramona's voice which
only results in more laughter at the
boy's failure
for laughter at the boy's failure
that's how I picture like okay she typed
that and it was like more laughter due
to the boy's failure
in the car and seats herself in between
Nick and Ramona Logan camera Chris says
in the front sir yes sir Ramona salutes
digging through her backpack for the
triplets camera oh no I want to know why
she has had it in the first place yeah
get your hands off myself I only have
mine Ramona States you dumb you check
the front pocket Chris asks no she
replies quietly and she began to look
began looking in the front pocket found
it Ramona shouts this girl has some
pent-up regression that she needs to
take outside
aggression you said regression this girl
has some pent up aggression she needs to
bring to life rage room or something
like boxes or something someone writing
this story is just real Angry yeah
it's enough
whoa settle down slow down okay I don't
care I'm I'm done with this story and
I'm ready for another yeah that story
was dog meat [ __ ] ass I agree dog meat
[ __ ] God I got a burp
I just like if I read the aggressive
things in that story like yelling like
that probably would have been our most
like graphic card video ever yeah I
don't know what is happening there you
and I yeah yeah
now I probably read this one already
dude wake up you're late my older
brother Luke yells from the kitchen okay
so uh today was my first new day at high
school since moving from Nashville to
Boston I checked my phone to see nine
plus messages from my best friend Amira
okay Amira was kind beautiful blah blah
blah
she's the perfect student I've always
felt been I've only felt like I've been
in a mirror Shadow my whole life but
that's how I liked it
I swear to God if you're late for your
first day
foreign
Lord I'm awake like she's texting back
and forth with her friend far away good
can we FaceTime while you get ready only
if you have time I'm actually really
late right now can I call you after
school fine I guess but have a good day
love you love you too and then whatever
I want to make a good first impression
at this high school because the last one
I switched schools it wasn't good no no
specifics it just wasn't good she throws
on the outfit that she picked out the
night before decides to go for a natural
makeup look I'm leaving in two minutes
if your ass isn't down here then I'm
leaving Jake yells louder okay I'm
leaving in two she moved get your [ __ ]
and let's move she moved to Boston for
something okay I don't care I finished
my makeup head downstairs amazing the
natural light car yeah the natural
luxury done with the natural look as we
get closer to the school I see these
three boys walking closer to the school
two in front pushing each other seeing
who Falls first okay and the other one
with the headphones on is yelling at the
first two I giggle to myself and look
back at them I want wonder who that is I
stare hard before one of the boys
catches me looking I think to myself I
peek over and see him wave oh he's cute
[Applause]
oh my God
it'll be like like look and then be like
like in the story she looks and sees us
in the giggles of what we're doing like
that's such a weird that's such a weird
thing like she looks like this
oh please edit that please edit that no
it's like this look she's I just imagine
you're like looking and she's like
getting her so that's gonna actually
then I just like awkwardness
[Applause]
yeah he pushed him oh the wave yes I'll
record the wave I'll record the wave
this is how it went it's like this hold
on it's like it's like a you guys pan to
me
they're pushing each other
go Mac [ __ ] your push push yeah push him
really get him on the ground push them
hard push them hard oh my God
go push push him and Chris don't defend
me and then I do the thing and then okay
Matt push him yeah get him on the ground
yeah all right
foreign
I don't know okay I found my locker and
I looked at the right of me and see oh
no I think to myself a boy with brown
hair and a chain dangling from his neck
come towards me the classic chain yes
from his neck
oh I got a horse Channel as he gets
closer and closer he turns to open the
locker door besides me you've got to be
joking right I try to make it make it
out without noticing me yet but I hear
him from oh be behind [ __ ] I say under
my breath hey you're the girl that was
uh looking at me and my brothers this
morning right okay you're the girl that
was looking at me and my brothers this
morning right I like I look behind me
and see the most beautiful blue eyes
I've ever seen in my life I stood there
in shock as he looks at me with a
concerned face oh um was I staring I say
trying to play it off yeah kind of
staring but it's all right yeah pretty
hard I'd say nothing close he says back
to me oh yeah haha that was me I say
with a slight change in my voice trying
to regain my confidence who's that in
your locker it's a picture of me in a
mirror what I don't give up
rather than the story you moved it's a
picture of her yeah she basically says
she moved from Nashville and that was
her and her best friend blah blah blah
if you ever want to hang out sometimes
what why do we want to hang out with
this girl we don't know cause Nick we
both caught each other's attention bro
okay
I just don't I've never invited someone
to like hang out that quickly in my life
dude like when you feel a moment like
that okay stop talking really cool if
you ever want to hang out sometimes he
gets cut off by someone who looks
identical to him smacking him in the
head wait are you guys twins I asked the
boy triplets the other one says hi I'm
Chris who are you bro I'm never that
enthusiastic hi I'm Chris hey man I'm
Chris the triplet
I'm Halle how are you Hallie that's a
really bad name like that's her no
that's a good name but I didn't know
that was her name I thought it was like
Amira
Amir is her friend she hasn't said her
name yet oh I try and get him to invite
me to hang out again oh like they didn't
make the plans yeah whatever
um
I'll talk to you later see you around I
watch him walk away as he turns back and
says bye
like okay butterflies fill my stomach
inside
oh [ __ ] like I gotta poop he's like
she has to use the bathroom as I walk
out of the washroom I see Matt or what I
think is Matt I took a chance to say hi
or whatever however
this wasn't Matt or Chris it was the
third one [ __ ] it was the head-fielded
brother from earlier in the morning ew
[ __ ] hello he says back with a certain
tone hello his voice that made it sound
that made it sound fake what I'm not
okay you're not Matt I say trying to
blow it off
she's trying to make it seem like oh I
didn't think you were Matt I was just
saying hi yo you gotta reword that yeah
imagine that like I made an error
try out the washroom too straight out
the washroom I'm trying to blow it I
took a chance I took a chance and say hi
like imagine okay no no imagine I'm
gonna read okay I'm just gonna try to
blow it off man but I just did that big
mistake I made laughs and says no I'm
Nick okay Nick Matt and Chris oh so
you're the third one right he Chuckles
yes I am no I'm not are you new I've
never seen your arms away I've never
seen you before yeah from Nashville
sweet you seem cool do you want to hang
out sometime girl I would never invite
you to my premises so early on
especially just because you're from
Nashville or cool you're not cool girl
you're using the bathroom
thank you
oh by the way I'm not asking you on a
date I'm gay he lets out a little laugh
corny I let on a side of relief because
I already knew I had some feelings for
Matt even though I barely knew him
corny but this was good I'll get to know
all the triplets we exchanged phone
numbers and say goodbye I would never
give my phone number to someone that
quickly ever I was bursting with
excitement because my crush's brother I
should hang out what kind of magical
town is this I don't know Fairyland
she texts her friend so she's her friend
texts her are you done with school yet
oh she's gonna recap relax
you wouldn't believe it he looked at me
with the most pretty blue eyes his
brother I tried to blow him off in the
hallway
okay I'm not hitting on you
I'm gonna honestly skip it because you
just said it like you summarized that
whole phone you wouldn't believe it he
just had the most gorgeous blue eyes and
my stomach was filling up she's the one
going to the bonfire tonight
it looks like we're all going what I'll
give you 10 bucks each I will get to the
bonfire I'll give you 10 bucks each if
you guess Chris isn't Snapchat username
oh no no Chris Chris yes please be Chris
[ __ ] Krispy Kreme
bro
I had stand in the five gallon bucket
stop talking talking about Chris says
Krispy Kreme related
that said it's okay I love my fans bro
chill you put my cover
[ __ ] Bro now she knows I like her
um I get there Chris opens the door with
a grin as a cute little dog creeps by
Trevor get back in because he's
gesturing for me to come in Matt and
Nick are sitting in the kitchen hey
Hallie Nick Telles from across the
kitchen yells I'm guessing and Matt's
still gay by the way Matt seems to be
texting someone he looks up from his
phone and greets me with a smile Chris
brings me to their backyard where the
fire is Matt and Nick why
there's no room I'm honestly done with
this because it [ __ ] it's another one
where I can't read it anymore because
it's unrealistic I'm not doing it again
I think it's funny I just think the
unreal the unrealistic Parts make me
laugh and I stand by what I said like I
could literally a leprechaun could show
up and give everyone fairy magic and I
believe in more than half these stories
it's just her in her story
or so YouTube like they're so like
um like we're gonna go film a baking
video in a car video in the parking lot
which we filmed in the minivan with my
triplet Brothers
like this I'm sorry I just don't gag
like oh my God
stupid
I need a Wattpad episode with no YouTube
involved and it's like weird as [ __ ]
straight straight
like this is what's scary that is insane
it really scares me send them over y'all
want a part five
oh my God man I just don't like
rewarding this type of behavior I think
it's awesome
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah
for my brothers