first question on your mind is probably
Nick
why are you completely alone
and it's because I have a surprise
so if you guys are unaware me Matt and
Chris because of our mom she used to
dress us up we had an unreal amount of
drip as children like unwarranted levels
of drip so for this week's video I'm
going to be styling Matt and Chris as
them young as their younger selves as a
surprise they're gonna have no idea that
I'm doing this she got us a bunch of
clothes and to help tell the difference
between us not tell the difference but
like in individualize us they all had
our names like sewn on the side so I
have a bunch of options and then I'm
going to choose from these old pieces of
our clothes and then style Us in new
outfits and there's this little
blue sweater with a sailboat on it which
is very matte
so I'm gonna try this will be my top
pick I have this red flannel
with my name in it Matt's flannel nice
cream color with red and gray on it
Chris is flannel
Chris's shirt
so cute
these are long sleeve but they're since
they're so small they look like short
sleeve shirts and Chris had this
but enough Matt's button up oh a little
90 on it all right I'm gonna make this
brief because I know you guys want to
see Matt and Chris in this video and
I've been talking forever but we're in
La we've been Nelly for like I want to
say like uh two weeks a week and a half
since I last talked to you guys at the
beginning of this video but I gathered
everything
that I need
to complete this video I've been
shopping and everything is finally here
so I'm going to show you the photo of
them in it as a kid or the actual item
of it like
as a kid and then I'll show you the
photo as well
good word so
as in the beginning of this video I
showed you guys like a little yellow and
blue rugby shirt that was Matt's and it
had his name on it so I went on polo and
I found it in his size right here so I'm
gonna open it
and it's this is just like the one I
showed you guys at the beginning of this
video
which isn't necessarily something Matt
would by himself now but I have this
right matches the other one and I went
to CVS and I printed photos I'm also I
also have a photo of Matt and our older
brother Justin with of him in that shirt
and then I have a photo of Matt and
Chris in that shirt
and another photo of Matt and Chris in
that shirt so I'll frame some of them
and give them to him with this so that's
one Ben as you guys know with Chris and
his brand and everything his love for
the color orange he always had this R
and R and John ever since he was a kid
insert photo of him almost in this exact
hoodie so I scavenged the world for eBay
and I found this which is super similar
to the one of him in that photo so I'm
gonna give him this and here's the photo
that I'm gonna frame as well I'm gonna
put it on the screen
which you guys may have seen on
Instagram and then I also found this
photo of him in like a little
I don't know same hoodie super cute
photo so I'm gonna give Chris the hoodie
in that lastly there's this photo that
me Matt and Chris always piss our pants
laughing at of us three on Santa and I'm
having a good time Chris looks confused
and Matt is bawling his eyes out and so
I went also to Polo and I found super
simple just three long sleeve shirts in
the exact same colors so I'm gonna give
them that and the photo as well the
things going in this gift bag white polo
shirt for Matt blue polo shirt for me
red Polo shirt for Chris and then this
framed photo okay I know I just put that
stuff in that bag in front of you guys
but I'm gonna put the photo at the
bottom so they get the clothes and
they're like what the [ __ ] is this and
then they are like oh like put the
pieces together all right pack number
two is gonna have this Frame photo of
Chris and this framed photo of Chris I'm
putting them at the bottom of the bag so
he gets the hoodie first and is confused
or he might even grab the hoodie first
and be like oh my God I remember this
and then see the photos and then you
know full circle moments are at the
bottom
hoodie on the top bag number two done
the mat I'm really excited for because
Chris was easy right like Chris had like
he has orange she had that hoodie like
he was very obvious about it but there's
a lot of things that Matt used to wear
as a kid like when we were babies
they're like he looks so cool in and he
knows that and he has like a very
particular style so I know he never
would buy this for himself so I'm happy
I'm able to get it for him so that he
can like relate it to when he was a kid
and then own it and be happy about it
because I know it's not something he'd
pick up for himself but he'll be happy
to have it get back to Matt these two
photos on the bottom your shirt on the
top bag number three complete let's go
clear off the kitchen table put the bags
on it and then I'll have them open them
what's the bag for what do you mean let
me all see the bag behind you again I
don't have a bag okay it's not that big
of a deal at all but sit down I feel
like I've been a troubled kid for like
years and I'm being sat down by my
mother I don't like the bag
wait start at the top [ __ ]
everything's putting there for a reason
okay
I'm about to drive it why are we getting
gifts shut up open it okay is this for
who
okay this looks so weird okay another
shirt I mean
in blue
and red are you like telling us you're
like having a kid or something yeah like
this are you gonna like pull out a pink
one and we have to like throw them
around
before we open it what does this remind
you of America wrong that too but what
else red white and blue I mean it's
pretty patriotic
don't say it
what
not put it together okay go ahead Matt
I don't get it well I know I why I got
it
oh my God
how did you even put that together kid
because look I just knew all right I got
you both individually something as well
as that group photo can you guess what
fit from your childhood I matched you in
before I give you your individual things
oh my God I'm not gonna cry on Santa's
lap again no I know we're gonna have to
do something else we'll have to like
take a photo but I already showed them
that but what do you guys think like an
article of clothing I possibly might
have gotten you individually is I have
no idea sorry for the washing machine
ugly it's hard Elite what I'm joking
okay we'll go with Matt first hold on oh
wow it's under the blank oh wow another
bag wow you're hiding a lot of these
bags I bought bags
now I also have video footage if you
want to see of me vlogging at home with
that actual shirt mom has it still so
you can have me go back to Boston yeah
that's actually so cute
oh my God okay and then Matt was such a
cute little kid dude oh I think I know
what Chris is gonna get no that's why I
would have put in the same bag but
that's so funny that is crazy such a
little cute kid bro
oh it's hard
no [ __ ] way holy [ __ ] it looks like
you hit it with like a big Ray literally
that's exactly what it is
holy [ __ ] this is beautiful
wow now look at the photo of baby Chris
in the little yeah that one's so cute
cow like I look like I'm licking my lips
like a cow
every single time I do that
so cute wow this hoodie is sick I'm
actually wearing this like it's a medium
I couldn't find it in any other size but
I put it on it fit me so okay
that I'm wearing in both of these yes
it's just Wombo literally it looks like
you took a gun and shot it and made it
one bow that's awesome
I'm thoroughly shocked me too and
moments from now that's about to be me
the same position and everything I still
actually [ __ ] like that like to this day
like a little girl yeah like really
girly like like I need to find
like this is how I sit very often
okay okay Little Mermaid well I also
find like really girly positions the
most comfortable way to find blue shoes
and camo pants Oh Brother this kid's
gonna make it like we have it just what
are you doing
are those red socks and white shoes I
think I think so too hold on yeah go
ahead Matt like what are you saying go
ahead I said do you have anything to say
I need to find camo pants we'll find
them we have them like is that is that
it
I'm gonna dress like the picture because
no what do you want me to say no she
said something he but he talked about it
you have nothing to say
burst my blood vessels and throw up at
three like what what
that sounds like a fan I'ma burst my
blood vessels and throw up a three
that's what I'm doing is that like what
you wanted like song burst my blood
vessels like oh let me just fly just now
and sit on his lap and
no he Chris had Chris had a thought and
he spoke and it made sense and it was
funny you said I'm gonna take a picture
and find camo pants and blue shoes like
yeah obviously in history as most
sentimental Story video ever because I
feel like this
oh
okay
all right yeah that ain't [ __ ]
come over sir cow I had that same [ __ ]
on
okay got the Hat on the video on Blue
Jeans
white shoes little red in the sock yeah
we found a parking lot that's ugly oh my
God
[Music]
get me out of here okay I guess you
didn't find a parking lot we can take
them there's someone right here there's
someone right here but we have to just
go fast because I can't oh my God
well you're making it a bigger deal
let's just go the zoo with coop it
sounds like the zoo with poop okay
individual photos
bro you just made me move over here
[Music]
all right
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things