[Music]
you're 10 minutes late serious trouble
you're going to be in serious serious
trouble you need a [ __ ] haircut all
right so I'm late but where's the boss
the boss's room where he always is so
let's go knock on the boss's room not it
those goes I'm not do that let's go
together no I'm not to present here
you're going to take this that's your
mve board you're going to take your take
the briefcase and we're going to go talk
theck a second s it to the man hold that
for me problem no
problem good morning see the hole in the
door hey man what's up bossy Mr Boss
Man Chris you were here on time great
Matt you were late
I understand but we have some very
exciting news to present to you today
especially me I love my ideas it's
actually nice to see you
again
wait I try my hardest to never be [ __ ]
you sir me too but there's a problem
with the wife and and the dog and the
daughter and I'm sorry I hope they're
alive cuz if you speak again when not
spoken to they're going to be [ __ ]
dead tour number three everything needs
to change nothing can look like the past
we moving forward yellow brick road to
the end goal both of you should have
something shut up both of you should
have something that you should be
presenting today he's going to go first
because he was on time I have some notes
and to play little pun they're my
Emerald City oh wow let's [ __ ] open
them um wait sorry this is those are
those are pictures of me I um I left my
work clipboard at home and I brought
work clipboard personal
clipboard it was a mixup yeah yeah what
are you do with that sorry I have I I do
have my
work this one's mine that's his I do
have my work vision boards right okay
pitch the vision boards yes I'm ready to
present
go I um I made a vision board and I'm
prepared to present it this is
definitely me I don't even know where
you got
this um I was working on more of the
concept of the walk out the intro I
think that we need to Captivate the fans
immediately and that's that's why I made
my vision work uh if you want to if you
want to borrow this meter stick you can
use it as a pointer love to use this
pointer stick meter
stick okay so basically I have step one
here we got to be
fly I'm thinking y 2K style I got some
Eminem I thinking like if if I do the
Jersey Matt you do the little matching
set Nick you can wear like a gay little
hat we're cooking so step two shut your
mouth you're Lake very intrigued by the
gay little hat it's peing my interest
exactly why I put I that photo right
there I I think I'm the only one of us
that that do step one every day but shut
your [ __ ] mouth be fly okay step two
we have hype need it so basically this
is a dark stage dark stage we would
creep up on the dark stage that would be
like us like that's us standing there
kind of like a head tilt Vibe I is that
The Wanted Matt I don't know who the
[ __ ] it is it's a sick photo okay super
blacked out dark like this like head
tilted boom notice I put that boom I
don't know it is US Mt I don't know if
we should go boom in the venue let me
present listen Spotlight look at that
look at the Arc of Spotlight beaming on
that young gentleman that would be us
three step four we have super hype not
to be confused with that too which is
just hype we have a 10c fire intro have
you heard the intro to Rack City play
Rack City by
Tiger Rack City by Tiger now playing on
Apple music Apple
music was he in your top
[Music]
five now we're in step five that's the
10-second intro step five last one by
the way last step okay yeah knock him
dead type [ __ ] crowd would go nuts if we
hit that move is Aura like the upside
down like break dance Nick doing it with
me I don't have enough and then some
Matt you can like leap through us like
if we're both upside down like that you
like leap through US kind of like that's
the vibe I might be able to do the Le
this one's some like corny [ __ ] but
if we hit that like floater move I think
we're I think we're in for some good
serious some serious intro action um
love the effort yeah this is not
happening I agree uh no one's looking
for you to agree you make zero decisions
around
here you wouldn't say thr get rid of the
board okay sorry
sorry I have one more mood board let's
see it okay this one I was thinking a
lot simpler I wanted to not get
distracted on one Niche moment of the
show so I was like another versus tour
just run the whole thing back it was
very successful for me no um don't I I
don't love agreeing with members of the
party who are tardy and Matt was late
today but we absolutely can't do this
one of my first rules was it needs to be
different from the other tours you can
get rid of this board
too you have anything else maybe that a
couple more notes I can go go ahead you
have anything else besides being late I
do actually I'm going to present for you
right
now this is actually uh all for show
there's nothing nothing in here I do
have a mood board that I made that I'm
ready to present to you guys if
and uh I hate to ask could I get the
yard stick maybe you are nowhere near
yard stick
privilege unless I get up the ass whoa
all right um so this is my kind of big
idea right so we have to integrate our
YouTube channel in a sense that's who we
are touring you know what I mean correct
but there there most of the time most of
the time when influencers can do this
gets a little bit on that corny line
we're in that corny zone so we got to
get out of that corny Zone a little bit
this is kind of where I I think is a
perfect place to be I think you guys all
remember filming the anonymous
confessions videos that we did this one
is from two years ago but does it maybe
ring a couple Bells mhm in here I filmed
the [ __ ] video yeah yeah we create
one of these put maybe a little QR code
scan enter your confession we react live
on stage they could say their
grandmother died that morning and we
have to talk about
it maybe something more light-hearted
like I love the triplets
no no that's boring I love the grandma
Anonymous can't get bullied can't say
anything stupid they say whatever they
want we react to it they could be top
left they could be top right all we know
is it's going to get red out loud how do
we feel about a boss I love it it's very
interactive uh uh uh uh uh how do we
feel about it boss you were late to work
today but there's one place you can't be
late and that's hitting the [ __ ] tour
bus when we take this on the road all
right so I think my idea is good but I
think we need a couple more concrete
things to do and then we can hit the
road I'd like to redeem
myself go for it okay so while I was
sitting here and I was thinking us
triplets tell each other everything you
know I love you
guys and I was thinking I just don't
like keeping secrets from you so how
funny would it be if I did now let me
explain this is
today this is our tour right here
imagine in between all this time we
randomly go out of the house shut our
location off and do something [ __ ]
insane so say on this day I go here and
I Skydive out of a plane this is the
plane oh sorry that doesn't look like a
plane and I jump out of the plane that
is a penis okay okay I'm sorry I'm not
artist go ahead loveing the direction
let's hear some more yes so then say I
jump out of the plane and I record it
and it was nuts and then I get home
later that day and walk in like nothing
happened right you guys are going be
like what did he do he went and filmed a
surprise but I have no idea when can I
see that surprise oh my God on tour oh
my God so then I'll have like a five
minute 8 Minute amazing crazy video of
me doing something ridiculous that you
guys have never seen and I'll present it
to you for you to react live on stage
like that's your face like like oh my
god
with everyone else in the crowd also so
reacting and shock and surprised so if
correct me if I'm wrong but we're
turning this tour into a Content
screening that two of the triplets and
the entire crowd are going to react to
also going to be a comedy show and have
bits and pieces from our YouTube channel
throughout the show as well yes exactly
correct oh God I must have made him
angry let's go yes yes you like it
okay not to be corny not to be cringe
but let's do this thing let's
trip
yeah come on it's not it's we're not
we're not I just got it going to go on a
trip you just got it cuz we're going to
go on a trip like we're going to be on
the road that's why has nothing to do
with our other two tours or merch well
no cuz he just used it in like a pony
way I don't p a Pon p it could be the
office hours tour it's still going to be
funny you're right it could be the dick
around on stage tour it's still going to
be
funny you're so right ham in let's go
okay all right uh meet on the bus that
won't be late if you get there on time
we got to we got to go though list
there's no this isn't like a let's let's
put the dates on screen as we leave the
road my middle name's ready by the way Z
let's
go action bro you're like 10 minutes
late by the way 10 minutes it's 2025
send me a [ __ ] Zoom link all right
how about
that I don't think you'd be later if you
tried the wife took the car today so I'm
stuck [ __ ]
biking dude you're so late I thought I
was going to turn 80 before you got here
today the [ __ ] stock market crashed
and I popped two cars
so you're late
again the dog got out
how bad was the traffic you're that late
really bad traffic rough night in the
bar I've been here for a half hour
waiting you're wait I was in the shower
and I ran out of hot water so I had to
do what I could you
know you're late again Matt got to be
moving quicker here look Sally got off
the leash the kids were running after
the dog it's not my
problem dude you're late again you got
to be figuring that out it's uh 72
degrees today and I normally work better
at a high
60 Employee of the Month gone if
you you can kiss Employee of the Month
goodbye if you're late one more
time if you're late again you can take a
by to employee of the month you going to
keep stuttering
or all right I'm ready hold up thank you
wait oh we're running I didn't know we
were going that's the first thing I'm
going to do I was Wai okay yeah I was
waiting for a countown my bad the prac
down okay wa should we should we start
here yes all right 3 two one action
Y [ __ ]
[ __ ] good morning you
BOS a new time
a second to like start walking 3 two one
action dude you got it you don't know
how to hand me
anything late to work can't hand people
things it's like
ridiculous hey boss rough
morning up
that that one's really good let's do
that one more time like just like that I
like
that I always try to be on
time
that I tried really hard to not be tardy
sir um anyway I
have I really try my hardest not to be
tardy
sir um um I have a couple ideas are you
open for to hearing them since that's
what this whole [ __ ] meeting's about
like yeah I'm ready okay um um before we
start you speak with spoken to Matt your
phone three two one action I'm sorry
boss I Tred my darness to be Hardy or
not not run it back run it back run it
back all right oh hold
on all right three two one
action focusing on my schedule was a
very important thing to me I try not to
be tardy me too I just I couldn't really
figure that out
today yeah also Matt when I say like
tour number three like I need you guys
to present I think that's your perfect
time to ask bathroom yes yeah actually
yeah I want to cut that part shorter too
all right okay what's happening on your
phone nothing sorry yes I kind of need
to go to the bathroom before we get into
the
okay
um
sorry okay tour number three and then
step two have to be hype we need to Hype
like I think we're missing that like in
your face VI okay Charlie so what I'm
thinking is
is
that here's my first vision board dep
two the stage is dark super dark can't
see a thing we tiptoe out there like
thieves in the
night thieves in the night pop smoke
reference no no no so then we're here
that's not even a pop Smoke song I don't
think well then we're here like a thief
in the night oh it is a pop Smoke song
yeah so then it's going type [ __ ] this
is the last step by the way and then
this is the aura move so if I do an
upside down hand spin Nick the aura move
you can do this like double kick lean B
on one hand you're going to have to work
on it we have to have a lot of practice
Matt you leap through us like the
Kool-Aid Man breaking through a an
armored wall and every single time we've
done this 9.7 million viewers we've uh
that's a completely incorrect stat yeah
I don't think it's every time I think
those are the stats no no no I said
every time we did it combined put them
all in the WR no maybe that's the bigger
note you put in the middle of 7 no no
I'm thinking that it's the bigger one oh
oh yes sorry sorry hold on my apologies
sir you should be this right here is
that one video that one
video million I I know yeah I know more
than you do but let me let me finish
this up 2 sorry sorry
23.5 I was late I I was late I was late
and I was nervous
23.5 million viewers overall on all of
these videos that's a lot of viewers and
if you look and stop it if you look at
the if you look at the subscriber count
69.8 th000 subscribers yes 69 more than
100,000 so exactly what I was saying
awesome I don't know if that's exactly
what you were saying I think that was
exactly the bush you were beating down
and maybe beating around but I don't
think that's what you said but do
overall good idea great idea cool I went
Lefty Lefty excuse me but if Sally who
wants to let let us know that Jimmy her
boyfriend slept with her ex that morning
we have to read that on stage and react
to it oh my God I love the idea I feel
bad for Sally Lou though [ __ ] Sally Lou
I have nothing to say what do we
say you really just hurt my hand I'm
sorry it's okay okay are we calling
something out no on three let's do this
and you say let's this no this isn't a
good idea okay all right I'll meet you
guys at the bus yeah