okay yeah good greetings
Earth hey what color did you
get we said we going to travel from the
island to Madrid we had a lot of plans
but they
all why oh because of some kid but it's
okay cuz
I'm today we're going to utilize wheel
once again once again two out of the
three last and we're going to get random
tattoos today or I'm not Nick and Matt
are but we figured it wouldn't be fun if
it was just Nick and Matt so we have
some friends coming over today to enjoy
the experience with us some of the
options on the wheel include the bomb
the UFO eye with wings you pick any of
them horses skull butterfly spider
cowboy star spider web B
horseshoe party frog an anchor a bomb
and a UFO you said bomb in UFO choice
but that's okay that's fine they get it
though they get the gist of it but
anyway but us and our friends are going
to be spinning this wheel and then our
amazingly T talented tattoo artist Mees
is going to tattoo them all us instant
while you talk they can't hear you yeah
he keeps fing I said it [ __ ] three
times don't talk while I'm spinning it
then you you go like this and then start
talking like you yourself they they can
they probably can but guess what is
better now now that it's off anyway he's
trying to make the viewer experience
better thank you Nick glad we get it but
basically everyone's going to spin this
wheel and then get let the wild rumpus
begin get what does that even mean it's
from the book
rumus Mees Drew all of these up so now
now when they get here and mes gets here
we're going to start the start spinning
I do not want this one either the
[ __ ] at the Carl Jun Lo is it it
looks like the Carl
Jun I'll be fine with anything but those
to that's that's my goal you have the
horse necklace on be pretty ironic if
you got the horse I think you might the
cowboy
store oh I got to put I got to take this
off did you just go is Johnny going
first okay hold on oh ready weak SP good
one all right
go oh
brother skull easy we
like just take the skull off and then
change it to another like spin
again okay or do we or do we do an arrow
to either one of these no just do spin
again okay cuz then that makes the horse
probability way too high yes I pray to
God someone gets the cowboy star I want
the cowboy star so bad really or the
party FR please dance for
us please
dance dance for us you know please I'll
go I'll stand next to you so you feel
more comfortable thank you this is great
I know do the [ __ ] it's like a talent
show go to super dance
awesome little spot I'll do it on my
forehead just like right between right
here yeah your third eye
yeah there yeah that's actually like
that spot was made for it fate I believe
in
fate I want the party frog I get the
party frog if someone gets the party
frog for me I'll be upset party frog you
look like a party
frog oh you're look you look strong all
right I
[Music]
what are your thoughts it's very cute
little fella cute little
friend oh wow
did exactly like out of all the
tattoos spider
spider you least excited for I can you
already know it's got to be the cowboy
star and where's that frog at party frog
no one's a fan of party frog and cowboy
star it makes me sad like I love the
party frog all right let's let it
rip spin it with some
Force Whi out fate oh
brother the horse all right that's
cool we have to post the Tik Tok that he
said does the inspiration of why I did
that at the wheel interrupted him they
need to know the
inside yes they do that's the funniest T
to well explain it explain it and then
I'll throw a clip the guy goes up to
random people and he goes hey and then
ask him a question and as soon as he
answer go all right all right all right
like is invested when he asks him Absol
zero time he makes him seem like he
wants to listen but then he just doesn't
do that
exactly hey is a highlight yeah yeah
really wow yeah this was the only one
they had in all right that's enough
that's enough
thanks um oh my God it cracks your
back how do you do it you like lay on it
you your spine go teach Johnny Chris
like pull you oh
like and then it cracks your back wow I
don't think you really need to lift your
legs yeah I think I feel pretty
pointless oh you didn't really give
yourself much F to work with was going
under the coffee
table oh
[ __ ] nice it puts me it puts me in more
pain than it does have I love it
[Music]
good horse a
horse
[Music]
hard I don't
know so wait wait so that
me
one
Oho Matt you have to ask him which one's
your what are you hoping for most what
are you hoping for
most Spiderman or spider uh is that say
it look like
spitter good old
spitter
oh is it the party the ball
I'll
[Music]
get oh my God I didn't think it was
getting filled in no the fill in is fire
bottom is done oh my God it's not
focusing hold on hold on
word all right Nick it's your turn I
party frog bro uhoh I kind of hope he
get hold on it's not fing Focus frog is
it Focus I can't tell go ahead please do
the party frog party
frog really good party
frog the eye with wings that's my
favorite that that's my second favorite
I'm like upset that Landon's not getting
this I feel fit him more than fits me
put it but I'm going to I think I'm
going to fill this spot filling the the
Gap the Bermuda Triangle
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah that's oh thank God
I'm that is
hard word I always feel like a slug on
here why I feel stuck to it I'm always
scaring to get up and leave like a trace
of my whole body on this
thing a couple hours 3 hours I think bro
ate it and then asked you already had
like four that's what I'm saying
good I watched him walk by and do it I
was like you might regret that yeah I'm
a little upset it's not the party frog
but I'll live if no one lands on the
party frog today I might get the party
frog eventually anyway all righty Nick
let's go
sluggy naturally Hold on shut up isn't
he so cute I feel like I should name you
stop like moving all jittery and [ __ ]
thanks all right all right I should name
him Iris Matt which one do you want most
yes Matt cowboy star I'd be fine with
anything but the party frog and the
cowboy star spin the wheel I really want
it to be the party frog you can't
chicken out if it's the party
frog okay with that
o ooh who really lands on you in the
same spot and you can't tell the
difference you get scared I think these
in real life have a little more color
[Music]
they damn that's my favorite one so far
before right yeah you got lucky dog yeah
I did thank God now you'll see that and
you'll remember this experience forever
yep a
Landon give it a
spin again
again
oh the cowboy star
[Music]
see
it cowboy star oh y how does it feel to
have it on I love it he said I love
it little l so cute slim pickings
now you're so close to party frog
oh I didn't even realize that wow that's
great which one should I get party FR
honestly go party frog do not if the
party frog gets picked in a up pick
that'd be insane I love the party
frog go party FR no way oh my gosh pH
what's his
name it's like it's a very predictable
name he looks like it is it like a
froggy no but like it does have a GRE in
it word it has a g in it uh Gregory
wow how did you guess his name that's
what I said that's that's insane now it
has to be Gregory yeah do like it I'm so
happy he's getting a home this is
wonderful he would have been so lonely
he's ready for a party
there
y you miss me yeah you miss me and all
the things that we did we said we going
to travel from the island to Madrid we
had a lot of plans but they all this why
all because of some but it's okay cuz
I'm moving different don't be saying
nothing when I
post brother