no that's no it's not usually that
bright no it can't oh I feel like I'm a
low rider tonight hold on is this good
welcome to the sternula triplet cheddar
jack brother Channel
we hope that you have a rocking sock in
time
that car has rusties on it like the car
like from tow meter yes
wait is this a tripod yes
she called it a metal stick I'm like I
thought it was a twig
what were you saying Matt nothing I was
just talking about camera stuff this
would be a great weapon if someone like
ran up on us okay okay well let's get
after it today we are going to be
raiding I don't know like how we're
gonna do it but we're gonna rate emojis
or like kind of
not rate them but kind of be like a TBH
like a TBH don't say that no that feels
way too like two thousand we're just
talking about them let's text it to
their group chat and then react like oh
good idea I think we should reenact it
the second it gets sent as well like
everyone does their best reenactment of
it okay
this is my favorite emoji for so many
reasons because it's like we I think
honestly what we should do instead of
rating them is put like the perfect
scenario yes yeah like this emojis and
someone just says like it's like if
someone texts the word actually like
about the yo are we having dinner at 6
30 and you're like actually six I would
send that okay okay Nick thanks no I
think
I think I think it's so funny when Matt
uses this Emoji because he'll like
genuinely be I I love repeating someone
and then just sending the Emoji with it
yeah
with the exact same thing Hold Up Wait
I'm gonna put that I'm gonna type that
emoji in like my text conversation bar
and see if there's oh The Twist yes yeah
oh okay so Chris was
is that God
Matt just keep going okay so me and
Chris were talking Chris is trying to
get my attention about something I don't
want to say quite what it is but I said
noted with the noted like that's so
funny oh my God
ever since the colby jack audio of us
went viral we always make fun of
ourselves
actually actually
lay low
camera Nick lights off our parking lot
got infiltrated so we're going to the
next area go move move roll out
the bottom of Don Julio on the ground
should have been a red flag at the
starters I love it honestly it shows
characterism okay
you don't even know what that word means
yeah nine I know I was gonna say neither
do you but you might
shut up help me
you're not good at it let's do it help
no it's help me
that's actually terrible
[Applause]
that is crazy
there's too much rambunctious stuff
going on okay we're gonna rate emojis
and we're gonna describe and we're gonna
talk
yo this is giving the same energy as
like knock knock who's there ding cow
interrupting cow moo type [ __ ]
you just read a whole book what the [ __ ]
is that
they live
there was like a movie that like every
like in like the franchise like there
was a movie like in Austin Ally there's
like a movie that they all go watch
Disneyland
type [ __ ] yeah they like zillion brain
sucked each other but the whole show was
just alien brainstalk and goop
everywhere I feel like you should like
add a clip for the people like me that
are very confused no that's Disney bro
I'm not [ __ ] that copyright oh that's
true anyways we're gonna move on to the
next emotions
[Applause]
I've also never seen that one before
like is that not crazy oh it's a knot
obviously yeah it's probably like a
fisherman knot no but I hate Fisher's
men not that's the nerd Emoji yeah it's
probably
not yeah I hate emojis that like and
you're not
what was the context being which you'd
send that no um
it was a Thai game
oh my God
what
I don't have any
when okay so when we would sometimes
order packages to Lara's house so when I
was asking you to bring a package from
Laura's house to ours I said please
bring the big package
that's so funny though that's insane
that's so funny the little purple
smirking devil I hate I hate when people
use that yeah I think it's cringe oh
hundred it just reminds me of like
Ranger 100.
I just think it's like a little like
it's just goofy it's like a naughty
little angry little I don't know like
it's like oh you like
what are you thinking what are you
thinking the backpack Emoji the pin
Emoji the money with the wings and then
like that one can I tell you it's mine
my opinion is is the kid that graduated
high school three years ago but is still
selling Edibles and yes yes I agree
that's the vibe I'm getting with that's
literally what mine is like like that
with like the backpack
like it's like I'm in my bag type you
know you said naughty yeah naughty
little devil like
it was just the Vibes that I got
help
help us
what the butter boat
like butter butter
where's the butter granny oh it's in the
butter boat
a million I hate butter I hate butter
popcorn on your lip I hate butter
my popular opinion okay no what dude
relax give me pop Christmas
is always crazy on like the making Mega
noise while he's eating
I'm not a big fan of butter either I
hate butter
like more than anything like when they
bring like bread and butter to the table
I just put the butter away you look like
butter your [ __ ] mom
all right I'm gonna send mine
this is my favorite emoji to use when I
think somebody said something like
stupid or something like like bro come
on yeah I don't I've texted that emoji
millions of times with like
nothing else after that's like the face
I constantly make when posting Snapchats
I love that we're like going about my
day-to-day life like I make that face
like probably
I was like
probably 200 times a day I moved it like
this because yeah that light is the only
way that they can see me in this video
and I felt you go in front of it so that
was just like I felt like so like pulled
back I was like whoa okay next Emoji for
me I love it okay if we go to the oh
[ __ ] like it's like
I
don't know what the context is like it's
like
um
Laura texted us a whole paragraph about
our life and how like there's ups and
downs and how like a friendship is
compared to a tree and like you have to
just trim off the Bad branches but the
the tree will still grow and be healthy
and I said amen I agree my goal is to be
a root for all of you if we're and we're
all our own tree help you start and Nick
said I love Roots I'm ready to I'm ready
to saw some bad branches off
let me see what else I use that in
context with
we were talking about oh here's our own
we were going to Hawaii and Laura sent
us the hotel we were staying at and she
goes staying here with like a link to
the resort and I said yes we are I would
like that that's weird it's so funny I
feel like a lot of emojis it depends on
like character like I could picture
something
and it totally depends who you are as a
person
I've never got scared of me
I've never got scared I never in my old
life got scared by the [ __ ] alarm and
that one did it I think like us
switching parking lots I wasn't
expecting it it's just funny because
like this is what
220th car video in and now what 220 like
be real I don't know what are you
what's your least favorite text to
receive
like what what you look at your phone
you're just like bro what emoji no just
like in general
your name oh oh bro Chris I hate that
[ __ ] that's embarrassing like I
hate you
not you or like that I have a question
all right I need to tell you something
worse
when you get a chance
um anything that like leads to like an
ultimatum of like I have no idea what
you're gonna possibly say next yeah I
agree
it sounds like you want to text but then
you also want to wait so that you're in
the right mindset but then it's like I
hate the I have a question
my least favorites I need some help hey
like hey
I need some help with something
or like hey like can you help me with
something or like when they like like
you know they're gonna ask you for
something and you just don't want to
face the fury The Fury Fury my least
favorite like you just said
Matthew that's it
that was the first one I said yeah I
know bro what's your least favorite
dentist tool what like you're at least
when the dentist grabs that you're like
[ __ ] I honestly like the pick one the
scraper like I don't know if it's a
script
that was my least favorite bro like the
pick
I've never had a dentist go open up
yeah like like when they the three on me
no I don't know I like the pink you guys
are confusing me bro I feel like at 10
every single day every single dad use
the thumbs up emoji but imagining
someone with a thumbs down
dude hey you free today nah with like a
thumbs down
it's in my way
I think I'd honestly rather be flipped
off and called a slur than the thumb
down you know what I mean I'm like
serious if someone was like if someone
straight up was like
I'm trying to think of the context here
and when someone give you like a thumbs
down like if like you [ __ ] were at
the store and you oh my God the
watermelon and it broke everywhere so
I'm just like
yeah imagine you have like a watermelon
and you're carrying it for someone and
then you trip and fall and drop it and
spill it better like water everywhere
instead of cook and someone straight up
was like
oh [ __ ] you like [ __ ] you you dropped it
right middle fingers I'd literally
rather that than like a oh man
no good oh no good no good with a thumbs
down bro that makes me feel bad for
raspberries bro why like how many times
have people pick up fruit that's just
not good now these are no good
this is the most random [ __ ] thing
yeah but just imagine that blueberry bro
imagine being a boss no it just made me
really feel bad thinking of like fruit
and no good like like do you know how
much fruit a day probably people like
look at and examine and they're like Ah
that's no good like maybe like humans
feel like fruit sometimes like what if
what if someone's like going through
like life and like ah no good on that
one like I'm good like that must be so
sad that is upsetting like dude imagine
being like a tray of blueberries and
someone just picks you up spins you on
and says no no good and then it throws
you back into the thing and then no when
it happens multiple but imagine imagine
they take you put you you're in the
basket you go all the way to the
register and the cashier scans and goes
you sure you want these they're no good
and you're like ah and then they have to
re-rubber ban you and like put you on
the waiting goes back to produce
probably worse oh this could be imagine
imagine getting put down
ultimate top 10 betrayals ever
dude I don't know why that was what I
thought of no sometimes I feel like
humans treat people like fruit and say
ah not good but they don't look at the
root cause what if every other
strawberry on that strawberry Bush
besides that little batch you picked up
was the best Bush ever It produced some
of the highest grade quality
strawberries ever
and then that one batch is a few
negative ones and we're gonna just go
ahead and say like no good if those
fruit can't get their feelings hurt like
this I feel like we're digging too deep
no it's a metaphor map obviously the
fruit I'm talking about life bro oh all
right like us three are brothers and
stuff right what if one day you did
something bad this was like oh they're
no good because him
what what us there is a group are great
people an awesome rad cool dudes yeah so
for them to profile us as a group
because you're no good for one minor
moment
how'd that make you feel if you were the
blueberry on the bush I agree
you can go see the worst the worst
blueberry
the worst blueberry in the bunch could
make the best blueberry in the bunch
think of it like this how about this no
I'm done with this [ __ ] I'm gonna cry
bro no I think Chris feels like this
because like when we do like hot tubs
and stuff like that he genuinely like
always talks about how he feels like
like a carrot you know so I feel like he
he very that's a vegetable and a totally
different topic
I'm not comfortable talking about that
further okay
I feel like you were late
no yes I thought you called me late and
I was going to jump right on because I'm
here give me something I said I thought
you were late but he said relate
[Applause]
stop
why because bro you look like a
strawberry
okay I actually get scared when your
like vein pops out of your neck
can I get angry my forehead man goes
nutty
is the worst dude I get angry way too
easily
thank God you finally realized
what the [ __ ] are you doing
I felt the wet like Splash on my lips
it was like perfectly circular that my
immediate bodily response was like I
felt like a ping pong yeah let me spit
on my [ __ ] brother make it feel all
wet and sloppy like you [ __ ] serious
I feel gross now oh are you gonna cry
about it you little baby the only thing
you're gonna cry about is my fist in
your mouth
lots of more okay he literally spit on
me and called oh my God that no that's
it it didn't even do something again
like that I'm gonna [ __ ]
I'm gonna make the sad blueberry wow my
nipples yeah I don't care
okay can we move on shut up Sylvester is
that your real name
get out of here oh look let me stop you
little [ __ ] loser don't call me now
Chris okay
the [ __ ] you gonna do about it you're
insane 39 calories per cup what size cup
are we talking
oh my God
what
there's like fur on my hand I thought it
was a spider
the whole car is shaking
oh my my fingers are out oh my God I
can't I can't hear it yeah let's go let
go
I'll have to go
and then I will [ __ ] rule the debt
you will Brew it I will I will make this
the hardest living life on Earth you've
ever had in your life get the apartment
you're a crazy little nut
s like there's a crazy little fruit loop
don't [ __ ] call me a nut or a loop
what are you gonna do you nutty Loop
what I don't even want to respond to
that bro nutty Luke this was this week's
Friday card video if you like
car videos keep damning us and comments
what videos
so much content soon every Wednesday
every Friday podcast starting soon
don't say that don't mention the podcast
again [ __ ] outro this [ __ ] I'm hot
new videos Wednesdays Fridays oh man I'm
hot all that good stuff make sure you're
following all of us thank you guys I
love you so much and thank you so much
for watching we appreciate all of you
and comment videos
comment video ideas for us to do for
more Friday car videos or part twos or
part threes or part nines or part
whatever is that you guys want peace and
love
oh