all righty it is Friday once again
welcome to another magical mysterious
mysterious who the [ __ ] is this the
Magic School Bus
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
another Sunday
Friday video are you telling them it's
Sunday no dummy I'm telling you what day
the January 1st is because we're just
having a conversation about oh
then you don't get any of my twisters
oh that's crazy right here
you can say you got those pulled and
built
that was chaos anyways
we're telling each other our icks about
each other and I'm very excited
basically what this reminds me of the
video that Nick we talked about your
coming out story and we were just
rolling out those like little red
candies
we should go tomorrow and get them but I
love how we just make plans like that
correct you know like correct it's
awesome I hate it I think it's stupid I
think you're stupid I think you're an
idiot and speaking of thinking our plans
and everything wow what that transition
gave me chills to this video okay but
listen I'm gonna be super excited
because this means I'm finally gonna
start an argument I feel like an
argument you always start arguments
you're always what's different for you
the problem is you're wrong always I'm
excited to prove that wrong anyway wrong
I think Matt does that when he does one
word and just like thinks he's the boss
Listen Hold on hold on okay I'm the boss
I'm gonna make this a little like a
little I'm gonna make this a little
challenging
bet it hurt didn't it
didn't it type of kid didn't it hurt
I have a cavity for sure really that
hurts so bad to eat of course oh no more
all right should we take turns like
going around okay I want to start wow my
voice assistant I want to starve go
ahead
no my biggest dick is that Nick always
wants to start
you always have to be first I didn't
have to start you just lost you got
angry I didn't get angry calm actually
thank you
there's waves a river is no a lake
right now you're not anyway universe
proportion
just standing there waving it's yellow
thing like we don't need to see that
anyway Nick can go first oh my God I got
my biggest ear Nick say it say it I feel
like one of my bed Nick's not gonna want
this one in the video go
when Nick gets out of the shower and
walks around the house
they don't pull it up that high I guess
you do bro I actually everything and I'm
just like oh my God that's your own
fault because it's like I'm wearing I'm
casually wearing large underwear that
fits me well incorrect I just like to be
secure and that's your problem it's like
to hang loose and that's not my I do
like the Hang lows so whatever I just
think if you're gonna wanna if you want
to keep it tight then wear some pants
you know amen we don't want to know we
all don't want to keep it tight yeah
it's like you guys complain but it's not
like I I'm never the Casual sitting
around underwear wear wearer I always am
going straight to my room to put pants
on no no no no no the sight of my
traveling to my room to get clothes no
because sometimes you just stand there
and start different activities in your
underwear right not true yes I don't
spend more than five minutes in just
underwear
like 10 maybe like ever I don't know but
even when I'm like sleeping in your room
I'm just like wow like
I think you just need to invest in
better fitting underwear investing and
putting some pants on what this is this
one's actually not about either of you
well that's the point of the video well
shut the [ __ ] up okay I think my biggest
ick is the fact that people have turned
the word ick into pet peeve like these
are all just pet peeves this isn't like
an ick and ick is like a different thing
you know do you have any do you have any
like relevant things to say wow okay I
have one written down actually go ahead
let me go find it
okay oh my one of my biggest pet peeves
is when Chris is wrong like he knows
he's wrong he's a hundred percent wrong
he's been proven by fact he's been
proven by me and Matt he's been proven
by Google and then he goes and he will
still speak and create like an interview
no here we go he'll go
backing himself okay but like whatever
yeah and like nobody backs himself up
for like two minutes straight like this
is 100 the truth and he knows he's wrong
deep down he just wants to keep egging
on his false thing forever
okay like forever got me there okay next
one of my biggest pet peeve about Nick
see you're getting confused because
they're two separate things or my
biggest ache about Nick tell me icky
picky
I hate that I tell Nick on hate is a
strong word well I do okay wow I hate on
Thursday nights when I tell Nick hey you
should probably edit a YouTube video
considering it goes up tomorrow and he
goes I know we've been posting on
YouTube for two years I've never missed
a video don't tell me that our YouTube
videos need to go up and then I get
yelled at and then I go back into the
room two hours later and I go hey Nick
you edit the video yet and then he goes
oh thanks for reminding me I would have
forgot
that is true it's
like why
that one I'll accept yes you will my
biggest pet peeve calm down and I know I
know
get your license whatever but I hate
when I ask Matt for a simple ride down
the street and he like is like oh my God
like that's not even the worst part the
worst part is he also wants to go I'm
like hey Matt let's go to McDonald's
you want to know my biggest pet peeve
about you
you think I'm gonna just drop everything
to drive you places what plans do you
have what are you doing even if it's
just like you could be sound the [ __ ]
asleep no no cause you got you go we go
out to McDonald's
[Laughter]
what's echoing you [ __ ] huh what is it
coming from I don't know this is what
aggravates me the noise is true this is
what aggravates me about I hate how many
times I have to wake up Matt in the
morning get up get up I'm up I go
downstairs like no I please like this
like Matt are you getting up yeah go
back downstairs go up he's like on his
phone under the blanket like in complete
darkness it's like oh Matt get up he
goes look I'm up and like yells at me
and as if he's like not hiding the fact
that he's awake I feel like go under the
blanket and like brightness on zero like
texting away and I go what are you doing
get up Matt get up and I pull the blade
get down he's wide the [ __ ] awake he's
just not answering first of all I'm not
texting anyone
I'm playing Clash of Clans
the whole driving thing that pisses me
off when you go well you drive me crazy
and I go yeah sure Chris I'll drive you
to McDonald's right I drive you to
McDonald's we're on the way home these
are making me we're on the way home shut
up we're on the way home I passed I
passed the gas station and you go you go
when I'm when I'm right past the gas
station where you turn in to enter you
go oh I want to go to that gas station
too
and then I gotta turn around and pull
back in because you get all that
happened every single time all the [ __ ]
every single time oh who are you telling
me I'm telling who gives a [ __ ] because
I don't care every time I ask to go
somewhere else on right when you pass it
every time
yeah I got you Matt is when we when he
shuts the [ __ ] up in car videos he
doesn't speak and we leave the house and
then you're interrupting him and in
reality in real world Matt speaks the
most out of all of us yes once the
cameras are off this kid doesn't
well no Matt is just he'll never
understand the real me then you're oh my
god restart the camera
because this has to go with what he said
same with mine I don't give a [ __ ] I'm
going first listen listen the thing that
pisses me off the most about the whole
driving situation [ __ ] is when I'm in
the I'm in the parking lot this is not
the parking lot I'm in the driveway
right it wasn't what he was talking
about I'm in the driveway and we're
going somewhere new knock knock
what
who's there
Fuji apple Fiji Apple who Okay that was
PG Apple you
that's a good joke anyway I hate when
I'm in the driveway I'm in the driveway
and would you say you have a chip on
your shoulder
no oh I do
well I'm not rubbing your feet either
I hate when I'm sorry
I hate when I'm in the driveway and I
we're going somewhere new and I need the
directions to it right
and I go don't even say this because I'm
listening
okay listen man it's not like I don't
it's not like I have no idea on Earth
where this place is like I don't know
how to get there don't say it don't do
not say it I'm giving you a chance do
not say I'm gonna say it do not say it
man
Matthew Bernard two seconds don't you
speak of this you give me a second I
know I know how to get to like the
general vicinity of the area I want to
go so I go Chris I'm gonna start getting
us there put put the address in our in
in my phone for me put the address in my
phone for me while I'm not say it you
know the address you have it written
down somewhere or you know where we're
going I have it written down they make
one after a second written down nowhere
oh yeah I just got it written down I go
I go let's get it no no no in the car I
don't even know where the [ __ ] we're
going but I happen to have the
directions
oh I can't figure this out Matt you
should have [ __ ] done this in the
drive like it's not that [ __ ]
difficult listen to me one note I hate
what when Matt asked me for directions
because I'm have my phone plugged in
uh-huh I literally get in the car I'll
be like this I'll sit down and close my
door for reversing instantly like I need
a buckle I need a [ __ ] buckle up I
need to take my jacket off I need to
take my phone out cue if you oh wait
grab my drink
you know I'm in I'm moving all right wow
and then and then and then we don't even
know where we're going oh I'm kind of
hungry guys want to eat what do you guys
want to eat so we don't have a location
to where like a minute away from the
house oh let's go to let's go to Canes
let's go to Cabo let's go to Taco Bell
and I'm like okay I don't know where
we're going oh Taco Bell I put it in
it's like Taco Bell [ __ ] this Taco
Bell [ __ ] Taco Bell [ __ ] let's
talk about I'm like there's 80 different
Taco Bells I get yelled at if I put in
the directions wrong so I have to like
look and pick which one and for some
reason the first one that always pops up
on my waist is 397 000 miles away like
oh hey head to this one it's only in
[ __ ] guandon Canada I've never even
seen that place in my life why is that
the [ __ ] okay what really pisses me off
Chris blows my mind yeah hey come on
guys I don't know how to get there and
then we're like pulling out of the
[ __ ] you want to know what really
aggravates me with this whole driving
debacle nope when I get home I don't but
I guess I don't want to know I put the
car it parked I don't I put the car in
park I get out of the car I start
walking into the house and I have I want
to lock the car door so I'm standing
there waiting to lock the car door and
it takes Nick seven and a half years to
get his [ __ ] ass his [ __ ] left
hand his foot does it sound familiar
with you yeah
I have a receipt he that carries this in
me yep yep
[Music]
sunglasses
sunglasses on can somebody carry because
it's a [ __ ] 3D printer it's like
Jesus Christ and someone carry this one
for me you guys are always giving me
like the Nick don't forget the Vlog
camera bring the photography camera
bring the car video camera bring your
backpack bring your laptop you have to
do this you have to do that and I have
my backpack what's in the backpack all
of the [ __ ] [ __ ] for your job my
camera sidewalk camera the battery
chargers everything listen everything
that makes you Matt sterniolo that makes
your job your job get in my backpack
foreign
so there's less room here for me to get
out more bread out one two three four
five
hold on for you guys
hold on whenever we go anywhere it's
like it's like this oh we're getting
give me do this with an apple chip it
says thanks it's funny because it's
actually here already we've got pizza
and crystals like this where's the [ __ ]
did that okay Chris has pizza
you have pizza at the front seat I have
my backpack I have my camera out I have
my phone and I have like a drink right
imagine the pizza and the first thing he
does is next Nick take that now fine
take this and he throws the pizza back
so then I have the pizza I just said
when we get out every single time we go
to a food place you give me everything
Matt brings his backpack grabs nothing
out of it all [ __ ] day he brings like
a prop and he gets in the driver's seat
and I'm putting my bag down and he goes
like this
takes it and goes Nick hold my bag and
hums it to the back so then I have his
bag my bag a drink
I can't drive and home when we get home
is an extra 30 seconds that's all I need
to grab my thing dude how about [ __ ]
let me lock the door instead of you that
would be [ __ ] wonderful so we'll
start doing that problem solved thank
you well no another one of my biggest
pet peeves oh God when Max when when
Matt when me and you say anything to
Matt during a car video or a vlog and he
goes okay all right says it all cute and
knows that the the fans of Matt will be
like oh yes you do he added like a
little he acts like a baby so that
people will be like poor man Matt
doesn't feel good I'm so nervous Nick's
being mean when in reality the [ __ ] that
Matt says that's mean to me I don't even
feel comfortable putting in the video
because he's like oh you're [ __ ]
crazy in lunatic
Matt's so rude to Nick if I attempt what
Matt said to me and really keep it in
Nick
so okay
I also don't pout like a little [ __ ]
baby like you because then you have to
see someone says something to you
someone says something to you not true
and someone says oh there's more macros
than it girls put a poll well because
they know I don't they know I won't like
them put a pool I won't like them back
they think you like them back because
you're a straight man I can't like them
back so that you already have the
[ __ ] do you guys Matt and Chris girls
are more populated than Nick girls
because I'm a gay man so guess what huh
guess what oh
if there's more mac girls if there's
more mac girls the biggest pet peeve
do you want them are those JoJo siwa
glasses I don't know bro all right can
we keep going give me some more pet
peeves when Nick does that when no quick
oh my God my biggest pet peeve is Matt
farting oh I was gonna say this
oh my God your farts smell like [ __ ]
glasses so bad
[ __ ] trim your toenails crimp your
toenails trim your toenails trim your
toenails cut up onions
put all three of those things in a
bucket let it sit there for a week get
milk pour it on top let it expire heat
it up for 30 seconds and sniff that and
that is the equivalent to Matt's Farm
yeah and he does it five times a day I
heard that place has really good rice
and chicken we should go there with it
okay
is when he asks you how to do simple
tasks just because he feels like [ __ ]
asking he'll he asks the simplest
questions ever he could be ordering
something in the mail and it could say
five to eight business days he's like
Nick is this our address do you think
I'll get this by this day it's like
Google it yeah he asks [ __ ]
what's my phone number I ask Alexa Siri
Google the question he asks me or I
[ __ ] remember hey he asked questions
how do I plug things into my GPS
when Nick goes like this he goes oh hey
Nick since you have hey Nick I ever
agree hey Nick
give me a second I hate when I go up to
Nick and I go hey Nick since you have
the the Wi-Fi password the Netflix
password the Hulu password every
password ever and I say can you log me
into Netflix and he goes yeah sure logs
me to Netflix on my TV right and then I
go Nick can you log me into Netflix on
my laptop and he goes log your [ __ ]
selfie out and he doesn't say the
passwords to me or give them to me he
just types them in and expects me to
remember them when I have to go log in
again
when I figure out the [ __ ] Netflix
password because he's trying to log in
then I put the effort into yours I go
Matt tells me he says oh Nick I don't
know the Netflix password my way to
reach out to Netflix I reset the
password I make a new password I send it
to Matt the next week he's asking the
Netflix password again or I someone's
trying to log into Netflix we don't know
the password I figure it out I tell
everyone we're all a part of this
conversation and I have the [ __ ]
bright idea oh someone might want to log
into this Netflix so I save it in my
notes do you wanna know what Matt does
forget until he needs it again so it's
sitting in my notes that I know when I
want to login gentle reminder I'll be
able to he doesn't write [ __ ] down for
himself
oh God
my password's created and he doesn't
remember I hate when I can't even get
through a doorway or a stairwell because
Nick won't get the [ __ ] out of my way he
happens to always be standing in my way
more like doesn't realize he's in the
way like he'll be in the doorway and
I'll obviously be trying to pass him for
like five seconds which in a doorway
interaction shouldn't be a problem and I
end up standing at that doorway
I remember vividly the other day I had
something in my hands and something in
my mouth because I was carrying a ton of
[ __ ] and I'm like biting on something
like this and I'm like trying to get in
the doorway and I can't even speak to be
like get the [ __ ] out of my way and he's
like this like in the doorway taking up
the whole I'm just broken I'm just
crooked hey can you move and then he
bumps into me as if he couldn't have
like got out of this I can't walk
normally it's crazy I have no balance
I've lost balance I have no control over
when my body I don't get it I don't get
how you don't realize it directly Chris
Chris is on the phone so instead of
Chris instead of Chris telling me Oh
Nick walk out of the room like we're
gonna go downstairs I'm in his room with
him he goes like this he goes Nick
Taps me and immediately 360s and is out
the [ __ ] I know I don't know what to
do guess what I would know I was on the
phone so I was talking to someone so I
couldn't speak how about that I'm on the
phone hey I'm on the phone and I go Nick
never happened he doesn't look at me
right away he's not on his phone like
this so I tap him tap him again he's not
looking so I just walked out and I
looked back at him because I knew he'd
eventually look at me as I'm exiting and
as I'm exiting once I got to the door I
go let's go you didn't do that out of my
fingers
can replay [ __ ] I know I did
that [ __ ] yeah
when we get
online
and I go Nick Nick on the phone the
whole time I go Nick okay [ __ ] it I walk
no he's talking to my dad
look back and he looks at me and I go
dude let's go
and then I just kept going on guess
where he was right behind me when I left
right
I want to show Nick something on my
phone I go like this I go hey Nick look
at this he goes hold on one second I go
okay
oh yeah what was that
it's gone I just want to punch him right
in the face correct okay
correct wow I feel like I didn't get a
lot against me today yeah you're awesome
I hit awesome Chris's
with Chris my whole entire life quite
clearly I know that Chris loves his
[ __ ] Pepsi Cola I got that down
I hate when I open the fridge I got
Sprite Dr Pepper Pepsi water Gatorade
lemonade
[ __ ] orange soda root beer I got
eight drinks in the fridge he goes more
than eight whatever there's like about
it
Matt grab me some drink
I go okay what do you want and then he
goes obviously I want a [ __ ] Pepsi I
bet you I bet you if there was a fridge
full of [ __ ] minute Mead lemonade
[ __ ] water and a Pepsi and I asked
nine out of 10 viewers would know what
to grab me if I said can you get me a
drink sometimes they don't the viewers
don't know sometimes you might be in the
mood for a [ __ ] good cup of lemonade
Dr Pepper water those are awesome do you
remember it is did you just say water's
in my top three well no you drink water
when was the last time I had a water
regardless I don't think I've had a
problem
oh I'm really craving lemonade that's
because I didn't have Pepsi I ran out
okay that wasn't acne it was in our
living room and I knew we didn't have
Pepsi so I said I pray to [ __ ] God
there's lemonade in the fridge and I
went and there wasn't you're a dirty
liar no it wasn't oh my God it was in
our [ __ ] home you just wanted
lemonade you didn't say you wanted my
man because there was no Pepsi I knew in
my head I didn't say out loud
a much of a Pepsi addicts that you know
what other drinks you want to substitute
before water with Pepsi the Pepsi you
are bizarre you are you got pepper
that is foul Chris let's wait till
you're done trying to tell them what
happened Chris the fact that you have a
backup
backup when you ride
a thing
it's embarrassing you're of course
you're making backup plans for about not
making backups yes you are plans aren't
made you grabbed the last a pen to be
made
you grabbed the last Pepsi and the whole
time you're [ __ ] drinking it you were
like damn after this one I have to
resort to Lemonade because there's only
that and water in them
here this [ __ ] [ __ ] I've ever heard
let him go prior to having the last
Pepsi I I did not think oh boy if I'm
done with this I'm gonna have to have
lemonade
I grabbed the Pepsi from the fridge and
I said oh man I'm all out so I went to
the little man I'm All Out went to the
living room oh jeepers creepers oh
brother chimney Christmas sure is going
to be the last Pepsi I indulge on for
quite some time due to the fact that I'm
All Out
went to the living room and drank it and
threw it away hours later hours let's do
it if you once I got thirsty again I
said oh I definitely want something to
drink right now don't want water no oh I
hope we have lemonade I audibly said the
way you're talking I don't I hear you
want to know what else is hold on let me
break the situation in our home when Mom
comes home with a case of 12 Pepsi I
look at it I go that looks like four
Pepsi's with my name written on it four
eight twelve I go that looks I go to
grab my a second Pepsi you're a fool for
thinking four I go why go why is there
only two Pepsi's left nickos I had one I
had said that leaves nine for you
and what wow give let them live and sit
for 48 [ __ ] hours how am I supposed
to start my day without a cold Pepsi
Cola okay you're weird so I I start my
day I go downstairs I grab like a baby
I get I'm done with it I'm about to go
out the house for the day I'm like I'm
gonna want a Pepsi on this travel of
today the big Pepsi's Pepsi YouTube
video Pepsi Instagram Tick Tock Pepsi
music song like that's that's how
nothing yep