First into the tank is Nikki Pope with a
money-saving idea to help parents
entertain their kids.
I'm Nikki Pope. I live in Los Angeles,
California, and my company is Toy Guru.
Look what I have.
Yay.
I have 13 nieces and nephews, and they
absolutely love playing with toys. I
call them my playtime professionals. The
problem is they get bored with those
toys really quickly. That is what
inspired me and my husband to create Toy
Guru. Toy Guru offers a coste effective
way not only for parents to declutter
their homes, but to keep their kids
challenged and entertained. My husband
and I don't have any kids yet, but we
would definitely like to. And an
investment from the Sharks would mean
that we would have the stability we need
to start a family of our own. My dream
for my company is that every family who
has children who love to play with toys
will use Toy Guru. And I really hope the
sharks will help make that happen.
[Music]
Hi guys, my name is Nikki. My company is
Toy Guru and I am asking for $100,000 in
exchange for 10% of my company. Toy Guru
solves a problem that millions of
families face every day. I have 11
brothers and sisters and I am lucky
enough to have 13 outstanding nieces and
nephews, all under the age of eight. One
thing that I've noticed is that my
siblings are purchasing toy after toy
for their kids. Their playrooms, their
living rooms, their bedrooms are
cluttered with toys that were purchased,
played with for a few weeks, and now are
left completely untouched. Toy Guru
solves that problem and more. My company
is the Netflix for toys. Consumers can
go to my website, pick a plan that's
right for them, fill their wish list
with toys that they would like to
receive, and I ship those toys right to
their door. The great thing about my
company is when their kids get bored
with or outgrow those toys, they just
throw them in the box, use the return
label that we provided, send them back
to us, and we send them their next box
of toys.
Can I just see your snail? I just want
to see what the quality is like.
Absolutely.
And how many toys are in your catalog?
We have over 300 different types of
toys. What is the servicing of it? You
know, the toys come back. Obviously,
kids are not the cleanest. So, you got
drool on the toys. You have bed bugs.
Would they have pee and poo on the toys?
Maybe. There has to be a process. People
have to be hired to do this
with our company. Uh the cleaning is the
most important. And so, the the toy gets
sanitized.
Shrink wrap it
and we shrink wrap it every time.
Who else is doing this, Nikki?
There is not another company that is
doing this.
So, Nikki, what about the damage?
In 6 months, we had zero toys that we
had to to completely replace. If a child
does break the toy, we sell it to the
member at a discounted cost.
Nikki, walk us through your business
model. How do you make money?
All of our members obviously pay a
monthly membership fee. We have plans
that start at $35 a month and they go
all the way up to $89 a month.
That's a lot.
35 a month,
right?
And how many families pay you that? Um,
we did a soft launch with 500 members.
It was basically like a test launch.
They were all paying $42 a month for a
box of toys that's worth over $200.
You're saying basically it cost them
about $500 a year.
Exactly. Which is great because the
average family spends anywhere between
12 and $1,400 a year.
And tell me again the cost per toy box
that you ship was $200, did you say? And
what's your cost on the toys that you're
shipping? On the box of toys, it's going
to be anywhere between 50 to $8590.
Two and a half months, you break even on
each customer.
That's exactly right.
Nikki, how do you scale it up? How do
you make this a big business?
All we need is more marketing, more
exposure. In the small amount of time
that we had our 500 customers, just by
word of mouth, we got a waiting list of
over a thousand people ready to sell.
Vicki, I think that's a great idea. Let
me ask you this. If the business begins
to grow, does it suck up a ton of cash?
Nikki, for every million dollars of
sales, how much do I have to put in to
buy inventory of toys?
Just in toys.
Just in toys. $64,000. That's going to
cover a year of toys.
Okay, Nikki, I've heard enough.
The problem is you don't have a million
dollar business yet. You're asking me to
pay you as if your business is worth a
million, and it's not.
But I want to be an investor in it.
You have a good idea. This is
interesting.
So,
this is a leap of faith for me because I
have to think you're going to grow this
thing. Do you have any partners? You're
doing this on your own?
Um, my husband is a partner and then I
have um web designers and two online
marketers that are partnering with me.
How much do you own?
I own 10% of the company.
You own 10%.
Who owns the rest? Where's the other 90?
We all own 10% and my husband owns the
the bigger chunk of
which is how much?
He owns 50%.
Why does your husband own a bigger
chunk?
Um because I that's how we decided.
How happily married are you?
Um incredibly happily married.
Why would you who came up with this idea
give so much to your partner? Why?
Um he's worked with me and blood, sweat,
and tears with me every day.
Do you have a prenuptual agreement?
No, we don't.
Oh,
we were half and half when we started.
Okay. and you sold your piece to all
these others and you didn't take any
from him.
The way that we worked the company is we
wanted to make sure our family as a
whole had the the majority share. Okay.
But to Kevin's point then why didn't you
each give away some of your shares?
Um I don't know.
Um I've had a bad history of speaking to
people who don't have controlling of the
company.
I'm out.
Nikki, you know, I I wish you owned
more, but nevertheless, I'd like to make
you an offer here.
I'll give you $100,000 for 35%.
Rarely, Nikki, do I not ask for control
because I'm a control freak. But I trust
you. You know what you're doing. I can
help you immensely in the toy space.
Immensely.
Do you have the right to sell 35%,
Nikki?
Um, I have the right to do whatever I
want with the company. Yes.
I had my eye on you when I came in here.
I have my eye on you,
Nikki. You are the first person ever to
walk into the Shark Tank and actually be
attracted to him.
You know what? He's got a tough
exterior, but I'm a southern girl and I
knew I could get in.
She's right.
He's blushing. He is blushing.
He really is.
Nikki, I've made you an offer. What are
you going to do?
Nikki, just just before you you answer
that,
Mark, I see this as an internet uh
logistics play. Would you be interested?
I'd like to get in on this one with you.
Would you be interested in putting up
more money?
Absolutely.
Because I think really this key issue
for me, it's a website, social media.
I'm in that world. But I think you got
to go faster than you're suggesting.
I agree 100%.
So Kevin's offering 100 for 35. I'm
thinking we raise more money.
What do you have in mind?
I was thinking 200 or 250 for maybe 35
or 40. I' I'd split 200 for 40. Okay.
Well, you just knocked me out. I was
going to offer a lot less.
I'm out.
Two sharks are out. Nikki has an offer
from Kevin for $100,000 for 35% of her
company and another from Robert and Mark
for $200,000 for 40%.
I want you to know something about me. I
am Mr. Toy. I sold my company to Mattel.
I know it.
I lived in Fisher Price for a year.
Those toys are my friends. I speak toy.
I just think you need more capital.
You got to get going faster. That's
going to be your only advantage. And you
need someone with internet hyperrowth
experience.
Okay?
It wouldn't hurt to start partnering
with some of the toy companies, let me
tell you. And there's two that own 90%
and I know all their board members. Mark
and I are offering you 200,000
for 40%.
Okay.
Mr. Olirri is offering you 100,000 for
35%.
What are you going to do?
Where are you at relationship wise with
Fisher Price and Mattel?
They're never going to forget me. Put it
to you that way.
Are you holding at your 100,000 for 35?
I'm thinking I'm thinking.
Um I don't know if you'd be willing to
go up anymore on your number without
moving that percentage. Um
what's I compete with myself? What do
you want?
She wants you to bid against yourself.
Nikki, I don't think the relationship
with the toy companies
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. You don't think that matters?
No, no, no. Hang on a sec. I never said
it didn't matter. It's not critical to
get going.
And somebody who's been through an
online service,
okay,
that's built around subscriptions,
someone who does business with Netflix
and knows how they work and other online
services. Okay,
that is what's going to get you over the
top. We can get the door opening to
Fisher Price or any toy company.
Once we have the customers, I mean, my
company secures and services some of the
largest internet sites in the world.
Once we have the customers, trust me,
there's no problem going to Mattel.
These
companies, there's so many guys that
provide internet logistics services.
There's a whole industry full of guys
like this. Dime a dozen.
I think I know exactly how to build this
business and exactly how to exit it,
which matters to you. That's how you
actually make money.
I like $200,000. Um I I was going to ask
you guys if you'd consider 35% for
$200,000.
Are you saying if I match their offer,
he'll do the deal with me?
Done.
How about this? I like what this guy
brings, so I'll split it with him.
I'll do that.
We have a deal.
Done.
Wow, you're out, Nicole.
Robert, cut you out. Robert, I'm so
sorry.
I'm very excited. This is a great idea.
Thank you so much.
I love it. Robert, you were the toy they
were playing with for a little while and
she sent you back.
New found respect. You broke up with
your potential partner without even
looking at him.
Give me someone that.
You know what happened.
And you join with the devil.
You're a savage. You got the steal of a
lifetime.
Why did she like him? I've never seen
anyone like him.
One of those mysteries of life,
man. What it means for Toy Guru to be in
business with Kevin and Mark is just uh
it's the perfect connections. I had my
eye on Kevin when I walked in there. Um
I'm thrilled. I'm so thrilled. It's
going to be great.