are we in we're in
I don't have any shoes yes new Berks for
tour
s
speaking of tour if you guys don't know
take the camera and record me if you
guys don't know we're about to go on a
magnificent tour of the United States of
America 14 cities near you
I would say go buy tickets but every
Show's already sold out hey
hey guys thank you we're very excited
and eager to meet you guys we're gonna
do challenges and stuff on tour and you
might happen to see them today in this
video
oh well well well
if it isn't Mr team blue Mr loser
this kid sent to me the other day
he's packing his packing his [ __ ]
clothes and he goes oh Matt should I
bring these blue jeans on tour
is he gonna accidentally pack his orange
hat no but am I gonna accidentally maybe
pack a blue pair of jeans
I'm gonna win this sword I'm gonna win
this I've been standing by myself but
going to bed at night I've been eating
dinner oh it's so dark oh my God you
look so ominous huh
this kid's funny you're a nerd like
why'd you laugh like that good morning
what happened a good old-fashioned good
morning good morning Nick I actually
have a plan oh and that's a secret plan
I actually want to ask this let's go
thank you
[Music]
I'll tell you guys about it later
there's a to-do list on that wall please
take it off so I can Vlog in that
direction thank you take it off the wall
yeah I don't want to expose our to-do
next team blue today
okay go change all right I already
showed his true color cut the camera
taking poopy get out of here
I'm feeling I'm feeling Juiced up right
now I'm ready to rumble I was gonna say
something but I just got so off guard
and you yelling look at the wall at
warehouse 79 this should get in complete
man shout out to the wall
term [ __ ] Jew stuff I'm feeling
Juiced up you had a problem with it
Eeyore ladder subjective objective
uh I had this Bee from that tattoo video
that we did if you didn't see that
tattoo video you should probably go
watch it's with some of my closest
friends I love those guys so I got this
bee here to fill a gap oh it looks so
good and then that'd be there looks
really good fill in the gaps filling in
the gaps Nick you want to show them or
no no oh yeah gotta love this View for
the Vlog wait
just figure out what mine are and try
and use your critical thinking skills
get out of here
oh there it is
what you comments this is what you fight
for you sound like Jeff Probst this is
what your tribe wants for a more trophy
this is what the winner thing show the
thing wow the hold on let me let it
Focus
the verses tour 2023
our tour is gonna work we're gonna play
a bunch of games that we're gonna play
right now on
door each have a teammate and every
single time someone wins those games
once someone leaves the venue with the
most points they'll be leaving with this
medal we have 14 shows so 14 of these
will be given out and then whoever has
the most amount of medals when we hit
Florida our last show will win the big
trophy first possible game that's gonna
be played during tour vloggy Vlogs
sternula triplet stop like you don't
announcement
um
use their mouth first possible game that
can be played during tour balloon blast
let's do it sadly all of our [ __ ]
balloons are popped so and we don't have
any of them with the balloons for the
balloon blast we'll be more prepared for
tour
next possible game basketball all right
one of those like homeless things like
the bindle but Chris has got the net
over there normally it's going to be
attached to like an actual shot well I
can't I'm holding the [ __ ] oh wow
oh don't break the TV yep and the trophy
awesome great already break it there's
no way
broke oh my God it's fine we're good put
it to the side so let's reverse toward
trophy on the [ __ ] second basketball
shot ever I would have literally how
many free throws are we taking each with
our family or something
us and our teammate are gonna all play
basketball
oh God he's money right now
and essentially We're not gonna hold the
hoop that's crazy but
basketball game number two
he's mad because team are he's gonna win
Chris has begged everyone we know and
love to wear our just like it's quality
over quantity I want every team purple
member to want to be team purple I'm not
begging anybody they're just team orange
that's all
bet you can't do that Chris girls are
gonna love this
okay next all right next one relay race
what balloon oh you're strong you're
blue you're so strong look at him Matt
13 blue wow this is
my face like this balloon color I feel
like no you see it right is this a
sausages
Nick I'm gonna kill both of you fox what
is up with the color of this balloon
earlier the first one we're gonna do is
balloon blast we told you that before
the basketball game but now we have
balloons so we're gonna do a balloon
blast one now after the basketball get
off me first of all um yeah get it off
the table it's a game we're playing on
tour obviously we're gonna be playing it
a little bit differently right now the
rules are gonna be different during tour
but we're gonna race to each pop one
balloon this is the pump this thing is
where the balloon grows and then pops
ready
set
go
oh my God
[Music]
I think these ones are stronger
oh God okay these balloons aren't the
right ones so I'm pretty sure the clear
ones are stronger I agree
but that's one once again this game's
gonna be played differently than it is
on tour but right now you have to get
this green cup from the bottom all the
way through the cups back to the bottom
and then empty this tissue box with
tissues once again it's gonna be played
differently on tour but that's what
we're doing for the challenge right now
it's gonna be very similar Ready set go
oh [ __ ] oh my God oh my God [ __ ]
Nick you're a [ __ ] loser
purple team socks more than one by
accident everything's the worst blue
team sucks even more
our team's going wow
[ __ ] holy [ __ ] oh oh my God we're
getting stuck dude what the [ __ ] oh my
God oh my God
hope y'all
done no way
Nick that's insane
team purple guy
pink purple get [ __ ] you're not
getting one at a time I'm done
wow you suck Matt
you're insane what
he said purple team get [ __ ]
insane actually I'm so impressed how did
your cups not get whoa team purple gets
[ __ ]
all right dude not no balcony idiot that
doesn't show you what team to root for I
don't know what does all right you guys
next up is giant Jenga no need to
explain
it's already team orange once again
gonna be slightly different than on tour
because you know this is just a little
preview but this game is not going to be
worth any points on tour instead it is
going to be minus points and that's all
I'll say for now we're gonna play Big
Jenga and on tour we're gonna have a
limited amount of time that you can take
to pull your Jenga block so don't get it
twisted
oh I'm not getting a twisted one bit
you're insane who you how
you're going for like
whoa whoa [ __ ]
let's go the other side [ __ ] it
there we go I'd like to see that Nick
that came out like Nick and [ __ ]
sophomore year vamanos
Matt's playing with his life right now
oh my God Nick
how did that bill
oh
you can take out any block oh
Nick just almost shattered a glass door
that was any High
[Applause]
ER
once you [ __ ] loser let's go perp
let's go bro
we're like celebrating
foreign
so basically overall that's going to be
our versus tour with a little bit of
rule changes depending
the whole thing and we're keeping a
couple games a secret surprise for you
guys to stay tuned on the internet for
yeah I'm excited bro I'm gonna win this
whole thing so if I don't win I'm never
editing a YouTube video again shut the
[ __ ] and I don't like to think of this
tour as a
um performance I like to think of it as
a YouTube video big giant um
no I had a word for it well it's also a
get together it's a big giant get
together it's like when people like you
know people want to pay to see people
compete because it's like people go to
sports games correct but at the end of
the day it's not even for y'all to just
come and meet us and see us at the end
of the day it's for y'all at the time
have a good time and meet each other
there's nothing more fun than hanging
out with people with common interests so
I think that and if you guys are gonna
see me whip their ass live
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things