I love my [ __ ] I love you Chrissy yeah
I sound like a woman I love Chris thank
you oh
okay that's enough I love matching oh
yeah
[Music]
you're a good boy I'm a good boy
oh she didn't say anything for Nick
I know what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
I just had a match against myself
guess who won the other guy
oh my God
[Music]
the beach towel is pretty crazy for a
[ __ ] mountain in the woods yeah like
but he's gonna go swimming the lake and
have a couple leeches on his back end
out of there what's that movie with the
leeches mom
great movie they love it oh my God that
would have a leech on me that'd be
pretty if I ever have a leech on me I'm
gonna have to be like fully sedated into
it yeah because they suck the blood out
oh my God you guys notice on leeches by
Melanie Martinez it's really good
look at the stomach on this guy dude
look at the [ __ ] shedding on this
character yeah it's crazy yeah I can
check where the wind's going oh I forgot
Chris you're gonna think I'm insane why
I had a red hoodie on and I didn't like
Dorian look
go shopping in a completely completely
the color
so I traced the whole thing and now we
can decide which one we wanted to be if
you couldn't tell already by the start
of this Vlog wearing the damn heels and
I ain't trying the Beverly Hills we're
in the [ __ ] mountain tops
Nick tell him about it
you just told them
stop crying give them some valuable
information Trevor's crying because
Trevor's crying because we're with our
parents and they're grocery shopping
right now so he's just devastated that
they're not sitting with him he'll be
fine
but yeah cries in the car went he cries
anytime that my mom's not in the room
like we decided like with our parents
like we don't do much when we're back in
Boston so we're like hey we need to
start getting out of the house you damn
whistle shut the [ __ ] up
don't talk to him like that so this
whole time what did you call him a
whistle yeah this whole time that we're
back we're going to
different places that aren't our home we
want to just spend time with our
beautiful family and Nathan while we're
here because his birthday is the ninth
oh he's so cute cutie pie
oh my God bro [ __ ] just did the man
challenge
dude is he Frozen in Time like he sees
dad or so you trap
happy birthday to you you got anything
to say mister
I ain't got one damn thing don't hide
the eyebrows with the hat it looks
better when it's like a little bit above
I didn't think I was hiding you're
hiding don't hide show your true natural
self dude stop being a weirdo I'm not
being
why is there 400 [ __ ] million of
these Pokemon what
what is this oh my God it's got to be a
community day it absolutely is let's
catch them what the [ __ ]
why are you looking outside for him no I
was looking at this
oh this is gonna do the magic for me
Matt is a little Pokemon okay guys look
Justin also plays Pokemon go and he has
one of these and he's telling me about
it and apparently it can catch the
Pokemon for me while I drive so I don't
get into a car accident
and my mom got it for me for my birthday
and Justin told her which one to get so
now I have it and now look I just
connected it it's gonna catch every
single one of the ones here
stinky little [ __ ] fart what honey
I don't know any producer you know how
like at the beginning what about like
Metro booming you know how like the
beginning of songs like rap songs and
stuff there's always like that little
message at the start message like um
there's like a little saying like that
DJ Kylie yes
I like him I like the way they shout out
for him and every song
oh he just yells his own name yeah
you don't like Metro Boomin
Metro Boomer make it boom okay I haven't
heard much young natural don't trust you
he's gonna shoot you oh then I like
Metro the best
I have a big tripod I don't care
Matt tell them about Pikachu
what do you mean
how much how many things could you tell
us about Pikachu and it also attracts
sleep
but you gotta set it to track sleep
is his voice copyright I don't know I
hope not well you sing it Twinkle
Twinkle Little Star that's beautiful
shout out to people
eight seconds if that was on in my bed
all right we're playing poker I got the
biggest [ __ ] because you think some
amount of chips ever right here first to
go so I got one big chip and I'm first
to go apparently Justin's looking good
over there Matt's got a good nice stack
I have all of Chris's over here I'm
feeling confident yeah all right
here they are that's nice cards
I don't even know how to play poker so
they don't care but I figure it out
because you're first all right Matt
let's see if you wanna oh sweeter
sweetheart let's do three oh [ __ ] you
okay
I can call three all right so Chris can
win four total that's that's huge
Premiere more than one Chris so if
you're you're getting back in it that's
what you can I'm winning this handling
seven five and eight what are you gonna
do man five oh wow five chips
holy [ __ ] it's looking active over here
five chips as well that's frightening
for me over here he's gonna match it
regardless of his stance yeah I have
trips to spare I beat Chris of it out of
the [ __ ] games
tennis Spades
who's it on uh you
Matt checked it on checking it on I'm
also doing the same wow someone got a 10
here they are in luck
Jesus Christ
nine I hate this song God and that's
gonna take me out it is well
what did you have oh
filthy yeah
oh brother
fans definitely don't know how this game
works but some of them definitely do
just know that Chris is [ __ ] bad at
it
Matthew Pepsi all right so nowhere guys
upstairs
it's genuinely fried oh you remembered
my drink otherwise it's frightening how
few Pepsi's are left already and Chris
are gonna have a little billiard battle
you want
good okay wait we should do like
matching trick shots like Dude Perfect
like okay I'm hitting it against that
wall hit this wall and then back against
that wall you just have to get it at
three that's not a trick shot but go for
it no it has the end on this side though
so it has to go there here there and
then back like past this stuff
that's really hard to you it's really
difficult okay go weak saw don't break
the glass
okay
see it's like impossible oh I got this
here I didn't even touch that wall like
hardly I touched that wall like actually
the challenge just hit that wall
Jay you're cheating by having it way
over there where'd you stop I [ __ ]
started yeah my pants are falling I
started right there shut up
I'm all for being like humble about our
Fame and success and what
you know saving our money and all that
type of stuff but you can retire the
five-year-old anchor pants pajamas
I was gonna say something about them too
yeah
they smell in the laundry
is just not true these pajamas keep me
grounded
oh wow Nick oh wow dude that was
actually really impressive thank you all
right
oh 7K egg live ladies and gentlemen
kids hat oh shit's ass
I said I'm back in my zone okay here do
you know who that is yes wow great work
do you know what his full name is
I'll give you my old Cuddy I don't know
what dude like stupid Justin do you know
Kid Cudi's full name
Matt knows his first name
Scott Scott yeah that's why Travis Scott
is Travis Scott his real name is
because he was a big Kid Cudi fan so he
puts share some solutions
um Travis Scott or no
um Kid Cudi Chris Kid Cudi is Scott Miss
Scotty
wouldn't you believe it because his last
name or his rap name is Kid Cudi so it's
Scott miscotti how hard is that I think
that's [ __ ] sick
he said he wanted Cuddy in it for sure
or like some version of his name
come on billiard battle let's do it
all hey Pokemon shut the [ __ ] up
this wall this wall into that hole holy
[ __ ] you're never
from you is stinky and editing
be it you [ __ ] lousy [ __ ] wow dude
oh just shy there you go take
wow missed the [ __ ] whole wall over
there
someone's atrocious
[Music]
all right y'all
because we have to dedicate a full day
of the week that we normally dedicate to
the filming to traveling and [ __ ] and we
put out three videos a week who else was
doing this I don't know anyone who's
doing this other than Jake Paul back in
the day when he said it was every day
bro now we're every other day bro
wow we really are like every other day
bro yeah we do post a lot but with that
being said that has been this week's
Wednesday video Friday videos coming
soon we're back with the fan for a
little bit podcasting
[Music]
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah