what do you got to say I think my
biggest pep peeve is when people give
fictional characters like in TVs and
movies like
nicknames like when they're talking
about them like they're referring to
them as like like they know them in real
life you know what I'm saying not a
[ __ ] clue give me and what you saying
how you miss me yeah you miss me and all
the things that we did we going to
travel from the is MRI we had a lot of
plans but they
all why oh because of some kid but it's
okay I'm moving different don't be
saying nothing when I'm with [ __ ] my
brother Auto Parts bow okay I have a
question yeah do you ever get like you
ever like think what the [ __ ] that's
why do you know want know what I said at
the very beginning of this video what I
said your burger tastes like onions I
said it smells like that too they put a
[ __ ] onion ring in my French fries
and it's a mystery and like I'm like
eating like all these fries and they all
taste like onions I'm like what's going
on and get to the bottom of it literally
I got to the bottom of it and it was an
onion ring oh my god get rid of it like
you're waving it around and I think
you're going to die I was about to throw
it outside but now that makes me want to
keep it in here for a little bit
longer it's not that Chris that was just
unnecessary
Nick now you got hit with an onion ring
you stupid
kid I don't even want these fries
anymore no they're even remotely close
Ry Auto Parts bow
I'm really angry at you shut the [ __ ] up
that just upset me yeah I don't care you
upset me by saying get rid of it as I'm
like about to roll down the
window just I knew that no one gave a
[ __ ] not one Soul gave a [ __ ] that you
got an onion ring no one gave a [ __ ] so
I was like get rid of it maybe cuz
nobody cared about you nobody cares
about you and not wanting to smell them
I didn't think people cared about you
thought people cared about you people do
give a [ __ ] no one cares I bet you I'll
see a million edits about why people now
you will now you
will nope I bet Noe I'm not allowing
that okay learn how to listen no learn
to listen say it calmly okay I bet you
there are more people that care about my
fries having an onion ring than you not
wanting that onion ring in the car now
they will and now they'll go back and
talk about it what do you think people
care about more me having an onion ring
in my fries or him not wanting they were
both forgettable experiences they were
both forgettable I'm not saying that me
saying I my fries is far far more
rememberable then not
true why eling on I'm not helping out
anyone cuz you why would stup people
don't care about your you're arguing
like I think people give a [ __ ] that I
smell it I don't I don't think people
care that I smelled the onion ring I'm
arguing that from one it's
one-sided I don't think people care
about my onion ring and the fries but
you were talking about it and I said get
rid of it and then you're like you're
just you wouldn't stop you're like
holding on to it naming it dressing
it's fine it's an onion ring why you go
why don't you go outside I just didn't
care you go outside your [ __ ] onion
rings out there go get them my God you
didn't take his clothes off he's
probably lonely and take a walk I'm good
I'm surpris you eat I'm good yeah I'm
leaving that in I just got body sham by
CH fat no I'm not I'm just surprising
yes you you just body shame me keep in
it has nothing to do with your size I
just know you're big
appe
okay do you ever feel like you just get
you're so stupid you guys are so stupid
shut the [ __ ] up I did okay I did no one
cares Don't Give A F he literally asked
me a question why don't you put that
pinky down before you keep pointing it
at me why just the pinky I felt like it
was a lot closer to me than all your
other fingers Matt get the [ __ ] off me
tickling your get off me get away dude
you're so strange what I was going to
say is you guys ever feel like you just
get way too close to like the the the
truth and the government's going to stop
you like sometimes I'm just talking and
talking I'm thinking and like even if
I'm alone I'm just thinking about it
like like I'm getting real close to
unveiling some crazy things that I know
the government's trying to surpress and
one day I won't be surprised if they
come stop me really you think the
government's watching you that much well
just I don't think they're watching I
think the Govern has a list of 10 people
that scare them and Nicks on it I agree
like they're just the 10 people are just
getting way too awfully close to the TR
so give us give us some of the things
you're really close on well I just think
about all like the different people you
see every single day and the amount of
like different like routines like you
have to think when you go to like the
grocery store right you could bump into
like a high amount of like 90 100 people
in the grocery store right and it's just
like all those people are there with a
separate goal and Mission and every
single person has their own drive and
their own like end goal for what they're
shopping for they could there could be a
full Breakout of anger and people
dueling and fighting there could be an
FBI spy lurking through the shelves to
try and get to an end goal what I'm
saying is like I don't think I'm
necessarily close to unveiling or
uncovering something I just think some
people are and I'm like I'm fearful for
them because like I saw these two guys
the reason I brought this up that I have
a podcast and they were talking about
just like some crazy thing that this guy
thought he found Bigfoot like for sure
like for real and then he was dead like
I think he that die after coming close
contact to things like that's just a
thing that I if you like die on us
should I like check what you've been
working on to see if it was the Govern I
feel like if they take away whatever
he's been think oh God but what I'm
thinking of you have to give us like a
folder with like a password no I'll find
a way but what I'm thinking of
is just the amount like I think
something underrated we do as like
humankind is let a lot of things slide
we look too quickly past people who are
close to discovering something or know
about something that just die or vanish
you know what I'm saying saying no one
you die once think about that you can
die one time you're gone forever you
know what I'm saying there's way too
many people that one death they're just
dying from coming close to something you
know what I'm saying or do I sound crazy
no it's like the guy who found got like
right like it's just like I feel like we
have to look out way more yeah not for
me personally cuz I don't feel like I'm
taking like enough steps towards like a
goal here of something like I'm
unveiling I'm a my thing is my thing is
right if the government's hiding
something right and they're doing a good
enough job you might find it by accident
because you might not even know what
you're looking for huh so a hidden in
plain sight type thing correct so what
if one day you find like a special stone
that isn't supposed to be where it's
supposed to be and you you pick it up
and it starts like glowing and he just
gets like sniped in the back head cuz
like the government oh cuz the
government picks up so quick that like
like they're like oh my God code red he
found the stone what are you looking at
I agree what are you always doing that
for like it's just I'm not looking at
anything you're talking you're talking
to Nick but you're like this I'm like
like if I was talking to you right now
and I was like this it's a little weird
and I'd look whatever Matt don't you
think the way that he just really shut
that down was a little suspicious I
agree like I feel like you might shut
down what like you were like oh I'm not
looking at
anything well I was thinking of the
stone being outside like the I'm just a
little like sometimes I get a little
scared the one that started glowing the
one from the story oh I was so confused
also like we're triplets right that's
rare yeah you know what I'm saying what
if that was like biological warfare
created by like like people set like oh
they're going to be triplets and like
one of them needs to turn against the
others and like they're we're going to
plant them scares we're going to plant
them there to monitor and see the
triplet life but they know deep down
that their in rooted goals are back to
come back here and give us the
information do you have that or do you
know you have to make it somewh I was
thinking it was you I don't have
that like I just think of like do you
have anywhere to be no like do you guys
have you have any like ulterior motives
like like transport conversation or
anything like let them know what like
cuz I just think all the time like I'm
trapped in my own mind a lot and I think
like I feel like wallets need to be far
thinner like can we believe that like
the F where are we going hold on like I
feel like just a wall in your pocket's
like the thickest thing you can have
like okay like look at your wallet that
just depends on what kind of wallet you
buy no it doesn't depends what kind of
wallet you buy regardless can we we
haven't thought why youing you watch I
saw I was like Wow put can I be real for
a second you want to know what I think
is really impressive I just feel there's
so much crazy madeup stories that are
turned into TV shows cuz I think about
it and I'm like like from the start oh I
know what you mean when you watched the
first episode like oh like if someone
makes a bank robbery show and it's like
a great
plan yeah like why did
why you just rob the bank agree why did
you have that plan that's what I'm
saying like it's like a TV show where
like there's like an alternative world
that drove through this portal at this
time in that place like something had to
happen to that person for them to like
get into the mindset to write this TV
show they're hiding something I think
they were
there sure they I wouldn't say there but
maybe it could be like they were their
way of living out their dream the Govern
let them speak about it so they use the
show is The Voice on do you ever think
like that guy was looking right at us
did you see that yeah that was
government that's a government
vehicle he was looking right at us he
first of all there's nothing over there
he you guys saw that yeah no that was I
wouldn't be surprised if he comes back
again and like tases us and tries to
take us to the government center I'm
being honest my God he could do it what
if a claw picked up the van right now
and did you see him I like he was
looking for he was looking like this
literally that guy just drove by and was
like this do I can look at the camera he
was driving this way wasn't even looking
there's a there's a parking lot over
there with nothing there where's he even
going what is over there I don't and
he's driving like this goes hold on I
have to get in the Cara me laugh
literally driving by and he was in such
a sus mobile bro yeah like with a really
big white beard like driving old car and
he was just like
that no that was Nick there he is oh my
god oh it's not him I'm joking that's
another
guy but no what I up his hair hold on
but what I was going to say we also
we're yelling in a car and all the
lights are on so it's like I'm a little
sused out but I mean I'd look to dude
but anyways I think it was just cuz you
Nick has such like cartoon character
manorisms you
know say
yippe Nick's the type to run in place
I've dead ass seen Nick get excited and
go like
this okay legitimately did that Len what
I'm also thinking is every single thing
that you say like as an idea like every
idea you have or if you're joking and
you're talking about like a a fake
scenario like a fantasy scenario you're
never I feel like it's not an original
thought like it happened from like
watching a different show even if it was
like when you were like years years
years ago like imagine if like there was
like a small world and we were all
living on it it's like nah you just got
that idea from way back in your head
from like Hort and hair a who you know
what I'm saying so I feel like it's like
everything in your life regardless of
what you're saying you lowkey got the
idea from something el else oh agreed
right so what I'm saying is he said it
weird since every single person had to
have got an idea from something like in
their past to like talk about it again
all these fantasy stories and stuff like
in the world it's other people's
perspective on things I feel like they
just have to be like lowkey real like I
don't believe in fantasy I believe
fantasy was real you know cuz like who's
making these up I'm with who's writing
like Disney movies as if like like
you're telling me that was an original
thought that you came I mean those are
like I could believe someone wrote there
is you have to you have to but you
because there's another movie that
exists already that gave them
inspiration listen you have to listen
there is like creative like there is
like creative like people create and
people have imagination it's just you I
have far more imagination Crea you have
far more storage in your membrane from
other things and it may not even be like
a lot hey Nick a lot of stuff nowadays
is hard to like in like come up with
creative General ideas because
everything is so like washed out and
everything has been used so that's why
it's like there's a difference between
being inspired by something and creating
something brand new but it's also very
difficult to create something very new
you want know something I don't
get 23 and me tests who's doing [ __ ] oh
my God they shut the parking lot lights
off like you're telling me like I spit
in a tube and now my grandpa there's
like an Italian Baker from exactly like
you know
Baker like bread Baker yeah like we're
related to a baker I made that up
totally fake thought you took a test
like he you just he sounded convincing I
was like dude oh we know this like I
thought you were just saying like oh
like we have an Italian
Christ we're catching
on don't
even no I just don't get like like what
you said like I don't get that like I
can spit in this little tube send it off
to some like Factory and you're you're
he's looking side to side I have another
thought can I listen can I can you
listen to what I'm going to say go ahead
I don't get how like I Nick you realize
all our eyes are in this car or forward
someone could be behind us don't say
that don't even I can't even I take a 23
and me test
right look at both of you look at both
of you do you see where that guy's going
yep the same spot
no that's even more look I take a 23 and
me test right I spit in this tube send
it to whatever that guy's circling
around just listen to him what is don't
y him to go if you won't stop
interrupting go mat I take a 23m me test
spit in a tube send it to this facility
they package it up they test it they get
the results how does do I find out not
only
like all this information about like
where my native family is and all that
but like down to the specifics on where
my great-grandfathers grew up and [ __ ]
it makes zero sense to me absolutely no
sense also I I would hate to do that
because I would hate to know like I'm
pretty sure they tell tell you what like
diseases and ailments you're susceptible
to and it's like I don't want to know
what I could get let me just get it but
they also like that's so strange to me
like I would not want to know any
information you also just then find out
you got mad my thing is if you know
about the future if I if you know about
the future you'd spend your whole life
trying so hard to change like what if
like you're related to a super cool
historical figure oh high five Nick not
anymore I I didn't know what if you're
like related to like a super cool
historical I'll find out one someday I
am a super cool historical figure anyway
you ever think of it like that no
everyone is history technically everyone
is making it impact enough to like like
like like what if our it's crazy how one
thing you do can totally alter everyone
in this like not everyone in this world
but like if I wanted to go like the
butterfly fact I know what you mean if I
wanted to go to Target and Chuck a
gallon of milk at an old woman and she
like broke her head and like Snapped her
spine or something and then imagine no
listen she goes she goes to the doctor
now her grandmother her her daughter
realizes Story scared to go to Target
never goes to Target again but then like
her uncle is like oh it's okay and then
like the doctor has like a near like
close experience with her while doing
surgery he goes home and tells his kids
his kids get emotional and like grow up
to be like some like it's crazy oh my
God you're so right and I also think
like what if like same scenario you like
if I just stop talking right now the
whole career could be different yeah but
like if I said something we could like
blow up on like a Tik Tok and be like oh
my God like our world could could be
different depending on what you say but
also I think of like imagine same thing
you threw like an Jaga orange juice at
an old lady's head oh so now it's orange
listen could change now the orange ju
the orange ju it could be different it
could be different you know what I mean
big big CH also I just imagine this you
take like an OJ like I was thinking OJ
cuz they have like the
long it looks kind of like a drum like
those drums but anyways you could take
it and hit the old lady in the face
we're not even gr it anymore we're just
yeah just like swinging whatever and
like I feel bad for the poor woman and
it like breaks open it's like listen and
it breaks open and she falls yeah and
then someone could have been going to
check out and they see me do that and
like hey stop and run over and like go
to help her but then at checkout they
could have met like their like wife not
only wife but like he could have been
like a scientist working on something
that was super close to figuring it out
and he could have bumped into another
scientist that would have helped him
figure that out and the whole [ __ ]
that's crazy that one like gave me like
chill Anything Could Happen you could
cause a complete shift and that's how I
think of like we can dead ask me a free
will like if I wanted to I could go into
a Target and just lay down and
go and I could affect everyone around me
you want to know what I think you know
what I mean like you have free will know
what I could go outside stop I just open
that door shut the door that scared the
[ __ ] and look and it scared him and he
didn't feel fear till I opened it
imagine you could I could go to a
[ __ ] I could go to a full field Acres
on acres and cut a blade of grass and
alter something's life correct you want
to know correct you want to know
something I want to start doing I feel
like they're on to us Nick wait you want
to know what I want to do imagine like
hey like you need to let him speak go
ahead go ahead go ahead you want to know
what I want to do go to the bank get
like $10 worth of pennies just get rolls
of pennies and just every once in a
while put a penny heads up on the ground
and give people good luck make someone
stay
but it doesn't work my thing is talking
about the butterfly effect thing listen
talking about the
butterfly talking about the butterfly
effect talking hey hey hey oh my God no
one's listening listen oh my God shut
the [ __ ] up i' hate talking to a wall
cuz a wall wouldn't respond you can't
say listen you know now talk about the
butterfly effect what the government is
doing that Nick is so close to is
they're doing like they might not be
like completely changing us or making us
like alter our thoughts and [ __ ] stop
looking but there's a guy sprinking
through the [ __ ] parking lot mat
that's why I looked if you wanted to
know okay cool I wanted to know where he
was heading thing is the government
might not be like in full Direct Control
to us but they can alter the the um
outcome of something they can alter the
butterfly effect slightly well no I
think they just know what would trigger
it like we don't know who to hit with
the OJ you know to affect someone's day
they would know the timing this is
called the OJ Theory by Chris and
ntera this is called the orange juice
Theory it's the target Theory I think
this is called no it's just like the who
to hit with the orange juice correct so
it's orange hold on I got to so
basically listen listen you made that
out speak but basically what we're
saying is the government could do the
slightest things and just really alter
all of us this is called the m and it's
like how many conversations do you have
like in your whole life that no h w t o
JT so it's what
w
w okay but anyway WT many WT H WT o JT
who to hit with like if we didn't film
car videos like everyone's life could be
different correct or better sorry it
could be better like what if like
instead of like what if feel like really
affected someone's day well it's all
like we but it's all they part of the
the system by watching the videos
correct this is just a crazy what if the
whole life I think
can we film another video like right now
after this to like keep going I'm
feeling like ready to keep going then
write some stuff down and maybe we can
yeah okay can we fil another
please I really want to think more come
on like part two part two what part we
haven't done a part two in so long and
it's already been like 25 minutes please
we're not right
nowos the milk don't do don't hit anyone
yet like don't affect anyone yet and
like don't think about it too much like
if you're going to go in line at Target
just go in line like don't think about
the just don't do anything yet hold on
give us a week we'll talk about it next
week hold
on saying how you miss me yeah you miss
me and all the things that we did we
said we going to travel from the island
of Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
all this why because of some but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
saying nothing when I'm post it with
other [ __ ] for my brothers