I grew up in India. I had no idea or no
concept of like what is Boston? What is
New York? I hadn't been to any of these
places. Boston generally is a very
multicultural environment. People come
there from a lot of different countries
and I went to Boston University where
that's especially the case. After
graduating from college, I actually
started a PhD in machine learning which
I actually dropped out of. I left my PhD
program and I joined a startup. People
thought I was crazy that I would just
drop out of it and get kind of go join
some startup, right? But I think it was
the right decision looking back at it.
It was a very high-risisk decision, but
it worked out. Especially in the US, and
I think that's what makes the US such a
special place. There's definitely so
much opportunity that I think it's
better to be a little bit more of a
risk-taker. Most of the time, you can
take a risk and actually get rewarded
for it. I think people don't bias enough
towards taking risks. If you just do
what everybody else is doing, then
you'll just end up wherever everybody
else is going, right?
My name is Goraf and I am the co-founder
and CEO of Captions. Captions is a video
creation company. Our goal is to make it
easy for anybody anywhere to be able to
tell their story through video without
actually going through the physical
process of recording or editing a video.
We've raised over $und00 million in
funding. It's gotten to tens of millions
of users and over 100,000 plus users
daily.
I was in the US for the first four years
of my life and my parents moved to
India. I grew up in India. Moving back
to the US like I had no idea or no
concept of like what it would be like.
What is Boston? What is New York? Like I
hadn't been to any of these places. My
parents were like Boston's great you
should go there. And I was like sounds
great. Let me do that. So at Boston
University it was an interesting
situation because coming from India sort
of the curriculum there especially
around computer science is just very
advanced compared to the US and a lot of
the things that we actually were being
taught in college we had already covered
in high school for the most part. A lot
of college classes were essentially
repeating what I had already done in
high school. It probably was the case
for a lot of people from India I
imagine. I think that did give me a
chance to actually go and explore
outside of just that and kind of see
what else I can learn and what more I
can do. I did tons of projects. I like
worked on projects with my roommates. I
worked on a lot of different apps that
we launched and this was like in 2012
2011 when the app store was still early
in high school and going into college. I
had started a kind of a company in a
strange way. I say that because I
actually didn't realize it was a company
until much later. I was working on some
games and there was some need around
like security software for those games
and I decided to make it and the game
company decided to buy it for me not
knowing that I was like 16 years old and
I ended up selling it to a bunch of
other companies as well. I didn't
realize at that time that this is what a
company is is like you make a product
you sell it but much later I was like
wow that's kind of what it was. It was a
interesting sort of experience to go
through because it kind of transitioned
from generally games and gaming into
sort of more general skill set. I really
enjoy learning new things. How do you
learn things quickly and how do you
figure things out quickly? It's
something that not a lot of people talk
about, but it's like one of the most
important skills in my mind. Go to a new
domain, you know, go to a new area,
something that you haven't done before,
try for the first time, figure it out
quickly, and be actually useful and
productive in it is like it's a pretty
cool skill and it's pretty fun one to
work on because you get to try out a lot
of different things. You'll get to learn
a lot of different things and focus on
that as a skill in itself. Being able to
do all those different things and
figuring those things out is really
[Music]
important. Through the early part of my
career, I was really focused on machine
learning as a central aspect of what I
was doing. At Microsoft, I joined them
on this new team they were developing
called Azure Machine Learning. It's like
a machine learning platform they were
building. And then at Snapchat, there
was a bit of a difference. I got a
chance to really get more on the product
side and eventually ended up joining the
design team which was like a huge shift
from what I had done previously and the
idea of like connecting technology to
actual design and actual product made a
lot of sense. So I ended up starting a
team there called design engineering
which was like how do you bring together
great design and great engineering to
build amazing products right? One of the
things I learned at Snap, if you think
about Snap as a company, I think Snap
was one of the earliest companies to
actually get into video for consumer use
cases, especially short video. It did
get me very immersed into the space of
like video in general, especially video
for communication, short videos, and all
the challenges both technical and
product that are related to that. But I
think in general, one of the things that
I noticed was essentially a shift in the
way that people were communicating. A
lot of people thought Tik Tok was just,
oh, Tik Tok, that's like just people
dancing, right? It's for fun. But I
think the reality was that yes, there
were a bunch of people dancing, but
there was a lot of people talking and
there were a lot of people telling
stories and, you know, sometimes bad
things that happened to them, good
things that happened to them. People
were like talking about ideas and like
what could be done and what should be
done and people were arguing with each
other, right? And I think that was like
a shift in the way people communicated
from like that's the type of stuff that
would happen like on Twitter or like on
text beforehand, right? and it was now
happening on video for the first time.
So, I got pretty familiar with all the
different ways that people are
communicating and kind of what works
better and what doesn't
work. When we started the company, we
were thinking about building a social
network and so we were thinking, okay,
there's like a distribution part and
then there's a creation part of the
social network. We thought, hey, let's
start with the creation first. So we
started off with the idea of literally
just adding captions to videos, text on
videos based on what people are saying.
The reason we did this is because we saw
there was a big accessibility movement
at that time. There were a lot of people
sort of manually writing text on top of
their videos and it was spent an hour
like typing it all out. There wasn't
actually a solution for this that was in
the market at that time. So we were the
first ones to build it and the absolute
first project we built it in one weekend
just as like a test essentially and we
put it on the app store and the next day
we woke up and it was like 600 people
per minute using it basically it was
completely at the top of the app store
with no marketing no nothing done
essentially and I think that was like
the moment where it was like wow it
can't be this easy right like it really
can't be because we had been told right
like it's going to be a lot of work to
find product market fit and things like
that. But I think that being said, we
had just started the company and we had
this idea of a social network and things
like that. I think we were like, "Okay,
this is working, but I wonder if we
should go back and like really think
about the social network aspect of
this." And so we tried to figure out how
to get people to post on the platform
and things like that until we
essentially rediscovered captions. And
this was a interesting moment where we
were working on another application
which was called Spam App. It was like a
photo sharing app. It was actually doing
really well. While we were working on
that, we're looking at the bills and
there was like a good $10,000 a month
going to captions. You know, I remember
talking to my co-founder and we were
like, "Okay, let's just delete it
because we don't want to spend $120,000
a year on this, right?" We decided to
delete it. I remember going back home
and on Saturday going through like, you
know, the UI to be like, "Okay, I'm
going to press delete now." And while I
was going to press delete, I was just
thinking, "Ah, but like we worked so
hard on this. Like I don't want to
delete this, right?" Like it's like I
want to keep it for memories at least,
right? So I had an idea just in the
moment quickly design a little payw wall
where we ask people to pay for the app.
If nobody pays for it then it's
essentially shut down but we can
continue using it because you know we
work hard on it and if someone pays for
it then it pays for itself. So we're not
paying the bills basically. So I quickly
made that in about 2 or 3 hours put it
on the app store and launched it and
then completely forgot about it. So, we
continued working on spam app and it
continued growing through the next, you
know, four, five, six months. While we
were doing that, I for some reason
decided to check my account. And when I
checked it, it was like at $500,000 or
more and growing. And like the craziest
part was not only did people pay for it,
people retained on it. And it was
growing in revenue completely on its own
with like zero employees working on it.
So, no employees. There were like 2,000
open support tickets. Nobody was
answering obviously, right? And it would
continue to grow. You know, we had to
have this like tough conversation of
like, oh my god, like this is truly
working, right? And it was tough because
we already had another thing that was
also working and that we were raising a
new round on essentially, right? I think
we discussed this for a couple of weeks
and we ended up deciding we're going to
switch to captions and we're going to
just focus on creation as the primary.
We switched over and literally the
moment we launched the first set of
features on top of the existing app.
What was looking like a fast growth
completely condensed because the new
growth was exponential just like
straight up. I mean, I think that's kind
of the crazy thing that I think about at
this point is like that split-second
decision was the difference between two
completely different paths. Here's the
thing, like we don't know. The other
side could have been even more
successful. That's the tough part about
these decisions is like you have to
choose one and you'll never know what
the other could have been. I think the
big decisions are actually in the small
decisions in a way and the small
decisions are what actually you don't
think about too much but actually turn
the tide of like what will happen in the
future. I think that was the case over
here too, right? Because like what felt
like a very small decision of like other
app should we delete it or not seem like
kind of obvious. Anybody we would have
asked would have told us, yeah, just
delete it, right? Whatever. But I think
those small decisions actually are way
more important than the big ones
sometimes. And I think this shows quite
a bit like if you look at any
competition at a global scale, right,
which building a startup is kind of a
competition at a global scale. Like look
at the Olympics for example, right? Like
people are like within seconds of each
other, right? Sometimes even
milliseconds of each other. That's not
because of some major decision they made
while training or something like that.
Everyone's very good, right? It's
probably like some minor micro decision
that happened in the moment like, you
know, while they're swimming and they
moved one arm at this angle versus the
other angle. Like that's what's deciding
who wins and loses, right? I think it's
like those small decisions that count
the most.
We did face challenges around like
identifying the user and making sure
we're building for the right user
because when we launched the app like it
was immediately sort of successful,
right? And it immediately blew up. It
made things easier and harder in some
ways. I think one of the things that can
happen when too many people join sort of
your app or product very quickly is you
kind of lose lose sight of who the
customer is because there's a lot of
people who are just checking it out.
There's a lot of people who don't
actually care about the use case, but
they want to just see what's going on.
Between all that noise, it's difficult
to figure out like which one of these
people are the actual user. Who's going
to retain and for whom is this actually
solving a real problem? That's really
important because at the end of the day,
without focusing on the right customer,
you'll end up building the wrong
product. Captions was a paid app from
the beginning. And I think elements
there that was interesting is like being
paid actually helped filter our user
base a little bit and to only those
people who were willing to pay. Those
people that were willing to pay were
people who had real pain point. And so
with that, we got really good feedback
from users, right, around like what we
should build and what we should
prioritize and what they want from us in
the future. We decided to keep the app
paid right from the beginning all the
way till today because of that reason. I
think on the technical side, we try to
avoid as much as possible technical
challenges that it's sort of unproven
essentially, right? Like I think one of
the mistakes that can be made is like
spending a lot of time building
something very technically complex
without fully recognizing whether
there's product market fit there or not.
We spend a year building something and
nobody wants it. Right? That happens
very often and it's happened to us too.
The key factor there is like how do you
reduce the technical risk to like an
MVP? How do you test with like just the
bare minimum? Get something out in front
of people. Have them see it. Have them
try it. If they don't retain, then don't
invest more in it, right? Try something
else. And I think that's the other thing
is like not going deeper and deeper into
the rabbit hole almost in a way. I think
there's also tendencies of like building
the first version seeing that it doesn't
completely work and then justifying it
by saying well if it only had this
feature and that feature and that third
feature then maybe it would have worked
right but I think the reality is like it
would not probably not have worked with
as many features as you want. It would
only have worked with a single feature
only one of those things right whatever
actually people want at the end of the
day. So, I think the better skill is to
just learn how to quickly build stuff.
Try as many things as possible. The most
important thing is getting stuff out in
front of people, testing it. If it
doesn't work, kill it and start again.
And keep doing that as quickly as
possible.
[Music]