[ __ ] idiots there didn't
oh wow
what'd you say I have select words
who's this idiot you got me dancing in
the rain
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
[Music]
my kid goes kid goes who's 10 piece
chicken nugget is this yours
listen is this gonna be a problem oh my
god get that [ __ ] light out of my eye
put it back down listen to his story
Matt he goes listen you're soaked yeah I
was getting out there in the room Chris
wouldn't [ __ ] kill me if the camera's
good or not listen to his story no if
it's good
go ahead tell the stupid story
he goes whose 10 piece chicken nugget is
this yours or Matt's I said max he goes
oh wow
what is that supposed to mean
oh is the pitter patter gonna be too
much
I think it's a calm pitter patter I
think it's fine
well
to our rain location let's see sour yes
you want one huh do you want one I don't
have chicken nuggets I'm aware but
you're still my orange
yeah I don't get it either I see you see
me wear team purple
yourself
you see my shirt yeah I did let me have
some cream and so are my shorts don't
say that dude I'm the cream machine
tonight cream okay cream on cream on
cream that's good what color are the
shoes cream cream oh [ __ ] they're
actually cream cream on cream on cream
so your triple cream tonight kid I'm the
cream machine they were white you just
warm so long if they're yellowing oh
now why would you do that you [ __ ]
buffoon
yeah that's such a good one
buffoon it sounds like a monkey I'm
gonna say I'm so shocked that a buffoon
isn't the type of monkey
it's like Australia find the Australian
map real quick Nick
wow oh my God more like this way no
camera other way yeah show the camera I
was looking in Australian chicken turn
the turn the camera
uh he's gonna put it on the screen
stupid it's looking Australian chicken
nugget
hello I think I wonder how much we go on
eBay you know how like they do the eBay
things in general gorilla shaped Cheetos
I think that has more value because
you've held it in your hand than it does
looking like Australia
hey you got to boost your car no but
have you seen
have you seen like the Cheetos oh these
are not good tonight yeah they're not
that good I'm just hungry so I eat
Australia and kill all the kangaroo I
think what
I think we should all go around a circle
saying our favorite thing about each
other let's do it
what
I'm doing that
why some negative my favorite thing I
know it's one person in this car is on
Santa's naughty list
who you
little naughty
you actually disgust me on like
honestly I don't it's not that I I would
do that I'm fine with doing that
for love
not at all yeah you're just such a tough
guy no not at all it's just more of like
I feel like there's a time and place
and like you got to be like in the mid
in the feeling
my favorite thing about Matt is no like
even though he wants to win the Tour so
bad he's still wearing team purple to
support Nick that's really can we lose
the super joke you ever try and put so
much energy into one bodily function
that you accidentally do another
are you trying to burp and you just like
[ __ ]
well it happened to me in my whole life
did you just break those
dude Trevor loves those but now they
look cooler no you look stupid as [ __ ]
look like [ __ ] Ross from Monsters Inc
whatever the [ __ ] her name is she
literally doesn't wear glasses
those exact ones actually stupid idiots
like this yes you look like her you
idiot
everyone I think we should all release a
lot that was an actual like blood
curdling screen that wasn't it mine yes
that was scarily loud I want to see how
loud I can scream I don't snore now
don't know now Chris no right now
don't you don't do that right now I
really wish I got an m m McFlurry
I've never seen someone so ferociously
miss a couple dude y'all know what's so
funny isn't this um this video that guy
and he tries to rob his nail salon
uncle on it
it's uncle's mints
I don't know just says uncle
I don't know this guy tried to rob a
nail salon give me the money hey give me
it give me it anyway
they're all like dude have you seen him
Matt have you seen that he tries he runs
into a nail salon and he goes give me
everything like give me all the money
and like start pointing the gun at
random civilians and the lady at the
cash register and they all like ignore
him they're like you need to just go
dude and then he's like so embarrassed
that he just left I feel like
I hate when people use manners to me it
just makes me feel like I'm doing way
more this is literally the magic word
yeah but I feel like thank you and
please it's just like oh like it's so
much like okay do that for me I
appreciate it bro like thanks you just
said thanks you just said both thanks is
cool thank you like is like like I just
saved the city thank you
he's like I didn't do all that save the
cities you know what I mean you're a
huge appreciate yeah like not even
appreciate it appreciate appreciate it
yeah appreciate it I'm a huge appreciate
it as well yeah me too I appreciate you
thanks no but I feel like thank you is
like such a song if Nick was a superhero
he'd be like like say it was like cream
machine the superhero thank you
like you know what I mean no
syndrome oh
like you the [ __ ] villain syndrome
yeah I love Cinderella I look like that
monster from Monsters if they make a lot
like solid makeup no if they make a line
whoa never knows is bleeding oh good I
hope it does bleed bleed bleed oh like
how disrespectful is this motion man
oh that drives you crazy I know it did
like that oh well how many oh how many
times did you stop talking today I'll
break your goddamn yeah
oh my God what happened oh
my God why'd you do that you're a
[ __ ] idiot give me my hat is it the
drink oh my God everywhere Matt I'm
soaked are you from literally it's all
down his arm it's funny because there's
Skittles all over that seat and then
snap
um
dude clean off I'm happy you're wet
at all what's gonna be awesome
you need a severe like help you're
cleaning this [ __ ] car no I'm not yes
you absolutely are oh I was gonna take
one today
thank you I'm in such a State of Shock
right now
yeah
and how about that
and now what would you do now that
you're equally as strong as I am we have
like not even started the intro of this
video and you guys have both dumped your
[ __ ] drink on each other well I'm
just curious how shocked you are now
since you just did that to me you didn't
feel exactly how I do this is Chris's
villain back story
we're gonna get demonetized
who's gonna win tour
yeah I know this is like insane the
car's gonna a whole car is gonna be
sticky because you guys are just [ __ ]
little babies
you guys are stupid
like was that fun
was it fun it numbers one to ten how
worth it was it
was it worth it Chris feeling like I won
okay
yeah feeling like I'm the king okay you
think you're the king yep okay and that
feeling like Nick's a cowardly yeah who
turned my seed heater on who does that
every single time probably him jumping
around like a [ __ ] monkey
it's all the final spill Matt it's all
over the final spells all over the chair
yeah this isn't real there it is like
the final spill
oh
it's on your arm
s lick it off my arm lick it off yo you
got another thing coming if you think
I'm licking that [ __ ] off your arm just
look at
I feel like I'm in the Snapple Factory
I feel like a Snapple fact this is
insane
dude the car is gonna be sticky for like
an unreal amount of time
did you release it
why'd you rip the shirt I've never had a
car made it all wet
I've never seen a carvio where we've
been so physical
I have like a stupid oval neck on now
because of you
now my [ __ ] Skittles are melting
don't Litter Nick it's Skittles you you
spot still don't put it outside what if
a bird choked on it he'll Taste the
rainbow while he goes out can we have
the topic for this video yeah you're
coming down here
okay you're coming
you're coming down here with Clorox
wipes you're gonna wipe the entire car I
hope you know that
pain
oh you're a stupid haircut
I feel so pissed
Matt stop
shower the second we get okay can you
put something can we play this game
you initiated the big [ __ ] spill not
true yes you
you built the things for just reason
with just reason no I didn't intend on
hitting the bottle kid you had the first
bottle spill with intention and I had
the finals
yes it is true I had first accidental
spill you had first spill with
intentions
had intention no it didn't yes it did
yeah
listen then you got to the spill by
accident listen get off remove your
hands so who goes like this
me he smothered my mouth
I would literally I would listen to you
and then I'd say hey wait let me speak
all right be quiet or even shut the [ __ ]
up is is fine and acceptable to me but
to silence
I've smothered your mouth to smug
oh yeah I've smothered your mouth
countless times in car videos
you've never Snapple attacked me and got
everything wet
ever
then I spill oh no I spill a little on
you oh no not that big of a deal and you
[ __ ] karate chop it into the [ __ ]
Oblivion and get the entire back seat
soaking wet
was it worth it for the both of you no
stop grabbing the old toys you don't
need any more I'm eating them get off me
now that's not even funny it's not real
that's not even funny you have initiated
every big spill because that was crazy
now there's all toys everywhere wait sir
you guys are both stupid
you're stupid he's stupid
hey you're perfect
you're the winner
what are you even talking about
I feel like an absolute idiot you should
feel lousy
lousy
gross um what's triplet is most likely
to yeah whoo yeah are you recording me
it's like exactly me personally no look
at your phone oh no it's freaking me out
I don't know you're trying to get some
who's most likely to douse their other
sibling and Snapple
don't do that
who's most likely to make a stupid
decision that turns into 20 minutes of
constant regret Chris I have no regrets
actually she's like a little [ __ ] kid
and you sound like a big baby big
[ __ ] baby Nick you're actually you
sound like a little kid I said he sounds
like a little kid
oh man shut up yeah and he argues at me
by saying you physically touched me
cry themselves to sleep me I always get
sad at night me too
take a freezing freezing shower me
me too because I get too itchy when it's
hot so I turn around there you go
that's disgusting like dirty dirty don't
call me that lean too far back on a
chair and fall over I did that yesterday
Matt literally almost fell into an
entire TV console yesterday yeah that
would have been so funny post a 2017
meme on their story Matt
and Nick I feel like Matt's like a meme
Lord okay you see the one I sent you
guys today yeah yeah that [ __ ] was so
funny actually I could have said
anything what is that my heebies are GB
oh my GBS are GB who's most likely to
get mad for absolutely anything Nick
Chris Nick you just punched a Snapple
out of because you [ __ ] grasped my
throat and shut my mouth who's most
likely to forget a person's name me
Chris Chris actually calls the most
amount of people the wrong thing there
and he's just rolled with it we're like
I can tell you at least three people
that have fake names that every single
person we're friends with also knows
their fake name because how often Chris
uses the wrong name correct jump in a
Sea full of sharks
none of us I'm good yeah like I'm all
right Matt Wood
because he's just a wild card
one thing about Matt is uh you never
know what to expect someone said who's
most likely to scream out of nowhere
Chris yeah invent a new recipe me
yeah it tastes like [ __ ] [ __ ] you crazy
[Laughter]
ah
wow good joke yeah score you should talk
my food said he'd eat it Chris used to
cook does cry cry those tears man I see
you laughing so hard you just want to
cry because he's used to cook disasters
when we were younger
you threw your hand over there correct
yeah cause I was gonna shut him up like
you we're gonna get demonetized yeah
because your face is so ugly
take a [ __ ] and forget to flush
no no explanation I flush every time it
just isn't all the way down no not like
sometimes the lever requires a full
manual action downwards
okay I've been oh
that's what you gotta do who's most
likely to forget that the stove is on
not me you did it three days ago left
the [ __ ] stove on 375 for four hours
no because I went downstairs it was off
yeah because I shut it off no you didn't
yes I texted me yeah I shut it off when
I went downstairs to go to bed I don't
care we have to wrap up this video guys
okay well it's such a shame I can't wait
to go home and [ __ ] shower I'm upset
I want to stay out we can go back out
but yes it's unreleased
no that's my favorite tree shirt hope
everyone enjoyed today's new intro and I
hope you enjoyed Chris making a [ __ ]
fool of himself so [ __ ] yourself lousy
[ __ ] cream machine goofball
come on maltoid Uncle Uncle man okay
goodbye