Next into the Shark Tank is Joe Moore
with a unique solution to protect
against germs and allergens.
Hi, my name is Joe Moore. I am the
president and CEO of the First Defense
Nascreen Corporation and I'm seeking
$500,000 for 10% of my company. Every
day, people flood emergency rooms,
doctor's offices, andarmacies seeking
relief from inhaling contaminated air.
And one out of every five commercials on
TV today is about the treatment of nasal
allergies. That's why I invented First
Defense nasal screens.
First Defense nasal screens are the
first and only lightweight,
non-inserted, almost non-visible nasal
screen ever invented. And they have been
clinically proven to reduce the
inhilation of allergens, pollins,
pollutions, pet danders, molds, viruses,
and more by up to 99%.
And the next time you're faced with
unhealthy, contaminated air, remember,
don't get sick. Just peel and stick.
Thank you. Any questions?
Are you kidding me? Um
um I'm I I'm I'm not um I just know that
like I said how big this really is.
$500,000 for 10% of the company. How
many have you sold?
Actually, right now about 1.7 million.
1.7 million units or 1.7 million in
total sales?
1.7 million units.
And let's just sell them for
wholesale was 60.
So your sales last year were how much,
Joe? Actually, we just we're not we
haven't gone to market yet.
Sorry, I'm confused. If you haven't gone
to market, how have you sold 1.7
million?
Um, actually, we have one big client out
of the United Arab Emirates that has
actually put in their first order and
given us a contract for 8 million over
the next six years.
So, you have an order for $8 million?
Yes, sir.
Right now?
Yes, sir. Matter of fact,
I have the contract right here.
That's a prepared man right there. Good
for you.
Thank Well, all of a sudden, you don't
look that funny with that stuff stuck up
your nose. Can I see that?
Yes, you can.
You know, you don't sound like the bozo
I thought you were. Is this a product
that perhaps is is going to be very
popular in other societies where face
masks are more prominent than they're
here stateside?
Definitely. This is a worldwide product
cuz I mean, you know, you're wearing
them right now. I can see them. It's
probably an issue for many people that
are going to look at that and say, "What
do you got stuck up your nose?"
May I see the actual product?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry, Robert.
The distributor guarantees that he'll
order one, Am I reading this correctly?
1,500,000
sets.
Yes, sir. That's for Saudi Arabia alone.
They've already ordered those.
And how much is he guaranteeing you?
Uh, he's guaranteeing me the 8 million
over the next um six years.
How does the filter work?
Basically, how the filter works is as
you breathe in, it's a nonwoven
material, so it closes and as you
breathe out, it flushes itself. So, to
stop viruses, bacterial elements. It
does.
What's to stop you from taking the germs
in through your mouth?
That's a great question. 90% of the air
we breathe goes through our nasal
passages. Also, viruses do not grow in
the mouth, the esophagus, or line of the
stomach. They grow in the nasal passage.
Is there a patent that protects this?
Yes, sir. I have we are patent pending
in the United States, Canada, and
Europe, and have been for three years.
And what would you use the money for?
The money for right now is so that I can
keep producing it because of the raw
materials I have to buy up front. So
basically, you need the 500,000 to make
the order.
Correct.
Okay. Tell me if I'm putting these in
right. So I just take it.
The best way to do it, put it on your
finger like a contact, touch your nasal
passage, slide it around the outside,
slide it around the inside.
Joe, let me ask you a question. Why not
just go license it to one of the big
drug companies?
Um, because I I I did that originally. I
went to one of the biggest in the United
States and they told me we were actually
a competitor and if they took the
product they would shelf it because why
would they prevent it for a dollar when
they could treat it for 14.
How much money have you put into this? I
mean
we have almost $1 million into this.
And where' that money come from?
Um about 600,000 of it was mine. The
rest is from friends and family. I think
I'd have a very hard time understanding
at all what the product is about unless
you had these big photos with the noses
and unless you're standing there
pitching it because I think the cost of
educating people is the big kahuna here.
Joe, based on that, I'm out.
Okay.
I'm intrigued. I got to tell you, let me
throw an offer out to you. I'll give you
the 500,000. And I want a 15% royalty on
every unit sold until I recoup my
$500,000.
Okay. Just the royalty, no equity.
Are you kidding? Of course I want the
equity. I took the risk. Now, here's my
equity. I want 20%.
You have an offer for me. What do you
want to do?
Um, I would definitely like to hear what
everybody else has to say. They're not
interested. They never told me they were
out
because of their silence. You know
they're not interested.
Not necessarily true.
We can work together on this.
Okay. You got a deal?
Yeah.
I like that.
[Music]
I like how cuddly they are, but I want
to give you $800,000 for 30%
with 10% royalty.
Oh, come on.
Screw that. I'll give you a million
dollars for the whole company right now.
I can appreciate uh and I appreciate the
offer. I really do. But um I would
definitely
You just turned down a million dollars.
Yes, sir.
I I I I couldn't take a million dollars.
I know that this is a billion dollar
industry.
Is there a number you would take
to sell the whole company?
Not without a royalty, no. With the
royalty, very possibly. Yes.
What's the royalty?
I believe that with the statistics and
the research we've done, the royalty
would have to be 10%.
Wow.
And then what's the number on the
company?
I I would like to stay part of it. Be
honest with you, because it's my
passion. I I'm going to show you
something. I am a cancer I am a I am a
cancer survivor. I am a cancer survivor
by the time I was 19 years old. I've
been through the army. I've been through
the Marine Corps. I've been halfway
around the world. I fought all my life
and doing different things. I believe in
this more than anything else because
I've gotten testimonials of people say,
"You've changed my life. You've changed
the quality of my life.
I'll give you a million dollars. I want
30% of the company. Also 10% royalty
until I recoup the money.
Joe, I'll give you $2 million for the
whole business and the 10% royalty you
asked for back to you.
I just love this whole thing. We're
about to make you a millionaire just
like that.
But I I I have three offers that I'm
kind of confused. I'd like to have them
a little bit more clear if I can.
The first offer was $500,000
for 20% equity. You're still the 80%
owner. and my partner Mark and I apply a
15% royalty just till we get our
$500,000 back. That's all. Then that
royalty, excuse me, before you start,
let me finish with one thought that's
going to stick in the back of your mind.
There's only two sharks here that have
ever sold a company for over a billion
dollars. I'm one, Cuban's the other guy.
All right, it's billions B. Everybody
else is an M. Millions. Small, big, big
difference. You want the billion-dollar
partners, not the small fry.
I've sold billions. I've sold billions
of dollars worth of product and still
doing it now, actually in Asia right
now. So, I have the offer of $1 million,
30% of the company and the same royalty
fee, but less than theirs, 10% royalty
until I'm recoup the money.
Joe, a fundamentally first difference in
the three offers is one is to sell your
whole business. My offer is $2 million
for the entire business. You get a 10%
royalty. You're the guy that runs it.
Any interest in selling the entire
business today, which is the road that
I'm trying to go down.
Not for $2 million.
Would you go to 4 million?
Um,
I would consider taking the very first
deal you were offered.
You own 80% of the company. We only get
20. All right. We're not pigs. We're
sharks. We just want our money back.
Is is is is that your final offer?
But think about it. We're leaving you
with 80% of the upside. So, you're going
to make a lot more than $4 million down
the road with us as partners.
I understand that. I understand. That's
why I I I haven't said yes. That's why
I'm
Joe. Are you going to sell this business
today or not?
Possibly. Very possibly. I believe that
um the 4 million is a little low,
but I think we're very close.
Um, I think if you went to $5 million
and 15%
and whether you want me as an employee,
which I would really like to to do as an
employee contract because I want my
royalty to be as much as I can. I can
get my mind around the four.
I can't go up to the five,
so I'm out.
Dang.
Listen, would you excuse us for a
moment?
Okay.
So, listen. It's a very simple
discussion amongst us.
Very often, the best strategy is to take
a competitor like you, even though
sometimes I find it distasteful. I say
bring him into the deal at our price.
Get him back out of this.
What do you think, DJ?
Uh, but we need to go up on the equity.
You guys wanted 20%.
That's interesting. Five, bring them in
for a third and go up to 20%.
No, no. I I think you gave away the
farm. You You It was so unclike when you
said 15% only until we get our money
back.
Once we bring Damon into our tent, we
we're the only offer left. We can change
our deal. So, what do you want to do?
Okay, before you say anything, you know,
the currents constantly change in the
rough waters of the shark tank. That's
why I love this place. Your enemies
become your friends. Your friends are
become your enemies. And sometimes they
bite you in the high and sometimes they
don't. So, what's happened is Damon has
decided to join Mark and I into one
offer. Now, it's great news for you
because there's going to be more money.
But I'm going let my partner Mark
explain exactly how great it is for you.
Okay. So, what we're going to do is
raise our offer to $750,000
and then we're going to ask for 30% of
the company and a 10% perpetual royalty.
That's our offer.
Um, I would consider your offer. I would
The only thing I would ask you to do is
if you go to 1.2 million for the simple
reason that will give me enough to fill
my first order. We don't have to do that
because if we own a piece of the
company, we're your partners and we have
to finance it, but we don't have to pay
for it right now.
If you need more money to fund new
orders and grow the company, you think
we're going to let our equity disappear
because we couldn't fund a new order. Of
course not. So, you get us without
giving up any more equity with this
deal.
Don't sell yourself short.
Joe, listen.
Joe, you got to say yes or no.
Life is like business. It's 20% what
happens to you and 80% how you respond.
You have a moment right now to take this
deal. Will you take it?
Does it come with season tickets?
Absolutely.
Then you got a deal.
Amen.
I didn't know you.
Congratulations.
Appreciate it. Looking forward to
working together.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
Good job.
Thank you. Great job. Pleasure meeting
you.
Think about that. That's remarkable. I
just offered a guy $4 million, which is
about as high as
That's the beauty of the show. This guy
we've never seen before walked in and
had the choice to be a millionaire
and he stuck with it.
And he stuck to his guns and he believed
in himself. That's what makes this
country great.
I feel warm and fuzzy. I just made some
money.
I would have to say to turn down $4
million was probably something I never
thought I'd say I did.