[Music]
Matt yeah check out this Tik Tok you
have good hygiene Matt look at that pose
and
everything I'm getting tired of these I
was driving one day on my way home a
poth so big that I broke a bone hit a
poth so big that I lost my phone hole
was so big that it straight the [ __ ]
around and drop
your good morning and welcome back to
another Wednesday Vlog Stern YOLO Vlog
Nation the time is now if you clicked on
this video do you want to know what that
means that means one thing that means
you're alive and you just made a
conscious choice and we are going to
collectively have a great day isn't that
right Matt I'm so [ __ ] right that's
so [ __ ] right he said
mm anyways Matt oh hold on this is the
shirt that I wore in the podcast that I
said I'm gatekeeping and everybody
thought I was making thermals this is
from Target get your head out of your
ass oh my God
okay good morning itchy bum no I just
[ __ ] crazy I I still feel like I got to
go what up man good morning I love to
see Matt awake it's so rare when I come
up here and Matt's just fully ready to
go let see the time what time is it 3:00
you're shocked yeah I just love seeing
Matt awake and up and at him right Matt
dude people still think I'm dead no way
I got like nine text this morning are
you alive are you okay like [ __ ] off oh
my God [ __ ] off yeah for those of you
that don't know what I'm talking about
someone started a rumor that I like died
in a car accident and [ __ ] and it just
bothered me cuz I'm like bro what if my
mom saw that and I had to call my mom
and say if you see anything on the
internet of me dying in a car accident
it's not true and it's like sad that I
had to do that and like have a whole
conversation with my mom because like no
people she SE that St twins we'd still
be the sternol triplets Chris would be
dead and then no what else I we are
moving on I refuse to put this much
attention onto this basically ever since
we went to the zoo forever ago Matt's
ankle has been consistant pain and he's
yet to do something about it so today
we're taking a group trip as a vlog to
urgent care and we're going to figure
out if Matt has been walking on sprained
ankles for about you want to know I've
been I'm talking to some of my friends
that are in med school and such and I've
been thinking like if you had like a
broken bone or a sprain or something
you'd know already and it's been so long
correct and I feel like there would have
to be like severe impact for that to
happen I guess I'm going to guess you
have like if you tore something it's
going to be like a ligament or like a
muscle or something and that's the
problem awesome
yeah let's hope you don't have like if
you had something s like chop your leg
off severe you wouldn't even be able to
stand right now correct I know that
that's why I've been hesitant to
go I'm talking about dude I'm pissed we
missed 7-Eleven For Your Own Cup Day I
just keep thinking about it I'm so sad
hello dude we were with literally I want
to say like 10 PE we were with like 10
people that we had never met before at a
meeting and stuff on 7-Eleven cup day
whatever we were out of the house like
strangers are around us and every 10
minutes Chris is like did you guys know
that it's 11 fill your out on cup day
I'm like you're a loser not I was
telling everyone he's telling everyone
people we don't know like this guy like
held a door for us like do you know it's
7el whenever there's like a rare holiday
like that or like something holiday yes
it is it is a Day celebrated worldwide
guys I really don't want to make this
about me like I don't want to go to the
doctor oh that's such a corny thing to
say I know it wasn't about you until you
said that lame ass that's so basically I
customized this tie and I wanted to like
post Instagram I want to start being
more crafty cuz I'm a loser um you're
not a loser I love doing [ __ ] like that
so I made my own tie and I was like you
know what this is like what I enjoy
doing I want to start making content
around it so I was like Chris you have
to take my photos I want to make a Tik
Tok like making the tie and stuff right
so I made the tie I go out I find like a
nice tree stump I was going to like
Photoshop like a a dirt hole in the
ground and like like I was going to I
wanted to photoshop it more like edit it
but I didn't get around to it but I
wanted to take photos at this tree stump
and I was sitting at the stump and then
I went to like get up and turn around
but like when I got up I forgot that I
was like sitting on a stump when I got
up I forgot I wasn't on like ground
level anymore and I started like walking
backward thinking I was on the flat
ground still but there was like a full
step up behind me and I just he fell
over and it was so funny I spilled over
and I was recording and I go oh oh oh oh
oh like he was a little baby yeah Chris
is dying laughing just because the way
he reacted it sounded like a 5-year-old
was falling but it was me oh oh
oh your hand oh
yeah pull me
up believe you just fell it was so funny
what a good outro to that video it was
awful oh Matt you look so good
today I just love that shirt on you you
look so Dapper come on look at his ankle
look at his ankle oh are you like
limping bad head
[Applause]
up oh my God I was to hit him in the
head and he caught it I'm that was
amazing thank you I'm I'm highly
impressed that was insane that I went to
hit him in like the head with it the
[ __ ] Spider-Man grabbed it here I
don't want to hurt your ankle you want
me to help you down I can get down [ __ ]
I got stop let me help you
down ow [ __ ] you good you're going to
hurt your own ankle dude no I'm
not I think that's we can literally
leave yeah we can head out of here I got
you this is perfect I'll tell Chris and
then we can just meet him in the car'll
be good I'm so
confused I don't know why you're
confused oh my God what are you confused
about relax I'm
calm what is going on Matt literally he
he opens the door I'm like sitting by
the door and he goes Nick let's go and
just starts headed out I'm like I said
Nick you ready let's go I'm like there's
nothing else to he in the room for
minutes cuz I'm done what happened that
she said that it could be tendonitis
whatever the [ __ ] I don't even know what
it means but basically all the tendons
in your leg like your forearm or your
like shin and everything go down towards
your ankle and like there's a strip of
them right where I am having pain and
she said that I probably need to meet
with an ankle toe Specialist or ankle
foot specialist okay so there wasn't an
immediate solution correct cool
let's eat we at home with the drink um
Nick wanted canes Chris wanted Jersey
miks and I got a soda at both which is
kind of not the smartest thing but
whatever which one do you like more
they're both [ __ ] good oh yeah I
really you know you just
can't keep walking
[ __ ] thank you we just trying to
get that good camera angle
[Music]
got your
ankles like I hate when do stupid
[ __ ] got your ankles give me them
ankles boy L really not funny at all I
thought it was so funny I was like the
second we left I was literally thinking
that whole time I was like I need to get
a basketball and pretend to cross up
Matt and then tell him I got his ankles
all right guys that was today we didn't
really do much after Matt went to go get
his X-ray um we are going to go out
tomorrow we have some plans I'm going to
bed we'll see you guys tomorrow
[Music]
good
morning bro H the classic sleep posst
get
up
hey say good morning everyone welcome to
day two of the
Vlog say it Nick good morning everyone
and welcome to day two of the Vlog
yes I feel like you're normally a very
active wake uper hm like normally you
wake up you have something to do right
away not right now look at all the
little itty bitty sausages in the in the
pan look at the mini sausages in the
pan six little mini sausages in the pan
this one's
Nick cooking myself some breakfast Nick
please wiggle for the
crowd guys I just cooked myself a
scrambled egg and six sausages and I ate
everything and I have a full belly and
now Matt's eating his breakfast what do
you have
Matt it's quite clear to
see um It's peanut butter on a [ __ ]
rice
cake o good bite oh some crumbs do you
want some berries I feel like berries
you need to go to the doctor because you
you are Mr sniffle like as Mona
San you like a pig they can't hear you
you're behind the
camera do we have any nice berries do
you think
like what do you think is a good Berry
at the fridge I was going to say this we
have some like you're at the fridge
today's a beautiful day I just went
outside to put the trash out mhm and I
could feel the warm weather already like
just by
opening I really want a 7-Eleven Slurpee
I'd love to go on a nice walk with you
guys kind of want to go bowling I'm not
going bowling party in match bathroom
W go go Matt hey hey get a get a Nick
hey hey oh [ __ ] yes come on mouthwash
cam there's my favorite teenage boy I'll
kill you I wonder if they have slurp no
SL see later hey whoa well I'm also
looking for the the Skittles Littles but
I can't Matt they have no slurp
me oh yeah oh yeah you don't need a
gigantic disgusting laugh I'm getting
this [ __ ] for sure stretchy and tangy
stretchy and tangy you're [ __ ] I need
shav do I look gross yes yeah okay
please keep your beard what mat this is
kind of the vibe going for my room the
vibe for your room just Kermit doing
cocaine look at all the Vapes Vape dude
when I you should get a vape when I was
walking into the gas station there was a
dollar on the ground and is he pick it
up you picked it up wait Matt did you
actually yes see I didn't pick it up cuz
I thought it was like bait like I
thought someone was going to like pull a
string and I was going to get caught I
piced it first make sure there's no Coke
in in yeah no I thought I was going to
get like I thought it was like a prank
so I a poison a poison I was like I'm
just going to walk right by it cuz I
don't want to be like that guy that like
goes to bend over don't think anyone
cares really okay wait mat turn toward
me saw that it they need an edit moment
like seriously turn toward me like try
and eat it up you're an idiot yeah ooh
driver thaten like I'm not one to
criticize what someone else is eating I
think eat as at your own will but that
that banana Laffy Taffy is like
monstrous like that's a lot of just oh
God I didn't know you had the [ __ ] you
are fully voting that thing what did you
say about this banana Laffy Taffy
nothing Chris Matt what did he say did
you hear him I I block out everything
you guys say every second of the day oh
my God you're so negative oh my God
you're so negative shut up dude you're a
[ __ ] idiot Chris said and I quote let
me flip the camera so I can tell you
guys he said I am drooling banana all
over this [ __ ] like he's drooling from
The Laffy Taffy drooling banana gush
Daddy's
home we're looking for those are the
peach ones Peach what circles chis was
telling me the other day that Haro
doesn't make like actual C trolley oh
yeah idiot I wanted Skittles Littles but
they don't look around look around
there's a dead
[Music]
end they not slurpy here either this
song is like what is this the outro we
have to outro in here with this song
on disgusting disgusting
disgusting oh
my wait no frozen
lemonade that's not I don't like that
you can add the flavor in put the cup
under
it are you an idiot is this good try
it ew what is this
jaw like the Crimson Chin taking a sip
out of your [ __ ] SL what do you think
M I'm is pretty good this is delish
delish you're
gay guys I went to the other side of the
store they have what Chris was looking
for he just didn't see it so I'm going
to go show
[Music]
him kid is screaming yes you found them
where were they on the counter oh my God
such a good eye you're an idiot got
these for fun right cuz I was talking
about them with a friend the other day
how much does each gr 20 each how much
reach those obviously obviously I showed
her my ID that I can buy these right
uh-huh she if I didn't know any better I
would think you're 13 no she didn't
yep that's like the rudest thing ever
right I'm like I look 13 years old
that's crazy you have a [ __ ] like
facial hair dude imagine that that's
actually ridiculous I'd literally jump
on the counter stab her what up boy jump
around Presley You're an excited dog
Presley loves Matt
guys Mr PE those are Mr P Presley rate
Matt 1 through
10 you look so
proper with my friend Matthew 20 years
what did you realize I realized today
that I live with the two most annoying
people on planet Earth I literally alert
compl said to them that I want to get we
got like a we little me and Chris gotten
an argument that Matt wasn't even a part
of and he let it ruin his day
God guys I have to [ __ ] so
bad oh hey
Vlog what's up with your like Chris has
a chronic fake laugh the second a camera
turns on
he's that's no I don't it's my life you
have the worst laugh I've ever heard in
my life but it's real it's authentic no
it's not yeah the time you go that's my
real laugh no it's not have I ever
laughed and it not sound like that yes
never I like when you like he that's my
favorite what do you mean
like I laugh I also don't really
understand why everyone anytime you has
to [ __ ] or piss I know he like like
leave it in your [ __ ] head I know
like if you want me to go wipe for you
yeah let me know I do Matt I want you to
wipe real slow for me oh
my real slow is crazy why would you not
that want that to be best experience
seriously wi real slow like real slow
what I were ever getting my ass cleaned
I needed to happen as like instant let's
go snap snap um my ex my ex going to do
it to you my blah blah blah gooa gooa oh
wow that's a good lyrics this that me
espresso thinking about me every
night this that me
espresso all right guys well outro the
Vlog oh is that I Wanna Make You
M oh my God stop doing that what just
happened bro I don't even know how to
outro or intro Vlogs on YouTube like I
feel like it's such like a corny thing
like yeah you just watch that and then
you're just like seea like what happens
you know what what are you doing next
I've been bumped into numerous times
guys you know I was thinking the other
day I was like wow
our house is so boring and unfurnished
and ugly this is a sensual rice cake I'm
like no can I finish what I was going to
say I was just thinking I was like Wow
our house is boring ugly and gross and
dirty all the time but that's just
because we have so much fun that we
don't even want to focus on buying
furniture cuz it ruins time away from
our fun time you guys will see more of
our life when we post more of our life
so thank you for tuning in and thank you
for caring about us because we care
about you so peace out love you we're on
the road to 7 mil subscribers then 8
then nine then 10 and then everything
after that and everything right now stop
tapping your foot is a
blessing Jesus God what is he
doing
wow you got to do that again in like
those like high heel boobs the tap
dancing shoes anyway if you guys want us
to bring back the OG Vlogs let us know
we love vlogging our day-to-day life but
we haven't done it in a while I don't I
don't know
why want to get rice in their
faceing the opposite of what I I just
felt it land in my
hair there spit on the camera yeah why
do you think I got [ __ ] Dumbo the
elephant next to me his big ear is not a
big
snout trunk
[Music]