Next into the tank is Brian Spencer, who
believes his product can be the next big
trend in action sports. That is so cool.
Wow.
Hello.
Oh my god.
Dang. Wow.
Wow. Way to go, guys. Wow. Wow. That was
awesome. Hey guys, my name is Brian
Spencer. I'm the founder and chief test
pilot for Vertigo Pogo Sticks. And what
we're looking for is a half a million
dollars for 20% of the
company. All these kids and adults that
participate in things like BMX and and
motocross and stuff like that, they're
always looking for the next big thing,
the next sort of evolution of action
sports. This could be that thing. We're
going to show you a video right here of
some of the stuff kids are doing around
the world already. By the way, don't try
this at home. Uh, it's not something
that you should do unless you're
professionals like these guys. Let's
take a look.
Oh,
cool. Oh, that is so cool. Essentially,
what we've done is reinvented the pogo
stick. How many have you sold? Uh, we've
sold about 7,000. Nobody's injured
themselves. Hey, you know, skateboards,
people get hurt on skateboards. These
are uh deceptively safe. And I say that
because um you're not dealing with
speed. You're dealing with just going up
and down.
And what's the typical retail price?
$330. What's it cost to make it? Cost
about 100 bucks. Obviously, there's
other pogo sticks. There is a competitor
that uses rubber bands. The biggest pogo
stick company in the world, by the way.
They sell millions of pogo sticks every
year. We plan on replacing them as the
world's largest pogo stick manufacturer.
Is this a mass market product or could
you continue doing what you're doing,
selling three to 400,000 a year, but
making specialized more expens? Cuz
honestly, when you told me it was only
$300 as a specialty product, that seemed
cheap to me. The same reason why most
kids don't buy a $5,000 mountain bike,
you know, their parents buy them a $500
BMX bike. Um, in order to make money
with this, we do have to approach the
masses.
Why don't you stay in that space, own
it, make fantastic margins, and build
them in California and be happy with
that. I mean, a strategy where you want
to go compete and sell at toy stores and
have mass distribution is a completely
different business. Look, I'll just tell
you, you can be a victim of your own
success. I mean, when you're cool and
hip, I bring you down to a Mavs game. We
already are cool and hip, right? See,
that's the point. When you go mass
market, you lose a little bit of that.
to be able to maintain your coolness and
segregate into an entire different type
of company that goes mass market and to
do it with, you know, $500,000 only.
That's not an easy task.
Listen, you got billions of dollars of
investors on this side of these tables.
Everybody's in sync on the same place.
They don't see your vision for the low
end. What's the matter with you? As I'm
listening to you guys, uh I I I agree. I
It's hard not to agree. I'll tell you
what I want to see. I want to see the
price of these things go up by 100% by
$600. I keep telling people that and
people say, "No, you got to go mass
market, but I'm It's nothing short of a
miracle that some kid didn't get killed
on this already." Now, maybe I'm a
protective mom. Granted, I am. Well, if
it's not mother approved, that's good
for us.
I'm out.
Here's here's where I'm at. Once you
bring one of us in, especially this guy,
right? Then all of a sudden, it's not
about cool. It's not about anything
else. It's about cash. Well, coming to
the sharks, I was expecting, you know,
um for the mentality to be more mass
market. We got to sell a ton of these
things and make a million bucks. Even
worse, that's even worse. Be you. When
you try to please everybody, you end up
pleasing
nobody. That's why I'm out, right? I
don't want to crush the pogo guys. I
just want to make money. You should get
out there, bring out the boost at
$1,200. Every kid and his dog is going
to want one. They're going to figure out
how to sell their sister to buy it. and
you're going to make an obscene profit,
but I'm not going to give you $500,000.
I'm out.
I have to sound like the rest of the
guys. The product is great. You're doing
sales. You don't need us.
I'm out. Okay, Brian, you're the
ultimate and cool. Cool product. Your
hair is cool. You got the whole look.
Everybody's right. The minute you try to
go mass market, it's a guy in a suit
selling in Wall Street. I wish I was
involved in some way, but I'm out.
Can I buy that one before you go today?
Sure. Make you a special deal. 1,200
bucks. Yeah.
You're a shark. All right, Brian. All
right, Brian. Appreciate it, buddy. Good
luck with everything. Well, the Sharks
didn't give me a deal, but they gave me
some great advice. I love what they told
me about, you know, maintaining that
position as the creme de la creme in the
industry.