Space is here. This is not science
fiction. It's no longer rocket science.
Space is is an opportunity for a lot of
biotechs, opportunity for pharmaceutical
companies.
In the past, it takes about $50,000 per
1 kilogram experimentation. But with the
SpaceX, Falcon 9, if they launch
Starship, which is the latest vehicle,
it's going to be dropped down about
$500. 2030 will be the next milestone.
people live more than six months a year
in space because commercial space
station will replace international space
station. So it gives a lot of potential
and room for many people to utilize this
assets.
I think people need to start to think
about the space station as a laboratory
for doing research. As long as you have
a path, it might not be a FedEx truck or
a plane. This is a rocket that you're
sending to the space station. And it was
so cool that your product is on that
rocket. This is no longer a science
fiction. This is an opportunity to
really leverage a unique platform for
drug development and drug manufacturing.
[Music]
My name is Jack Lim, executive director
at Borang. Borang is a pharmaceutical
company. The way we are doing is kind of
age of a discovery from like 15th 17th
centuries that the European people
explore to different American
continents. I think it's the same type
of things. We are currently confined in
blue marble earth. But we all have our
mission to explore space. That's why we
providing our service as a
pharmaceutical but also looking at space
as new growth opportunity as a business
wise but also provide the right solution
for humans exploration in space as well.
NASA commissioner Bill Nelson said
rockets runs on fuel. NASA runs on
inspiration. That inspiration will lead
more and more people to space. That's
why we are here. We need to be ready to
send people to space safely. That's what
all carrying space is all about.
Humans in space challenge is about the
uh open innovation global challenge
program. We are actually trying to
discover the novel technology who
actually providing the business service
as a startup company and also the
researchers who's willing to send their
experimentation in space in terms of
biomedical space healthcare. So we see
the space as a new opportunity but we
didn't know where to start in the
beginning. We started contacting with
all the expertise all over the world.
Luckily I got in touch with one of our
alumni who is actually the ex astronaut
in NASA and also professor in Georgia
Tech and I asked a lot of questions and
we did a lot of the zoom meetings back
then and then she kind of help us to
frame what type of problem we should
solve. We kind of divide into two
scopes. The one sector we call critical
problem in space which is we're trying
to solve the healthc care issues for our
future astronaut in space. The human
explorer in space there's going to be
many health issues that we occur from
human body and we're trying to solve
that problem first and second one we
trying to we call the critical problem
on earth which is using space
microgravity condition to solve many
different kinds of health issues on
earth such as cancer or aging related
issues. So mainly we have a two scope to
solve the problems through our humans in
space challenge and then luckily got in
touch with NASA HRP the human research
program they actually study very similar
type of problem they were trying to
solve when you think about NASA we
automatically think that they're going
to have all different type of solutions
right we saw their current work in terms
of the human exploration and how human
body risk in terms of low earth orbit or
lunar and Mars are different kind
condition when you send people to Mars
it takes at least like six months and so
during the time period of course there
are many things you should be considered
in that case NASA didn't even know how
to solve that problem so even NASA
doesn't know the problem then there
might be something that as a commercial
company can contribute the value with
all different kinds of the people all
over the world but as a commercial
company we can we are more flexible
working on this type of initiative so we
luckily got in touch with them and then
they became one of our judges in 2022
and then the partnership kind of
escalated. We uh get in touch with the
Stanford, MIT, Harvard Medical School.
Everything just starts kind of hard in
the beginning. The main reason that how
we started and how we actually be able
to connect with all these you know very
prestigious partners is because nobody
started this type of initiative before.
[Music]
We can actually use not only just
research test bed in space but there's
actually company who's trying to use as
manufacturing platform. One of my
favorite company called the lambda
vision. They actually developing new
artificial retina in space.
Lambda vision participated in the human
in space challenge in 2023. We had to
come up with a pitch competition and we
pitched in front of a a large audience.
You know people came by and and talked
to us at our our individual booths. We
were a winner that year that supported
us to do some additional research in
microgravity. We were really excited
about the results that we got from space
because what we're showing is that we
can actually get a more even stable
product. What we did is we took a those
open beaker experiments. You cannot fly
open solutions on the International
Space Station. Flew that in a box. So
the box that we're flying is about the
size of a shoe box. I didn't think it
was possible. It's just wasn't first
thing on my my brain. There's actually
some of the case that some of the
startups they haven't thought about
applying their current prototype model
to kind of apply to space. They never
thought about that. But space will be
you know kind of next opportunity for
them to develop kind of long-term phase.
Our main road is we connect the right
teams to right partners so that they can
send their R&D and research to right
platform. When it comes to fund we have
a different model like one equity state.
We actually invest their equity in the
company but at the same time we also
investment model called orbital launch
funding which we cover their space
launch cost for their specific
experimentation. The people who apply
those program we have a right procedure
for our judge process. So each
individual judge they actually review
each individual applicants and then
mostly equity state companies obviously
we see them as a investment opportunity.
So our venture capital partners also
looking at taking a look at that company
as a potential for the investment. I
mean running our business initiative is
a very smart way because we only invest
like $100,000 for startup equity but at
the same time we connect with your most
space agency like NASA European space
agency issa
we supported them through the funding
and two we have our internal own
accelerator program it's called humans
and space accelerator program we are not
space company we're not fully expertise
of space healthcare but we know how to
create actual the platform that we can
connect right people with our right
partners not only just the research
level but also the uh the platform and
utilizing space environment for those
people as well.
This is a really good time to get
involved and and we're also building
something from the ground up doing a
blueprint of of the future in 10 20
years. You're you're being pioneering
not just what you need today but what
are you going to need in 5 years? What
are you going to need in 10 years? Where
do you think the industry is going to
go? When you're doing new things it can
be very challenging. It doesn't always
feel like you're doing the right things,
but if you're stagnant, you're not going
to grow.
One of the thing that I realized running
the program was how individual
researchers and startup actually work on
different kinds of problems when it
comes to space exploration also trying
to solve the problem on earth. We saw
how they are scattered, how they are not
be able to connect each others because
each individual technology and research
has a lot of values and potential but
they just don't know how to connect with
right partners. I think we have a pretty
good network in terms of all the
prestigious university level and also
space agency level historically conduct
numerous space related research before.
So we can make sure that connect the
right people who is a very kind of
similar research experiments with our
expertise.
One of the great things though about
being part of these challenges are the
people that you meet. The only way we're
going to be successful is if we all work
together. In order to do something very
very bold, very very visionary. You need
to have a lot of thought leaders in a
room working together to accomplish
that. So many of the people that I met
during that experience uh we still are
sharing ideas every place that I've gone
the energy from the other entrepreneurs
uh the excitement in the space that also
helps to keep you going. When people
talk about space, it's um very
complicated. It's very difficult concept
to understand. But the International
Space Station, it's actually built 1998.
It's about 20 years from now. The way
we're trying to have the space
healthcare ecosystem, not only just
running the humans in space challenge,
but actually we trying to secure the
right infrastructure to provide the
experiment service platform. It's not
like a new concept. I think it has been
established from ever since
International Space Station built, but
there's no one actually trying to play
the way we're doing it. So that's I
think a pretty big value.
Don't be afraid to take the risk. Be
bold, be visionary. This is a very uh
you know pivotal time for for space
research. But I would also tell them
that opportunities in space are not just
for scientists and engineers. Right now
there are opportunities in space for
people developing space suits for people
sewing in space for insurance in space
hotel and hospitality anthropology in
space. Where you start might not be
where you you end. I think the most of
startup they change their business model
very frequently but I think um space
will be you know kind of next
opportunity for them to develop kind of
long-term phase. I want those startup
out there to look at space as a new
opportunity or testify or apply your
current business model or your current
technology in space. Everything that
we're doing it's pretty much like a
first step. Space healthcare is a very
rare topic but at the same time we are
leveraging healthcare society to break
into space economy space industry is
obviously intersect between two industry
in one program together.
I don't think
[Music]