hey guys
hey oh [ __ ] I dropped my phone
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
[Music]
it's just me
um this is really really weird but after
VidCon Matt and Chris went to Summer
Smash and I stayed in VidCon and went to
Disneyland for two days and then I
stayed home alone for two days while
they were in Chicago doing their thing
so now I'm finally going home to Boston
I'm catching my flight in an hour hey
everyone me and Matt are in Boston
Massachusetts the Big B but I haven't
seen Minecraft in four days and it's the
longest we've been apart so I'm really
really confused by it like it's just
like a really bizarre feeling because
it's like literally since I was born
this is the longest I've been without
Matt and Chris but I'm excited to head
to Boston and I don't know what their
apps too but
I will see them soon happy that they're
in any random MC parking lot right now
back in their Mick Hometown making mixed
jokes and make content together back
where they make belong
it's like the good Mickle days anyway
the last three days me and Matt were in
Chicago
uh for summer Smash and Nick didn't come
and it always feels weird when one of us
isn't there and before because it's such
a rare citizen says that Nick didn't
come from his own well-being he didn't
want to be there himself that was his
decision nobody else's yeah bro he had
the time of his life just staying home
so Nick's flying we got VidCon in Disney
he wasn't even staying home no for real
I was out and about anyway me and Matt
been home for a day we landed this
morning and Nick comes in tomorrow
morning so we just thought it would be
funny since we didn't see him for a few
days that we're just gonna make make it
seem like we we're gonna make his return
seem like way big idea and Nick Nick
knowing him like this is the exact type
of [ __ ] that Nick absolutely hates he
hates scenes he hates anything that's
like GIF related or anything like you
don't even open gifts on Christmas like
with like more than three people in the
room this should be fun so
Frank we got two things of streamers and
confetti poppers I need to find balloons
like I want like the classic blow up
balloons but I can't find anything is
this a big sign
I'm gonna go welcome home bro we can
make it they get the paper and the
markers over there yeah let's go
paint okay paint yeah we're not doing
that no [ __ ] no
oh does it only bro
do you get a template no it's kind of
worth no it's not oh what it's a waste
of money get one piece of paper
oh my God bro this [ __ ]
you're just killing me there's no one
I'm the one oh
well don't do that I'm the one there's
only a 10 pack so you can figure it out
okay grab it you stupid idiot get some
tape as well the 10 pack no the [ __ ]
11 pack
so we got wall safe well safe do you
want to be well safe yeah oh it is wall
safe I literally said that as like I
thought that's what you read I didn't
even read it no I'm for real I'm wanting
something goofy bro something he's gonna
laugh at the like the um
oh the Superman bag could be so funny
but it's small I'd be like you're my
superhero and I couldn't wait for you to
be home
okay let's pick something else the green
machine
put it in the bucket kid you're gonna
what are you doing put it in all right
okay why are you folding it like that it
won't fit in the [ __ ] bucket okay
well you're just like breaking the
product
let's do some light compression socks
let's not put those back hi bro that'd
be so funny
oh we gotta go to the little kids
section
toys we gotta get them like this thing
what paddle ball yeah
what what else oh my God 7.99 for that
oh wait he's playing with that [ __ ] at
the other that's not 7.99 worth though
why'd you say it like that 7.99 worth
it's not that get them that drawing the
Buzz Lightyear one where over there over
there right there right there
ten dollars
kid he'll enjoy it oh the princess one's
better whatever oh yeah get him that I'm
using that princess one after God damn
for sure okay let's get some candy for
him
he's the sweetest foot human so he gets
two of those
he hates Whoppers so I might ironically
get some no that's just a waste of money
let's go I'll eat them okay then go for
it no we won't it's a waste of money I
don't know bro look for oh twin Snakes
get two bags
[Music]
he loves goofy stuffed animals too bro
what
I'm not about to be that guy and make
them unlock the cans also that's crazy
Nick you saw I tried to get you a candle
it didn't work warm or Birch Woods damn
he would have got you warm Birch woods
and Woodland path damn all right let's
go to the Dr Pepper well
sweetest fish I mean twin Snakes Twin
Snakes
two Swedish fishes he loves these little
banana things banana that's crazy he is
so late I'm tired little wax bottle for
the baby
coloring book
I told you we should have got the
Superman bag yeah
but whenever and we got two Dr Peppers a
little paddle ball and that's it there's
this little gift bag for sugar cane all
right now it's time to we'll decorate
yay we're gonna make the sign and then
we're gonna put the strawberries right
there because the Dr Peppers oh that's
what I'm saying what the freak happened
we're going to make the sign put the
streamers up and and what is this
confetti oh wow confetti poppers yeah
okay so I guess we're gonna light these
things up too all right we'll be back
when the sign's done
hold on
it's a gift card you got from Christmas
I'm putting it in that bag
Starbucks gift card and be like oh we
got you 15. all right
two different signs will be made one to
hang up on that wall or that wall
whatever and then one to bring to the
airport to show how much we missed him
gonna say
well
does it have two l's bro welcome
what are you carrying over I'm not I'm
spelling it okay
see how I mean
it's a small home for a big welcome
ugly assign
okay you're an idiot you're an idiot
okay
really bad
okay we're good and then we got the one
for their we we missed you and then
let's add some color
kind of looks like him really yeah
not anymore
what did you write
you're my sunshine okay
are you writing my only sunshine no just
that you are my sunshine
my back hurts bro we just found a car
accident okay
right yeah I think I think tomorrow you
and me both need to like prop up a
camera do them at the same time in here
or at least one of us okay yeah I have
three yeah
yeah I think I'm doing now
to test it and so that there's confetti
on the floor already yeah no I agree
why is it not
he looks down at it and Pops like in his
face
to use rotate base and direction of
arrows yeah that's what I'm doing
okay
yay very good that's perfect awesome now
it's all confetti
he's gonna be so happy
once you leave take a left and walk all
the way down like you'll see me try like
trust me you'll see me in a second
oh I swear to God I saw it
[Applause]
I made you a sign
[Music]
yay
hurry up
we miss you
we miss you you are my sunshine you're
not real
you're not my Clash of Clans grind
you wouldn't believe it let's go
what the [ __ ] is happening I'm just
going to go get lotion
that's so awkward I'm like walking
through the house of lotion why is it
not going my shoulders are dry yay
[Applause]
they're like you need to sing this house
thanks I'm so happy you wouldn't think I
fought in the War
we set it up for you
do you like it wow
we wanted to surprise you with a gift
wow
oh awesome look at it
nice and what is this it's a it's a look
and find okay Disney princess okay
nice a gift card yep what are we doing
you're acting like it's my birthday
I'm just like I don't even know how to
react because this is so bizarre like
why
because you're gonna tell him no okay
what
what are you talking no leave it well
I'm trying to look it for what you're
talking about nothing there I don't know
what he's gonna be saying candy soda
oh that wasn't anything
welcome home
thank you
what am I supposed to be looking for
Matt nothing okay you're gonna hit one
this is unreal I did not expect this I
really thought that the games were over
at the airport this is crazy what am I
looking for nothing no stop being
[ __ ] annoying maybe you're like oh
should we tell them like what am I
looking there's nothing there
ew what is that everything we got you
well I don't know oh no Nick look
it's going through
it's what goodies
your favorite like you love twins yes
yes
Nick look we got you like your favorite
things oh no I love it I just thought
that you guys were like I thought that
you guys were all booting into something
to figure out the only thing that's
extra and I just told Chris this 15 was
for Mom and Dad on Christmas and I just
took it from that bag and put it in yeah
I was like the gift cards
that was the only part that I was like
there's no way this is like really
strange
I can't see you ruined my decoration
already because I'm taking a nap and I
don't know the [ __ ] feeling on the
spider web
the [ __ ] doesn't work so it's gonna be
easier when there's no streamers
my flight was horrible I'm already kind
of like saving the details for a car
video because I have a lot to complain
about oh God
dude that [ __ ] doesn't work okay yes it
does you just have no strategy
to believe
who's Flareon keychain is that Justin
got it for you I love it you honestly it
says Abigail on it he was dying laughing
that's nice
Abigail from Abigail I just walked in
here I was really caught off guard but I
do I'm very thankful did I did I um was
my Clash of Clans comment no I I thought
that you were taking a photo of like I
thought there was like a new update in
me like a photo because I knew you were
taking a photo or video but I did not
know that it was going to be to this
so you thought Clash of Clans had like a
cell phone he goes I'm back in my like
Clash of Clans like he didn't if he
didn't because I was holding my phone
sideways he didn't speak I would have
honestly
just walked right by you
okay Chris
dude I'm so tired but like this is crazy
thanks so much I love the confetti that
was a really nice touch
I liked when it like went everywhere
like you were doing it I think you're
gonna have a lot of fun cleaning it up
later
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
for my brothers