do a check actually can you go check the
rest I checked just go go check because
Chris sucks at it he doesn't even check
if it's in Focus respectfully
and all the things
all right today we're not running with a
topic we're just gonna speak freely and
see how it goes it's kind of scary
no it's a gumball not gummy
oh oh it's overflowing
if someone's just watching that's crazy
it's super sour gonna blow your face
is he accurate
this really puts my hair on your chest
he'll blow your socks off I just heard
someone say they're gonna blow your face
off I haven't heard that phrase since
like 2011. so we just said that I got
major flashbacks all right go ahead if
you eat this without making a sour face
I'll give you my blueberry little bites
at lunch tomorrow
no actually like Cosmic brownie in my
teeth and I can't have adult video oh is
it bad no it's a regular smile
yeah I get that better
you look pretty
okay I'm good really ugly okay
did you make us have a face were you
working to pay attention
can I get a sip of the Pepsi please I
think next time you go on a tour we
should manipulate one of the mics to be
like super different voice like imagine
if Matt went out and he was like just
sound like a little girl
I thought we were gonna manipulate the
mics to sound like different voices no
like that's what it would be that was my
joke
oh
because he's a little girl good [ __ ] all
right let's get into this no idea okay I
have a great random thing to bring up to
start off this video okay that's gonna
pee himself laughing am I when Chris
used to give us foot massages
sticks and mango motion I remember this
bro what the [ __ ] are you saying oh
Christie's throwing me like a masseuse
or something no he didn't want to be he
was just trying to make it I was trying
to make money I'll rub their feet we had
like I think our grandma gave us like
five dollars and Chris was like offered
like foot massages for like a dollar
that was a hustler that's some dirty he
had like a piece of like I never do like
splintered fireworks
rub it between our toes and it would
like Splinter oh my God it was so funny
like I just I thought of this I was
thinking it was like just the funniest
[ __ ] that Chris used to just like
because it was this mango lotion too do
you remember I remember I remember when
Nick got an easy bake oven for Christmas
I I never had an easy yes you did it
it's literally on camera Nick opened an
easy make oven and my mom like didn't
want to like exclude Nick so she wrote
like to the Boys and Matt was so
embarrassed that he got the easy way
government
it was like to the boys Matt goes what
Nick wanted it and like walked away I
have to find that video I've been
feeling really Primal lately Primal I
just wanna
that's terrifying what do you mean by
that oh no I just feel in touch with my
old people ancestors like I can just
like isn't it pretty talented like cake
and stuff
caves yeah they just they happen
naturally so I don't know what no like
writing in them
you mean you mean engravements and stuff
so wait what are you asking us yeah
whatever bro you all know it's crazy I
could really picture Nick in a choir
I couldn't really like belting it out
like front row okay like he's surrounded
by all his hands no like do you know how
they all have the same outfit he has
like the one unique color so like
everyone has white on and say he has
like the green yeah
I'm trying to think about it and I
really can't
you wanna know what what's a little
funny to me what you know how like Apple
products are always changing their their
Chargers and stuff so that when you
upgrade your phone and you gotta look at
the different wire you know like drills
and screwdrivers and stuff yeah why why
didn't they make all one drill
because like why maybe they did why so
why make funny why make I don't find
this funny but why make some of them
they're all all drills change
why make some flat heads though like
screwdrivers like why make some of the
screws flatheads and then some Phillips
heads because at the end of the day
you're screwing in no matter what so
what does it matter the grid they should
have just made one universal
thing
no oh
get out of here what am I what's going
on sniff it I took carpentry for four
years Chris I don't want to sniff your
[ __ ] hand I put lotion on I smell
like vanilla okay put your hands down
sniff it no I'm not [ __ ] sniffing
your hand for real do you ever like the
feeling of like falling asleep
not falling asleep falling like in your
sleep like you know when you're like
laying there you're like no I kind of
like it sometimes that's so weird
like it feels good sometimes I feel
really sad before I go to sleep
I feel like everyone feels sad that's my
saddest moments is like two minutes
before I fall asleep well I feel like
everyone and my mind's just like yeah
you're so sad but you're so
you're so upset and you're so tired that
you lay down to like fall asleep but
then you're just genuinely so upset that
you lie there comfortably for two
minutes but your body doesn't let you go
to bed and they just open your eyes and
like stare to the wall yes that's
something that really just pisses me off
what and I'm gonna be fully honest here
you ready he's gonna be fully honest we
better brace for impact put your arms no
if I get if I get a bag of chips a bag
of chips
baggy chips isn't a good example no let
me think hold on no no no
do you know that there's a desert lizard
called the thorny devil really yes I
want to meet him
serving size 160 calories for six oh
it's [ __ ] tell me what's in the
whole bag correct I want to know what
I'm getting myself in and at least be
real with the service be honest
I'm serving size like two and it's like
gushers the Pop-Tarts blows my [ __ ]
mind they put the serving size for one
of the two Tarts like bro come on well
most people actually a lot of people
wait is it called a Pop Tart or is it
one would be like a pop or one would be
a Target okay they'd be Pop-Tarts or
Pop-Tart but is it like a strudel or is
it like a Pop-Tart you don't even know
what a strudel is so that didn't answer
your question well like what is a
Pop-Tart like what is it it's a Pop-Tart
no like if it's if you were describing
someone who never had a Pop-Tart before
what would you say it is I think it's
like a frosted piece of like pastry
frosted pastry it's a strudel no because
the strudel's a brand it's like calling
a tissue a Kleenex no it's not I don't
get that strudel is food
no it's toaster strudel I don't think
strudels anything but toaster strudel
that's [ __ ] because it's a strudel
kid he's a toaster strudel
I'm pretty sure he's Swedish now
is that Swedish what does he say bomb
flaky
I do not like any of that yeah
I feel like there's only one
circumstance where you're allowed to
judge somebody and and it's whatever
their contact name it is for their
mother birth giver Mama Bear is crazy oh
my god I've never seen that Mama Bear's
insane I've seen a mama bear with a red
heart and the bear Emoji oh my God
it shouldn't be anything you call your
mother
mine's mom mine's mom mine's mom but
like you shouldn't put your contact as
anything you wouldn't call your mom
I wouldn't put it called like rear view
mirror because I'm not gonna call her
that well nobody's here no
nothing it's like it's like are you
gonna go home
that's the only way you could judge
people I think there's far we can judge
people about other than their contacts
yeah I think there's like ow [ __ ] I
just almost broke my finger I put my
hand here and then I need like at the
same time you're so stupid but no I
genuinely do think that that's the
second time I hurt myself in the car
um
okay how long would you have to be
dating somebody to just drop a [ __ ]
right in front of them in front yeah I
don't think I could I don't think my
body would let me look they're in the
bathroom with you and you dropped a
stinky like wait like in a relationship
wise is that what you're saying so I
didn't get that would be the whole
question yeah
God oh man
ew Chris that's such a mad thing oh man
crazy one
it's crazy
I said this in a car video before but I
think it's so important though it wasn't
gonna be in a plane crash it needs to
happen right during takeoff I agree like
imagine you seamlessly get through an
entire flight and it's like a 12 hour
flight to like a foreign country and as
the plane is landing it crashes well
most of the time I'm playing crashes
it's on takeoff or Landing so it's a 50.
yeah but it's like bro it's like you
never really we're gonna crash once
you're in the middle of the air it's
like really bro she's like imagine
you're in like first class and like you
just got served your drinks and then the
plane crash and there's like drinks I
think natural disasters are crazy that's
what I say I think it's crazy that like
an earthquake can just like Rumble like
if you see a drink like like my first
initials who's tapping their foot
foreign
have to like take a second and be like
okay like I'm a person watching this
movie like I'm not a part of this at all
oh well that would mean they're doing a
good job backing it out
okay whatever
bro
okay I'm scared of you Nick's the type
of guy to order a pizza five minutes
before New Year's I'm like I ordered
that last year
I would never do that
my humor genuinely has been more like
complex than silly jokes like that okay
all right just saying please wizard
you're an idiot no that's way more you
think I think I've seen Chris come out
of the bathroom once the ball is dropped
said I've been shooting for a year I
think he does that every year
you always don't bro you do something
like that you're the first person to
make the oh since last year Joe yes you
are so Nick hasn't complained since last
year
it's not true also what in what
circumstances would you say that
you're so silly take it out of here I
want to experience at one point in my
life an earthquake yes but like on
another topic
oh yeah like we're sitting here watching
y'all Gotta Give me some wow everyone
just get loose everyone shake shake
shake shake everyone
let me know when y'all are ready go man
okay you ready I'm ready I want to
experience an air mattress air mattress
not an air mattress a water mattress
sorry waterbed yes water mattress like
get it right bro all it did it was two
words trying to think sorry you started
vocal exercises
shook it out like me and Chris said you
would have had that thought processed
totally disagree because I had it before
I was in shut up for that you only gotta
right say it
say it
sometimes they like mix oh my God
I'm quitting I think I I'm never looking
at you again if you did that to me all I
did was below yeah and I got [ __ ] wet
with spit and that's not true yep bro
who said Abracadabra first and why is it
so [ __ ] perfect like
Abracadabra and something changes her I
just can't believe that stuck around
usually Abracadabra something someone
was saying like you make fun of them and
they like lose it you know what is
Abracadabra mean it's like a Alakazam
like it's like it's like one of those
words that just like leads to like
mystery it sounds it leads to Mysteries
it sounds mysterious as [ __ ] I feel like
they should use it in court then what is
it again Abracadabra no cause Court
you're trying to find out the truth this
is all fantasy we have a big Abracadabra
on our hands totally wrong contacts I'm
gonna start listening things that Nick
just bothers me we're gonna start
listening things that bother me about
you go ahead never let anybody else get
their point across okay because you
can't know how to speak just talk too
slow speaking I can't even hear you okay
let me go you ready next the thing oh
that wasn't a list that was only one
thing I hate that you can't even finish
one thing you commit to I'm gonna say a
bunch of things that Chris bothers me
said one
stupid ass I it's crazy when like TV
shows or like movies
so it's more entertaining that TV shows
and movies like come up with made up
like terms or words or names just for
that
thing
I think I feel like I've been turkey I'm
gonna throat puncher yeah
dude that's it ah yeah look at you yeah
it's like the grounders from um
the 100 when they're like oh my God yeah
we should get an ASL trans fictional
stop touching my nipples
God I [ __ ] hate when you poke my
underarm bro you know like bro I'm
actually wrong I'm gonna actually
[ __ ] knock your [ __ ] do you wanna
know what's something important to me is
what my vital organs
this is all what you need to protect do
you know why hey stop you know when
people are fighting
ow okay buddy
okay we're gonna actually get
demonetized please don't hit each other
do you know when most of the time when
something crazy is about to go down most
people go like this because they're
protecting their vital organs everything
you need in Love Is Right in here I just
do that because I don't like it they
can't in my arms if I do that either
okay let's test it out get outside
I'm angry I can't
I can't do you have any other thing
other things I smell lotion you're
making everyone else smell it 20 minutes
ago [ __ ] you that's why I don't use
lotion it feels like a [ __ ] sticky
rabbit right now get off my [ __ ] oh my
God bro oh my God we should each make an
unreleased karate move or Jersey
unreleased karate move yeah you guys
need to stop hitting each other the
video's gonna get taken down
I'm not looking out there because this
is your unreleased yeah move it would be
the snap attack yeah it doesn't
but I think that's it snap above the
head they're like what are you doing
oh my God if I ever punch somebody
that's a better name than snap attack
what you should have said the mistletoe
like oh look the mess
I love that butter eggs come in dozens I
feel like it should be bread why what
bread instead
[Applause]
I don't like that like do we only have a
term for dozen is 12. do you all know
what I hate like why is like half dozen
six stupid yeah and then [ __ ] two
dozens a Baker's dozens 12.
it's gonna still be 12. oh I don't think
so it's not a Baker's Dozen still 12.
what's a baker's dozen
13. 13
oh cause the bakery probably gives you a
little extra yeah
it's so cute that's like a cute little
thing that I got a nickname The Baker's
Dozen shout out to nice but here's a
dozen and here's the baker's dozen for
being such a kind customers
it makes it a bigger
Baker
if I gave you 12 cookies and then gave
you an extra it becomes a Baker's
daughter no yeah
correct no you said here's here's
yourself cookies and then here's
a dozens
okay here's a dozen and here's the extra
one you know the classic Baker's lesson
no I agree you're the one throwing out
25 Donuts so I left this when you start
talking about Baker's dozens I'm out of
this conversation first I left this one
shut up
Nick why don't you give us something
what's your favorite soup I [ __ ]
don't like you what's your favorite soup
I don't like soup I love your ass Nick
what's your favorite cheddar ooh stinky
yeah I know what's your favorite what's
your favorite what's your favorite soup
me we don't care
there you go
you guys have strained the energy out of
me what's your favorite word
[ __ ] you that's how to say bro
what's your favorite vowel
although I think I think Chris Hunter I
think you'd be like the worst at ever oh
yeah actually no no sitting still like
relax your guys both of you guys yeah
you're funny both of your guys is like
let's do math okay read it I love you
guys I'll see you next coming up with
content that's a good one working yeah
joining a meeting yeah
let's think what else give me another
one not sleeping till 12. I love
sleeping until 12. okay what else
hey what is he doing hey big yellow
banana peel get back in here get in here
what am I saying
both of your guys's personal hell would
probably be having to play Wheel of
Fortune I love you guys would both be
[ __ ] awful at playing The Wheel of
Fortune that's all I have to say yeah
what are we doing with this switch back
and forth thing
that why I don't know I didn't like oh