dude are your scabs ever itchy like I
don't pick my scabs I scratch them look
forward oh
and then what you're saying how you
missed
we had a lot of plans
okay it looks all right but that light
being out definitely affects like the I
know like we definitely gotta um what
the second light yeah
oh my god dude I've never seen a um uh a
car light like that out yeah like an end
here like dude the one you're talking Oh
I thought you I thought like put the
[ __ ] Pokemon go away he's gonna catch
this Onyx he thinks his Ash Ketchum or
something I am no you're not and another
lousy Pikachu Hunter oh wait in front is
it Hunter another plane like dude all
day today plane left and right it's
[ __ ] Plain City over here but you
know I don't have a Steelix yet
the Steelix yeah well you'll get one
what's your favorite Pokemon that was
really so beautiful you don't have a
[ __ ] stupid no get the Onyx hearing
and pine silver pineapple right all the
way Chris if you were to compare Matt's
head to one fruit what would you compare
it to like shape colors probably a
warped dirty watermelon That's crazy
dude people are gonna think that this is
scripted why people are gonna start to
think our content why because I have a
dirty warped watermelon why
because I thought that that's what you
were gonna say so I was like Nick if you
actually have that that's [ __ ] crazy
Chris
no [ __ ] way dirty
warped watermelon
it's about the that's actually that's
like the most that was the weirdest [ __ ]
ever that's the most triplet connection
like an apple or like a cantaloupe and I
was like
I was gonna say like oh I think it looks
like a watermelon then pull this I was
like no it's the witch from Oz
why was he just what
Nick recess
I don't know if you could see him
through the back window but that guy
just went by on a bike and was like
like he never stopped looking at our car
that was terrifying but look yeah Matt
no NYX literally said you guys he goes
you guys go to the car early because I'm
gonna grab something I don't want you to
see
and then and then he said that I didn't
even know what he meant for me to say
but that's crazy that I guess that yeah
that was pretty terrifying well there
really isn't that many fruits that are
like head shaped I guess but in fact he
said dirty warped and that's what I have
yeah I feel like I'm more cantaloupe
though so that's like a little upsetting
y'all ever been I feel like
a kiwi was enlarged I agree like an
enlarged kiwi I kind of [ __ ] with that
bro I wish they called me something you
always want a nickname yeah one of my
biggest regrets is not starting YouTube
with like an alias name like I hate that
everyone knows like my regular name that
like my friends calling me you know yeah
like I wish you guys called me something
different that then that well surgical
is something different as of today and
not tell the internet
okay stinky I was thinking big fart but
you got yeah you guys are really funny
no think of an actual fun one because I
know that that's something you've wanted
I feel like you're the way you should
start it is just entered like change
your username no why have the goddess
internet name ever okay start
introducing yourself well my youth my
Instagram like handle is literally just
my full name Christopher I could never
give that up I would if I felt like if I
felt like you and I was like oh I want a
different Alias I'd change it well my
middle name's Owen and I've always
wanted you're never gonna have people
call you something different if you well
my middle name's Owen and why are you on
your phone yo can y'all [ __ ] off this
guy's walking straight at us what is he
gonna do about it oh he's a big Vapor
keep walking Buckaroo the biggest red
flag of me I don't know if I said this
recently okay car video or not but I
wrote it down the biggest red flag for
me of all time is when it comes to new
people if you can't picture them
sad and alone
[Music]
like if you meet someone and you can't
picture them like sad and alone at some
point to some level that's a red flag
for me I disagree really I think if you
can't picture them sadden alone
everybody gets sad and alone so that
means they're just over compensating for
something which means they truly are
it's really sad no look
here I can remember like not being able
to picture them like sad and alone
even though they had this like sad front
constantly
and that's why I was like
hmm I don't even know what you mean bro
like if I can't picture someone I'm
gonna if I cannot picture someone's sad
and alone that's a big red flag what
about sad and together no I feel like
dude I'm always sad
whenever I'm alone no Chris yeah
garlic bread is easily yeah
yeah the thing that makes me the
happiest
like without questions dude did you see
the amount of garlic you put on it there
is ungodly I was I was like I literally
was sitting there at the kitchen just
minding my own business probably on
Pokemon go and Nick's just Nick's just
like this
doing the thing and then it's just like
it all pours out like on top
a little bit and like and like press on
the top so it like fell down like I like
waking up the next day and still tasting
garlic you don't you know that's [ __ ]
gross that's [ __ ] gross I'm kidding I
just wanted to see what you would say do
not brush your teeth you know I could
brush my teeth that's good I love
brushing my teeth actually people who
don't brush their teeth they're the
dirtiest of dirty and like they try and
like like little kids used to try and
get away with like not brushing their
teeth it's like you are you nasty little
hate brushing my teeth when I was
younger like around like 10. look that's
weird or 11. like I just hated brushing
my teeth like it was such a big deal so
Mom and Dad would like make me brush my
teeth and I would just run the water and
stand there gross I think it's [ __ ]
mind-blowing that I didn't say the word
[ __ ] till like senior year dude I was
thinking about like actually
mind-blowing because that when I just
said [ __ ] and then picture myself as a
10 year old kid
like no I thought well I should have
been cursing since I was like like we
didn't we never used to swear until we
were like
not even freshman year I didn't swear
until like junior year of high school I
remember the first time I swore to each
other in a conversation I think our
first YouTube video ever
literally one of our first YouTube
videos ever I probably my first swear
was probably like three months before
that
that's insane I'm I'm so for real put it
on my life God I see our old content and
I feel like I was so little
yeah but like where I was no I think my
least favorite thing that people that
like a comment I see is like there's 20.
it's like yep
yeah yeah and we're we're funny I look I
look the most different out of all of us
three and I let I fully have like for
real I think that I might take the cake
on that
I think you you or me he looks exactly
well I've always had the same hair but I
thought that [ __ ] was Zendaya like but
only the Spider-Man version guys like
the Mary Jane guys
yeah I feel like Baton Rouge is such a
good dope city name
with Baton Rouge Louisiana Indianapolis
Indiana we were talking about this the
other day because we were talking with
like old friends about school and I
remember I you know the states and
capitals there's 50 states obviously and
they all have a capital and we had to
like memorize the song and memorize them
all and I remember in fourth grade I
memorized every single one of them and
took the states and capitals test and my
teacher gave me a 49 out of 50 but it
was like the answers were matching so it
was a list
you had to get an even number score in
order to like even have taken the test
so I showed it to her and she [ __ ]
marked Rhode Island wrong I'm like
you're dumb as [ __ ] like you're [ __ ]
lousy bro get it together one of my
favorite terms wait I wanted to ask you
guys this question what's the max amount
of things you could cook while you're
hungry that you'd think you could eat
and then realize how much you made
wow you know what I mean hold on no no I
don't know what's the max amount of
things you could cook for yourself while
you're hungry and then realize you like
made too much
like you ever like me making [ __ ]
because there's any sense to you at all
honestly I'm trying to avoid the
question because I've been able to eat
like a [ __ ] hungry gorilla lately
like I could eat a lot like depending
the circumstances of what it is like
so you don't want to see me on the tour
bus at 2AM because I could put down a
lot of food you're a major little bite
guy oh my God no bites down like dude I
think the max that I've ever eaten in
one sitting is an entire box of
Cheez-Its which is crazy
I hate Cheez-Its I eat a handful of
Cheez-Its I dislike cheese and I'm back
inside a cup of water you don't like
white cheddar Cheez-Its dude why'd you
use the worst thing what were those
cheeses we ate on the plane the other
day so oh my God I thought I bought Matt
got like
beige burnt dude eyeshadow I thought I
got regular [ __ ] like
cheese it I thought I got cheese and
cheeses
it tasted like curdle milk
mixed up with like Feta cheese and just
that's repulsive were you guys doing Dad
literally we were talking I know exactly
what you're talking to Dad can I say it
first no no because I was there and I
know what you're gonna say I don't care
he's like you're not giving the
backstory though I'm [ __ ] about to
okay we were talking about a kid that
was at our school that's a weirdo or
like used to be a weirdo me and Matt
like and like it's not like [ __ ] up
listen it's not no it wasn't like making
fun of this it was like just like eat
dirt
okay no I'm not we call this kid a
weirdo and it's not like oh you're dude
you can't get mad at us
conversation that you have with your
friends you're like oh remember in third
grade when the kid like threw up at the
[ __ ] no he was eating dirt no Nick
listen whatever I'm not just giving them
a [ __ ] example
right here we were on a field trip no
not even field trip was like a kickball
tournament and he was playing
the kid that that we were talking about
was in the field and the balls I'm like
really trying to stand the balls right
like I was doing good girls weren't
getting kicked that far and he was on
all fours eating grass like a little cow
yeah and I was like and he was mooing
and he was mooing that's why he's a
weirdo yeah and then he would eat that
it's kind of like you just put hand
sanitizer on his hand and then pump a
squirt into his mouth whoa
whoa yeah me and Matt were just hated
that like we're talking about the other
day listen me and Dad were talking what
are the other me and Matt were talking
about it the other day no
why would you
like 9.9 adjustments
right now
there's people everywhere
go get away from me now I literally
sucker punched this [ __ ] into Oblivion
if she comes over here Nick don't say
that I would Matt what wait me and Matt
were talking the other day with dad in
the room right we were just talking
about weird people we went to school
then Dad goes oh I had a weird kid that
goes that went to school with me and
we're like oh tell us about it and it's
we thought he was gonna say something
that like matched what we were saying
like equally as weird like eat grass or
like yeah he goes yeah the the kid used
to watch like magic shows where the guy
would just Ozzy Osbourne I don't know
who this is I don't know who Ozzy
Osbourne is but apparently he did like
crazy [ __ ] in his magic shows and dad
said that the kid was like inspired from
that and at recess he ate a pigeon's
head off
he found a bit and grabbed it ate its
head off why your reaction was not great
enough for me well because I heard dad
say it kind of like a little bit from
the other one reaction the kid a bit a
[ __ ] pigeon's head off
the pigeon's head alive is a different
story if it was dead already in like
there's no what no I'm not there's no
like there's no like what [ __ ] don't
look at you you stupid [ __ ] there's
never an excuse to bite of awesome not
as weird but Dad said that the same kid
ate a water gun like the little water
yeah
like dude wait hold on wait I'm trying
to think like when you bite a pigeon's
head off that means the whole beak gotta
be in your throat dude it has to Die the
decisions beaked out of me he didn't eat
it no but like still like to bite
is that not terrifying oh my God I
couldn't move I wonder if he instantly
let go like the body yeah
girls that went to our school too and I
called them weird before in a video and
you guys yelled at me not to just in
case they saw it playing they were
playing with a dead pigeon no I remember
anybody that [ __ ] with animals and [ __ ]
like dead and stuff like grow up to kill
people
if you want to like [ __ ] her out with
little dead mice and [ __ ] then go be
weird but like you're gonna grow up to
kill people maybe like the odds are
highly dude steer the [ __ ] away and if
you do that submit yourself all I know
is that if someone in your school is
killing animals and [ __ ] like don't be
friends with them but be chill with them
like yeah
you don't want to be on their bad side
but you don't want to go to their house
for dinner correct it's like for sure
correct today we should stage a fist
fight like if we know we get noticed by
a fan or something just like start
punching each other yeah just like hit
each other that's not a bad idea what I
don't understand like state lines and
how they have different laws like you
can buy sparklers or fireworks somewhere
and then drive it somewhere else all
about who's running the town because we
were all right
we stopped at a gas station and they
were selling like fireworks and
sparklers I get different states for
sure different cities is what throws a
wrench in my plan
not original not in your airplane in
like a lot a lot of people like your
mind pick your thoughts yeah it throws a
monkey it throws a monkey wrench in my
banana in my banana pudding
I like that like I like the monkey
wrench thing meter maid got to be one of
the like goofiest jobs ever it's kind of
it's like you imagine telling someone
you're a meter maid
I don't like the word made with that I
don't know I don't either
man it does sound like you're making fun
yeah it just sounds like you're taunted
I also think every single time we met
Chris at the airport which is pretty
frequently because we technically live
in two places I make fun of the pilots
while they're walking through the
airport yeah you've said this before on
the cupboard podcast I just I really
can't get I hate like bushes like they
just grow up like that that's a lousy
[ __ ] piece of greenery yeah it's like
get some sunlight do some photosynthesis
like just be bigger be bushier like
you're a [ __ ] you're you're an error
well I can see parking lot through them
yeah like you're a weak Bush grow up I
feel like it's weird that's a validating
there though yeah thank you that's like
I feel like a I feel like a bushel oh my
God this kid is sprinting
toward us no he's we're good holy [ __ ]
this guy's got speed this guy's got a
bus I'm worried what's going on yeah I'm
really scared whenever whenever anyone's
running with like a backpack it freaks
me out because you never know well he's
running with like a button-up shirt
khakis oh he's finally running up he's
running into the groceries oh what's
that [ __ ] oh he's going into the
grocery store oh they close in two
minutes oh he must have really needed
something everyone take a guess what he
needed milk but the way he's running it
looks like he's gonna miss something for
dinner no it looks like he's starving to
death right now and yes he's got like
30. no if it was this important he'd be
running to the hospital like it's
probably just gonna be like I don't
think he's even running Nick what dude I
don't even think he's running to get to
the store fast I honestly just think
he's one of those weirdos that like run
in the hallways at school but like never
slow down Nick used to run through the
hallways not true yeah not true I
remember
not true yes it is not true yes it is
not true not true and the reason I can
tell you why the one weird thing I
remember doing is I had one of those
like satchel bags like oh yeah the the
half the crossbody ones it was it was
actually kind of lit no it wasn't I
liked it I would have dude I really I
really hate I feel like talked about
this before but I hate that I was like
embarrassed of like bringing lunch box
to school hold on because I would always
just be hungry all day can I bring
something up real quick what we're in a
car video dude say what you want I think
there needs to be some type of middle
ground for like I think men need purses
women don't really have pockets well
nowadays people do like crossbody bags
they got backpacks I feel like bagware
is huge I agree it's a major way of
accessorizing I'm ripping the same
background do you have any nice bags I
actually have a purse technically do you
the black bag that I carry around oh I
like that I feel like it's necessary
like I want like your bag like I like
your bag okay this is crazy well
reverting back because I'm unentertained
um everything I do is just
unentertaining not true
you got the whole Squad talking about
each other's bag no I'm not no but I
just it's honestly not that I wasn't
entertained it's just that I had it it's
just that I just thought that I I don't
want to get too far away from okay go
remember because it was funny and I hope
I make you laugh with this because I
interrupted you oh I probably won't I'm
gonna give you I'm gonna do two
different names like fake names because
I don't want to talk about who they were
but say it was like Jonathan and like no
it was a girl so I'll say Sally and like
Dr Orange right they were the teachers
there's a teacher at our school and a
student that ran and the girl was
running through the hallway and the
teacher was turning oh I know exactly
yeah turning a corner that she was going
to run to and he turned the corner right
as she was running and he couldn't do
anything uh oh that's the guy who's
running what'd he get a cake I think he
had a cake I think his I think he got a
cake oh maybe surprise party I'll go
check I'll go check okay yeah
the craziest thing I've ever seen I've
never
if I was this guy I'd be so freaked out
because Matt's simply approaching him to
see what he just bought at the store
there was like this is just so unlike
Matt but yeah a little afraid me too I'm
gonna record that yeah he's going all
the way over there Matt
what is he doing that's walking in the
guys wait what were you saying though
Nick what are you saying
Nick what the [ __ ] I'm so interested to
see what he comes back to tell us
what were you just saying Nick
um anyways this is so uh oh he just met
up with someone on a CVS Matt no the
[ __ ] dude
he's with that girl
oh here's Matt jogging back what were
you gonna say Nick
um I'm so caught off guard yeah me too
just go but the the girl was running
around dude I just looked to your left
in that girl's cars right there and
there's a bush behind her and I thought
she had a Christmas tree on her car no
she doesn't and I was like what [ __ ]
month yeah that really threw me off but
the the guy was running the guy was
standing there and the teacher was like
350 pounds right yeah that's for context
I'm not like yeah yeah whatever the girl
turns the corner and he goes like this
and she runs into himself guys yeah that
was the best intermission in the car
video I ever took in my life because I
found out what they got and I got a
shiny Spiel yes Shiny Pokemon what do
you get Okay so
his girlfriend or wife I don't want to
assume anything
she was at the CVS oh
he ain't got he got eggs because they
ran out of exit CVS but she got creamer
and um like probably like a baked good
no it was something else it's they're
making breakfast
check it out ladies and gentlemen I said
milk I was close you were close dude my
second guess was gonna be eggs
soda
I want to Fenway Frank so bad right now