[Music]
Oh, I love it. Do a chair salsa.
Oh, they got some moves.
[Music]
Yay.
Hola, Sharks. I'm James
Joanna from Raleigh, North Carolina.
We're seeking $400,000 for 7% of our
company.
Papa Fry Barapa is a Colombian
expression meaning
good people. But it also means good
potato because who doesn't love
potatoes? But they never seem to get the
center of attention. How many times have
you heard would you like a side of fries
with that?
But potatoes make everything better. And
as a couple from two very different
cultures, we've learned to put two
things together create something even
better. And that's why we created Bueno
Papa. Latinspired meals piled high on a
fat stack of hand cut made to order
gourmet French fries.
Oh, it's a fiesta in your mouth and the
whole world's invited.
Each of our signature dishes start out
with 33 oz of fresh cut potatoes.
That's over three large potatoes in
every meal. No one can ever finish one
by themselves.
Our unique culinary experience combines
the comfort of French fries with the
irresistible Latin flavors from cultures
around the world like Colombiano. Oh,
Colia,
Mexico,
Puerto Rico,
and many, many more.
Why are you translating for me? They
know what I'm saying.
They don't speak Spanish. Look, Mr.
Wonderful looks confused.
Okay, sharks. I can't tell you exactly
what she just said, but what I can tell
you is with our bilingual menu,
customers can order in Spanish and have
a little fun at the same time. So sharks
enjoy these Buenas papas as we bring the
Savor sensation to America.
All right, sharks. Who's ready?
Let's go to papa.
Let's try papa. All right, guys. Uh Mr.
Mark, what do you have there?
Yeah, I got the healthy one right here.
Well, healthy salmon makes it healthy.
Smoked salmon, sweet potatoes, guac, and
pico. That's all healthy.
I have regular potatoes, right?
Oh, you have the Carolina. That is
pulled pork.
Pulled pork.
I've got to get through. There's four
sauces.
There's four different sauces. So, we
have a special one called Buena Sauce.
It's our housemade. It's mayo. It's
garlicky. It's cilantro. Delicious.
I just had it. It's delicious.
The fries are really good.
Awesome.
Well, I'm going to give you an ichiwa
karamba. It's
pretty good.
Muchas gracias. And people have fell in
love with this since we opened. It's
been an crazy amazing ride. When we
first opened up, we had $18 in our bank
account
because we invested everything
$18.
$18 because we had invested our life
savings. Uh we had $40,000 saved and uh
this company actually started in the
pandemic. This idea just came to mind.
We thought about Latin food when you
kind of go on vacation. You're in Cancun
or San Juan, Puerto Rico, all those
different street foods that you have
there and how good it tastes and how can
we bring it back to America and adopt it
on top of these fries, right? So we
serve the family. They were our test
dummies. They loved it. The kids loved
it and they said, "Uh, hey dad, can we
have some more?" And I was like, "You
know what? I may have a business here."
So we opened up uh July 2021.
Where did you open? in Raleigh, North
Carolina. After that $18, two weeks
later, we had 18,000 in our bank
account. Two weeks after that on Tik
Tok, we went viral. Influencer came and
tried all of our dishes and two days we
had 16 million views.
16 16 million. And when I saw people
just coming and eating those potatoes, I
said, "Oh my god, it's working."
So, tell us about your background. How
did you guys meet?
Sure. We're we're actually high school
sweethearts. Really?
We met Yeah, we met the last two weeks
of high school
and I pursued her like nothing other. A
that's a prom photo.
A look at that.
That's us. Yeah. And ever since then,
we've been building with each other.
Anybody got restaurant experience?
Not restaurant experience. So, I've been
an entrepreneur all my life. I started
out actually working for Queen Latifa at
Flavor Unit Entertainment. And at that
time, um the Latin boom was going on.
So, I I pitched, how about we do a Latin
management, you know, agency. No one's
really like focusing on these on these
new Latin stars. And I kind of always
been into the Latin culture.
Joanne, we haven't heard from you at
all. Wow.
I talk a lot. Okay. You do talk a lot.
I did. I know this. I know this.
Um, well, my family immigrated from
Columbia, South America in the late
1980s. And when I went to school, nobody
could understand me. I ended up being
placed in the back of class. I
eventually learned how to speak English,
right? Yay. Um, I was the first one to
graduate from college for my family. And
then I went back to the school where
they sat me in the back of the class.
And I worked as a teacher for 12 years.
Oh. Teaching at that famous school.
Talk about triumphing.
Okay. So, talk about this product.
Yes, sir.
Tell me about the cost of making it and
what you sell it for and what the
margins are
and your margins.
So, on average to make any of these
dishes, it it ranges about 350 per plate
cost.
And what do you sell it for?
On average 1350.
What's your overall margin?
Our food margins are 28%.
28.
28%.
It's a little light. Is that your net
profit margins or
That's the on average that's where it's
at. Uh 28%. Uh for our food costs.
Oh, no. You're saying cost of not your
margins, right?
Yeah. His margins are 72.
Okay. Well, then you're okay. You're in
good shape. Today, are you in stores
like this?
So, that's our first store. Uh and it's
a 200 ft² footprint.
Yeah. I love that.
Our first year, we did 1.1 million.
Wow.
We took all the profits from that and
invested into this store.
How big is that one? That one is 700
ft².
And how's that doing?
It's doing really well. So, combined
this year, we're going to finish at
about 2 million.
What did you make last year on the 2
million?
Sure. Uh about 200,000.
Did you pay yourself paying?
We paid ourselves 80,000. So, that's
what uh
120.
120. Mhm.
So, you have two stores.
Well, no, no. Well, we have three
stores. The third one is uh at an arena.
Actually, we're opening up a fourth one
in Miami uh this month.
Where in Miami?
A Windwood Miami.
Oh, you'll kill it.
Yeah, we're excited. We also I didn't
mention this. So we started franchising.
Okay. And on our opening month of our
franchising program, we sold four
franchises.
What do you charge for those?
295 for initial franchise fee.
And then how much per month per year?
8% royalty fee. 2% of that is uh
marketing.
And how long has the longest one been
out there? Is this new?
Well, this is this is brand new. Brand
new. So we just sold these franchises.
So what are you looking for?
We're looking for
besides 400,000.
Well, a strategic partnership to help us
build this brand. All right. We got
franchises selling. We're excited about
those. We know we can move this company
along at a nice snail plate pace.
It doesn't sound like a snail pace to
me.
I'll tell you the hiccup though. We're a
young company. So when we go to banks
and we walk in, we're looking nice and
pretty and they're like, "Yeah, so we
need some money to open up a new store."
And they're like, "No, you're still
considered a startup." So that was the
issue. So we've been taking our own
profits in opening up these stores,
which I've learned now that it's not
healthy.
Why is that not healthy?
Because we're sucking up all the cash
flow.
But do you have any debt today?
70,000 of debt on the business. Not
nothing huge, right? But I think it's a
fundamental question like do you would
you rather grow with a lot of debt and
scale and maybe not make a profit or or
do it the way you're doing it? You
started this when you only had $18 in
your account and now you're running a $2
million business. I mean, you should be
so proud of that.
Thank you. Thank you. But the issue is
we want to have more speed because I
know that somebody else is going to come
into this market.
Listen, I think you're doing everything
right. I think when you race and run
with something like this where you have
to make sure you land in the right
places, that you do everything
correctly, right? It's not like you have
to blitz the market with it fast. People
can't copy that. I would not want to
speed it out there. I would not want to
race it. I wish you good luck, but I'm
out.
Thank you so much, Laura. Thank you so
much.
So, so the the fiveyear plan for us is
to open one corporate store every year
in the next 5 years, and that's going to
end up at uh at the end of five years at
$10 million. So guys,
Mhm.
running a restaurant is a hard business.
Once you franchise, you're in a second
business. You're in the babysitting
business. You're in the daycare business
because you're taking $29,500 from
somebody and they're buying your dream.
And when they want your help, you better
be there.
Mhm.
If you guys were just in this, I was
interested. But you're in two different
businesses. I think that's going to
crush you. So for those reasons, I'm
out.
Ah, wow.
Thank you, Mark.
So very impressive. It's delicious, but
frankly u with the change of my
lifestyle of eating, I I I I wouldn't
eat this. And I like to get behind the
products that I invest in so I can use
my face to push the business. You know,
I'm out.
You know what I think? I think you don't
really need anybody. I think you have
the whole package. You have each other.
You're progressing nicely and I think
you'll continue that way. So, I'm out.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Barbara.
You still have one shark left. Robert,
what are you doing? All right, guys.
What I've learned is if you find great
people, great things can happen. And you
guys are amazing. I mean, to go from
where you were, no money, to build this
size of business, I've been there.
Mhm.
Let's figure out this thing together.
Okay. Five.
The only thing I hate is the valuation.
There's no way this is worth 5.1
million.
Let's talk about it.
Okay. You're making $120,000 a year. How
is it worth 5 million?
Actually, Robert, it's 5.7 million
valuation. Thank you, Kevin.
So, after Miami opens up with our four
stores and our franchise stores, we
should be about 6 million in gross
sales.
Gross sales next year. But that's not
today. It's probably worth about
2 million today.
I'm valuing it off of what we're going
to do next year. Yeah.
Well, I'm valuing it off what it's
worth.
I got you.
Today, make us.
So, for me, it's about $2 million. So,
400,000 20%.
Okay. Okay. Can we counter offer you?
That's the beauty of Shark Tank. You can
do whatever you want.
Let's talk papas. All right.
The good potato.
15%
for the 400k.
No. 400,000 20%. You know I'm going to
be there. We're going to invest more.
Mhm. Let's meet halfway. 17%. Let's
close the deal. Eat some papas and let's
go.
400,000 20%. Let's go.
18%.
20%.
What do you say, honey?
Gosh. Oh my goodness.
Squeezing the potato. Squeezing
19%.
Thank you, sir. Appreciate you, buddy.