all right y'all it's yet another car
video where I'm eating a slice of pizza
I feel like at this point my body is
like 25% pepperoni
pizza and then what you saying how you
miss me yeah you miss me and all the
things that we did we we going to travel
from the island to Madrid we had a lot
of plans but they
all why because of some but it's okay
cuz I'm moving different don't be saying
nothing when
I'm I switched to Sun kiss everybody for
team orange foror why not why know what
word I hate like I really hate pepperoni
no it's actually very different life
master no can I just say it no you can't
why cuz I want to guess you said you
want to know what word like you implied
take a guess no I didn't said guess what
no you said you want to know what word I
what was that second thing you said life
master that's two words and where did
you read that right there yeah that's
crazy oh ready ready ready go chug chug
chug chant it chant chug chug chug chug
chug chug chug chug keep going keep
going I stopped cuz you
[Music]
stopped oh I almost threw up on Nick
like a little baby oh my god that
actually smell like those little orange
fruit candies oh
yummy chug chug chug chug come on no
one's cheering on just drink your soda
pleas no I want to feel like I'm in a
fraternity upside down on a ping pong T
fraternity it's FR my least favorite
[ __ ] is when people say like oh that's
frustrating is that like why are we
dropping the r no you just made me think
of that cuz you just said some word
frustrating you just said a word can I
have a bite to that you just said a word
without an r and it made me laugh and at
the beginning of this video before you
interrupted me the word I was going to
say I hate like it's a really creepy
word just the word
coochie like the word coochie freaks me
out and I know it's like crazy to just
say and blurred out and like you guys
prob like Nick what the word coochie is
crazy that's all yeah I really don't
like coochie
okay do you disagree or agree on that I
don't like what they called crazy word
oh that's what he said fraternity it's
FR fraternity fraternity can't believe
those can't believe those are a real
thing I love them that's how I feel with
them I feel like I'm going to go Alabama
Rush kadash Kaboom plow like I would to
be upside down with a tube in my
mouth to beer I want just drinking Bud
Light I want to wake up Saga Afra I want
to wake up put Bud Light in Cheerios and
eat it for
breakfast then I want to eat lunch and
wash it down with a Corona and then I
want to eat dinner and have whiskey like
a real man put hair on my chest his
dog's really cute I he doesn't drink as
much beer as I do I am the king of beer
beer beer beer me I am Samuel Adams the
drain I am Samuel Adams wrap it
up
we're already a good chunk into this
video but today's video we're going to
be doing there a 10
but let's an absolute Stern little
classic here yeah we've done this we've
done this a lot of times but I genuinely
think we didn't create it from Tik Tok
but I genuinely think it's like one of
the funniest things we do when Nick said
mother and father you said that no but
he said it like I said it I think I ran
with the joke more oh okay we need to
bring back the OG shumbo triplets were
around for that
OG OG OG OG stroli like they were 10
butt ready you [ __ ] are awesome no I
just say get ready right now cuz like
you're you're getting OG strum bully
content again yeah it's it's coming back
around hate to be the bearer bad news
there's no such thing as OG stolo
content you're right we always doing
you're weird your mother like a that is
your mom too I'm going to tell her I'm
going to call mom right now no you're
not swear to God I am no don't call Mom
right now call her and tell her call her
after they're a super big mama's boy
skip no I don't like the word Mama uh-uh
I love it no I'm going to start calling
Nick mama what classifies what
classifies [ __ ] you I hate that you're
just yapping still like let's talk about
it I'm what let's talk you're he's like
what stop stop talking at all like go
eat a
munchkin ah
oh don't look like Bert and Ernie it's
crazy Bert
[Laughter]
Ernie that be such a good name for
n okay it's not funny at all holy [ __ ]
Ernie
no can you
stop stop we didn't answer the first yes
we did there 10 but I give up on it
mama's boy yeah what's our answers go
ahead recite all three answers eight oh
there's the first [ __ ] number thrown
have I don't have one I don't have one
ni you have to I don't have one I one
what I have though a [ __ ] headache go
a headache stupid I already took an
Advil shut up they stalk your mom's
Facebook page before hanging out with
you [ __ ] like weird zero correct zero
zero like you're just strange you're so
[ __ ] lunatic I agree that's some
weirdo [ __ ]
[ __ ] out of here I don't want that
weirdo
[ __ ] okay go next who is he talking to
they pick food out of their teeth in
front of
others with a barf Emoji they like that
I'd rather someone do that than
have I agree I agree and it's like if I
point out oh you got something in your
tooth what are you going to get up and
leave seriously oh see you I got to go
[ __ ] in the bathroom and pick up no
just do it real quick weirdo [ __ ]
doesn't take
I'd be more thrown off if somebody like
fully like got up and left and left for
sure oh give me a minute I got to go run
just like grab your phone grab your
phone put it on your that's Tye a
[ __ ] got a flosser on them
normal it's also like something that
happens like maybe like once every like
9 months wa that's not that frequent I
would say more
frequently well that's not so frequent
is this just bully Chris car no it's
bully the idiot and you just happen to
be the idiot so look at you stupid [ __ ]
they can't cook anything like every they
said it wrong so I'm correcting them
idiot don't look over my shoulder trying
to correct me I just read get the
Vaseline off your lip it's not Vaseline
get it off it whatever anyone in my and
Nick's position would be in the just
have fun with me drink some coke and get
loose come listen I was just correcting
you they can listen here let me put it
in in like a perspective that you can
actually imagine it okay right all right
everyone today to today we're going to
draw all right we're all going to get
our pieces of paper and markers and
we're going to draw so I give out all
the pieces of paper I give out all the
markers and then I go all right everyone
we're going to draw today all right
everybody we're going to draw and then a
half an hour's gone by all right guys so
we're going to draw so make sure you
pick up those
markers you got how it can be
annoying how you never get to the
[ __ ] point of anything hey guys we're
going to draw we're filming a car video
we're filming a car video we're filming
a car video we're filming a car
video Let's just [ __ ] do
it oh time to wake
up I said a timer cuz I was going to
take a nap while you were just yapping
your mouth
off a little bit never again never again
like it's talk at me I see I would have
stayed on the topic but Nick interrupted
me because look that says they can
you're a snooper looking over my
shoulder like this oh you should get a
telescope the way you [ __ ] look at my
screen get out of here your ha hang down
stop get off my ha I hate when people
look at my phone get out of here you got
one right I was 90% of the time I
wouldn't look at someone's phone but
when we're all waiting for what you're
going yeah yeah yeah blah blah blah o
I'm Nick everybody listen to me that's
how you talk get out of here they can't
cook any
cuz every single time they try they burn
something there are 10 nah seven stop
burning [ __ ] cool again figure it out I
feel like burning it is so extreme like
if you're going to burn it every time
just take it out a little sooner you're
are used to burning everything the
second I burn something I'm never
burning it again promise to swear to God
put it on my life okay literally sugar
cookies I cook them they burn not
happening again with those sugar cookies
no way I think the thing that's making
them not a 10 here isn't the fact that
they're burning everything I think it's
the the fact that they just keep trying
to cook if you can't no just give up no
never give up never give up I was going
to say that at least they're trying I
have the polar oppos never give up you
have tears in your eyes wipe them it
looks like you're sad come on why do you
have tears in your eyes I you just look
really emotional about the burnt stuff
don't get upset you're the one getting
upset no I'm not they don't clean their
shoes I don't that's what I'm saying I
never cleaned a shoe a day in my life
I've personally never got and scrubbed
up some shoes you ever see people at the
mall with like the shoe shiners I wish
that I was
OG every shoe I wish was like an OG the
OG go
ahead for the only shoes that I would
have to clean are like my air forces or
like my all white New Balances cuz
they're the only ones that are like all
white I don't know if it's just these
glasses but it looks like you're going
to cry am I do I look like that yeah
your eyes just look Full of Tears like
let me know I know why I look like no
I'm not I don't need to cry I'm confused
on why I love you Matt I love you too
hold
on he looks perfectly normal yeah it
looks fine no it look like really you
look like just like really upset well
I'm good so if there's any thought that
I have tears in my eyes it's not true I
would say I don't clean my shoes so I
say they're still a 10 I agree agree
they're 10 there we go they hate the
holidays wrong you can't hate every
holiday that's not a real thing you
can't be like filled with hate toward
every holiday I know [ __ ] that
don't like Christmas but they were up
and running during [ __ ] St Patrick's
Day what are you a leprechaun you little
stupid freak grow up go chase a rainbow
you dumb little dummy I hate that [ __ ]
hate the holidays how do you hate
gingerbread man can't catch me as fast
as I can the gingerbread man is like a
staple in my life like I can understand
like oh I don't like Christmas whatever
oh I don't like I don't like a certain
holiday whatever I can understand I can
understand I can get behind disliking a
holiday holidays there's at least one
positive to almost every holiday and
it's not even holiday to me it's
tradition it's Vibe I think of the
Christmas tree putting up the star I
think of Halloween carving the pumpkins
seeing the seeing the cute adorable
little kids go get candies and snacks
and treats and maybe tricking one
another I I live for this you know what
I mean hating every holiday is
ridiculous like you're a [ __ ] loser
and you're old probably if you hate
every holiday you're your favorite day
of the year is probably [ __ ] April
fools you goof you hate every holiday
get off your rocking chair pick your
cane up and go [ __ ] cane till you
find spirit I was going to say that like
if you eat every holid you got
be say like the crazy every every single
person who hates holidays has to be
bitter and old go get a cup of coffee
get a Cup of Jo they got to ha it's like
their 60th one you know it's like the
the episode of Squidward when Squidward
is doing the same coming to bed honey
yes de whatever it is he goes every day
is the same thing you old bat they got a
bushy
mustache I don't like the word bushy I
hate the word it's very descriptive a
little bushy stash um Nick no I hate the
word bushy yeah but you love bushy
stashes I know you that's your type bro
you like it's not my type at all I like
yes it is no it's
not no it's not how you going to say yes
it is you can't say cuz I can I could
explain if you would shut your trap door
go ahead [ __ ] face red trap door that's
attached to your [ __ ] go ahead red
trapo what I don't got lipstick on what
I'm saying he called my lips pink and
started flirting with me what I'm saying
is the word bushy thr me off cuz bushy's
like uncontrollable you look dirty and
gross like there could be a bu if we're
talking about the guy from Grand Turismo
that bush right there is trimmed oh my
God I'm going to literally if we're
talking about the guy from Grand Turismo
different story he has a bushy stash
bushy
go they have a completely empty bedroom
like it's only a bed and a dresser
that's it here we go all right so we're
in we're in mat yeah here we go so right
we're in mat's room that's it I don't
know Matt what do I rate I rate Matt ATT
10 still cuz it's about Charisma and
attitude deep down Charisma yeah Matt
Matt carries himself with a lot of
Charisma and attitude I feel like people
who have and I love them for
it [ __ ] ring
like dude
[ __ ]
[ __ ] I'm just proud of no I'm not doing
it that hard yeah you are I'm giving you
Assurance Pat okay
harder come on dude go that makes you
feel wor but imagine this like eight
times you know get out of here all right
they have seven cats zero zero I'd also
like to say I got better at decorating
my room oh yeah you did little cabin
theme I just want to frolic on your bed
like this okay we're going to move on no
I just feel like I'm one with the Autumn
Leaves when I'm in Matt's room that's
the vibe definitely stop talking for
sure definitely go away they have seven
cats I said zero they have webbed feet
oh they have seven cats I didn't answer
that one hold on they have seven cat
skip it they got webbed feet honestly 10
I bet they can swim crazy nope zero yes
ch0 I bet they can't if you have webbed
feet you're literally liers on your own
bare skin get out of here don't say that
[ __ ] webbed feet fun oh I just want to
cut the web
off oh my
God little panic I just like actually
fled my body with this Comfort same
reaction oh my God like I felt my feet
and hands get so in pain right away yeah
no that would oh my God next the room is
always untiy untiy untiy oh my God that
person's a zero they drink they drink
diet Pepsi
no um as opposed to the original doesn't
matter as long as you're drinking
something I don't there's no really big
change oh I did leave myself some
crust as long as it's not like you're
drinking something weird then that's
fine okay next yeah the dog is so cute
my dog doesn't like
them I give a [ __ ] it depends on if your
dog is like a picky dog or not I like a
zero if your dog doesn't like the person
you're with then you can't really be
around him no cuz the person you're
around could be a 10 the dog pict your
dog your dog should love everyone you
weirdo [ __ ] stupid they casually put
their LED lights on flash oh my God
that's the scariest thing I've ever
heard the scariest zero like actually
zero that's the scariest thing I've ever
heard is that not crazy put them in jail
yeah arrest that person literally send
them to prison
someone said they openly scratched their
butt it depends how open I get it I say
10 like if you're going to pretend you
never scratch your ass you're
crazy okay all right no do you know what
I mean everybody's scratching their ass
if you're going to make a big deal out
of it you're weird I mean you can always
like tuck it away you don't got to be so
open with it well it's not like it's a I
don't know I'm not I don't think I'm
like are we talking like someone goes do
you scratch your ass and like they're
like no
never well what is this what are we
talking
about you scratched every inch of your
body from [ __ ] head to toe in your
whole life probably nope okay Chris what
what party have you not scratched
probably the back of my knees okay yes
you have definitely have the back of my
knees are one of my top three in itchy
levels probably the dead center of my
back like right there you just touched
it stop being you just touched it you
just scratched it when you did that so
there what you said dead back scratch
scratch oh oh I always feel like an
oranga Tang when I scratch my arm okay
okay um so said they don't wear
deodorant between my pinky toe and the
other one you've definitely scratched it
before sometimes I go like this I go
between my toes I go like
this and like rub them oh my God that
was weird get clean I can't believe that
to get clean said they don't wear
deodorant zero
zero ABS there's absolutely no excuse in
this world for to stink nobody should
ever have to like nobody should ever
stink I remember in sixth grade when
they taught us in like sex ed what like
deodorant was AG the the [ __ ] one of
us three always got a stick on us for
sure of deodorant what are you talking
about obviously Chris well Matt looked
like I said Weaponry they're rude to
service staff biggest thing rude to
service staff zero go up to your mother
look her down in the eyes and say I hate
you Mom that's the equivalent that's the
equivalent I agree I don't know about no
I agree with it is that was that was
very well said at least your mom isn't
getting paid I respect that a lot
actually okay last one I have you should
treat you should treat your they're
working hard to should Tre staff the
same way that you would treat your my
thought is if once again you can't
afford if you can't afford to be kind
you already have the leverage customer
is always right which I don't think is
true it's not definely however you
already are winning 90% of the battles
cuz the customer's always right which is
baloney but just treat him with some
respect I agree no I who they say um
what's it called if if you can't afford
to be kind to the person helping you and
you also can't afford to tip don't go
out to eat order it to go you useless
[ __ ] like I get I get it server some
servers start start [ __ ] and like this
and that but I always feel like this is
like a big thing actually I always feel
like people get wrong at people for the
wrong things like people start cussing
out servers because it's something like
the chef messed up on it's like first of
all you're screaming at the wrong person
second of all even if mess up you're the
one with the [ __ ] complicated order
so if he didn't get it out every time
you go be idiot it's just a big game of
telephone
mhm they wash their body with dish soap
that's for the dishes you're zero no but
honest to God I I was going to say zero
but then I thought about it we all seen
the commercial when it clean the duck
duck all right you want to know what I
heard what one drop of Dawn and grease
is gone I've heard that my favorite SL
the only thing here's the thing though
like I have to
poop okay's go home and go I don't think
anybody's really washing themselves with
dish soap like that we're done they use
the wrong form of there there and there
I've yelled about this before say there
a 10 no matter how you want to
say man that was good they're always out
of breath and breathing really heavy
okay we can be done for sure we can
definitely be done for sure wrap it up
on
that
and what you saying how you miss me yeah
you miss me and all the that
we from the is to Madrid we had a lot of
plans but they
all why all because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
saying nothing when I'm post to with
[ __ ] my brothers