[Music]
hello is that good hi can you stop
screaming oh God what I just can't
believe this I can't [ __ ] believe
this
what can't you believe I don't know what
where is he
going he just walked inside he just said
all right [ __ ] it I'm leaving is it good
you tell me you go check I'm not getting
out of the car no also don't pat me like
this don't do that pisses me off I
did the light right above you
Nick okay he's like sucking my soul
it's taking my soul away come on actual
content toward you CHR Jeepers Creepers
man I feel like I [ __ ] sprained my
ankle oh no call the nurse call the
nurse Nick I'll [ __ ] kill you who
[ __ ]
them like who [ __ ] that your pants it
doesn't smell that in here smells
horrible want to sniff this mint
chocolate get the [ __ ] out of here just
saying can you lock the car the lights
are pling
you're insane there's no way we're like
cool to an outside perspective like we
have to be [ __ ] lame people will meet
us and probably be like you're so cool
be like who are you talking to I'm a
[ __ ] hermit I live in my house I
don't go
anywhere and I breathe heavy going up a
flight of
stairs
[Music]
whatever you're kid like you're for
ER you always make me laugh like thank
you all right guys welcome back to
another Friday video I [ __ ] am
excited
um so right now I can't believe I see
this is my thing M and Chris have set
ourselves up that we haven't filmed a
car video in a while and it always feels
better when we take a little bit of a
break we filmed one
yesterday moving on cuz I just want the
people to be alert I don't give a
[ __ ] everything you've done so far is
getting cut out of the video so why are
you speaking in a negative tone shut the
[ __ ]
up shut
up oh my God my eyes are watering Nick
you already have me c oh my goodness
that's so good um today's video topic is
there a 10 butt or there a one butt and
like you know like you it goes higher or
lower depending on the I can't do this I
can't get it okay awesome thank you
Einstein appreciate you luckily for you
what's up Sneezy
can you [ __ ] off don't take aex
disgusting bug you doing get out tisue
look at your allergies rub your eyes a
little bit can you do it dude I can't
even look at you it's making me feel a
little
SC spank your ice cream like I'm about
to eat you okay that's crazy that's
insane
Chris at your grown age he just airplane
himself at I've never seen somebody like
I've never seen a 20-year-old man sneeze
with both hands by his side and just go
like that and sneeze out world yeah just
like out and about for anyone to enjoy
my name's Chris don't wear it out no
one's going to wear it
out not even remotely close what was
that what did I just Nick did you just
see that I need Advil did you just this
all this whole mat is negative persona
it's all in your head
magnic all in your head all your head
watch that watch all that footage back
you'll see the the [ __ ] stupidity
that just endur with you guys saying
that I'm negative and that I'm not
speaking you need to stop acting like a
[ __ ] idiot what's going on easily I'm
trying to move on you're sucking ice
cream and Matt's causing
problems what's your favorite serving of
potato dude I'm not doing the potato
jokes cuz you're out of [ __ ] [ __ ] who
out of [ __ ] what are you talking about
chis anytime there's silence anytime
something's not hilarious Chris brings
up [ __ ] potatoes no I don't out of
this you [ __ ] Spud all you do you do
anything to bring up potatoes or french
fries shut the [ __ ]
up my God anytime there's sweet [ __ ]
silence Chris brings up potatoes shut up
my ears are finally enduring a break
what's your favorite kind of potato
french fries or this or that sh shut the
[ __ ] up please I'm literally begging you
it's either you shut the [ __ ] up or I
cut my ears off and sew them to a
necklace I'm sick of
it my God so many people in this world
need to just practice the [ __ ] Sweet
Sensation of Silence dumb [ __ ] I
practice it yeah and I love you for it
thank you all right 10 butt they pick
their nose what the [ __ ] else you do if
you got boogies and let's be real blow
it blow
it you're so gross yeah they're a mama's
boy or a daddy's
girl I hate those sayings I hate them
too what was I have to go blow my nose
can I have a minute yeah
you whatever you got to do actually
here these [ __ ]
lights he's playing the trumpet out
there oh my God you're a [ __ ] gery
Smurf Jer can you close the door so I
don't have to look
horrocious I'm making sure I'm put
together all right should have tried
that hours ago lock the car door Nick
watch your tone with me watch your tone
with me what are you going to do about
it I'm going to [ __ ] fill your room
with packing peanuts I'll call the
police no you
will like what Nick the type A guy that
own a sham wow and be hella hype about
it dude that's lit there are 10 oh check
out my sham wow you don't even spell
sham wow I don't want to spell sham wow
God God I can't read this one out loud
can't read this one out loud it's been
so long since I've seen a comment that
I've been like I'm not reading that out
loud let see let me see it this person
said there are 10
but e weird I
wouldn't no [ __ ] Matt thank you Matt God
I don't I hate that you actually answer
that like practically correct can I have
that next of course you can they dislike
sweets two annoying ways to say
something right dislike don't like
sweets candy grow up thank you like
what's going on they dislike sweets like
you're [ __ ] weirdo yeah
door lock the door okay conductor
Matt lock the doors you didn't close
your door all the
way lock the
door
oh and how does that make you feel it
smell like did you eat pickles no did
you eat I hate that he's guessing and
sniff buff what's wrong with you buffalo
wings they're 10 but they don't wipe
their butt after they poop it ew bro how
do you walk get out Max what is that
like this is why I hate giving you the
phone cuz you read the weird [ __ ] what
what was it the weird [ __ ] is what we
want read it out loud tell me say it
nothing say it I can't I can't say it
just I'm not going to make you're
annoying read it no you can read it and
then bleepy you can read it then bleepy
are you a baby they chew with their
goddamn mouth open in all
caps
[Applause]
no oh my relx I don't think I'm ever
watching somebody chew like that I'm
never an all caps text her either like
this girl puts that in all caps like
relax relax I feel like I'm being
shouted at I was that to squint to read
all feel the wind of your heated breath
coming at me like it's insane I have to
[ __ ] get my my blinkers
on dude this is the weird [ __ ] how do I
react to that you're putting your
blinkers those also those would be
windshield wipers blinkers mean oh
thanks car expert [ __ ] bro thinks
he's Luigi kid got the car Luigi's a
plumber talking about the [ __ ] Dum
Guido Guido you're talking about
Guido oh you know Luigi it's like oh the
plumber no Guido what are you even
talking about whatever you think you're
you push me past my own they use the big
spoon to Watt instead of the little
to that's what they said that's the
question girl to
what did you just fart again no it was a
chair okay okay I hate like goofy [ __ ]
like they're 10 but they prefer dogs
over cats they were T but are allergic
to stuff like okay their last name is
stolo oh unbelievably funny and creative
it's crazy how Nick has like four custom
La they hate
[Applause]
Pepsi they eat their toenails then try
to kiss you get out get out go get help
sh your toils they have devices for this
what Jesus get
away dude what's up toenails eatting
shail they love it they love it toenails
feet boogies and pickles that's all I
see come on pickles pick eat pickles
they got pickle breath they eat pickles
and chips I don't I don't care that much
about pickles what's up with them dude I
love when Matt say words with peas he's
like I don't care about pickles like he
does that P like that really his lips
are smacking
back when Matt says like alliterations
it always gets me what like just two
words that like Bing yeah Bing Bong
[ __ ] boo la
la oh my God they're talking without
thinking the consequences what what are
the consequences holy [ __ ] all right
Joker holy [ __ ] they don't like they
don't like your mommy dude zero Merl the
goat you don't like Mommy I don't like
you kid don't say mommy like that they
say already saw that to everything you
show them that's already saw it that's
completely Justified that's me with Matt
almost every time Matt goes to show me
something I've seen it already they're
10 but but they have terrible
comebacks two
dude especially compared to me I have
good comebacks so your comebacks got to
be you're Mr comeback King Nick you
actually might go down in history as the
come that's a crown I can wear I'll fit
it on my head give it to me I want it
you really are there were 10 I hate this
I hate
it I hate these videos cuz it's like
they're a they're a one butt and then
people put things that makes a person a
10 like oh they have the best
personality they smell good they're an
amazing person it's like that would
imply that they're not a One to begin
with no they're it's talking about looks
Nick they're visually a one but they're
an amazing human
being oh they're a 10 but they pick
their scabs ew e never tell me that
again the word scab just scab freak out
you're more of a boo boo guy right what
are you saying to me like yeah it's like
oh I don't have a scab I have a boo boo
like if you're what you say
yeah like if Chris had a scab on his leg
I got a boo boo that's you right you
just get such boo boo energy that'd be a
sick nickname for you Nick shut the [ __ ]
up okay internet takes that [ __ ] so
seriously I'm going to be boo boo for a
month like actually I'm not even kidding
I'm leaving it in it's all good dude
they never wear socks not even in shoes
you sound like Dr Seuss they never wear
socks not even in shoes there's one
that's purple Spen one that's blue wrong
you can't don't do that don't just
don't I feel like they never wear socks
they never wear shoes they never wear
socks not even in shoes they don't even
own pairs they come by the twos what are
you saying Nick so many shoes which one
oh I hate you they're a t that's what
I'm saying his laugh is crazy they're a
10 but they're a reckless driver they're
a 10 but a reckless driver stop just did
like a combo sequence on my arm what was
that I was just hitting you so you
stopped like I was just hitting you
do ew you
stinker uh I hate recklessness be calm
and stay in the lane oh that's nice
that's like a life reference don't be
Reckless stay in your lane that's nice
boo boo stop man I'm going to actually
[ __ ] fist a fury your ass right in
the face oh I'm
scared I love that [ __ ] yeah I know you
do
they are 10 but they claim they have
superpowers say that again they're 10
but they claim they have
superpowers um that's you that's
actually you claim oh you just called
him a 10 that's awkward how's that
awkward I brother incest dude
what on what level was that like
anywhere remotely close un real that was
insane there were 10 but they don't like
animals you're [ __ ] zero that's
concerning no I don't think that goes to
zero I that goes to negative O Negative
going
down you make me regret you say things
that no one can you make me regret
everything everything I say you make me
be like I wish I didn't just say that
cuz like now that's like the most sad
thing you could ever said to me okay
well every time you say something to me
it just makes me wish I never spoke
they're are 10 but they gritty
everywhere oh
11 okay dude what the I'm the gritty
King I gritted into Lucille's barbecue
the other day a you're the gritty King
see now how do you respond to that I am
the gritty King okay like I'm not like
I'm not going to do that you know one
gritty two gritty three gritty four
gritty blue gritty purple gritty orange
gritty yellow gritty what are you saying
I like looked down from it I thought I
was dreaming that's insane Dream a
Little
Dream don't T
me
they're a 10 but they don't ask you to
be their Valentine grow up this isn't
kindergarten this isn't first grade
we're not exchanging Little Valentine
with fundip and lollipops it's time to I
I agree I'll never I won't I won't ever
get that ever oh they didn't ask me if
their Valentine do you think they're mad
at
me that's like a like real people get
mad at that like oh my go I can't
believe it we have a Ser if you were
dating someone would you ask them to be
their your I'm going above and beyond on
Valentine's Day and I'm doing everything
that's like the the romantic things on
Valentine's Day not asking yeah sorry I
just think it's weird I just think it's
corny I think it's I think it's really
really corny I just think it's built in
bro obviously wait we should have like a
boy Valentine's day trip this year hold
here's my thing no hold the
[ __ ] okay this is my plan oh God I'm
so scared we all go somewhere cool that
has some nice things going on yeah
bowling bowling Adventure Trail zoo park
water slide whatever just something fun
and we all spend the night together as
boys and we do it for for Valentine's
Day for the boys like like that's how I
like just us
three I don't know I just want to spend
Valentine's Day with like there's no
girls out there that I'm like like that
I don't have a valentine this year you
don't have a valentine this year you
don't have a valentine this year let's
just have a boy Valentine
moment I wish there was a button right
here that erased the last two minutes
and just goo i' hit it really fast I
wish there's a button right here that
erased the last 20 years of my life
that's
good just kidding you I wish I could
stick my eyes with toothpicks and eat
them off like a
kebab what why come on Chris it's weird
no it's not weird just call it a trip
it's a trip Bros trip sure it could be a
Bros well it's the same way girls have
like gallentine look you be my
brotine is crazy brentin is INS bye
everyone holy look you would be my bro
in time stop talking bro it's like a
dinosaur like bronchitis like all right
that's not a
dinosaur that's like an illness right
brosaurus broncosaurus
no no no Nick you got anything else to
say I the T-Rex
King God what a crazy video today was
it's a wild one everyone name an object
at three and then whoever gets the
closest wins three two I don't even know
closest to what just name something just
name something and then whoever gets
like most similar 3 2 1 mirror what we
he said grenade no he said
lemonade I said raindrop I said Mirror
Mirror raindrop lemonade yeah go
lemonade do do shower do shower Lemonade
Stand
y car pellet yellow car pellet yellow
car pellet yeah how are we going to
guess pellet like stop saying intricate
words we're supposed to all guess it
three two one taxi bus taxi I said
banana okay ban ta banana I feel like
there's one thing here Ready set go
banana boat oh my god you're an idiot
yellow and banana boat let's try again 1
2 3 Sunday sunscreen God Banana Boat
yellow banana ice cream sunde and
[ __ ]
sunscreen you're
insane you push
me
all right that's it for this week no
outro
all
yeah are you done that's it for this
week's Friday video make sure you go
check out our merch link down below
because right when we hit 6 million
subscribers we're going to look rough
because of the lighting hold on around
we hit 6 mil we're going to have 6 mil
merch and we have a fun plan for 6
million subscribers so stay tuned and we
will talk to you guys when we talk to
you guys and make sure you hit that
subscribe button if you're not
subscribed yet like the video turn on
post notifications cuz we post video
every single Friday love
[Music]
you