it's like an eclipse when you close in
on it yes I got you a gift Matt for
Christmas no you didn't yeah I just been
waiting to film a car video to give it
to you you didn't give me a gift swear
to God I did what is it sound a little
more appreciative and maybe I'll give it
to you I don't believe you that's why
I'm
like do you know what happens when you
don't believe in the holiday season yeah
Cole exactly Matt you ready for your
gift yeah ooh drum roll
please
dude 100% dull pineapple juice these
were in the house yep I brought one to
the car for you that's your gift than y
they've been in the house for like 2
months no problem all right guys welcome
back to this week's car video it is
Friday happy Friday
everybody it's been a while since me mad
Chris filmed the video it is December
29th filming this which is literally the
day that this video also comes out oh
no I just spiled so much prime okay this
video topic we announced forever ago and
we didn't know what we were going to
film oh [ __ ] but now we're doing it yeah
as you know we've pre-filmed a lot of
our content but we're all out now which
is great it's been so long I feel like I
just am ripping at the walls to film I
just rip the
Stu I just want to rip the Stu let me
out of my own head but basically we
posted that this video was going to be a
this or that without having any idea
what this video is going to be we just
like the idea I have an actual question
though what are you guys doing if
Christmas carolers show up to the crib
knock on the door start singing Joy to
the World the slam the door right in
their face Matt didn't even say anything
he went he did slaming the door in their
[ __ ] mouth I feel like that's very
appropriate I agree to shut the door
well I feel like if someone's singing at
my doorstep I and what if I was busy see
there's a here here's what if I was like
What if I was watching a movie and then
I get interrupted by song an ad skip the
ad there's a couple things that shut the
door yeah there's a couple things that I
would do it's like virtual skipping the
ad
like it's not virtual that's real life
or real life IRL ad skip there's a
couple of things that I would do if I
wanted to listen to holiday music turn
it on turn on the radio put on the TV
put on YouTube watch a Christmas movie
getting a bunch of festive oldie through
your front door singing maybe even go to
a concert the second I got people with
scarfs with like the their open pamplet
singing you know what I mean no it's
ridiculous get out of here I can't it's
just I just think of people with like
little kids or like dogs and it's like
if you're like like you're like watching
imagine like someone Rings your bell and
your dog like
nonstop oh my God imagine you put the
baby down for the for his first nap of
the day and they always I feel like they
always knock at night like it's like a
little late I want to wind up like a
punch like having a cartoon
like see I open the door say go away I I
th this pineapple juice right there
[ __ ] I'm just a massive fan of booby
traps like I just think I'm a net on my
they up they all get taken up in a net I
think put a springboard that you can
activate with a button so you open the
door and see that it's them I'm sorry
you open the door and see that it's them
and you grab the button and you go boom
and then they just launch away like from
your door or there's like a trap door
into the basement or they sink down and
they're stuck the video of the sing
jackass sing to sing to leave you must
sing if you want to exit they like Joy
to the World sing more the floor slowly
Rises to exit do you know once I gave
this kid in our school a thing of
pineapple juice cuz he really liked it
and he drank the whole thing it was like
it was like probably like 12 of these
together no eight 1 2 3 four and then
like four more on top was the size of
the can and he drank the whole thing and
he had to pee so bad he pissed in the
classroom in the in the car in the thing
like he put the thing in his pants and
filled it up with pee the jar the jar I
was in that eighth grade do you remember
that yes how weird of a kid super weird
how big was the hole no it was can it
was a can where like you needed a can
open
it he uned easy access to PE I was going
to say he liked pineapple juice so I
gave him the gift of the pineapple juice
and he opened it you couldn't put the
lid back on and that's why he drank the
whole thing I don't know why people like
a straw who gave him a straw I don't
know who had a can
opener good question like opened it at
school and Dr well it could have been
one of those peel off cans I hate tomato
soup no one's going to ever force you to
have some um would you rather be it's
this or that not would you rather though
oh this or that lamp LED lamp I'm a huge
lamp guy I don't think we needed all
that all the color options see no I kind
of overwhelming that was my biggest
regret getting LED lights all the way
across my room biggest regret if I could
get LED lights that were like lamp
colored bulbs I'd do that balls bul bul
said balls we've had this debate balls
or bulb no someone said bulb like an
idiot once before on the internet
probably Matt B um would you rather
be it's not would you rather it's
winning or losing winning what I'd
rather lose and be an underdog the
underdog Underdog would I have that
fight in me the underdog would win no
it's like I want it more um would you
rather eat would you rather [ __ ] [ __ ]
why didn't we just do it would you
rather I don't know okay this or that
which one do you like more of those
words will it get really literal I like
that I like that yeah I like that I hate
that this is me this is it like this
this that like this is so more like oh
what was the pirate movie rated R
[ __ ] I want to know what the [ __ ]
happened to guitar solos I agree
we need some more of those where did
they go that's a great guitar solos I
feel like if I went to if I went to
someone who's like 10 or younger and I
was like oh like have like and I asked
if they even knew what a guitar solo was
I feel like they wouldn't know and
that's something that concerns me I
agree like the little kids know about
guitar solos or no oh it makes me sick
that they everybody better know about
guitar I think that a guitar solo is I
want a guitar solo next time we go on
tour I don't want to be playing it I
need someone there as I walk out to
like and like play a guitar solo see I
feel like I feel like drum solos are
kind of like o this or that drum solo or
guitar solo okay I think we need just
overall more solos I agree like get out
there do your thing individually
saxophone solos are really good I love
saxophone who what's that song I don't
know the freak one she's a very freaky
girl
[Music]
I slid on the side yeah bring back solos
this or that
oh that was good like come on that was
good guitar solo or Prime energy or
chili cheese dogs I'm not a fan of I've
never mind I have chili cheese fries the
other day and I regretted everything
where did you get chili cheese fries
with you nope yep where did you get oh I
got chili cheese fries ooh it went South
quick I asked it's just like one of
those things where the top layer is so
soggy so much chili and like G gross hot
tub bath bath Hot Tub a Bath's like a
personal tub yeah I'd rather be with the
friends I agree like if I ever sang and
I finish my
song I like it I like
czy thank you everybody all right what
else what else do you what else have a
good night thank you everybody have a
good night I love you I know I'm not on
top you didn't do
it you didn't even do it than everybody
have a good
night you're you're not doing it every
once in a while I like a good nightmare
I agree it adds some spruce up to your
life like I got a story right when I
wake up you know nightmare or daydream
nightmare nightmare Daydream it's like
let's just put some action daydreaming
is like oh like come on get up
daydreaming is not real daydreaming is
like hello anyone home like when I dream
in the
shower keep that to yourself dude no I
feel like you always make everything I
say weird no daydreaming is like dude
get up and do it you're awake hello like
there's no better time when I'm in the
shower there's no better time to not
dream than during the day I agree
when I'm in the shower I feel like
everything's possible I leave my shower
with a sense of I could rule the world
can I tell you guys another thing that
Everybody Wants to Rule the World okay I
think that like when my least favorite I
always have I always say my least
favorite thing or my biggest pet peeve
like I probably have a million on the
internet but currently my biggest every
pet peeve is your biggest one yeah I
guess currently my biggest pet peeve who
created that stupid
currently my biggest pet peeve is when
people say you wish after you say oh I
wish blank blank blank like if this is
Chris's crew neck and I like it and I go
oh I wish shut up thanks shh and I said
I wish I had this crew neck it's awesome
and then you said you wish it's like
yeah I just [ __ ] said I just said
that hello like if if someone expresses
a wish they have and your respond your
response is you wish sh light yourself
on fire light yourself on like correct
good job well just like you're telling
me what I told you you're saying what I
just [ __ ] said correct
disrespectfully yeah I'm having wishes
and you're saying you wish like it's a
bad thing I'm going to start doing that
as someone blows out their birthday cake
you wish like right away yeah cuz it's
like they like if they made a wish like
I just made it awkward believe in those
birthday wishes yeah well no cuz I
wasted my first 10 on raining gumballs
yeah where are they at nowhere yeah I
one of mine I vividly remember wishing
for every single Beanie Baby ever I just
wanted them all oh they're so cute I do
like beanie you ever get like really
depressed and wish for like a new
brother or something no what I never did
that either I'm just
asking feel like some did you ever wish
for jelly cheese rice you seen seen the
videos have you seen the videos and the
little kids like blows out his can and
the mom goes what did you wish for and
he goes a new mom like straight yeah
that's crazy that's crazy if my kid I
seen on Tik Tok this the grandparents go
to like the kids house like I've seen
like a compilation of it and like the
grandparents are like walking over to
like their grand kid's house and the
grandkid like runs around their Grandma
to their grandpa oh my God i' be if I
ever got swerved by a kid to go to
someone who they found more important
than me I was thinking about that the
other day no I would get if I got
swerved by a dog I'd be crushed I'm
going to start filling my pockets with
food and then walk by dogs and then when
people think that they love me so much
I'm just going like people will think
I'm just really connected with dogs but
I secretly have like bacon in mycket ham
is like a good dog treat come get some
ham
fluffy fluffy least favorite dog name I
think my least favorite thing is when
people name their dog off of like the
visual or like tactile experience of the
dog huh like if you scruffy yeah if you
pet a dog and he's like scruffy and like
they name him scruffy name one dog named
Scruffy scruffy no show or if you pet a
dog and they're fluffy and they're oh
fluffy the dog's name fluffy fluffly get
fluffly get a life hello fluffly or if
the dog's like brown and they name him
like brownie brownie
poopy name the the dog like got one spot
spot
spot that's cute I like spot like oh
you're spot but that's rude though to
just name them what they are you know
what's up triplet like that's how spot
would feel to me oh hi triplet hi
brother Hi boy like I'm more than that
boy you know yeah get pride pride fests
and they go hi Gay I hate manuals I'm
never reading it never ever wait this or
that manuals for your phone or manuals
for your car can you stop talking mullet
Nick or regular
Nick um um do you guys like Christmas
fluffy or spot do you guys like
Christmas lights I love them Christmas
lights Halloween decorations Halloween
Halloween decorations Christmas I love
Halloween I like good like just like
powerful
hose like a power like a power hose like
a powerful hose I love it I love a
powerful hose just like like if you
could turn on a hose and it like wao
like it kind of like a fire hose is so
impressive to me like if you no your
feet get lifted a little yeah like have
you ever seen those videos of the people
that open that big fish bag and it soaks
it out into the ocean and all the fish
are flying out of the
trash it sounds like you have a dream
yeah it's like a big tube that leads to
the ocean and it like connected to a
truck and they open up this like bag and
like water and fish come flying out no
no I didn't never seen no clue what
you're talking about people just dump
fish and it's like and then sometimes
like if they don't miscalculate they
have fish everywhere like fish all over
the place and it's all supposed to go in
the ocean you've never seen these no oh
my God they're so satisfying to me like
they just open up this big bag of like
it look like a trash bag and it's
connect to this car boom water and
fish going down into the river and then
fish start swimming like crazy they want
to escape so
bad
that's hold on I'll show you I'll show
you I hate little birds that just could
just Peck into your soul soul is crazy I
don't think they can do imagine like a
bird heavily just like flying at you and
pecking into your body it's crazy crazy
I love them I love birds birs no you
don't yeah I do I'm like afraid of
rodents I asked my grandma the other day
what her favorite animal was she goes
she didn't say a bird she goes she
starts whistling like what are you doing
she's like a bird I'm like you're crazy
I love
rodents little rodent saw a video of
this guy and he do camping
trips camping trips and there was there
was and there was what you got to bite
through your fingers there's mice in a
sleeping bag you can tell them there was
mice in a sleeping bag oh my God why you
whisper
that don't
don't what are you doing I don't know I
felt like getting crazy okay get crazy
get wild come on good night everybody
the holiday Adventure videos were fun I
agree and I loved filming them I love
Christmas time content it's super fun
and super amazing too I agree um what
else was I going to say guys me and is
this our closest video that we're
dropping to the new year yeah yeah can
we get real sentimental this the last
video of
20203 a the last video of 2023 is it
really is it wow it is is it wow guys
what an amazing 2023 it's been we're not
going to get too much into detail right
now of like recapping on the year cuz
our next podcast and no our last podcast
was kind of already about that so you
guys already kind of know how that went
for us but it's been a it's been a
journey it's it's been a experience it's
been it's been what did we start this
year off with tour the first tour no
like like number wise we hit 4 million
on the on the first tour so we like 3.8
or 3.9 mil
wow don't I'm sorry I'm never going to
do it again yeah if you're new to the
stolo family here thank you for joining
us if you're not subscribed and you're
watching subscribe down below yeah cuz
we have a really exciting year coming up
yeah 2024 going to be a really great
year me Matt and Chris are up to a lot
of plotting and lots of scheming yeah so
much stuff going I'm so excited for 2024
I've never in my life been so like
looking forward to the transition of a
year me either I've like never been more
prepared I'm going to do everything I'm
going to eat grapes under the table I'm
going to wish my best to everyone else
around to get good karma back I'm going
to do every superti I can I'm going to
get all the black cats and put them in a
street somewhere else not near me no
one's crossing my path path and then I'm
going to get all the ladders closed them
every Superstition thing for the new
year not happening to me I'm going to
light for what else can I do for Good
Fortune there's three of us we should
all do something in threes like eat
three raisins or eat three well think
the best thing to do is to go into the
new year together would be to all kiss
on the New Year's Eve I feel like it's
going to be hard cuz there's three of us
so we have to think of something else
yeah we just do it like kind of like all
together as like a triangle no why no
you should just kind of interlock toes
like
this like little Talons Big Bird like
that that that that dude can we talk
about how dangerous and scary Big Bird
from Sesame Street actually is Big Bird
oo he's a big Goofy I'm kind of like a
snow leopard perched on a rock and the
year is the the scene that I'm looking
at I'm like this right looking where I
want to conquer and I'm just waiting to
dive yes I like your metaphors thank you
it really sets you in it makes more in
like
but with the new year on wait this or
that 2023 2024 both um this or that um
Matt or
Nick can't
pick this or that um Chris or Matt like
the video go down there and click that
like button and while you're down there
the Subscribe button is so close so just
click that as well so you we to 6
million I didn't want to bring my up so
that you never miss a video and we have
so much planned for 2024 you guys have
no idea you're going to like we're going
to we're going to I'm out of stern
little hibernation we're in like these
little like rocks and leaves right now
we're going to make our way out this I'm
going to crawl into a rock and I'm going
to
go that's me and that's more deep than
you think no it's not yes it is that
would actually make a good gift for
Christmas that would make a perfect gift
for Christmas okay wait do the thing do
the thing good night everybody I love
you so much
the things that we did we said we going
to travel from the island to Madrid we
had a lot of plans but they
alled why oh because of some but it's
I'm
moving [ __ ] my brother