if you try to accommodate all of the
advices that you get from your mentors
your company will most likely become
like an underwear company totally
different from what you wanted to build
having some fundamental like foundation
for yourself and for the company and be
able to say thank you for your advice
but no thank you right so having that
the gut to say no to someone that you
you respect as a Founder I think I grew
a lot hi yo my name is Jay I'm one of
the co-founders and CEO of 12 Labs 12
Labs is an AI research and product
company based here in San Francisco and
so we're building video Foundation
models for developers and Enterprises
building video Centric product we
basically build humongous AI models that
can understand videos like humans and we
serve it to developers via apis that are
looking into building really powerful
semantic search or classification or
summarization into their product we
currently have a little over 20,000
developers that are actively using our
search API we have large creators of the
world adopting 12 Labs as well as uh
media entertainment and large Sports
organizations and law
enforcement so I was born in Soul I
spent about 10 years in Soul uh I had a
chance to move to the states I moved
when I was 11 so went through Elementary
and Middle School in Knoxville Tennessee
I was able to pick up a lot of the the
the culture and and and things like that
I was uh very interested in expanding my
perspective and uh exploring the new
world my first experience with software
engineering or at least coding was uh
met lab my uncle uh was actually getting
his PhD at the University of Tennessee
so I I see him kind of like plotting
this distribution graphs and things like
that and which made me curious what what
he was doing that's how I got into
playing around with like small data sets
and doing the same thing that he he was
doing because I wanted to be relevant
and I wanted to talk to him about a
bunch of things he probably thought what
I was doing was pretty cute which
sparked my interest in learning more
about how do we capture all this data
and be able to create a system that can
really understand the distributions of
the things of the world and it just kind
of felt like if you had the
understanding of that it gives you power
predict anything and I went to Berkeley
for college and study computer science
so I really geeked out on AI and and
software engineering um so spent about
15 years uh in the United States um so
half of my life in Soul and in the
states I was dra Ed into uh this
organization called Korean cyber command
where like-minded people were already
there um with Incredible knowledge and
software engineering and and and AI I
joke about it you know I served the
country with keyboards rather than than
than a rifle I was really fortunate to
have met my Chief Architect SJ and then
Aiden kind of also joined in US you I
still clearly remember Aiden with this
buzz cut coming in from from boot camp
but from day one uh we knew we had this
common interest in Ai and what can we do
as a as a young scientist really like
push the frontier of AI development and
we've spent a lot of times reading
papers discussing arguing and it turned
out there were two clear paths uh one
was after military we go personal career
in Academia go become a professor or
start something of our own and looking
back what we realized is that we were
spending so much time together and
Military is this really special setting
where you know you're basically jamming
in 50 to 100 12 year olds right with
testosterones and what we thought was
you know if we're having this much fun
in military imagine what we can do when
we go out so it was pretty clear to us
that we're going to start I think we've
spent about year and a half really
thinking about what is the next Frontier
for AI and how can we contribute to
pushing that boundary there's this
seminal paper called attention is all
you need which some people call it the
Transformer paper which is making a lot
of impact now but when it was published
in 2017 at least for text and
image-based you know Foundation models
probably Capital was going to be a mode
whoever raises most amount of money what
we realized was there's still a lot of
unexplored research areas for multimodal
video understanding there rather than
capital is probably going to be really
passionate smart but also slightly dumb
people that's like dumb enough to start
it will have really good chance of
succeeding and also we've realized that
with the explosion of that video and and
other complex multimedia data is going
to be the infrastructural data for the
internet and we realized that probably
developers and Enterprises need
something better than object detection
or or transcription to make sense of all
all this video data that the humanity is
creating so it was like a no-brainer to
start building for video understanding
the model that 12 Labs is building it's
basically trying to map human language
into whatever that's happening in video
content so if you can map precise human
language to whatever that's happening
within video content that gives you this
emergence capabilities like being able
to search for things really well or
being able to classify things or
summarize you know we didn't All Join
the Korean cyber command at the same
time so SJ was already like 6 months
ahead of me and then Aiden was 6 months
behind so like okay we we decided we're
going to we're going to start this
company but then SJ is like leaving like
next year and then I'm leaving the year
after and then Aiden's like 6 months
after so how do we do it so it was
genuinely very scary so we had our ideas
I remember SJ was discharged on Thursday
and he came back to the military base
Saturday of that week with our laptops
and he took us out in front of our
military base there was a bagel shop
called Las vagel and that was like our
office where SJ would bring all of our
laptops and we would do our research and
and do some little little bit of
prototyping and we did that for 6 months
and then I got this charge and I did the
whole laptop carrying and and picking
out Aiden so we did that for like a good
like year so that everyone is out and
then we had a bunch of friends that were
working in Ai and crypto and blockchain
and and and web 3 was just booming and
we had a mutual friend like the founders
had a mutual friend that had like a
really nice office in Soul and he was
like oh you guys can come in and and use
our office space uh so that's what we
did and then after like 3 weeks that
company went bankrupt and then really
scary like people started coming in and
and we had like our desktops and our
gpus all set up there and we got really
scared so we brought everything back out
and we found like really tiny tiny
office probably like a size of a
dressing room uh that's where like all
five of us kind of spent uh the next 6
months uh before uh we raised our proper
seat ground looking back if we were to
do it again I don't know it we'll be
able to do it but some people say
ignorance is bliss and I think we were
just like really naive and just really
excited about building this company and
I guess not knowing what was ahead um
allowed us to kind of do what we
did hi all I'm J from EO I have a quick
question for you which is the better
prompt if you're looking to use AI to
apply directly to your workflow I would
say this one does the job this promp was
made using the five essential resources
for using chat GPT at work a free bundle
of AI resources provided by HubSpot our
amazing partner the bundle has the
following resources tips on implementing
Chad GPT at work in various professional
settings The Ultimate Guide for adopting
AI at work checklist to make sure your
AI generated content feels authentic and
more for this prompt I use templates for
setting CER guidelines which gives
simple guides to dramatically improve
your prompting and results using chat
GPT the best part is that it has over
100 prompts that you can use right away
so you don't have to start from scratch
so for anyone who's tried really hard to
use the power of AI at work give this
tool kit a try down for free using the
link in description and start
supercharging your workflow with AI
thanks to hopspot for sponsoring our
video now back to the
video when we first started a company
and we hired our first employees they
had hard time explaining what 12 Labs
does to their parents really new thing
what is foundation model what is video
understanding It's A New Concept that's
hard to understand for I guess uh people
that are not in the space nowadays
people talk about the foundation layer
the tooling layer and the application
layer it all everyone's very familiar uh
when we started 12 Labs I think
technologically it made total sense we
knew it was going to happen but what was
uncertain about it was Will Market
accept but knowing that we are at the
verge of breakthrough in building an AI
that can at least you know get to
certain level of human understanding of
videos so we were betting on Market's
acceptance of foundation models the
founders are pretty pretty much broke
right because we spent 2 years at at
military and I think we had
$22,000 uh to start with so barely
barely enough to do anything but
figuring out what was going to be
impactful that we can do given our
current resources that'll put us in the
map or at least you know let the world
know that what we're doing is relevant
so our tactic here was okay we're going
to talk to a bunch of customers and
there were early Believers in 12 Labs
who took our apis and built awesome
things with us but we needed more more
exposure basically so as a team we've
decided uh to participate in icb's its
International Conference in computer
vision they're putting this like awesome
competition for video understandings so
we talked to Aiden we have nothing to
lose and only to gain the team was
extremely supportive of of Aiden
spearheading that effort with the team
all I can do to support is you know
there was some ideas and and directional
kind of feedback that I gave to Aiden
but we needed compute and we needed
determination to put some serious cash
behind and back then for 12 laps like
$200,000 in in compute was was a lot of
money for us right so and just thinking
that okay we're going to blow through
$200,000 in 10 days in compute was
really scary but the team was able to
use that Capital that that precious
capital and build something incredible
helped us win the competition um so I
think the important thing is if you're
building something really impact full
and you think that it's going to
significantly change the industry that
you're in there will always be someone
that has very similar thesis it's just a
matter of how do you get yourself out
there how do you let the people know
that you you you exist for us that was
the competition after winning the
competition companies like index
Ventures and radical Ventures had very
strong thesis around multimodal AI the
next idea would be what's next and video
happens to be the most relatable
multimodal data these amazing companies
actually came in inbound and so they
reached out to us and we started jamming
the conversations turned into next
conversation and then we talked about
technology and and it just happened very
serendipitously right the first pitch
deck I was in Soul and and my first uh
call with index Ventures was at like I
it was like 3:30 a.m. Soul time and we
didn't have pitch deck and we just felt
like hm this is our first meeting and we
we we knew nothing about fundraising
then we didn't even know this was going
to be like a friendly introduction but I
just kind of felt the need to like oh we
don't have pitch Tech we need to build
one so I remember staying up till like
3:00 a.m. building it I think the
storyline was like quite simple we
didn't have much to much to show for it
the idea was hey the problem that we're
solving is massive 80% of the world's
data is in video and there's no adequate
solution out there or technology out
there for developers and Enterprises to
make sense of it all that is the market
that we're we're tackling we want to
index all of that like 80% of the
world's data and this is the technology
underlying research work that we've done
and then that was it VC's asked a lot of
hard questions the most memorable one if
I bring you Tik Tok as a customer and
they want to index like billion hours of
content how long does it take and I
think we were we were thinking about
maybe like a million hours going to take
like 10 years right that's when we
realize we should never be comfortable
of with what we've built this whole new
incredibly large world out there you
know that maybe some people are
impressed with our system being able to
index like a million hour but there's
others that are thinking about billion
10 billion 100 billion hours and that
was like a really challenging question
because like what we said during our
pitches we want to index all of the
world's videos and that question kind of
made me stun and I think about all of
the technical issues that that we had at
the time you probably find it like funny
right I was trying to give my best
answer as a Founder in like so the
company has raised about $30 million uh
in seed
funding my name is so young I'm one of
the co-founders of 12 lots and I
currently lead our business development
and go to market we had a customer who
was paying for our product um but they
weren't actually using it um but we had
gone through a lot of work to actually
get them as a customer through a lot of
sales and kind of relationship building
and so on but I think they were they
know were extremely early and we had
almost pushed the sales to happen and I
think what we learned from that
experience was we have to optimize even
early on it might have been better for
us to not actually make the sale because
the customer probably wasn't ready they
didn't have the passion or the
Innovative drive that our other
customers had had but we were optimizing
for kind of hearing the yes we tried so
hard to make that no into a yes and we
had succeeded but at the at the end I
think it turned out that we probably
should have kept it out of no and
focused on all the other customers where
the yes was very more clear and they had
a very clear vision of how they can you
know build their new experiences with
the the technology and especially for
earlier products and earlier
Technologies where resources are limited
and you want to you know build for your
Mo best customers and the innovators in
every field uh you should probably start
to optimize for hearing the no uh then
the yes because that will help you find
the right direction faster we quickly I
think we learned through trial and error
that the types of companies that we need
to early customers that we need to find
and work with are true innovators in
their field uh whether they come from
like the content creation space law
enforcement space e-learning and so on
you know we've had instances of trying
to oversell we were going through sales
you know sales 101 books or like sales
methodologies and we were trying to
pitch to the customer hey here's the use
case you could build out with our you
know with our technology you know we'll
improve your Roi by x% with our
technology and we did make some sales
from those but I don't think it was
something that we probably should have
you know spent so much time on doing
because if you find the right customer
who's Innovative you don't need to
explain anything to them you show them
uh a use case based demo of you know for
us it would be and we we would index uh
some videos that resemble the customers
and then we show them how you can search
or you can generate text very easily
like a like just like a person would um
had they been watching the video they
can draw out the full map of okay this
is what I want to provide to my
customers or my users uh this is a
technology that you have and I can and
they can you know fill that Gap in
pretty easily and they know already uh
what the return on that or what the
opportunity of that experience would be
for them for the kind of really large
high-profile customers that we have
right now it was all the same process we
actually learned all of these from the
customers because they had you know
seeing our demo and seeing the early
hints of the technology uh they were
able to teach us about how they could
utilize the technology and even today
it's not just a single use case that
they want to power uh they come to us
with four or five different ideas of how
you know the technology can impact
different units different business units
um and different you know optimize
different workflows or build new
experiences I think we we make stupid
mistakes probably every day the one that
I regret the most is we knew we had like
this conviction around building a
foundation model but then we didn't have
any data point as to how do you build
that company and I think I blindingly
kind of believe that the startup montra
like identifying a narrow problem and
building a very narrow solution for it I
think we've spent a lot of early days
thinking about okay if we have this
really powerful AI that can understand
videos what do we do with it and we know
we know from the from the gecko that we
wanted to servey to developers and
Enterprises but I think you know we've
had mentors and and and and other
Founders like oh you should build Tik
Tok 2.0 or you should build like YouTube
2.0 or you should build that and I think
we've spent a lot of time thinking okay
maybe like Tik Tok 2.0 makes sense or
maybe like gong 2.0 like sales call
analysis but that didn't really like
excite us because we knew like we're
good at building the infrastructure and
and helping developers build the next
thing and that's probably the stupidest
thing that we've done it's like spending
time on thinking about things that we're
not excited about as a founder and see
it's really hard to get distracted if
you're a firsttime founder or a young
founder your mentor's advice means a lot
to you but having like your own
grounding having your own also re like
relying a little bit on your own gut
feeling is very important because what
we've realized if you try to accommodate
all of the advices that you get from
your mentors your company will most
likely become like an underwear company
totally different from what you wanted
to build so my key takeaway is having
some fundamental like foundation for
yourself and for the company and be able
to say thank you for your advice but no
thank you right so having that the gut
to say no to someone that you you
respect as a Founder I think I grew a
lot right 12 Labs has multi-year Compu
partnership with Oracle Cloud
infrastructure where we get all of the
uh state-of-the-art and media chips and
Oracle had put together uh this small
event for their key partners that are
building Foundation models for and Aiden
and I had chance to meet with Jensen
because Jensen was at that event and we
had I think 5 to 10 minutes to talk
about 12 laps and I think it seems like
he had he has a special uh place in his
heart about computer vision and video
understanding is you know that was one
of the first use cases that Nvidia chips
powered so we we got to uh meet with
like Nvidia folks from that event and
then 12 laps was featured in nvidia's
2023 GTC and I think that kind of
sparked other people from Nvidia to be
interested in 12 labs and the mvidia
Venture team reached out to us it was
quite casual we were talking about 12
labs and the future that we're drawing
and the future of multimodal video
understanding and I think the Venture
team also had an idea of how Nvidia and
12 laps can partner up more than just
Financial investment but also think
about really robust product partnership
from then on what 12 leps is doing and
what Nvidia want in vision and video
understanding was just like a perfect
match it happen quite uh naturally from
from conversing our our technology our
road map and and mvidia future in terms
of like producing really powerful uh
chips for Edge devices uh for smart
cities right so there's that natural fit
of two companies product really creating
Synergy nowadays I am focusing mostly on
hiring so I think 12 Labs is group of
great people I spend a lot of time
meeting great people I want to be able
to recognize greatness when he or she
comes in good Engineers or even like
just good people in general have this
core values I would go uh near their
places and get together at a cafe and we
would speak for 3 4 hours my way of
deciding whether this person is a good
fit for 12 laps is like I am able to
learn from their core values everyone's
really good at coding nowadays but great
Engineers can apply their core values
and their skill set and is able to talk
about the company that they're excited
about and how they want to impact it how
do you see the product evolving how do
you see our interfaces evolving the best
some of the best Engineers are not the
best coder but having that perspective
really strong perspective and and
groundedness is very important and and I
try to look for that 12 LA's Vision in
the next two years is really uh becoming
horizontal video understanding
infrastructures for all of the
businesses and developers that are
working with video data we want to enter
into uh streaming as well so real- time
uh video data and uh really become a
visual cortex for modern video
applications
[Music]