go to too many events good for the ego
really aren't progressing a mistake you
make is thinking your line then you have
too many alternate pivots or agendas
where I spent nearly a decade in sales
and marketing roles challenges have a
history of repeating themselves there
are patterns we have people problems
product Market fit issues financing
issues ETC but what I've learned is my
name is Jason zint I'm the CEO of
sixense sixense is AI Big Data driven
sales and marketing platforms last 7
years we went from 5 million in ARR to
200 million completed our Series E $200
million fund raise at 5.2 billion in
valuation that was roughly a year and a
half ago 2000 customers a great cap
table of Marquee
investors customer acquisition in the
early days is very tough because why
trust why trust the startup with an idea
everyone finds a way or a relationship
for that first customer again it comes
down to solving the problem if you can
help someone solve a problem and you
find a friend a fan usually through a
relationship you might find someone to
trust you and give you a shot you need
to be vulnerable to these customers
saying can someone give me a chance you
need to lean on a relationship and you
need to bring something of value if you
find those aspects you can probably get
a customer and then you have to try like
hell to retain them satisfy them keep
them and make them better more than ever
we're now in a macro that's more
difficult post pandemic and that's all
around high value High return does it
help me do my job better more
efficiently with a dollar return and and
so we're focused on a mutual success
plan with our customers we set that plan
we communicate the plan add Innovation
and they'll give you honest feedback
feedback is a gift may be painful we've
lost customers along the way but we get
the feedback I think the big mistake is
not looking yourself in the mirror as a
company judging where you actually are
in your journey optimizing changing
pivoting adapting around that feedback
in B2B SAS world it's all about
retention and retention of a customer
retain your customer and can you cross
sell up sell down so what's the magic
quite often we find your buyers leave a
company the next year you've got to
renew your original sponsors aren't
there or what do you do because the
proclivity is new executive new tool and
so yeah we're faced with that as well
there's really one thing if the Baton
gets passed on your product to another
executive will they find Value in it for
us I really focus Less on the sales
strategies around human intervention and
tactics to relate with these exec have
we proven it up value through product
and delivery and Adoption of it that
when the next person comes in the door
they can see it and feel it such that
they aren't tempted to replace them with
their buddies from another past
relationship this comes back to our
mutual success plans that we write with
our customers if it's documented and we
achieve it those measurements should be
able to pass along to the next exec at
the end of the day it's just does the
product work and work well it will be
talked about inside the company if
that's the
case common mistake is sort of getting
too excited in the hype of a startup and
that around a fundrais and a concept and
it's all very energizing and toxicating
in a way at the end of the day you have
real work to do in order to be a high
performing team everyone needs to get on
board with our objective and go for it a
mistake you make is thinking you're
aligned and then you have too many
alternate pivots or agendas it is common
to really just get distracted go to too
many events really aren't progressing
good for the ego but not necessarily the
agenda of the company it's not
necessarily about the product we invest
in teams many many startups start with
one idea and end with a completely
different ultimately finds product
Market fit smart people goodw workking
teams figure it out but what they're EMB
betting on and what I can tell you I've
lived it's the team that makes the
difference that nucleus of team and
Leadership is Paramount it's not only in
the product but show up in the culture
and the eepos of your company by the way
it's one brick at a time to build the
house I joined at 30 and we're now over
1,200 constantly message uh what's
important to us and people like identify
and those that identify stay and those
that don't leave and that's that's
appropriate cuz you can't be all things
to all people there's no shortage of
leadership books that talk about making
tough decisions leadership is lonely you
have to make the call instally I don't
find leadership at all lonely I like
working with my team and I find us to be
more of a family and I lean on them when
I'm lonely so it's not a big deal but
the tough call is at the same time this
isn't personal this is a job you know
this is a business our responsibility is
to be The Shepherd of the Investments
financially like the money we raise as
well as the people we hire the true nor
should always be is it the right thing
for the business and then everything
else is explainable and makes sense you
know I like to say we're an a company we
deserve a people why would you settle
for anything less like why you now if
you're an a you get A's you you are an a
you act like an A and you're higher a by
the way a a people want to work with a
people so you got to make the tough call
decisions at age get more expensive with
time so make them quickly
do you use cenly to book calls todoist
to manage tasks Trello to keep track of
projects what if I told you that you
could do all these with one tool but
then it also integrates with all of the
tools that I just mentioned hi everyone
I'm Hannah from the EO team and I'm here
to introduce the gamechanging
productivity tool akif flow it's
basically a smart combination of all the
essential productivity features I need
on the daily first is the beautiful
marriage of task management and time
blocking akif flow has this interface
where you can create a to-do list just
as you would in any task management
tools but you can also drag these
certain tasks right into your calendar
to the exact time of day I find this
particular visualization of todos and
schedules side by side very helpful in
prioritizing my work carving out chunks
of focus time needed for video editing
blocking time here syncs with all of my
other connected apps such as slack Ken
Lee and more secondly it's the magical
command bar the go-to shortcut for all
features within akif flow instead of
navigating the app manually I simply
click on the command bar to command what
I wish to perform for example let's just
say that we confirmed an interview
filming and I want to put that in my
calendar I could just set that up
manually on a Google Calendar or I could
simply go ahead and type akif flow
founder interview filming on October
28th from 12:00 p.m. to 3:00 p.m. and
there's my schedule we've been using it
to keep track of our hectic filming and
traveling schedules every
day say most effective is to be in given
my experience in sales nearly 30 years
is to be an informed seller a lot of
sales is not how slick can you be in
your presentation it's much more what do
I need to know what can I question or
get out of my Prospect and customer to
be relevant and so I think the biggest
job in sales is actually being informed
or asking the questions to help them
solve their problems as much as you can
know the more responsible you'd be in
your Outreach and personalizing your
Communication channel in the ensuing
message if you're asking me how do I
relate to our customers that's really
just back to the be curious and ask
questions most people proclivity is to
react first really you should listen and
ask more and lastly on you know asking
questions you got to care too many
people ask the question don't care and
don't deliver a result and if you care
for your customer you'll inevitably
build a better product that delivers
better results entering a new market
Market sort of being a young team you
need to be different somehow some way
and you need to appeal emotional aspect
of why people buy not the feature
function people react to emotions the
brain works that way and what is your
purpose as a company what are you
delivering the why someone would
consider the new Acme company and so
you've got to strike a chord and you're
messaging why 6 cents or why new Acme Co
reduce to the core and simplify your
focus what resonates with the customer
why do they buy your product or service
I think in past experiences challenges
seem to be similar and have a history of
repeating themselves how do we bring
these products to Market what are the
challenges in growing the company there
are patterns we have people problems
product Market fit issues financing
issues ETC but what I've learned is sort
of remain calm these are normal I've
learned to ask more questions that helps
us get to the root of problems as we're
trying to solve any of those matters
patience for sure is a virtue exercise
calm in the storm so that people
understand that leadership and that
resolve uh it's a big worlds leverage
your network learn listen be humble
probably the best thing I can say and
have fun doing it that should guide you
and teach you
[Music]