[Music]
I'm Jonathan Tory. And I'm his brother,
Alex Tori. And we live in Athens,
Georgia.
Okay, let's try the guacamole.
I come from a super tight-knit Mexican
family, so it's no surprise that we have
a business together and the whole family
pitches in.
Can I help?
We've developed a unique fashion brand
called Uman. We know that clothing is a
really great way to express your
creativity and we want to build a
fashion brand that has a really positive
social impact.
Pops, can you make sure we order some
more ink?
Jonathan and I put everything into
Umano. We move back home with our
parents. We share a room like we did
when we were 7 years old. We did that
willingly because we really believe that
UMANO has tremendous potential.
We're going to do two black V-necks.
Yeah, we got them right here. Because of
our mission, there's a lot of people
counting on us that we want UManu to be
able to help. But now with increasing
demand, we're missing opportunities
because we don't have as much inventory
as we should. We hope the Sharks will
join our movement where you can look
good and do good.
[Applause]
[Music]
Hi Sharks. My name is Jonathan and this
is my little brother Alex. We're from
Athens, Georgia and we're seeking
$150,000
for 15% equity in our business. Omano is
fashion for good. We design men's and
women's elevated fashion basics with a
personalized meaning to connect people
to a bigger purpose. The awesome artwork
you see here is curated from some of the
most amazing upand cominging artists.
Kids, sharks, meet Jessica. She drew the
skull and wants to be a teacher.
How old is she?
She's seven.
Wearing Omano is a badge of pride and
it's a pledge because with every product
you purchase, Umano will give a backpack
full of school supplies to empower young
creative minds. Investing in Omano means
that you don't have to choose between
doing well and doing good. So, who wants
to take a ride with us on this elephant,
the tiny dancer drawn by 5-year-old
Emmanuel, or this bike, the Fixie drawn
by future firefighter Reuben?
We have handpicked some of our favorite
designs to show you, and we'll share
them with you now.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, John.
You're very welcome.
Thank you,
Mr. Wonderful. Thank you very much.
You're very welcome. Thank you. Thank
you.
It's really nice. Feels soft. We have
traveled the world literally to get that
fabric.
First of all, how much is it and how do
I buy it?
Those shirts that you have, they start
retailing at $48. We are sold at
Bloomingdales. We are sold at specialty
stores across the country and through
our website.
Does it have the child's picture hanging
at Bloomingdales?
Yes. The way it's hang tagged is with
the hang tag that you currently see on
it.
Does the child or the parents, do they
get a royalty? So the way it's
structured now is that we have a really
good relationship with all of our
partner schools. We give the backpacks
full of school supplies, collect the
drawings, come back to Athens, Georgia
to create the artwork. So as the brand
expands, we will expand the giving.
Can I ask is this a business or is this
a charity?
We are a business 100%.
So your pursuit is for profit.
The concept of social entrepreneurship
is right in the last 5 years, right?
People walk in, particularly
millennials, they don't just walk in and
buy a product. They walk in and buy a
cause.
But to sustain it, you've got to make a
profit.
Well, no, they go hand in hand. That's
we have the margins to do that.
The t-shirt is $48. Walk me how much you
pay for it. And then how much the gift
bag costs that goes back.
Retail $48.
Okay.
The cost of the product $7. The backpack
and school supplies is $4. So we load up
total at 11. We have a 48% margin. Plus,
where are these schools? Are they in
countries of need?
We have schools everywhere. We have
partner schools overseas in places like
Mexico and Peru where we manufacture in
Haiti, but also right here at home in
Athens, Georgia for us, Los Angeles,
Harlem, New York.
What were your sales last year and what
will you do this year?
Last year we sold $106,000.
This year we're scheduled to close at
250,000.
Getting into Bloomingdale's is so hard.
How did that happen?
It's not just getting into Bloomingdale,
but the doors we're in. We're in 59th
Street. We're in Soho. We're in the
flagship stores. The reason we got in is
because of the story.
Do you guys have any inventory right
now?
We do.
How much is that?
8,000 units. Those 8,000 are already
sold.
Do you plan to be a t-shirt company or
what's the full expansion of the land?
We absolutely want to be a lifestyle
brand and we can actually show you a
preview of our spring 16 line.
That's cool.
These are dresses. These are rompers.
These are leggings, hoodies, zip up. And
that's just on the women's side.
Guys, let's say you get to 10 million in
sales. Do you think there's any risk
that people turn around and say, "Let me
get this right. The children get a bag
worth four bucks. You guys are now
making $4 million a year in profit
pre-tax. It's child labor."
I mean, I could see a negative story
developing here. You worried about it?
That's definitely not one of the reasons
why the bigger brands can't go in and do
what we're doing. This is grassroots.
Why can't they do that?
Because they're the ones that going to
be under the greatest microscope.
Correct.
It's an important point for us to make
that as the brand grows, we will grow
the giving.
I think the designs are beautiful and I
applaud you for the cause. I agree with
you that people today care about what
they're buying and why they're buying
it. Absolutely. So, you're really a
design company with a great cause.
Tough business because designs are like
restaurants. Something's hot today, it's
not hot tomorrow.
I see a lot of risk. I'm out.
Thank you very much. And on that note,
as you guys have already mentioned, for
us, millennials are are expanding. By
2018, they will surpass the purchasing
power of baby boomers. And those our
favorite brands are being discovered
right now. Guys, let me take a shot at
it. Look, it's very creative and it's
good-looking stuff. We've seen a lot of
t-shirts come through the Shark Tank
door. This is different. There's no
question about it.
[Music]
But it's embriionic.
Maybe you can find a shark that wants to
start your journey here. I don't know.
It's not me. I'm a
Thank you very much.
What's holding you guys back? What can
we answer? What's
You said the 8,000 units were already
sold. Where are they going
to fulfill the the Bloomingdales orders
until December
and you don't have the money to go out
and source more?
Correct. Our biggest challenge is
inventory and we are missing
opportunities. Blooms is asking for more
doors. We can't do that.
You guys are scrappy. You have a cool
look. I like entrepreneurs that are
willing to do whatever it takes. You
guys seem that way to me.
Thank you.
And I like your mission. I'm going to
give you an offer.
I'm going to give you 150,000 but for
25%.
[Music]
you know, you're just starting. There's
a lot of design work to do. There's more
sourcing to do. I think that I can help
you a lot with that.
Thank you.
So,
that's that's amazing offer.
Congratulations. You made an offer. We
really appreciate it. There are are two
more sharks. We want to make sure that I
mean,
you know, I've been in this business for
quite some time.
I have maybe one brand in Bloomingdales
and I had to beg to get there. So,
we did a lot of begging. I have to I
have to congratulate you on that.
I would have to offer the 150k for 33
and the third.
Thank you very much for your offer.
You now have two offers.
And here's why I'm worth the third. It's
going to be all three of us working at
it.
I just know I bring a different skill
set.
And those are two amazing offers and we
really appreciate it. Jonathan and I
have worked
given everything we have.
We still have Mr. Correct. So we would
love to hear from I love what you guys
are doing. Really, where you need the
help isn't in the sales. You need credit
basically and you need online help.
Correct.
I'll make an offer of 150K for 20%. I'll
give you the option if Lori wants to
come in or Damon wants to come in.
That's fine. Just because it's a good
cause. So, but I'm happy to do it by
myself.
I go in with you.
Damon. Any
I have no need for non-Clo individuals
in my deal.
What an interesting situation. Damon
John, who's the fashion guru, wants to
be an equal partner. He's offered you
$150,000 for 33 and a3%. Mark and Lori,
who don't have the same experience in
fashion, are willing to give you the
same amount of money for only 20%. This
is one of the rare times in Shark Tank
history where two sharks are asking for
less equity than one.
What are you going to do?
It's a little brother's call.
Damon, we we really thank you for your
offer. We need to be able to protect
some of that equity so that we can raise
more money in the future. We would love
to make a deal with my
So, we have a deal.
We have a deal.
Awesome.
I can't wait to see the stoic.
I love it.
Oh my god.
E.
Thank you guys.
I'm keeping the shirt.
Yes, it's all yours. Thank you. Thank
you. Congrats.
Through our journey, we've probably
heard a 100 nos to one yes.
100,000 nos.
So, these yeses really help not only
build our own confidence, but also the
teams that we are on the right track.
I'm Eric. And I'm Sasha. And our company
is Buckmason. And we're based in Los
Angeles, California. American men are
ready for a different type of fashion
brand. One that's rooted in completely
different sensibilities, not connected
to fashion. This is a real truck of
shell button.
And you have a business model that
simplifies the shopping experience and
makes it impossible for guys to mess up.
How's the neckline this time?
20 and 38, baby. Americanade is
absolutely a priority for us. Most
people don't know that less than 2% of
clothing purchased in America is
actually made in America.
We really need to press the collar out
and get all the wrinkles out. The idea
of not having a personal relationship
with the craftsman making our jeans,
making our shirts, just didn't make
sense to us. Told me 88 bucks. Since
we've launched less than a year ago, our
business has been growing rapidly, and
every new product that we create sells
out immediately. We need this investment
to create enough inventory to keep up
with demand. The sharks shouldn't invest
in us just because we're made in
America. They should invest in us
because we're proving that Americanmade
can actually be profitable. And we're
doing that day after day.
[Music]
Hi Sharks. I'm Eric Schnockerberg
and I'm Sasha Conn. We're from Los
Angeles, California. Our company is Buck
Mason where we're seeking $200,000 in
exchange for 8% of our company.
Growing up, I always thought my father
dressed cool. He wore the exact same
thing every day. Beat up blue jeans, a
white V-neck tea, and a flannel work
shirt. He was a brickmason, so I guess
he wasn't trying to look cool. He was
simply dressing out of function.
These days, it's pretty easy for a guy
to get overwhelmed when it comes to
shopping. Too many choices, too many
trends, too many products coming from
countries we've never even heard of.
We've created Buckmason to provide
highquality Americanmade clothing at an
accessible price point. We focus on the
basics like the perfect t-shirt, the
quintessential blue jean, and the
classic Oxford shirt. On our website, we
show our customers how our products are
being made and who's actually making
them. We call this Americanmade price
transparency. At BuckMason, we're
ignoring fashion trends. It's not about
standing out or fitting in. It's about
taste. And listen, we're not your
ordinary fashion designers. We're two
Midwestern guys obsessed with reclaiming
American quality. Sharks, who wants to
help us build the next great American
clothing brand.
Can we see some of the clothes?
Sasha's going to hand you some.
Thank you.
Yeah, save my size for me. Got my 28
inch waist.
Oh, this feels nice.
So, Eric, walk me through how I buy it.
Where do I get them?
Sure.
Uh, we sell our products direct to
consumer online through the Buckmason
website.
There's two ways to purchase product.
One is the individual single items,
which, as you can see, are really
wearable.
They're cool now, they'll be cool 50
years from now. There is another way
that we sell merchandise on the site and
that's through curated packages. So what
we do is we put together three to six
pieces that you cannot mess up. The
reason why it would work for you is
because it's for guys that are just
busy, you know, guys that don't have
time to shop
or guys have no fashion sense.
And what do you charge for a pair of
jeans?
Uh so those jeans are 135.
135 is not cheap for a pair of jeans.
The $135 is a great value for the
product that we're actually making for
Americanmade. We're about as competitive
as you can get for the price.
Okay. And what about the shirts?
The t-shirts are 24. Button-down shirts
are 88.
Sasha, what are your sales so far?
Our sales are $300,000.
In what time period?
8 months.
What did you do for a living before you
did this?
I've spent 15 years in the apparel
business
and I come from the totally opposite end
of the spectrum. I come from a more tech
media side. Prior to starting Buckmason
with Eric, I created a interactive
content platform called This Built
America, profiling companies that are
re-imagining American manufacturing.
That's cool.
And uh it did nothing but inspire me to
be completely passionate about what's
happening.
If I become a customer and I buy, let's
say, a shirt and jeans, I like it. How
many more times in a year do I buy?
What's the lifetime value of one of
these guys?
Well, 38% of our customers are repeat in
the last 8 months.
It's good.
And of that 38, 10% have purchased more
than three times.
That's amazing. So, you got guys buying
a white t-shirt, testing us out,
realizing they like it, coming back and
buying five more at a time. And that's
how guys shop.
What matters is brand. And I understand
what you're trying to do. Buck Mason is
an American heartfelt brand and you're
going to pick a price point where you
think your customer acquisition cost
online is going to be less than their
lifetime value. That's what this
business model is. Cuz I don't hear a
retail rollout strategy. I don't hear
you putting up retail stores in Soho.
Uh he's partially right. We've been very
successful today with acquiring
customers at very little to absolutely
no cost. We've been doing it through
both our social and PR channels. We've
had a lot of success through social.
It's been a valuable tool for us.
So, give us your metrics on social.
Instagram's been very helpful. We have
an influencer program. Okay. We identify
people that we relate to very well on
Instagram. They have very high amount of
followers. Most of them are
photographers. And the reason why we
focus on them and not specifically
putting a lot of effort into fashion
bloggers is because more or less we're
an anti-fashion brand. Like we're
focusing on the basics and the classics.
We're not following trends. And our
customer is following these
photographers, not the fashion blogs.
They're not GQ.
And what are you doing for these
photographers? Are you giving them
affiliate money?
It's a gifting.
Is your vision to take the 200,000 and
accelerate the existing business model
or are you going to expand into retail
or go into wholesale
primarily online? Stay with this
business model.
How much have you guys invested?
S and I are the only investors. We've
invested $10,000.
Are you can you do 500,000 this year? Is
that what you figured?
Sure. Yes.
Yeah.
And what are you going to make on that
after you pay yourself something?
We just started paying ourselves. We
think that we'll make about probably
about 35,000 on that.
Oo.
Guys, I think what you're doing is
great, but I just don't want to be in
the clothing business. It's that simple.
I'll be a customer. It's just not a fit
for me. And for those reasons, I'm out.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I think it looks great. And I love the
Made America story, but um I think if
you were farther ahead, farther down the
road, I'm not sure how much I could add
to the mix of knowing what's really
right to hit guys in the heart of what
they want to wear. So, for that reason,
I'm out.
Appreciate. Thank you.
Thank you.
Well, look, guys, incredible that you
gotten to this point with $10,000.
That's remarkable.
Thank you. But I just don't understand
how customers are finding you.
Yeah.
And for me as an online company, that's
the struggle.
I'm out.
Appreciate it, Rob. Thank you.
You know, guys, basically companies in
clothing trade at around four times
their cash flow and they're much larger
than you are. So, you need to be making
somewhere between $6 and $750,000
after tax to get a valuation of 2.5
million.
You've come in and been very aggressive
in terms of your valuation here. And
it's not clear what you're worth yet.
It's a concept. It's starting to show
some traction. I love the branding. I
really do. But to get 200,000 out of
somebody, I think you're going to have
to part with half the company.
I think what you're investing in here
is, you know, the vision and the talent
on board. Come on, guys. If you've been
in the business this long, you know that
this valuation is somewhat crazy.
2.5 million, you're putting a value on
what you think you're going to do in the
future. I guess that's the value of it.
But my daddy didn't have two crystal
balls. So, I can't see in the future,
right? This is way too costly for me cuz
this is my industry.
I'm out.
So, there's one shark left.
Wow. The most fashionable sharks left.
Mhm.
Kevin,
I don't know what to do here. I'm not
sure what you're worth right now. You're
worth a partnership and the beginning of
a brand that no one's heard of until
today. So, the only way I can do this
deal is I'll give you $200,000. I want
50%.
And even that's generous. There's no
other way to do it because you're so far
from from making money. I mean, how are
you guys even eating?
That's why they make skinny jeans.
Eric Airbnbs is placing crashes on my
couch sometimes.
Well, that's what I mean. I mean that
that is a startup. You are governed by
gravity.
Is that your offer?
It is my only offer. I'll give I'll give
you 200,000 for 50%. I'll help get your
word out. I'm probably obviously going
to be one of your customers because I
like what you do.
I don't know if that's going to be
helpful.
I think it is. I'm very fashion forward.
So, you know, at the end of the day,
that's the only offer you're going to
get cuz everybody else is out. Um,
you know, this is something that we have
scraped and clawed to do and we're
building it brick by brick and, you
know, for us to give up more than 15%
equity in the company at this stage of
the game is not something we'd be
interested in.
You understand what gravity's done to
you here today in the Shark Tank.
Looking at the dollars you generate from
it in a commodity business, there's no
way to give you that value. But stick to
your guns, guys.
I mean, there's there should be no
desperation being accomplish.
Why don't you counter him?
Um, we would like to counter offer you
with 200,000 for 15% plus $100,000 line
of credit. Current would only go%
Yes.
15%.
They changed
for 200,000.
200,000
plus 100,000 line of credit specifically
for inventory.
They'll throw in a lifetime supply of
free clothing.
You get a lifetime supply of free
clothing. I can buy a lot of jeans for
$200,000.
What do you think?
You know, guys, I provide uh factoring
for all my companies. When you have real
sales and it's working, it's not hard to
finance that. I don't even worry about
that. I'm still stuck with how I ever
get my money back. Under the model you
just gave me, you're going to have to
make $2 million
after tax.
Kevin, all you got to do is go door to
door, sell some jeans, and at their
margins, it won't take you long. Look, I
I I'm It's the first
Eric, I'll give you the 200,000 plus
$100,000 on line of credit for 25%.
H, now it gets interesting.
Now it gets interesting.
Yeah, I'm not going to compete with
that. I wouldn't even do that deal. So
guys, if you don't want my original
offer, I'm out. And clearly, you don't
deal with that.
Yeah, I'll go I'll go uh down to 25%
from Kevin's. I think you're going to
make it. I don't know if I see the huge
future vision. You got to take me out
for a beer and explain how we're getting
customers, but I think you're going to
make it. Um,
would you consider
I wouldn't I wouldn't consider anything
below that.
So far from you need you need 800,000 of
free cash to get anywhere near even
that. Let me let me look. Robert's a
great partner and I'm going to sell you
on Robert and why you should do this
deal. You're going to be able to turn
your inventory from that cash so many
times and create so much more value with
that cash. You'll swamp the 10% delta.
That is a hell of a deal. That is a hell
of a deal with what you're at today. You
make no money. You're Airbnbing your
house, Robert. Robert, we're huge fans
and we we appreciate your offer. Um,
it's the right offer at
at this point.
It's the right offer. Don't make a
mistake.
Because we believe because we believe,
guys, you're overvaluing the Sometimes
cash is more valuable than equity.
Let the man.
Look guys, I am all about owning the
equity as long as you can, but some
businesses require cash upfront. 300,000
is going to get you inventory. You're
going to turn it over. You're going to
get to the next step.
Stop and think for a minute. If you're
going to walk out of here and you're
going to say to yourself,
"Wish I had said yes."
Robert, we know that we're going to get
there. For us, it's it's a matter of
when. And for us to give up for us to
give up that much equity at this stage
is not is not in our interest. We could
do the same deal for 17%.
Now guys, now we're getting into the
realm of silly. An 8% delta on something
this new, it just doesn't make sense.
This is really investment about you guys
and what you've built so far. 200,000
25% $100,000 line of credit. We'll get
there quickly together.
Thank you so much for your offer. for
your offer, Robert.
Um, we have to decline.
Thank you so much.
Congrats, guys. Good luck.
Thank you.
Good luck.
We're trying to build something that we
could give to our children. Giving up
25% 10 months into the life of our
company is not in the best interest of
the long haul.
I really think that was the right offer
for them.
Welcome to my world, the world of
designers.
Oh, come on.
No clue. Go.
Next up is a stylish way to show your
school spirit.
[Music]
Wow.
Yeah. Very good.
Hello, my name is Ashley Jones and I'm
from Virginia Beach, Virginia.
I'm the owner of Tones of Melanin O.
I'm seeking $300,000 for 5% equity into
my business.
Hello.
So, Sharks, for years, thousands of
students, faculty, and alumni from
historically black colleges and
universities, also known as H.B.CU, use
have been underrepresented when it comes
to fashion. They're tired of bedazzled
t-shirt and polo being their only option
for years. Tones of Melanin is here to
fill that void. Tones of Melanin has
combined street wear and collegiate wear
together to create its own genre of
fashion. Today, we have over 40
different H.B.CU licenses. What makes us
so unique is that we come from the
community that we serve. Tones of
Melanin has become bigger than just
fashion. We've become the hub for all
things H.B.CU. So, Sharks, who's ready
to change collegiate wear forever? Give
it up for my band.
[Applause]
[Music]
So, today in front of you, you have some
of my signature items. Mark, you have
our reversible basketball shorts with
pockets. Ladies, we know that we have to
have pockets in all items. So, if you
turn that thing inside out, it's a whole
another pair.
I like it. Thank you. Right here we have
our Winston Salem half zip windbreaker.
In front of you, Mr. Wonderful, is our
reversible satin jacket. So, if you
unzip that, it's going to turn to a
whole another side. Lori, you have our
other windbreaker. It's a full zip. It
gives you a a blast from the past, a '9s
feel. And Damon, you also have our
reversible jacket from my alma moater,
Northfor State University.
Nice quality. How much does it cost you
to make? And how much do you sell it
for?
The jacket that you have right there,
um, we get it for 28. We sell it um on
our site for 110. We sell it to the
department store for 56. Uh the
reversible shorts right there we get for
20. We sell it to the department store
for 48. They sell it for 100. Um our
reversible jackets we pay $30 for that.
We charge 165.
How did you start to do this? And and
what's your background?
So I designed from early high school
into college. It became a side hustle. I
began designing for every organization
on campus. And I seen there that nothing
looked like the things that I was
designing. So I decided to start my own
brand. At the beginning I was doing
Greek apparel and then I decided to make
H.B.CU apparel because I seen that there
was a bigger need in that community.
And how many HBUs are, you know,
historical black colleges, universities,
how many of those exist?
Depending on the person, some might say
100, some might say 102.
And you have 40 licenses already in
existence. So that's great. You have
almost half of them, right?
Yes. Um, but the thing is I've gotten um
our license for everybody that allows
it. The other schools they don't have
licensing programs in place.
They don't have licensing programs in
place.
That might be an opportunity for you
right there.
Absolutely.
So a very big the number one shoe maker
in the world has just invested I think a
couple billion over 15 years to H.B.CU.
So this is a very very hot and fast
growing area. I tell you what gets me
hot to try is sales.
Yes.
What do you got?
Uh to date we made 3.3 million sales.
Oh, that's over what period of time
since 2017.
So, what have you sold the last 12
months?
The last 12 months, we're at 1.4
million.
Wow.
Can you walk me through this calendar
year sales and potential profits?
Um,
and how they break down online versus
retail.
Okay. Um, this calendar year so far, we
made about $1.1 million. That equals up,
I want to say, maybe 75%. Um, the rest
are e-commerce. Uh we're currently in
Dick Sporting Goods Flet with services
uh 25 of the HB.CU bookstores and also
on fanatics. Literally two days ago I
got a purchase order from Flet for
$973,000
for our fall.
Wow. Wow.
So good for you. How exciting.
So are you going to make money this
year?
Uh yes we are.
What do you think you'll make?
Today we revenue we have 343,000 that we
made this year from the 1.
Okay. So you've profited about 25% so
far. You've got a purchase order for 973
coming in. Plus, you've got all your
other sales that are coming.
Also, we have more department stores.
How are you financing them?
Um, we have a really good manufacturer.
He allows for us to pay him after we get
our payment.
Now, this is very creative and this is
what in our business we call the
factories holding the paper. Yes, that's
what we called it. All right. And a lot
of people can learn from this. So, you
were able to scale because he's doing
that. So, what would the money be used
for then?
Um, the money would be used for we're
actually inhouse. We have a five person
team. So once they get here, we have to
tag them all that. I want to go into
fulfillment and having a 3PL company
tagging getting it ready for department
stores to make sure that that's right.
But you don't have to pay for a 3PL per
se. You find a good 3PL and then you
send them the inventory and then you
only pay as they pick.
We would also use it for marketing.
We've only um spent $50,000 in
marketing.
But do you need to spend anything on
marketing? I honestly believe that we do
because all the stores that we're in,
we're not even we don't have like a key
a key place in the store. We actually
wanted those other schools that we don't
have licensing for convincing them, hey,
choose us.
Yeah. Marketing won't change their mind.
The sell through will.
Okay. Yeah.
Are you running this yourself?
Yes. I'm head designer. I'm talking to
the manufacturers.
This is your baby and you're running it
dayto-day or is there a separate CEO or
No, I day.
You wear everything, right?
Every hat. Every head. Ashley, I have to
ask you this. I mean, your enthusiasm,
your confidence is huge. huge
and amazing. Can you please tell us a
bit more about your story? Like where
did this come from?
My grandparents had one of the first
African-American beauty supply companies
in our area. So I seen entrepreneurship
firsthand. And then when I turned 13,
but my mom worked for the Ford company
subsidiary. They left Northern Virginia.
So I went into hustle mode and it was
like I could at least pay for me to go
pay for lunch for myself. I can pay to
get my hair done. So it just it became
second nature to be honest.
You had to take care of you.
Yes. Yes. And it wasn't my mom never
asked this. I just wanted to help. Like
I know I can do this for myself. Like I
can handle this. You don't worry about
that. Mom,
you're hot stuff. Yeah. I like it.
Ashley, you've got to be putting money
in your pocket right now.
Not yet.
You're investing in inventory.
Everything is going right back into the
business.
You're not making a salary. You don't
pay yourself anything.
I pay myself next to nothing. I'm still
trying to get
How are you surviving?
Uh I have a great community. My family,
my mom, she believes in me.
That is really mindblowing
problem for me.
I don't know much at all about this
area. I am not really and never have
really been much in the apparel world
nor in the sports and
I understand
it's not really my thing and so for that
reason I wish you good luck but I'm out.
I appreciate it. Thank you.
You are on fire.
Thank you.
But this isn't a business I know a thing
about. Sadly I'm out.
Ashley, I look at it as a inventory
challenge because the bigger you get,
the more capital you're going to need to
hold all these different SKs and more
licenses, more SKs, more inventory, more
capital. That's what I've learned about
the clothing business. It's not a
business I want to be in. I'm sorry. I'm
out.
Thank you.
The challenge I have is I I'm I'm in
this area in certain aspects. I I either
advise or own companies in this area.
Eastman Golf and Actively Black Foo and
then another company you may know of
AACA
familiar.
So I I would uh it would be challenging
for me to split hairs like this and I
don't think I would be giving you doing
a service but I will give you one idea.
Instead of having trying to go to a lot
of retailers, we've had one
representative young man and one
representative young woman at each
school who are the official sellers of
the goods and they get maybe $1,000
$2,000 worth of product and sell however
they want and they've been doing it like
that. I would highly suggest you do that
but at this moment it's a conflict for
me.
I appreciate your advice. Thank you.
Absolutely. I'm out.
Thank you.
So Esther, you're a superstar. You're a
force of nature. You know your stuff
cold. I mean you didn't back down. You
kept a smile the whole time. Nobody
phased you even the tiniest bit. And you
know, being in the business I am with
the Mavericks, I know a few people that,
you know, are excited about all this.
So, I'll make you an offer. We'll see if
you like it. I'll give you the $300,000,
but I want 15%.
Can we do 12?
Done.
Wow, that was quick.
Good job.
You're the best. You're the best. That's
awesome. I'm so excited.
Excited. Excited. Excited. Thank you.
Now go sell some stuff.
Yes, absolutely. Make me some money.
I made a deal with Mark Cuban, like one
of the biggest sharks there is. I
provide a beacon of hope. If I made it
and I went to an H.B.CU, I'm providing
the sense of hope for anybody that
attended an H.B.CU.
Next up, an original way for kids to
express themselves.
[Applause]
[Music]
Hi Sharks. My name is Jennifer Stein
Bishoff and I'm from Brooklyn, New York.
I'm seeking $250,000
in exchange for 10% equity of my
company, Super Mix Studio Sharks. As a
mom, I've witnessed the self-esteem
boost that kids get when they pick out
their own outfit. As a designer, I
wondered how I could enable kids to
create something that's a true
reflection of who they are. Introducing
Supermix Studio, the world's first
interactive custom kids clothing brand.
Our innovative platform empowers kids to
celebrate their individuality by
designing their own clothes. If a video
game and a clothing brand had a baby, it
would be Supermix Studio. Users can
hyperpersonalize our clothing and
accessories and create something that's
100% original. Just like Jake, who loves
soccer and skating,
nice,
and Jasmine who loves tennis and dance.
But Supermix is really all about the
design experience. Let me show you.
First, visit our website and choose a
style. We have sweats, denim jackets,
backpacks, and accessories, all made of
sustainable materials. Then click
customize. Now our design platform opens
up and you'll find over 500 premium
patches to choose from. Just drag and
drop and place them anywhere you want on
the style. The front, back, sleeves, and
even the hood. Step three is our job. In
our studio, we bring your child's
masterpiece to life. As you can see, May
is wearing the final product just like
the one designed on screen.
Nice.
Nice. And the best part, your kid won't
want to take Supermix off because
they're proud of it. That's the Supermix
magic. Sharks, who wants to join me in
empowering kids to express themselves by
literally wearing their hearts on their
sleeves. Ready, set, patch.
Good job, guys.
Thank you, guys. You're amazing.
Thank you.
Good job, guys. Thank you. Excellent.
Excellent. Bye. sharks. In front of you,
you'll find Super Mix that I took the
liberty of designing for you.
Oh my goodness.
Of course.
All right, I'm in.
It's really cute.
Sniffle,
Robert, you have our classic denim
jacket. And what you're seeing there are
our superized patches. As I mentioned,
we have over 500 patches and we have
over 30 of these large superized
patches, which is really what everybody
gets super excited about. It's really a
cute idea.
Very cute.
This is really well made. It is thick.
This is a jean jacket, but it's soft.
Yes.
And how much is it? What would this jean
jacket cost?
Sure. So, that jean jacket is $69.
That's the base price. We're seeing an
additional $15 to$20 upsell in all of
the patches per design. It comes
That's an amazingly good price.
It is an amazing price.
What does it cost you to make? So that
denim jacket is 1375 and as I mentioned
it retails for 69. So the margins on
denim are in the high7s.
What about in the sweatshirts?
The sweatshirt. So Damon, the sweatshirt
that you have there is 705 and retails
for 55.
And it appears that you're actually
manufacturing the patches yourself.
All of them. All of the patches are 100%
proprietary artwork. I'm a designer.
I've been in the industry for two
decades. I'm responsible for generating
billions of dollars in a pair of
companies were you with?
Well, my first big job was for Gloria
Vanderbilt. I was hired to launch their
first ever junior brand. I would create
a gene there that ultimately was written
up as the $100 million fit. Tommy
Hilfiger saw that article and the next
thing I knew I was sitting in his office
and at 28 he hired me to be the vice
president of design for Tommy Jeans to
breathe some new energy into the brand.
Wow,
Jennifer, you're a real loser.
Yeah. So, you have no experience going
at all.
My last role was as chief merchandising
officer for a large-scale private
children's wear manufacturer. It took my
entire career to finally figure out that
kids is what I love doing the most. This
is definitely the most fun I've had in
in my whole career.
What inspired you to say enough of the
corporate world?
It was the pandemic and my kids were
home and I was just looking for things
to keep them busy. We started tie dying
and putting patches on things. I was
like, "This is so much fun. This is the
white space idea that I'm keeping for
myself. I love this."
So, you're rolling out kiosks. Where
would the kiosk be going?
So, we're looking at taking these kiosks
to all kinds of physical locations. The
first people that we're testing the
kiosk with is actually with Claire's.
They're the premier destination of all
things tween. Smart. But we're also
looking at putting them in kids clubs at
resorts and on cruise ships and of
course department stores and boutiques.
Okay. So when you came in I thought that
this was you do this online direct to
consumer. I go to your website. That's
correct. Yeah. Me too.
Is this now an expansion? Yes.
But Jennifer why?
Well because I'm a trend forecaster and
that's how I've been successful in my
career by doing things that haven't been
done before. And this is an incredible
instore experience. Everything's about
retail tamement.
What are your sales?
I launched in October of 22. My first
holiday season was $60,000.
Okay.
And year to date, we've done 110. So,
it's 170 lifetime sales.
You're not making any money yet, are
you?
Not yet.
You're not selling the kiosk at all.
You're putting them in stores, right?
It's a very interesting relationship
with our retail and venue partners.
I hate this kiosk idea. Take your retail
shackles off. Set yourself free.
I am be reborn.
I am reborn and I'm very happy to go
into this from a DTC perspective, but we
all know that customer acquisition costs
are very expensive and they're rising
and they're getting more and more
difficult. This is customer acquisition.
Yeah, but it's not. This is
It's not. And here's why. Because we've
gotten to the point now with direct to
consumer where there's online and
there's instore and typically when you
make the decision to go in store it's
the immediiacy of the product right I
can grab it and get it right there
that doesn't happen with your kiosk
I think you're going to have people walk
up to it and maybe put in some
information which is great for customer
acquisition and then expect it to pop
out and you're going to get a lot of
canceled carts because that product
isn't right there. So, for those
reasons, I'm out.
Damon, what are you doing?
I'm struggling. I I like I like this
thing a lot. You know, this kiosk thing
can either be a massive hit or a real
problem. It's just too risky for me. So,
I'm out.
Jeff, incredible quality, great price
point. The sales are so low and now
we're going into kiosks,
but I still love it.
Two Sharks are out and Robert may be
interested in Jennifer's customizable
kids clothing brand, Supermix Studios.
I I hear your feedback about the kiosk
and it's certainly giving me a lot to
think about. The people in the space
that I've shown it to have been very
very excited about it. It's an
incredible instore experience keeping
people in the store longer. Why do you
pay the retailer?
And the arrangement here as we're
discussing going into Claire's is that
they will receive 30% of the revenue
driven from the machine. That's fine.
It's a win-win. Ultimately, I'm holding
the inventory and fulfilling. So, all
they have to do is put this kiosk in
their store and then it's it's 100%
incremental volume. I'm telling you,
this is the next massive children's
brand. Imagine it as the Build-A-Bear of
apparel.
Let me take a stab at it. Okay. You're
very impressive and I really believe in
the demand and it all came to you during
CO 19. But before CO 19, you got a
different virus. It's called retail 19
and it's it's running through your veins
even now. You can't let it go. It's 30
to 40% of your margin forever. It's a
curse.
But she's selling online.
She's about to do retail, which I hate.
I'm sorry. I'm out. And and don't come
too close to me with that retail 19.
I mean, that's just me.
Listen, I actually think you're pretty
brilliant.
Thank you.
I think that you think out of the box.
You're an innovator. You've done
something completely unique and
different. And I think it's super smart.
I see this for Disney. I see this as in
places where you have the mom and the
kid. They're a captive audience,
right? It's empowering and
it feels empowering to me. All right.
So, okay. We're going to make you an
offer. I don't know. We're going to
figure it out. I mean, honestly, I've
never done a kids clothing line.
Oh, we're going to do a kids clothing
line.
So, at this point,
yeah,
while you're on to a great thing, it's
still pretty early. We're going to offer
you 250,000.
We want 25%.
We'd also like a royalty because we pay
you a cash flow of 5%.
Until we make back the initial
250,000. After that, it goes away 5%.
And then it goes away.
What a bad deal.
Well, you can negotiate. I
mean, Mark, you're not putting up any
money.
Mark is not in this deal.
I do not find that a bad deal in today's
market. Capital is completely dried up,
particularly in your space. The fact you
have an offer goes to your credibility
in your past, even though you are
infected with retail 19.
Obviously, it's really important for me
to remain liquid and to be able to grow
this company. So, I'd like to counter at
20% and
2% royalty.
I'm sorry. I just can't.
All right, Jennifer. 250,000,
20% equity, 3 12% royalty.
Lori,
I'm good with that. Are you?
The royalty goes away after you're
payback.
Correct.
You have a deal. Amazing.
Thank you so much, Lori.
Congrats. Well done.
Great presentation.
Thank you so much.
Lose the retail.
Oh my gosh. We did it.
This is so awesome. Lori and Robert just
got it. They really understood what I
was doing and this is the next big thing
and this is revolutionary and they saw
the vision and I couldn't ask for
anything more. This is absolutely
incredible. So exciting.
[Applause]
Next up is a company with a mission to
normalize mental health struggles.
[Music]
Hi Sharks. My name is Sophie Nstico. I'm
from Trumble, Connecticut. And I am here
seeking $250,000 for 10% of my business.
Sharks, you may not be able to tell from
the big smile that I have on my face,
but I cry. And I cry a lot. But guess
what? We all cry because we're human.
Kevin, I know you have a tough exterior,
but I've seen even you shed a tear in
the tank.
Never happens.
I'm on a mission to destigmatize mental
health as it's not something that we
should hide, but rather something that
we should embrace and wear it proudly.
And that's exactly why I created See the
Way I See, a size inclusive mental
health awareness clothing brand that
emphasizes positive affirmations in a
way that's never been done before. What
we do is simple. We add signature
reassuring reminders to the sleeves of
your sweatshirts to give people that
little boost that they find themselves
needing. So Lori, if you're anything
like me, you're an overinker. Just
remember to breathe in and breathe out.
And Mark, if you're ever feeling anxious
about all the deals you have in the
works, just look to your sleeve to be
reminded that this feeling too shall
pass. And I get it. If you don't want to
wear your heart on your literal sleeve,
we also have rings, stickers, keychains,
and so much more to give people that
reminder to carry with them throughout
the day. Sharks, I built a community
through the power of social media, and
my followers are with me every step of
the way. Together, we are breaking down
barriers to end the stigma surrounding
common mental health struggles once and
for all. So, what do you say? Are you
ready to see the way I see? Sharks. In
front of you is a crew neck, a keychain,
and a sticker that I designed. So, feel
free to check them out and get in your
feels.
Sophie, how did you come up with your
business idea?
You know, since I was young, I've always
had a passion for helping others. I
always knew that I wanted to be a nurse.
And, you know, going into high school, I
started to develop pretty severe
anxiety. Fast forward to my sophomore
year of nursing school, I started to
develop even more severe anxiety. So, I
decided to go down to part-time. And in
that time, I refound my passion for art
that I've had since I was 10. I took the
$500 that I had in my bank account. I
bought a printer and a sticker cutting
machine. I started to design mental
health based stickers. I started selling
them online. And I just continued to
reinvest the money until I was able to
actually purchase my first order of crew
necks. And I thought that it was going
to take at least two to three to four
months to sell a hundred sweatshirts.
And I was willing to do it. But to my
surprise, it only took two days for it
to sell.
Oh my gosh. Nice.
What happened?
So I have been using social media for as
long as it's been out, but I was able to
use it to my advantage at this point
where I was sharing my art on my page
which was called See the Way I See. So
that was also where the name came from.
You were seeing my art from my
perspective.
So something's happening here. Are you
spending a lot of money on advertising
or not?
None. I am.
This is pure community.
None. None. None.
You go. That's awesome.
Sophie, what you think you're going to
be doing this year?
So sales for this year would be
$260,000.
Is that year to date now?
Actually, I'm sorry. That was $260,000
in 24 hours.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait a second.
Wait, hold on, guys. Let's take a couple
steps. You're selling your stuff based
off of drops then apparently.
Yes, exactly. I'm trying to do a drop a
month
rather than having something for sale
all the time. You make an announcement
on social media. If you're doing it
right, then there's a frenzy. Everybody
tries to get it and it sells out
quickly. Right. And so this is your
primary product, your
the crew necks and hoodies. Yes.
Okay. So crew necks and hoodies, what do
you sell them for and what do they cost
you to make?
Crew necks. I sell them for $60 retail
and they cost $21 landed to make.
Okay. And hoodies.
Hoodies. Um, I charge $75 and those cost
about $25.
Okay. This year, year to date.
Year to date. Year to date is $790,000.
Wow.
And how many people are in your company?
Just me.
You are making a boatload of money.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
How old are you?
24.
What's taking you so long?
So, how much money is in your bank
account right now? So, I just had a drop
and I need to purchase my next drop, but
it's around $450,000.
Nice.
Wow.
And that's profit, but you're just
reinvesting your profit.
Exactly. That I've started with $500 in
my bank account and I've grown it to
this point with nothing.
Yeah. You know what? I'm getting
anxiety.
Wow.
Listen, I have a crew neck for it.
That'll reduce your anxiety for sure.
Sophie, I got a I got an idea of a
business that I want to start. I'll sell
you 20% for $450,000.
Well, you're selling to her?
Yeah, she got the money.
So, what do you need a shark for? You're
doing so well.
So, I'm proud of myself for how far I've
gotten it, but I have zero background in
business. My family has zero background
in business, and I just feel like I'm
hitting that point where I need a
mentor.
Sophie, why do you think you're worth
2.5 million bucks?
So, total sales for my company has been
just over 2.3 mil.
Nice. and I'm projecting to finish at a
million this year and then next year
1.75. I just continue to see this
business growing and continuing to
scale.
How much did you make on that 2.3
million?
So the first year was $900,000 in sales
and that was the year that I really did
not know what I was doing. So I profited
still a good number around 115,000.
And then the next year, 2021, I made
$640,000 in sales, profited around
235,000,
and then this year 790,000.
So, I'm start I'm finding my way.
You're a star. You
Sophie, this cash flow should bring a
lot of peace to you. I mean, I got to
tell you that I don't really know how to
help you. A lot of people talk about
when they're sitting or standing where
you are, what's going to happen. Just
listening to what already happened gives
you 100% street credit. I mean, it's
unreal. So, this thing where you don't
know anything about business, I don't
really buy it anymore. Okay. I mean,
it's you're doing better than 90% of the
people that stand in front of me there.
That's just incredible.
But look, I I it's not a fit for me. I
don't know how to help you. You're
killing it.
Thank you.
But for that reason, I'm out.
Okay. People should be able to show
their emotions and that's probably why
we're in such a bad situation because
people shame you for doing that. So, I
applaud you for for doing this.
But you don't need our help. I think
you're doing excellent. And right now,
you have a great community. That
community is searching for people like
you who they resonate with and they're
ready to support you. And the proof is
here. You don't need me. I don't think
I'll add much value. Uh so, I'm out.
Okay. Thank you. Listen, I think you're
amazing. Thank you.
I had no business background.
A true entrepreneur to me is somebody
who knows how to drive a business. You
have great instincts and you figured it
out. You actually maybe don't realize
it, but you are a businesswoman. You
already are.
Thank you.
I would not feel good taking a
percentage of your company. I don't
think you need it. I will be a
supporter, not an investor.
So,
thank you so much.
Sophie, what does being an entrepreneur
mean to you?
It means, you know, to me it shows me
that I'm capable of a lot more than what
I thought I was because it let me find
that I am capable of doing this. And to
become an entrepreneur is just something
that I never thought
not. I never thought I'd be standing
here alone. So, you know,
what what you've been able to accomplish
is insane, right? And I'll caution you
that, right? Let your community grow
your business, not a team. Because when
you bring in a team, you try to act like
an old school business because that's
what people think they they're supposed
to do for a business. Be who you are to
your community and your community will
you'll grow with it. And you don't want
an investor for that because you're
already putting money in the bank and
all we'd be doing is taking what you
earn, right? Keep on being you. Keep on
doing what you're doing because it's
it's amazing. But
thank you.
I just wouldn't feel right. So for those
reasons, I'm out.
Thank you.
You're welcome. Uh, you know, I think
your great strength is your
vulnerability.
You would be hardressed to convince me
that you were the least bit anxious on
this carpet today.
You have no idea.
I have no idea.
Well, you've got quite an act going
because I couldn't pick it up and I'm
listening carefully. Um, like the other
sharks here, my problem I don't mind
investing in your deal. you're a winner.
But I like to feel important and I I
play a key role with every one of my
entrepreneurs. You know, either a
mother, grandmother, advocate,
supporter, basher, whatever they need, I
become. What would I do for you?
I think Mark put it best where maybe I'm
in that old mindset of where I think I
need a team. I'm not as clear on that
answer anymore, to be honest.
You're not sure you even need a shark.
We're convincing you you don't need it.
I know. I mean, all of you guys have
such great points. So, I still feel as
though I would need that extra guidance,
but maybe that's the overthinker in me,
you know?
Yeah. Because you've come full circle on
that. I'll go out
for sure. Yeah, you don't need anybody.
Thank you.
All right.
So, we're all out. We're sorry we wasted
your time.
Far from it, you guys. This has been eye
opening for me. Thank you guys so much.
Good luck,
Sophie. Thank you.
Well, she just went up a notch in
self-confidence.
Yeah.
Yeah. Man, what a start.
That was very difficult for me to do,
but they really did give me a boost of
self-confidence. I did it. I never
thought that I would be standing here
today, let alone being capable of
actually forming a pitch and practicing
it and saying it in front of the sharks.
But after today, I really feel as though
I can almost do anything.