[Music]
[Applause]
First in the tank is a modern revamp of
a stale product.
[Music]
>> Hi Sharks. I'm Leslie and this is my
husband Greg. We're from Short Hills,
New Jersey, and we're seeking $1 million
for 6% equity in our business.
>> Hello.
>> Wow.
>> Sharks, picture this. It's the perfect
beach day, and you can't wait to dig
your toes into the sand.
>> You put on your favorite beach outfit.
You go to dig out your beach gear, and
then,
>> oh no,
clunky,
outdated, uninspired.
Beach gear hasn't changed for a hundred
years. True.
>> Until now.
Introducing
>> Sunflow.
>> Sunflow, a completely reimagined premium
beach chair that opens big and
comfortable, but closes small with just
the push of a button.
>> With both fashion and function in mind,
we also created thoughtful accessories
like
>> our water resistant dry bag to protect
your precious mobile phone. smart. A
drink holder that rotates and adjusts to
fit all different size beverages.
>> And Leslie's favorite accessory,
>> a double panel canopy that protects your
skin from 98% of the sun's harmful rays.
Clever.
>> You just recline and you're all set.
>> Ready to pack up?
>> Just push the top button and collapse
it.
>> Nice.
>> Voila. You're good to go.
>> Impressive. So, sharks, who wants to
swim to shore and help Sunflow make
every day a beach day?
>> I'd like to buy a dozen of them. How did
you come up with the idea that let's
make a great beach chair?
>> Did you have background?
>> Are you an engineer? No, but I'm I'm a
handbag designer. So, we started a
fashion line of handbags right after we
got married.
>> We were partners in that business for
many years. We actually had to learn the
process of sketching something, right?
finding the factory, finding the
materials.
>> Now would be the time to tell us the
phenomenal sales numbers, which I'm sure
is going to blow all of us away
>> because there is a 16 million pound
elephant in the room.
>> That's your valuation. Um, we launched
13 and 12 months ago. Uh, we have 2.9
million in sales.
>> Wow.
>> Um, we're on track to grow 409% this
year.
>> Talk us through the distribution. Where
did you sell that direct?
>> 100% direct to consumer. We haven't even
touched any yet. That's great.
Congratulations. What do you sell them
for? What's your cost?
>> We are selling the product. The chair
itself is 198.
>> That chair retails for 198.
>> 198 without the accessories.
>> Seems it seems high.
>> 60% of our customers buy every single
chair accessory.
>> Let's break down the numbers. 198 for
the chair, 48 for the sun shade, 25 for
the drink holder, 25 for the dry.
>> What's the margin on this piece of
plastic when you sell for 25 bucks? That
is 78% margin.
>> Wow.
>> What does it cost for you to make one
chair that you're selling?
>> Uh $70 to make a chair landed, but we
sell three accessories for every chair
we sell. So, we have sold 11,000 chairs,
but 44,000 units have sold.
>> Your numbers blow me away. Amazing.
Leslie, what drove you to become
entrepreneurs?
>> Um, so my parents immigrated from Taiwan
50 years ago. They're very um proud of
the fact that they came here with
nothing but a little piece of gold in
the bottom of their toothpaste tube.
>> So I watched them both work really hard.
And my father um actually was an
entrepreneur. He started a business in
the basement of our house. He started a
construction company and he built it to
be a multi-million dollar company. Wow.
And he was we're so proud of him. and he
actually passed away a little over a
week ago.
>> Oh, no. I'm sorry.
>> Um, so to be here is very special.
>> Sorry to hear that. That's too bad.
>> Yeah, I'm sorry.
>> No, but he'd be so proud.
>> Back to our reality here. Let's talk
about these numbers here. Um, I give you
a million dollars for 6%. I'd have to
see 32 million valuation on this
company, let's say, in the next 24
months, 36 months to even get a chance
to double my money. Well, if you only
double your money, I'd be really
disappointed. This is an enormous
market. The outdoor market
>> just on a beach chair.
>> No, I have so many products in the
pipeline. I'm already developing a
higher chair that's, you know, a lot of
people requested it. I started
developing that 3 years ago.
>> I was going to ask you about a longer
chair.
>> Yes, it's going to We were talking about
a lounger and I have an amazing table
that's coming.
>> We've expanded beyond just chairs. We
are building a beach brand.
>> I love your relationship. Very good
energy. Your dad's immigrant story
resonated a lot with me with your
father. My dad only went third grade in
school because after that he was sent to
a concentration camp and he had so much
joy with my mom of seeing me go to the
first person in our generation to go to
college and graduate school. And I feel
that your dad is here with us and so is
my dad. And so I like all of that.
Here's my offer. I would give you the
million dollars. I was going to say 25%,
but I'm going to say 22 and a2%.
>> Thank you. I want to go back to
something Kevin asked. How do you make
money? This will be one of the most
successful businesses from Shark Tank.
And I'm not saying that because I'm
arrogant, and I hope you could see we're
we're humble.
>> You seem humble.
>> Thank you.
>> I would go that far, but Okay, go ahead.
>> No, she's pretty humble.
>> This is going to be a hundred million
plus business.
>> Okay, let's let's stop there because
that's a great talking point. Yeah. But
the number that matters as it relates to
valuation based off of what you've um
offered us is $16 million in
distributable cash. When will you have
$16 million in distributable cash?
Because 6% of that is $1 million. Of
course,
>> that's how we only not even a return.
>> That's just to get our money back. When
I talk about scaling a company, it
really has to scale.
>> Leslie and Greg, I gave you an offer.
>> Do you guys want to accept it or
counter? We
will respond to both. We hope that if
any or all of you invest that you're
along for the ride. This isn't a goal to
distribute money a year from now.
>> I didn't say when. I just said it all.
>> Well, I'm getting a little bit impatient
though. I might go hang out at the
beach.
>> We're not even close. So, I don't want
to.
>> Do you want a counter?
>> Uh, just
>> because it's not just a million dollar.
It's millions of dollars in time from my
team and from myself. I've seen what it
takes. I I'd like to invest in this
business, but it's so far stretched. A
million bucks is still a million bucks.
>> Go ahead and counter, Greg.
>> This year, we're going to do close to 4
million. Next year, our goal is to do 10
million. And we're estimating a 20% net
income. So, $2 million. Multiples on
this in this industry are 22 times right
now. So, we believe our business will be
worth $44 million unrealized.
>> Hey, Greg and Leslie, you're answering a
lot of questions. I ran out of patience.
I waited for you to give me a counter.
You could have given me a counter. You
want to give me a counter. I'm out.
>> Hey guys, I'll clear I'll clear the
deck, too.
>> It's a great business for you, but it's
not something I want to invest in. I'm
out.
>> Okay.
>> I think you're overconfident, and I wish
I would share that confidence with you,
but because I don't I don't believe it,
I'm out.
>> You did come in at a very high
valuation. You you did rocket sales
fast, which is great, but also sometimes
that can slow. So, unfortunately, I'm
out.
>> Okay, we understand.
>> All roads lead to
>> All roads lead back to Mr. Wonderful. As
usual,
four sharks are out. Kevin is Lesie and
Greg's last hope for a deal for their
beach chair company, Sunflow.
>> I'm struggling like all the other sharks
are in the valuation and just the
returns. Understand?
>> Okay. And you are in the Shark Tank. So,
here's my offer.
>> I'll do the million bucks. Okay. I'll
take a 4% equity position. All right.
Less than you're offering me, but I want
five bucks a chair on a royalty until I
recoup $2 million. All right. Then the
royalty goes away and I stay your
partner at 4%.
I knew that would
>> Yeah. Well,
>> I would say ouch on that one.
>> No, that's not as bad as it sounds.
>> I think it's too aggressive though to
>> uh $2 million return to you. Um after
>> all I wanted was to double my money.
>> Yeah. So, can I counter?
>> Sure.
>> Yeah. So the 4% equity, but instead of
$5 per chair, up to two million, up to 1
million, so that you're no longer at
risk that then when we've paid you back,
you're our ongoing partner.
>> So my if you say no to that, you're
crazy.
>> With no chance of a return other than
one day getting an exit with a 4%
position. That's basically what you're
offering me,
>> Kevin. It's actually not a bad offer.
It's pretty bad because the 6% he he has
>> No, it's not bad.
>> Has half of his equity for this.
>> It's not bad at all. I'm shocked that he
offered it.
>> I'm willing to be flexible. I'll do your
deal if you get me back to the 6%. I
give you my million dollars. I'm your 6%
partner, but I get nothing back in my
cash except the return of it on the
royalty at $5 a share. I'll do that
deal.
Okay.
5%
and and we pay you back the $5 per chair
till we get to a million and we have a
deal.
>> Done.
>> There you go, Kevin. Good job.
>> Congratulations, guys.
>> Thank you.
>> Congratulations. A phenomenal
presentation.
>> Sure.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Congratulations, guys. Good luck.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> Wow. I know my dad's watching right now
and just knowing that you could take a
dream and make it into something, you
know, a reality. It's it's uh it's
something I watched him do and now we're
doing it.
[Applause]
Next into the tank is an affordable way
to enjoy a luxury.
[Music]
Hi Sharks. My name is Tommy Pristella
and I'm an Air Force pilot from Sandy
Miss California. I'm here today seeking
$100,000 for 25% of my company. Now
Sharks, I love summer days as much as
the next guy. What's not to love, right?
I mean, backyard barbecues, evening
baseball games, I love it all. But
sharks, there's one thing about summer
that I just really don't like.
>> Uh-oh.
>> It's freaking hot.
And if you've been stationed in the deep
south like I have for the last 12 years
or deployed overseas to Iraq,
Afghanistan, Africa, you know that those
places get crazy hot. I got sick and
tired of sweating through my clothes
every time I stepped outside and just
always being uncomfortable.
>> So, I fused together a creative way to
stay cool and beat the summer heat.
Sharks, you guys ready to cool off?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, sure.
>> Introducing the one and only pickup
pool.
Sharks. As you can see, the pickup pool
is the ultimate truck bed swimming pool.
This patented pool liner instantly
transforms the bed of your pickup truck
into an above ground pool. Simply pull
the corners of the pickup pool over the
corners of your truck bed. Add water and
bam, you're ready for a pool party.
>> When you're done, there's a drain at the
back. You can drain the water without
lowering your tailgate.
>> I like it.
>> No sharks. The Pika Pool is a brand new
product in an untapped market. So, what
do you say? Who wants to go for a swim
and make a deal with takeup pool?
>> How did you come up with this?
>> My inspiration was my daughter.
>> A
>> way back when when I got the idea for
this, we were living in Arkansas. It's
2014, crazy hot summer. And my daughter
says, "Daddy, I want to go swimming."
And I'm like, I'm heartbroken and she's
heartbroken because I don't have a
swimming pool. So I was like, well a
>> I was like, let's see what I can do. I
go in the garage. I'd seen it done
before. I was we'll get a tarp. I got
some bungee cords. I make this thing in
the back of my truck and it's it worked
but it was an ugly mess.
>> And what if it leaks?
>> These do not leak. These are very thick,
durable material. Lifetime guarantee on
them. It's the same stuff above ground
pool liners are that last 30 years.
>> Yeah. Wow.
>> Good for you, Tommy. First of all, thank
you for your service.
>> Hey, it's my pleasure.
>> What's the patent for?
>> So, the patent is it's the adaptable
watertight barrier. I'm the only person
who can make the bed of the pickup truck
watertight.
>> So, where are you selling these now?
>> So, I sell them mainly online.
>> How much do you sell them for? So they
cost me 110 and 117 to make for the two
sizes and then I sell them through my
website for $2 and210 respectively. How
much have you sold
>> year to date? $7,60.
>> Killing it, huh?
>> Killing it. Lifetime sales $12,000.
But there's a story there.
>> What's the story?
>> I got the idea 2014. Did a proof of
concept in 2015. Bought 20 pools.
Immediately I got the website up. I'm
getting hits on the website and I'm
like, people really like this. I sell
those 20. I go back to get more
manufacturer retired.
>> That sucks.
>> So now I'm back at square one with
nobody to make the pools. So 2016's
pretty much gone me looking for a
manufacturer. 2017 deployed to
undisclosed location in Africa, but I
had to obviously hit the brakes on
pickup pools cuz I was a oneman show at
the time. So I brought my sister on,
very responsible. Love my sister to
death. She found me. the manufacturer
makes this. She She's part owner. She's
got a percentage of the company as well.
>> That's not her in there, right?
>> No. So, can I talk about her? That's my
beautiful wife of 12 years right there.
>> So, so supporting me really.
>> Well, who's the guy she's fooling around
with?
>> She's in a hot tub with some other guy.
>> Yeah, that's my best friend from
college. That's
>> So, what are you going to do going
forward? What's the plan? So, the reason
I'm asking for money today, I want to
reju my website and figure out how to
drive traffic to my website. My website
right now, it it looks nice, but I made
it. I'm not a web developer. I'm really
proud of myself. I made a website. I'm
like, "Wow, I want to have a
professional redo my website." You're
basically saying you're going to spend
the money to market the product. The
product's in the market. It's good
quality. 12,000 lifetime sales since the
beginning is really abysmal.
>> Okay. Well, look at this.
>> The guy gets deployed to an unknown, to
be unnamed place. I get it, but the
products
>> I got this. Thank you, Mark. I got this
one.
>> You mean is the only way it can sell is
you, Tommy, are like barking at the
internet. I just don't know if people
care. You've sold $12,000 worth of it.
Like, it's totally 100% increase from
last year, Kevin.
>> True story. Yeah, Tommy.
>> What do your platoon buddies think of
it?
>> Oh, they love it. I've actually I've uh
brought it to undisclosed location in
the Middle East. Tommy, who would work
your business?
>> You're still full-time military?
>> I I am married to the military for the
next eight years. So, there's no pulling
the wool over your guys' eyes here.
>> Back to the question, who would work
your business?
>> My sister is the other part of me.
>> Where's she based?
>> She's here in Southern California.
>> Can you get the price the cost down
lower?
>> Thank you for asking that.
>> You're welcome.
>> Yeah, I'm proud to say they're 100% made
in America.
>> Good. It's part of the reason why it's
so expensive. I want to make it for $25
and sell it for 60. That's where I'm
trying to get with this. I think there's
room to get that done a lot cheaper.
>> Listen, I think you did a good job of
name pickup pools intuitive. You got a
patent. Great job. My problem here is I
have no idea of the market. I believe
you. It would work and keep people cool,
but I have no idea the market research.
And for those reasons, I'm out.
>> Tommy, you're a great guy. I really
admire the the effort you've put into
it. I just don't know if there's a
business. You haven't sold very much.
You've got to find a way to get from 20
or 30 to hundreds.
>> Well, think of the value you're going to
add when you join me, Rob.
>> And then all of a sudden, we have all
those resources.
>> You're a great sales guy.
>> I'm not jumping in the pool with you.
I'm out.
>> This thing you fill up with water and
then next hour you got to drive
somewhere. Forget it.
>> No, don't don't drive with it. Look, the
product is telling you, Tommy, I don't
think so.
>> I'm out from an undisclosed location.
>> Copy that.
>> I'm going to make you an offer cuz I
think it's
>> I think I love this product. I
>> see that coming, too.
>> But I have a few contingencies. Your
sister has to be committed to it.
>> She is.
>> It has to have a salesman. And I really
have to like your sister.
>> Oh, you're going to love her.
>> You have to bring the price down to
under 100 bucks.
>> I absolutely think you can. I believe
you. With those contingencies, I'll give
you the 100,000 for 25%.
>> Okay.
>> Tell me, is there anybody that has a
formal product?
>> No, sir. No. I am the only person that
that sells this.
>> And you think your um patent protects
you from anybody else doing it?
>> Absolutely.
>> I don't think so. Anybody can get a
piece of plastic, throw it in the back
of a truck.
>> I'll offer you a $100,000 for 33%.
>> No contingencies. Recognizing that
you're going to be off quite a bit,
we'll just work together to get the
price down. I'll also get this to my
guys at Tower Paddle Board. They can get
out there and start promoting. That's
it. Tommy, let's rock and roll. What do
you think,
>> Barbara? I love watching you. You have
two offers. I can't believe it.
>> Thank you for that amazing Wait, just
the last time somebody told me he loved
me, he left me and married my sister.
>> I would never do that. I would never do
that to you.
>> Mark, I I appreciate negotiate that you
understand where I'm coming from.
>> Yeah. Don't negotiate.
[Music]
>> Let's do a deal.
[Applause]
>> We'll have a lot of fun, man.
>> Marry your sister,
man.
>> Thanks for what you do.
>> I have no idea if the business is going
to work, but it was a great pitch.
>> Pleasure meeting you guys. Thank you for
your service.
>> Shakaroo. Thanks, Tommy.
>> Wow. Mark's deal was not necessarily
sweeter in terms of money, but he
understands what my work life is like
and he's he's willing to flex on that.
So, that's why I ended up going with
Mark.
[Applause]
First in the tank is a portable version
of a classic game.
[Music]
Hey Sharks, I'm Tom Filipini from the
Mile High City and today I'm raising
$150,000
for a 10% stake in my company, Pepper
Pong. I'm here to tell you that the
world's largest racket sport
uh pingpong
is uh the world the world's largest
racket sport
uh pingpong has become pretty crusty.
This old dog was invented in the 1800s
and has uh uh and and that was a century
before sliced bread. And it shows
It's time to spice things up.
Meet Pepper Pong. Our brand new game
that is fun for all ages and sets up
anywhere. Roll tape.
Pepper Pong ditches the need for a
dedicated table. Any reasonably flat
surface, including the floor, becomes a
battleground. Our fence expands to fit
any surface and sets up in seconds. No
flimsy clamps.
But the real spice is in the peppers.
Three unique balls designed to be
adaptable to any surface and making
pepper pong easy to learn but very
difficult to master. Low bounce jalapeno
is great for beginners and small tables.
Medium bounce habanero is an all-around
favorite for all table sizes and all
skill levels. And then to really spice
things up, you have the ghost pepper for
intense rallies on larger tables. Pepper
Pong is whisper quiet and furniture
friendly, so even mom will be playing
ball in the house. So, Sharks, which of
you wants to rally this movement and
serve up the spiciest game of our
generation?
>> Good job.
>> All right. All right.
>> Who's going to play?
>> So, which which of you wants to come up
and play Pepper? We'll play doubles. All
right.
>> Come on. Come on.
>> All right. Now,
>> we go.
>> Oh, ace. I think we won.
>> I do, too.
Okay. So, how many have you sold?
>> We sold about $260,000
uh worth of product. We we launched less
than a year ago.
>> Are you selling them mostly on Amazon or
where?
>> We're only selling on our website. We're
really trying to control the consumer
experience and 100% of our reviews have
been five star reviews. Wow. Wow. All
All
>> How many reviews do you have? Four
reviews.
>> We have about 160 reviews. The cool
thing about it is, you know, ping pong
has some real flaws to it, right? You
need the big table. You need the gear. I
don't know if you've ever shown up
somewhere where the paddles are broken
or the balls are cracked like that or
the
>> paddles have splinters in them.
>> Exactly. The other big problem with ping
pong is it doesn't level the playing
field. So if one person is good, the
other person is not good, it's a
blowout. And nobody likes blowouts.
>> What do they cost to make? What do you
sell them for?
>> So landed cost is about $20. Yeah,
>> we're selling them for $70.
>> Why so little? Why so little?
>> I thought so much actually. I think we
have some elasticity up to 89 and you
know without much detriment to sales or
conversion rates. So
>> you got you got room on price and Tom
you got to tell me what's your
background and how did you come up with
Pepper Pong?
>> It's it's actually a very uh interesting
and personal story. Um so I've had a
long career of success uh in business.
In my mid20s I started a a travel large
travel company. It was a well-known
brand. Unfortunately, I was afflicted
with uh alcohol, alcoholism for a number
of years. And after my successes, I
found quite a bit of failure. I was able
to become sober in 2016.
>> Good for you.
>> With the amazing support of my wife and
my my three beautiful daughters who I
almost frankly almost lost lost
everything else financially was
devastating for me. But I bounced back.
have had no relapses since. I feel like
I was shot out of a cannon. This is
truly my passion project.
>> So, are you the only investor? Is that
you?
>> Yes, it's only it's only me.
>> How much money you have? How much did
you put into it?
>> About $500,000.
>> Wow. It's really my entire life story in
a product.
>> Well, did you make your own molds?
>> Yeah, because what what was this
$500,000? Because we have Yeah,
>> that was a big cost for you because it's
probably a multi-avity mold.
>> Yeah, it's a multi-avity mold. They're
expensive. You know, we've got a good
amount of inventory. So, um, so a little
under 10,000 units remaining right now.
>> Do you know what your customer
acquisition cost is?
>> It's about 21 $222.
>> Basically, you're you're you're giving
up a majority of your margin to acquire
that customer, but they only buy one
game. They don't buy multiple games.
>> Well, we're actually seeing a tremendous
amount of repeat purchases because why?
Because because gifting this is a
massively popular gift.
>> Tom, take us through your sales and your
profitability since you started. Yeah.
So, we really started selling in earnest
last fall.
>> Okay. Last fall.
>> Yeah. And we did $160,000 of net sales.
>> Got it. And you're on track this year to
do how many sales?
>> Between 600 and $800,000. But this will
be a generation defining game. And it's
patented. So,
id about it.
>> So, the the fence is the is the is the
patent.
>> It's a foldable fence.
>> Yep.
>> What do you need the money for?
>> We we need a second mold, I believe, at
some point to double output production.
But that's not,
>> you know, that's one of the biggest
lessons that entrepreneurs have to um
learn and mistake they make often. So,
you really should go slowly. Don't start
another mold, which is close to
$100,000. Go step by step.
>> Walk run.
>> Yeah.
>> So, anyway, I think it's very fun, but I
don't think it's the right journey for
me. So, I'm sorry. I'm out.
>> Thanks, Lori.
>> Um, it sounds like it's getting some
traction. But it boils down to, well,
how much of a royalty do I want to put
on it? How do I ever get back my cash? I
want to make 5x on that. It's not
grabbing me by the ping pong balls.
Listen, I've enjoyed the presentation. I
I think it actually has proven itself
and now it's about how the gasoline gets
poured on it. But for me, I'm out.
>> Tom, look, what you've done is great.
your personal journey. I mean, just to
go from where you are with your family,
to take the step and just have the
confidence to keep on pushing forward is
amazing. You deserve a ton of credit,
but this is who you are. This is your
identity. And those types of businesses
are really difficult to invest in. I
think you'll be great on your own, but
for those reasons, I'm out.
>> Tom, my my question is just how you feel
about retail. That's where I kind of be
interested. I think I'm really
interested in your story. I mean, to
come out here and be vulnerable and talk
about sobriety, I I I haven't had a
drink in 2 years.
>> I didn't have Thank you. I kept saying,
"Oh, dry January. Couldn't make it past
dry January." And I looked at my life. I
said, "I got over cancer. I got out of
the clutches of drug dealers in the
hood, but I can't get away from just
doing this. You know, you went through
that dark stage." Yep.
>> Right. So, welcome back.
>> Hope you're feeling the same way.
>> I'm feeling absolutely amazing about it.
Um, I'll give you the 150K. Uh, but my
idea is to help you with the retail
side, but I want 30%.
>> Woo. But I think the Todd is still in
the deal.
>> Yeah, I'm still in the deal. Um, Todd,
>> I've read about your background.
>> Come in and save the day.
>> I could see these at every raising canes
just as a as a as a as a customer
entertainment vehicle.
>> I love uh ping pong. Like actually, I
did a collaboration restaurant with my
friend Post Malone. I'm also invested in
a pickle ball team. That's been a great
investment and continues to do better.
And so I love the portability. Um I love
you. So I'm going to make you an offer,
right?
[Music]
Three sharks are out. Tom has an offer
on the table from Damon for his portable
pingpong game, Pepper Pong. But Todd is
also interested. So, I'll give you the
$150,000
and I'll go uh 25%.
>> Todd, you animal.
>> Why would you undercut me like that?
You're a guest.
>> I I'd love to hear, you know, sort of
your respective visions. Like, how how
could you help me? I mean, that's
obviously a big haircut uh on the equity
for me.
>> Yeah. No, I I can tell you what what I
can add, right? I told you about the
collaboration with Post Malone at our
restaurant. Our sales went through the
roof. I know how to do these things. and
I'm a social media machine. I got a
whole team behind me that helps me with
these things and I live it every day.
And so I'll get your product out there.
I'll help you expand it for low
acquisition calls. I think that's what I
bring to the table.
>> I believe you. Damon, what's your sort
of vision for how this would play in
retail?
>> Well, how would do you think it would
play in retail?
>> Well, when you sell retail, you know,
you have a difficult time, you know,
bringing your customer into the family,
so to speak.
>> Yes. And I want to bring my customer
into the family, at least in the
beginning, to nurture that relationship,
make them feel part of a movement. So, I
want to go to retail, but not right out
of the gate.
>> Well, then I I want to be um respectful
of your your dream.
>> TomTom,
>> I'm in, buddy. You me.
>> Listen, listen. You know,
>> love it. All right, that helps. That
helps. He's
>> You're concerned about retail, which I
can understand that you're building it
up slowly. I think out of respect for
you and your dream, I think that I'm
gonna take my offer off the table. I'm
out.
>> Okay. No, I get it. Um Todd, I I would
love to do a deal with you. I I'm
curious if you'd split the difference
with me down to 17.5%.
>> 17.5 in the spirit of a of a long-term
partnership.
>> Let's go 20 and you got yourself a deal.
>> Could you go just 19 just
psychologically?
[Music]
Why not? All right, let's do it.
>> Let's go, man.
>> I guess we're going to do it, baby.
You're going to build it. It's going to
be great.
>> Thanks so much.
>> Congrats.
>> Thanks, guys. Well done. I appreciate
all of you. Thank you.
[Music]
I believe Pepper Pong is going to make a
big difference in the world, not just
for fun, but as a way to inspire people
to go do great things and to be
vulnerable and to connect with other
people and put your phone down and just
build relationships through the joy of
competition.
[Music]
Hey, I'm Chris Rutder and my company is
Spikeball. I'm here in San Diego today
for a spikeball tournament. We've got 45
teams and they are psyched to play
today. The way I like to describe
spikeball is if volleyball and floor
square had a baby, it would be called
spikeball.
Spikeball is so much fun because it's so
active. It's so competitive. There's
strategy, a ton of trash talking.
Absolute blast to play. Spikeball
started as a fun, casual backyard game.
It's becoming a competitive sport,
especially on college campuses.
>> Thanks for coming, everybody. Spikeball.
>> Potential for spikeball is limitless.
There will be sponsors. There will be
professional players. It will be the
next great American sport. I know a lot
of people may think I'm off my rocker by
talking like that, but when we started
this company, people thought we were
crazy as well. And look where we are
today.
>> That's what you call spike ball.
>> We're hoping to blow spike ball up.
Sharks, I believe, can help us get
there.
[Applause]
[Music]
Hello Sharks. My name is Chris Rutder
and I'm from Chicago. I'm here today
looking for an investment of $500,000 in
exchange for 10% of my company,
Spikeball. Spikeball is poised to be the
next great American sport. Like all
great sports, spikeball is very easy to
learn but really really difficult to
master. It can be a casual fun backyard
game or it can be hardcore competition.
Another great thing is spikeball is
ultra portable. So all you need is this
ball, that net, and one of these
backpacks and you can take it absolutely
anywhere. So standing to my right here
in the black jerseys is Chico Spike
Ball. They have been the number one
ranked team in the country for over 12
months. These guys are just absolutely
dominating. dominating.
>> They're going to play a couple points
against Tyro United. Now, you're going
to see in a second they're going to
serve the ball basically just by
bouncing it off the net towards Tyro.
Now, just like in volleyball, Tyro has
up to three hits between each other
before they have to spike it back on the
net. Now, they of course want to spike
it so Chico can't get to it. If you
can't get it on the net, the other team
gets a point. First team to 21 wins.
Once the ball is in play, there are no
sides. All four players can run
absolutely anywhere they want.
Gentlemen, I'm going to ask the guys to
come out here and play a couple points.
[Music]
>> Awesome. Thank you guys.
>> Who invented this game? You?
>> No. Brought it back to life. So, it was
around back in 1989 and one of my good
friends bought it at a toy store and uh
they and my older brother played a bunch
and absolutely loved it. And about 10
years ago, you know, the light bulb kind
of went off. We went home and kind of
did our homework, found out that the the
product had been off the market for like
15, 20 years.
>> Who owns Spike Ball?
>> We do.
>> How did that happen?
>> Uh their rights were completely expired.
So,
>> and you just reclaimed them.
>> Uh the trademark, yes. There was never a
patent. Has it ever been contested now
that it's successful?
>> No. And we actually did get a utility
patent.
>> Some guy that's going to be watching
this going, "Oh my goodness." You you
mentioned obviously that it's a sport.
Where can you take it? How big can it
be?
>> It can be huge. So we've got a governing
body called USA Spikeball. So we have
tournaments all over the country.
>> How many tournaments are being played?
>> We'll have about a 100 tournaments this
year.
>> And you charge them.
>> It's a loosely a premium model. We also
sell memberships. And how did you
>> Wait, wait, wait. It sells memberships.
Tell us about that.
>> Yes. So you can buy a quote baller
membership on USA spike ball.
>> Say that again.
>> Baller.
>> Are you all ballers?
>> Markers.
>> Ballers, baby.
>> What's the the demographic? What's the
average age that
>> 18 to 24 male is our sweet spot.
>> What does one cost?
>> Uh $59.99 plus shipping.
>> Can I go to a toy store and buy it?
>> Some toy stores, yes. We're focusing
more on uh sporting goods stores. We've
been around about 6 years. the first 5
years pure e-commerce.
>> Chris, how how many units are you
selling a year?
>> Uh, this year we've sold 29,000
units.
>> And how much do they cost to make?
>> Uh, a little over $14 a unit. So last
year your total gross sales $1.4
million. And this year you expect it to
be around three between 32 and 35.
>> And you've got to be killing it then
because it's all margin. So what are you
what are you netting at the bottom line?
So last year we netted I want to say
about 170 180 grand.
>> Why so little?
>> Retail is growing like crazy. So our
e-commerce business is good, but retail
is really eating in.
>> So how much you paying yourself?
>> Um my salary uh 175.
>> There you go. Okay, that makes it up.
Good for you.
>> Can I go back to one thing? Just the
price.
>> Sure.
>> Can you get your cost down from $14?
Have you tried that? Where do you think
it could go to? Um, my I'd love to get
down to the $10 range.
>> Chris, what are you going to use the
money for?
>> Uh, working capital. We're starting to
get really, really big orders from
really big retailers.
>> How big from who? For what?
>> The biggest we work with is Dick
Sporting Goods. We've got POS for 10,000
units to ship.
>> Have you done any tests with them to see
how it sells through the store?
>> Yeah, our initial test was 100 stores.
>> You started your test how long ago?
>> Uh, two months ago. Do they take it to
more stores each time?
>> We're in 250 now. So, wait. In 2 months,
you've gone from 100 to 250.
>> Yes.
>> And just in that brown box, I mean, that
was your Can I see the box?
>> So, probably word of mouth is getting
out there. Let's call it a um uh not a
toy business, but it's a
>> it's a sports.
>> Amen.
>> Sport
not sell it in toy stores cuz you have
to protect your brand and as soon as it
shows up there, you're just
>> Would you sell it at Walmart if they
asked you?
>> Maybe. Okay. So, dude, dude, so GoPro,
>> huge fan.
>> We do extremely well at Walmart.
>> Got it. This is the expertise I need.
>> I would not shy away from that
opportunity.
>> If you actually achieve your goals this
year, you'll do about 320
to 50,000 pre-tax.
>> You're asking me to pay 20 times your
cash flow for a ball in a net.
>> Ball in a net. That's kind of like
calling your baby ugly. I mean, I love
this. It's a little more.
>> He just called your baby ugly.
>> Look, I think the business is worth
about seven times the cash flow. It's
worth around 2.5 million bucks. That's
what I think.
>> Would you do a deal with a value like
that on it?
>> No. I think that's discounting it way
too much. Um, we have
>> Let's see if you can I'm going to sit
back and watch and see how enthusiastic
another shark might be.
>> I think it's very clever.
>> Thank you. I think it's very interesting
what you've done, but not often do I say
I can't see my way to the valuation, but
here is one of these where it's like I
just I don't see it.
>> For that reason, I'm out.
>> All right. Thank you, Lori.
>> I I'd say you've got a great opportunity
to cost reduce this thing. I wouldn't be
too hung up on your $60 price point.
>> Okay.
>> Especially as you move into larger
retailers.
>> One thing I'd love from you, if I may,
>> it's not something that I can personally
get super passionate about. It's just
not right for me. I know.
>> All right. Thank you.
[Music]
>> Look, Chris, I'm going to be brutally
honest with you. When you when you
walked in, I thought this was going to
be stupid. If you would have brought
this to me and just described this to me
and said, "Mark, would you invest? We're
going to turn this into 3 million in
sales. Dick's going to place an order
for 10,000 units all within a few
years." I would have said, "Step away
from the bar." And then if you would
have said on top of that, you think
that's bad, we're going to have leagues.
>> Absolutely.
>> I would have said, I'll take what you're
drinking. But you did it, right? You're
killing it.
>> Thank you. Thank you. But you know, I
can't see my way to a $5 million
valuation. I can't
>> you right. Can't I can't I can't I I
can't. I'm out.
>> Oh, ouch.
Three sharks are out. Chris only has two
more chances to make a deal for his
backyard game, Spikeball.
>> So, Chris, I'm impressed. Okay. I'm
impressed in your articulation of your
business and what you've achieved so
far. You've been very aggressive on the
valuation of you're very, very
passionate about being worth a lot and
you've run into a lot of roadblocks
already. all the encouragement from Mark
and then he goes out. That's just
ridiculous. So, here's the deal. I'll
loan you $500,000 because this business
can now support some debt. I'll take the
10% equity as a warrant for doing it.
All right? Um the terms on the debt are
simple. I'm going to charge you 9%. I'm
going to work very hard for you to be
successful
because the 10% could be worth something
if you achieve success. And there's
enough evidence here that you've got a
bit of a viral thing going on, which I
find very interesting. So, what do you
want to do?
>> Um, I thank you for that. I'd like to
see if Damon, uh, can we have a chat?
>> Very, very, very smart guy. Um,
>> I have the same concern that most of the
other sharks have. The evaluation is not
spike ball, it's balls with spikes, you
know. So, here's what I'm thinking. Your
challenge is making goods and providing
them to the store, right? I'll give you
the 500,000 and my agenda will be to
take that pain away, which is starting
to do licensing, starting to do
manufacturing and shipping to the
stores.
>> Mhm.
>> That would be what I would be interested
in for 25% of the whole company. You'll
be able to run the sports division.
You'll be able to run the online sales
because that's creating your sports
division.
>> Got it.
>> Value your business at 2 million.
>> Yes. Um so thank you for that. That's
that's that's quite rich. Um would you
consider 500K at 15%.
[Music]
We have got this snowball that is
rolling downhill and getting bigger and
bigger. We've got an army of amplifiers.
school.
>> I got army suppliers, too, that will
help you. So, that's going to cost me
alone $200,000 that's not passed on to
you.
>> You're saying you have no flexibility.
>> You're you're in a crossroads right here
where you have a very high valuation
>> and you're getting a little greedy
>> and um you know, this is one of those
moments that you can lose it all.
>> I'll go 22.
Call it even at 20.
>> We're done.
>> All right.
>> You're kidding me.
>> Go, Chris.
>> Awesome.
>> Congrats, buddy.
>> Thanks, guys.
>> All right, guys. Thank you.
>> Now, congratulations,
>> guys.
Having a partner like Damon just really
makes all that time and hard work and
effort just really worth it. And I mean
just feel like we're on the top of
Everest right now. This is just awesome.
[Music]
Next up is a convenient way to bring the
campfire with you.
[Music]
>> Hi Sharks. I'm Brent.
>> And I'm Brian. And we are fired up to
show you our new product. We're seeking
$50,000 for a 20% stake in our business.
>> Campfires have been a crucial part of
man's life since the beginning of time.
>> Yes, but campfires are difficult to
start, maintain, clean up, and let's be
honest, stumbling around in the middle
of the night looking for wood is never
easy. But we solved that problem. Check
this out.
[Music]
Wow, it's fire.
>> Meet the Radiate portable campfire. The
most convenient way to make a campfire.
>> Radiate is easy to light. It's easy to
store. It's easy to carry. And it leaves
no trace. Take it to the beach,
tailgating, camping, even using your own
backyard. Gives off heat, light, and the
urge to sing campfire songs.
>> Yeah. But if Robert is going to start
singing or uh Mark, you want to end the
campfire in a quick slide the lid back
on.
>> Ah, cool.
>> So,
>> he's ready to make a smoking deal.
>> Smoking. Can we see?
>> Can we get samples?
>> Got some samples to you.
>> Yeah. Great puns.
>> Is there a difference between the tins
like scents or anything?
>> They're absolutely absolutely getting
the original.
>> Thank you so much. Lighter, too.
>> Wa, that's heavy.
>> Yeah. You want to light it up?
>> Oh, it's wax. Just on the side
>> directly on the briquettes.
>> Oh, you just got to hold it for a little
bit.
>> There you go.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, cool.
>> Hit a couple of them.
>> This is Oh, there you go.
>> Oh, it's really cool.
>> What do you make it for?
>> 575. Okay. Wholesale is $1250. It
retails $25.
>> How many hours does this burn?
>> So, this will burn for up to 6 hours.
>> How much does How much does this weigh?
>> It's a four pound four pound. Does this
create ship shipping problems? The fact
that it's so heavy? So, it costs about
$950 to ship it in the US for one, but
it only cost about $13 to ship two.
>> I want to go back to the burn time
because it's $25, but you only get 6
hours burn time.
>> 6 hours.
>> So, okay.
>> Yeah, that's our InstaFire burns
indefinitely.
>> It's not that long. So, how does this
compare to Instafire? A deal that Lori
and I did.
>> Instafire is meant to, you know, make a
traditional type of campfire either in a
fireplace.
>> I can just buy I I can bring a tin with
from my cookies, right?
>> Instafire is an awesome product. There's
no question about that. This is built
for families. Okay? If you want to have
a campfire in your backyard, you take
this out, you throw it up.
>> Why couldn't I just take a tin and put a
couple Instafiers in there to save save
some money?
>> Convenience is a bigger factor. Real
outdoors people use Instafire. Okay.
This is a product for a lot of people
that don't necessarily want to be
outdoors for days at a time.
>> Break down the numbers for me.
>> We've been shipping for 30 days, Rohan.
We sold,00 units.
>> Oh, wow.
>> We crowdfunded 400 units.
>> Okay. How much? What was your goal?
>> $1,000. We're trying to get a proof of
concept. We've done
>> So, you've only been in business
essentially for 30 days and it was a
crowdfunding campaign.
>> No, no, just wait a sec. Once we got the
concept proved and people were
interested in it, we've sold 600 through
traditional wholesale retail
>> where what kind of retail?
>> Surf shops, camp stores, sporting goods
stores. My wife and I were vacationing
even before we were shipping. I had
samples of it. We went to Kawaii and we
were using it, taking pictures of it,
and people were coming up and saying,
"Oh my god, where'd you get that?
Where'd you get that?
>> Okay. Wait, before you jump in that,
>> guys. Hey guys, we're starting to get a
lot of smoke. Can you um put a lid on
it?
>> Yeah.
>> Pardon?
>> In areas where I can't have a fire, like
a beach or a forest.
>> Sure.
>> Am I allowed to light this?
>> Yeah. In in most instances, what you
need is a contained fire. Okay. This is
a contained fire. And so, yeah, you're
allowed to do it. You can shut it on and
off just like I I I demonstrated here.
So, you can have a campfire and
literally get up and leave and no one
knows you were there.
>> What are the other scents? Is that a
mosquito repelling one?
>> That's correct. It has a eucalyptus and
lemon oil in it to repel mosquitoes. And
the last one is a samore kit.
>> A s'more kit.
>> What about uh a concern I have is the
heat of the tin. I don't see any warning
on the tin.
>> As soon as you open up the tin, there's
a warning label and instruction manual
inside.
>> Okay. So, I'm going to make you an
offer. All right. I'll give you $50,000
for 25%.
>> Thank you so much for the offer.
>> Well, you're not going to just say thank
you because I'd really like to have an
answer.
>> Okay, great. You want to tell them that
the other sales point?
>> Yeah. Let me
>> Is this coming to a yes or no?
>> Absolutely. Absolutely. We just need to
educate you one more about one more
feature.
>> One more feature.
>> She just made you an offer. What else
you need to educate her on?
>> We want her to know what she's getting
into. Mark, come on.
>> Well, that's what you do after you do
the deal.
>> Selling time or is it closing time?
>> Right.
>> Let me say something, Brad. There's a
piece of me that is saying you'd be
really annoying to work with.
[Applause]
All Sharks are still in. Brent and Brian
have one offer on the table from Barber
for their campfire in a tin product,
Radiate. However, Brent's personality
may jeopardize the deal.
>> There's a piece of me that is saying
you'd be really annoying to work with.
So, don't prove me right on that
instinct.
>> Guys, I'm going to make it easy for
Barbara. I think the product's too
heavy. I don't think it's original
enough. I think it's a little bit too
expensive. I just am not all that
excited about it. And so, for those
reasons, I'm out.
>> Okay. Thanks, Mark.
>> I'm going to make it easier, too. I like
the concept. Mark and I did Insta Fire
and it
>> it's a great product. Instafire burns
indefinitely and it's safe, all natural,
and non-toxic. This burns for only 6
hours. So, I'm sorry. I'm out.
>> Thanks,
Sorry to hear that.
>> Rohan, what are you going to do?
>> Well, they haven't given Barbara a
response yet. So, I mean,
>> well, I think they're waiting to see
what you're going to do.
>> Really? Are you out or not?
>> I'm waiting to see what you're going to
do.
>> I'd like them to respond to Barbara. I
mean, I feel like she got to respect.
>> No. No. He has an ulterior motive. He
wants you to respond to me so he could
give you a worse deal.
>> You know, Barbara, I want to work with
you and and and I don't take it
personally that you think I'm annoying
because honestly, I'm not annoying.
>> You farted before. I just I do what I do
and I get things done. So, I I don't
find that annoying. I just find I find
it honest. Like, I'll tell you what I
feel and I hope you tell me uh you know
how you feel.
>> I find you a little annoying.
>> That's fine. That's fine. That's fine.
But at the end of the day, if we're
working together and you need me to go
out and pitch somebody, you're going to
want me to know all the information
before I make a deal.
>> Right. Honestly, I have total confidence
in you as an entrepreneur. You have that
fire in your belly that I'm always
looking for. All my great entrepreneurs
are annoying in one way. When I used to
manage sales people, I always knew who
were going to be the best ones because
they drove me nuts. Okay, I don't object
to that.
>> I actually like your engaging
personality. I like the fact that you
got you've intimidated the crap out of
Robert. He hasn't said anything sitting
in the corner there.
>> Robert, you're a boy scout. You've been
a boy scout.
>> I was a queen scout. That didn't come
out right. That didn't come out right.
>> You want to define that
>> in Canada
scout you could be would be a queen
scout. So it was like an Eagle Scout. I
just wanted to define that. Anyway, go
ahead.
>> Anyway, so um
>> I I think I have a larger network,
>> okay,
>> than Barbara has. I feel that the
products that I have go in a lot of
those areas. So, I'll also offer you
$50,000 for 25%.
>> And if I could just add something else,
I have no doubt in my mind that this is
a winner. The portability of this, the
size of it, the weight of it, you can
stack it, it's easy to show in an aisle.
You don't need an end cop. This is a
phenomenal product. It's a money maker,
honey.
>> I don't see it just in camping goods or
sporting goods. I see it in gift shops.
I mean, you've done an amazing job
>> with this. Mark laughs, but I have this
in several clothing boutiques that have
been selling it and reordering.
>> Absolutely. People pay for convenience.
People pay for cool. I don't find you.
So,
>> Robert, is there an offer there?
>> I find you
>> Robert, make your offer.
>> I find you quirky. I'll also offer you
50,000 for 25%.
>> So, the key to this game is buzz
building and distribution. Two areas
that I can bring to bear better than
anybody else here. You just need a few
key connections and some great ideas and
you guys have the energy to punch this
through. Roan's a great guy. I'm sure he
can invite you to the best parties and
you can hang out. It's a business.
>> Robert has to give you that deal because
he doesn't have the distribution network
to help you. That's This is This is
ridiculous. Now you're just pissing me
off.
I I hate to lose and I want to invest
with you guys and win with you guys.
I'll give you the 100,000 for 25%.
>> I've doubled my amount. I'm tired of
this. This product is going to be huge.
100,000 for the Queen.
>> You have the passion for the business.
We'd like to make a deal with you.
Yeah,
>> the queen's cap comes on board.
>> The new mama. There was not even like,
"Would you like to come?"
>> Congratulations, guys. I would have gone
up. Thank you so much.
>> Oh, please.
>> Goodbye, buddy.
>> That's how it's done.
>> The waters a little bit.
>> We went with Robert because he gave us
the best offer. He was the one that was
passionate about the product and he made
it known with his offer. It was easy to
tell he was the right choice. No,
there's other way.
>> Scout rubber.
>> I like it. Good job.
>> Come on.
>> Come on. I
>> I'll give it to you. I'll give it to
you,
>> Rohan. At a certain point, you just piss
me off.
>> Desperate. That's what I say. Desperate.
That was annoying to me. You're
annoying.
>> You're annoying.