[Music]
All right, guys. Let's do
this. Next into the tank are young
entrepreneurs with a beverage for a new
generation.
[Music]
Hey Sharks, my name's Justin Fentel. I'm
Brad Schultz. And I'm Amy Steedman. And
we're from Austin, Texas. Our company is
Beatbox Beverages and we're seeking
$200,000 for 10% of our company. Now,
Kevin, you know wine. So, picture this.
A delightful Cabernet from the Bordeaux
region of France. It's been Asian oak
barrels for 15 years. It's perfect. You
could almost taste it, right? That's
true. Bring it over. Well, there's just
one problem. Why?
Boring.
Exactly.
Now we're getting down. Oh, this is
Beatbox Beverages and we are not boring.
We're changing box wine forever with
flavors like cranberry limeade and blue
raspberry lemonade. All in one sweet
looking Beatbox. But it's not just a
box, it's an experience. Take Beet Box
to your next party and you're instantly
a legend. Box wine is incredibly
popular. It's affordable. It's
convenient. It's got a large size where
you can share with everyone at the
party. But the wine you find inside
leaves much to be desired. We're using a
unique orange wine that drinks more like
a spirit than a wine and allows us to
create mixed drinks that our customers
absolutely love. Beatbox is a party in a
box with almost seven bottles of wine
packed into every box. Wow. We've
created an innovative, fun brand that's
really speaking to our generation, and
we're ready to take this company to the
next level. The only question is, will
the Sharks be joining the Bee Box party?
Let's try some. Okay. Yeah. What is
orange wine? I've never heard of that.
Yeah. So, orange wine is a is a unique
wine. It's actually uh clear, much more
like a white spirit. The blue one is the
blue raspberry lemonade. The pink is a
cranberry limeade. The yellowish color
is our margarita flavor and the tea is a
sweet tea. This tastes like
Oh, are you kidding? This is good. He
loves it. This is delicious.
I love this one. Reminds me of those
like blue raspberry snow cones. Wait,
how much alcohol is in here? 11.1%.
What? Yes. Lori, cheers. Yep. Only 120
calories per serving and only 7 g of
sugar per serving. You know what? I love
the wine. Kevin, give him the money.
Tell us more about the business.
Manufactured. What are your margins?
Who's actually distributing it? So, we
self-distributed. We actually um became
a winery ourselves. the Texas winery,
you can self-distribute. But we got, you
know, to the point where we were
spending more time in our facility
making it, gluing the boxes and
distributing it. We couldn't market it,
right? We're getting too big. So, we
found a c-acker in Dallas and they now
make it for us. And we saw a
distributor. Since then, we've grown our
sales pretty dramatically. What are your
sales so far? Just We've done $235,000
in 14 months, and 120,000 has come in
this just this quarter.
How much money did you raise when you
started? So, so we self-funded it for
$55,000. We took on $100 $100,000 in
family and friends debt. So, tell me how
you're going to go from $235 to 5
million. So, the strategy is to identify
new stores where we know it's going to
sell. Go into that store and support it
with at least six tastings. Tastings are
by far the best way for us to get the
product out there. What do you need the
money for? It's for the engine of
growth. Opening up new stores and, you
know, supporting it with tastings. Our
tastings cost on average. So, hiring the
people $100 per tasting is on average in
That's expensive. That's expensive.
Doing it in the stores sounds really,
really good, but it's really hard to
leverage one store at a time. Even with
brand ambassadors, your leverage points
per any one store aren't great. In my
mind, the strategy was
wrong. You know, you need to take
advantage of events, take advantage of
big, you know, places where there are
thousands of people. Feel like we've
eliminated a lot of the risk associated
with a new consumer products company in
this space. We've got outsource
manufacturing. We've got the largest
distributor in the states and we need
someone to help us scale this business.
The good news for you guys is there
there's there's examples of beverages
that have gone viral and gone national.
You remember Skinny the Skinny Girl
story? Absolutely. Absolutely. That was
the same thing. Very viral for one
location then New York, Florida, Texas,
California, but she ran like hell for
everywhere else. The path of least
resistance is converting that person
that's buying that box of wine for a
party, but they don't know why they're
buying it. That's the easiest
conversion. And so Fronzia, an example,
is the number one box wine in the world.
Number one by volume, a billion dollars
in sales. Fronzia does a billion dollars
in sales. It is 3%. Do you know why?
Because they've got 100% penetration in
distribution. And everybody's tried to
knock it off. I'm in the wine business.
I sell 15,000 cases a year, 2.6 million
this year. It took me three years to get
there. And the thing that's holding me
back for I'll tell you what's holding
you back. The name. It's called Oly.
That's why it sells. You got to call it
BB Boss. Yeah. I'll make you an offer.
I'd like to offer you 400,000 for 20%.
Thank you so much. 400,000 for 20%.
Barbara. Yes. Guys, our biggest
challenge is breaking those states
through their distribution system. And
you could certainly help with that. No,
definitely. I'll put my offer on the
table with my own experience. I think
I'm worth twice as much as Barbara. I'm
sorry. She doesn't know what she's doing
in this space. I'll give you 200,000 for
20%.
Cuz I think the business is worth a
million bucks right now. 200. So you're
cutting Barbara's offer in half. Yeah.
No, they can go because you make a
snoody wine that has nothing to do with
No. Unfortunately, I've lived through
distribution. We're going to do 22,000
cases, 9 liter cases this year. Mark,
what? What up? What up, homie?
I don't see this as a wine product. You
guys got that down, right? You guys
don't sell wine, right? Period.
Industry. You guys sell fun. You're
absolutely, right? And then the biggest
question is how do you connect with
enough people quickly enough to make it
grow fast enough that all of a sudden
you're going, what am I going to do now?
Right? cuz you you're going as fast as
you can. You need a lot of help. You
want to create as big a splash as
possible. And I think I'm best suited up
here to do it. So, what I want to do is
make you an offer of
600K for
33%. You guys got to make a decision
what you want to
[Music]
do. All Sharks are still in. Beatbox
Beverages has three offers on the table.
400,000 for 20% from Barbara. 200,000
for 20% from Kevin and 600,000 for 33%
from
Mark, but Lori and Robert may also be
interested. I think you've got to blast
off. You've got to go fast. Last thing
you want is not being able to deliver
because, you know, viral is just that,
right? And either you're there to
fulfill Yeah. or you lose an
opportunity. I really appreciate you
saying that and that that offer you.
Thank you for making it. We we didn't
anticipate giving up. You know the
counter would just come back and tell
me. Yeah. So would you do a million for
a third?
Yeah. All right. Deal. Ready?
Wow.
[Music]
Congratulations. Let's party.
Can we do work, guys? Let's do work,
baby. That's a 3 mil valuation. All
right, guys. I'll be in touch real soon
and we'll get it turned around. Wow.
Thank you so much. You know what? He's
going to make money on it. Thank you so
much. Congrats, guys. Thank you so much.
And those are all mine. Don't take them.
We were going to make an offer, but I
wasn't going to come near that thing.
Did that really just happen? Oh my god.
Would I have ever imagined that we'd be
doing a million-dollar deal for with
Mark? No. Uh but here we are. We've done
it. And uh holy cow. Time to get to
work. I'm jealous of the deal. Let's
party.
[Applause]
Next into the tank is a Silicon Valley
veteran with an innovation he hopes will
save
[Music]
lives. Hello Sharks. My name is Charles
Michael Yim and I'm the founder and CEO
of Pthometer. I'm asking for $250,000
for 10% equity stake in my company. So,
just imagine you're at a dinner party or
maybe even a tailgate. Better yet, we're
at a local bar with some friends having
some champagne. Would anyone care for a
glass? Yes, please. Sure. Yeah. Well, I
thought I thought you were joking. Thank
you, Lori. Here you go.
Damon doesn't like champagne, so I'll
take his. I was told he does. There you
go. That's Damon's favorite drink.
Thank you, Senor. Charles, what should
we toast to? Uh, pitching to the sharks.
To you, Charles. Thank you. Sometimes it
ends badly, though. So, you know how it
goes. Eat some food. You have some
drinks. Before you know it, the night's
over and it's time to go home. And the
most important question is, are you safe
to drive?
And who would want to carry one of these
bulky old breathalyzers around? So
that's why I
created Brethrometer, the world's first
smartphone
breathalyzer. It's so small it can fit
in your
pocket. Let me show you how it works.
Simply retract the audio jack, plug it
into the
smartphone, activate the
[Music]
app. Within a matter of seconds, you'll
be able to know what your breath alcohol
level is. And better yet, it can even
tell you how long it'll take to sober
up. And if need be, you can even hail a
cab with a push of a button. So please
join me on this mission to help people
make smarter and safer decisions one
breath at a time. Thank you. So is this
already on the market? Are you selling
it currently? So we basically launched
in March via an Indiegogo campaign. We
sold 4,000 units within 30 days. We
generated $140,000 in revenue. Indiegogo
is a crowdfunding. It's just like
Kickstarter, correct? What do you sell
them for, Charles? $49.99. Can we see
it? Can we see it? Yes. I've thought one
of the biggest issues around these
things when the first handheld units
came out was that you get arrested or
worse you harm somebody because you're
drunk and you relied on the device to
make your decision. Isn't that a huge
liability to you? First and foremost,
there's no replacement for good
judgment. And so the pathometer device
basically promotes making smarter and
safer decisions. We provide the
instruction manual. We clearly label
disclaimers throughout the app. And as
long as we do our part in the due
diligence and we uphold our side, we're
in the clear. Should I come up and try
this with you? Uh, sure. Feel free to
come up.
And if she doesn't pass, if I can't
walk, if she can walk on those heels,
you already have your answer. So,
basically, go ahead and plug it into the
audio jack of your smartphone. Um, all
you need to go do is hit the start
button. Okay. Go ahead and breathe into
this hole like there. A little closer.
You're at a 04 right now. That would be
legal. Yeah, you're legal. Does it tell
you if she has bad breath, too? Uh, it's
funny as you mentioned that uh there's
an also another sensor we're looking
into. It's for halattosis. And
seriously, I'm starting to think of this
as more of a multi-function
breathalyzer. So, the next one we're
actually trying to focus on is uh
diabetes. It's in clinical trials and
it's obviously less intrusive than blood
pricking. Right. Charles, how did you
develop it? Are you a software guy? Are
you a hardware design guy? So, I used to
code back in the day. I built and sold
my last company within 18 months. So
essentially I went straight into
developing Bometer as soon as I exited
my last company. If you sold your last
business and you did very well, why
don't you take some of that money and
invest it in this? I have. Uh so I
started off with the first initial
50,000. I've already raised half a
million dollars in total from angels.
What are you going to use the money for?
Uh strictly uh manufacturing of the
product. Well, the good news for you is
that both in Europe and Canada, Mexico,
US, we're going to almost a zero
tolerance on alcohol and driving.
Correct. That's the trend. I'm sure
you've heard about the Federal Safety
Board in the United States that's trying
to lower it from 08 to 0. I'm I'm a big
fan of the sensor business. I've got a
company, Motion Loft. We're all about
sensors and I think that's the future of
technology. Okay, I'm going to make I'm
going to make you an
offer, right? What I'd like to do is
offer you
$500,000 for 20% of the
company. That's my offer. Okay. I'll
give you a chance to talk to other
people because I know you
Mark, would you let me go in with you?
No. And handle the retail end. This is
not really I'm not worried about the
retail. That's just like a smidgen
versus the long-term benefit.
I'll give you 250,000 for 15%.
You wouldn't have to lose that much
equity then. That's not bad. Okay, it's
much less diluted than Mark's 20%. Okay,
and not nearly as much cash.
So, just to open up the the the funding
channel of communication. So, the whole
idea within the next 60 days is to close
a full $1 million round from the Angels
back in Silicon Valley. So, what I'm
proposing is I'm more than willing to
open up the round, potentially involve
more than just one shark because I think
there's an incredible amount of value
here. Why don't you let the sharks do
the whole round? That's what I'm
proposing.
I don't I don't want to work with the
other sharks.
[Music]
You want to raise a million dollars,
don't you? I do want to raise a million.
So Mark's not giving you enough anyways.
Mark's not done talking yet.
All right, here's what I'll do, Charles.
I'll give you another $250,000 if Kevin
will have me on that. I'll do it. That
makes a lot of sense to me. And I'll
give you another 250,000
for 30%. Wow. Okay. Okay. And they have
no idea what they're investing in.
That's not true. It is absolutely true.
So, you've got 750, three times what you
asked for today, right, for 30%. Right.
You're very smart. I like to surround
myself with people much smarter than me.
That's why I have a challenge being up
here. Thank you very much. Um I want to
uh I think I want to match what you're
offering.
250,000 unlimited manufacturing. Okay.
10%.
and you wouldn't want to partake in the
groups. I've tried to get these three
bows together at breakfast one day and
and it's it's hard, you know? It's like
we don't we don't need all these people
right now. We can't agree. We've got
three maybe one. You could agree, Kevin.
What if we raise the dollar amount?
Wait, wait. I'm just saying for a
million bucks of straight equity and get
all the sharks in it. Now, I don't know
if Mark wants to play ball, but we need
a significant discount to do that. You
would be an unbelievable story if that
happened. That's true. Mark, because of
your previous investments in sensors,
you need the lion share. Tell us what
that is. Because competing with each
other is going to be very expensive
versus colluding with each other and
giving this guy every single
shark. Come on, Mr. Cuban.
Damn. You You're in on this, aren't you?
I'm willing to go in if Cuban's in and
you'll get all five sharks.
Charles has the potential of raising $1
million. All the funding he needs at
this point if Mark will join the rest of
the Sharks on a deal. Damian, you're in
on this, aren't you? I'm willing to go
in if Cuban's in, and you'll get all
five sharks.
Come on, Mr. Cuban.
You get the line share. What does the
lion share mean? What What equity do I
get? You get all five sharks. You need a
million bucks. Now it's your turn. Now
it's your turn to sell me.
Wow. Um, what can you give us on a
straight equity deal? This is your round
right here. Right now, the whole damn
thing. Wow, that's pretty serious. Uh,
oh, Charles, think.
You got to come up with a really good
offer.
[Music]
Okay. Would you be okay with taking say
300 doing 300,000 they split up the 700
amongst them?
I'll do I'll do 500k for 15%. For 15%.
Yeah. Okay. All right. All five sharks
will give you a million dollars. 500,000
for Mark Cuban for 15% and 500,000 split
amongst the four of us for the other
15%. So $1 million for 30%. Um,
do it. Do it.
There's a reason the champagne's open,
my friend. Can I have a second to make a
phone call to my CFO? Yes, of course.
Okay. Thank you.
Hey, Matt. How's it going? Hey, Charles.
So, they have basically uh all have uh
provided an offer um all five of them.
And so basically a million dollars uh
for 30% uh of the company. So I just
want to kind of get your thoughts. You
know, a million for 30 um 30%, you know,
it's a $3.3 million valuation. Not a
huge valuation. Sure. I mean, I
fundamentally I'm a little bit worried
about too many cooks in the kitchen. I
mean, they all have big egos. Um and so,
you know, can they work together
effectively? Who wants to bet what he
comes back at? He'll come back at 25. I
say 25. Yeah, you're right. Well, let's
see what happens. He's been out there a
long time.
Charles, welcome back. Thank you. You
have an opportunity to get all five
sharks and the power of all sharks
behind you. Right. Here's the deal. $1
million, 500,000 from Mark Cuban for
15% and 500,000 from the rest of the
Sharks. We're going to split it right
for a total of 30% for $1 million. And
the power of Shark Tank, what are you
going to do?
I accept. All right.
Wow. That's great. I got to tell you, I
didn't see that coming, but that's Thank
you. That's great. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Change our mind. We all have a toast
with us. All right. Cheers, guys.
Cheers. Cheers.
I've never thought about raising all the
cash that we needed from the entire team
of the Sharks. I'm ecstatic right now. I
have no words. I'm shocked.
[Music]
Hi Sharks. My name is Ari Tolwin and I'm
Joe Ceino. We're from New York and we're
seeking $1 million in exchange for 5% of
our business. Wow, you got our
attention. Sharks, milk today means
something totally different from what
the milkman used to deliver to our
homes. Sure, some of us still drink
cow's milk, but most of us have switched
to almond milk, oat milk, or even hemp
milk. But sharks, that comes at a price.
Most of those milks are hyper processed,
filled with gums, preservatives, and
fillers galore. Well, sharks, that's
where we come in. Move on over cow's
milk because making fresh, dairyfree
milk just became utterly easy.
Introducing new milk. We built a custom
machine for grocery stores where
shoppers can make delicious, nutritious,
pure, dairyfree milk at the push of a
button. We use the best ingredients.
Organic almonds from Spain for our
almond milks. A blend of organic cacao,
vanilla bean, and maple for our
chocolate milks. And a whole lot more.
Our new milks are homemade without the
mess or the fuss. We're on a mission to
bring plant-based diets and zerowaste
lifestyles to the world. So, Sharks, I
just have one question. Who wants to
milk this deal for all it's worth?
Sharks, in front of you are a flight of
delicious dairyfree milks for each of
you to try. But before you do so, Mark,
you've mentioned you're dairyfree. Come
on up and make some fresh milk for
yourself.
Sure. So, you can select almond milk or
oat milk. I'm going to go with almond
milk cuz I've had it, so I'll know what
it tastes like in comparison. Great. So,
just press that almond milk button and
then start on the bottom. So, the
machine is actually making it fresh.
It's not a concentrate or anything else
in there. It's taking pure organic
almonds from Valencia and making the
milk right now. That's fast. That's
cool.
The almond milk's very good. It tastes
nothing like the store brand. The milk I
just made incredible. You can tell it's
fresh almonds. It's incredible. Just to
understand what's in the machine. Give
us the choices. So, the first thing
about New Milk is that we're uh really a
food tech company and we built a
platform. Right now we have almond milk
and oat milk in there, but we could do
cashew. We could do hemp if that becomes
popular. We could do sesame. It's really
limitless. So, how long does it last and
what would be the expiration date on one
of these? Great question. It'll have a 7
to 10 day shelf life and it has to stay
in the fridge. I mean, I think that's
the,000lb gorilla in the room. You
coming to the Shark Tank, you want to
think big, right? You're asking for a
million bucks. Obviously, you need
capital to build out and lease these
machines to all the locations. That's a
different kind of business model because
they require maintenance. They require,
you know, the capital to build them.
Yeah. And then you also have to get the
space inside the grocery store to give
you what looks to me like about 10
square ft. Barbara, you're a real estate
mogul. You understand the value of
square footage. I'll tell you exactly
what it is in Midtown Manhattan for a
street location. It's 3,000 a foot in a
primary location. Yep. How big is that?
So, it's it's eight square feet. The
machines average $50,000 per year per
machine. And so when you think about it,
revenue in in revenue. Yep. And it's
unmanned and we pay no rent at all. What
does a machine cost? Uh the machines are
$30,000 each. They'll come down to 15.
You know, guys, I think it's a genius
idea. Number one, you're reducing
grocery stores perishable loss, right?
Number two is you're attracting new
customers. I like that uh that whole
concept. But were you in this area
before in traditional business? Like
tell us a little bit about yourselves.
Yeah. So, uh I come from the food and
beverage world. Before this, I did
aviation catering uh for commercial
jets, private jets. So, if you guys flew
to New York, you've eaten our food. Then
I started my own co-acking uh company
doing food and beverages. Uh after that,
I left and I started this with Ari. I'm
also a second time entrepreneur in the
space. I had a brand called Happy Tree
Maple Water. I had national
distribution. We were about 8,000
stores. Did you have an exit on that
water company? Uh, no. I shut it down
actually after we started this. I have a
question. What would Mark pay for that
bottle of almond milk that he took away?
Yeah, you'd pay $2 for the for the
bottle. That's a onetime uh charge. And
if you brought it back, you'd pay $3.99
to refill it. Okay. It's $3.99 for the
almond milk, $2 for the bottle. How much
goes to the grocery store? Yep. So, the
grocery store takes about a third. All
right. So, how much have you raised? Uh,
we've raised $12 million.
Wow. What was the last valuation? Our
last valuation was 40 million pre-
money. So, we've actually negotiated
with our investors in advance to give
you uh a Shark appropriate deal. Guys,
is there a bigger picture here? This is
obviously a big picture. Yes. Hit him,
Joe. So, this is our countertop device.
This is the bottle that goes with it.
Wow. We took a grocery machine. We
shrunk it down so it works on your
countertop so you can have the best.
That right there is a necessity for the
family, I think. What is that going to
cost the consumer? It's going to be
about $85 landed. That's your cost. What
was your plan to sell it to them for
then? Uh $1.99. Can you show us how the
small machine works? This is actually
just a 3D rendering prototype. Okay
guys, let's get into the numbers. Just
the basics, please. Top line, bottom
line. Topline, bottom line. Last three
years. Yeah. So 2018, $40,000 of
revenue, one machine, partial year.
What'd you lose? Spent a lot on R&D. So
we spent about $2 million on R&D in
2018. Losses were 2 mill. Correct.
Approximately 2019 320 topline. We ended
the year with 10 machines. How much you
lose? And then we spent $3 million on
R&D. So 5 million total losses so far.
Now we're getting to some critical mass
here. Yeah. What happens in the third
year? So third year is this year. Uh we
would have ended the year in about a $6
million year, but because of Corona
virus, our launch with Kroger, some
growth with Whole Foods, a launch with
Gellson's and some other regional
retailers were delayed. So what do you
think losses will be this year? This
year it's going to be about $2 million
as well, mostly R&D. 7 mil in the
ground. How much cash do you have in the
bank? 3 and a2 million. You projected
six, but where do you think you'll land
now? Uh, this year we're going to be
like 400k by the end of the year in
sales. Yeah. Wait, wait. I'm sorry.
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa. You said you
projected 6 million for this year, but
you feel you're going to end at 400?
Yeah. So, we would have we would have
ended up with 100 machines at the end of
the year. Can I get your attention just
for a moment, please? I've been sitting
here listening to every word. I still
don't get it. And I'm paying attention
like crazy. Ash, I'm sitting here
feeling like I'm back in second grade
failing again because I don't know what
the hell the teacher is talking about
yet again. You talk so much that I can't
grab a single word. I'm sure you've got
something good there. I don't know what
the heck it is, but I'm out.
I'm confused, too. I'm out.
[Music]
Lori, you can help us bring this to
millions of people around the world. And
I see you maybe struggling a little bit,
but I think you want to do it. Problem
for me is, you know, you only have so
much time in here. There's a lot to
explain about your business model,
right? And I don't think we've gotten a
lot of those answers out. If you're
asking for a million dollars for 5%,
you're losing money. This is a
prototype, so you don't even know yet.
We don't know. We actually have five of
these uh countertops in the field, but
they're stainless steel models for
coffee shops.
You came in asking for a pretty hefty
sum. It's just not investable for me
right now. I'm sorry. I'm out.
Joe, what do you sell the stainless
steel commercial unit? Uh $6.99. And
what do they cost you to make? 300
bucks. 300 bucks. All right, guys. Look,
I thought you were nuts when you first
walked out here, but now I have a
different opinion.
You did a very good job in presenting
the opportunity. I don't agree with my
fellow sharks. I get what you're doing.
It's extremely interesting.
I'm going to make you an offer.
Three sharks are out, but Kevin is
interested in Joe and Ari's plant-based
milk machine, New
Milk. I thought you were nuts when you
first walked out here, but now I have a
different opinion. I'm going to make you
an offer. I actually think there's a
huge fundamental demand for your
product, and I love watching Mark go
nuts over uh plant-based stuff. You
know, I'm a modified vegan. I only eat
vegan on Tuesdays. So, serious. The uh
the structure is difficult here because
you've already raised so much capital. I
would stick this in my venture debt fund
and I'd do an offer like this. I will
loan you a million dollars at 9.5%
interest for 3 years. That will cost you
8,000 a month and I will take 5% equity
that you offer. You know, I don't know
what Mark's going to do, but it gets you
into my sphere of the shark world and
you can talk to any of my entrepreneurs.
I do a hell of a job on digital for
them. So, if you're going after
consumers, I can help you. Yes. So,
first of all, really appreciate the
offer. Um, we do believe you could bring
a lot of value to the business. It's not
what we had in mind uh when we walked in
here. So, we want to at least get It's
an offer. Absolutely. Believe me, I was
not planning on giving you a million
bucks when I first saw this thing.
Okay, so here's the thing. So, you've
got $3 million left in the bank for two
products. I obviously love the stainless
steel version that you're putting in
coffee shops right now. I think that'll
sell like hot cakes at home. I think
you'll sell a million units easily. You
have it priced at $6.99. I think it'll
be priced at $8.99. And given your
margin at that price, you make $500 a
unit. That's a lot of money. But with
just $3 million in the bank between
marketing, right, and inventory and
receivables and everything else, you're
not going to have enough cash. So, you
guys know coming in you're going to have
to negotiate. So, let's just cut to the
chase. 5% is not enough. Can you do 6%.
No. What do you want?
Okay, guys. Here's my offer. I'm going
to give you $2 million. You only ask for
one. I'm going to give you $2 million. 1
million of that is going to be for 7%
equity. The other million is going to be
a loan at 3% interest. But I get an
additional 3% of stock as advisory
shares of straight up equity. But if you
don't use the loan, you don't have to
give me the 3% equity for that loan. So
in total, if you use all the capital,
it's $2 million for 10%.
Um, do you have a little bit of
flexibility? We we really want to work
with you. You can help us grow this. It
can be awesome, a major global success.
Do you have a little bit of flexibility?
That was my
flexibility. It's a It's a great offer,
Mark. We love it.
Depends how much you want to change the
world. Is 1% going to change?
Flexibility. We're at five, seven, can't
do six. You came in asking for a
million, and now you have access to 2
million.
[Music]
You got a deal. Deal. Yes, sir.
Appreciate it, guys.
Joe, you spoke up at the right moment.
Congratulations, guys. Good luck with
everything. We accept the
congratulations, but the work starts
now. Exactly. Right.
We just did a $2 million deal with Mark
Cuban. He beat us up a little bit at the
end, but we couldn't be more excited to
work with him and continue to grow new
milk to be a great
success. Next into the tank are
entrepreneurs with a business profiting
from competitive thrill
[Music]
seekers. Greetings sharks. My name is
Brad Scutter and I'm Rob Dickens. We're
from Boston, Massachusetts. Our company
is Rugged Races and we're seeking $1
million for 10% of our
company. So, what is Rugged Races? We
operate a popular 5K obstacle course
race series in 20 cities across the
country called Rugged Maniac. At our
events, participants of all ages, all
genders, all shapes and sizes will
complete a challenging running course
featuring 25 epic obstacles. But these
aren't the pop-up kitty obstacles you'll
see at our competitors events. At Rugged
Maniac, participants will climb over
towers and shipping containers, rocket
down in 100 foot water slides, crawl
through tunnels of mud, and even jump
over fire. All while running through a
combination of forest, fields, ski
slopes, and even motocross tracks. In
short, Rugged Maniac strikes the perfect
balance between fun and physicality with
our award-winning courses and our dayong
festival. So, which one of you sharks is
ready to get rugged with us? And just to
show you what we're all about, we've got
this video clip right
here. Wow.
I didn't even know you existed, but I
know about your competitor. me like
tough mutter. How are you different than
that? We're we're different in this
sense. Basically, tough mutter is a 12
mile course, right? With about 20
obstacles. We have 25 obstacles over 3
miles. So, it's more about the obstacles
and less about the running. And being a
three-mile course, it's much more
accessible to the general public than
something like a 12mi course. Are you
saying this is a tamer version of that?
Something that Barbara would do? Oh, I
could handle the 12 miles. It's this
little short guy over here that wouldn't
have a shot at it. Well, we get people
of all shapes and sizes at our events.
truly from 77y old guys to uh you know
mother daughter teens 14y old and up. Is
it more workout or more party? We think
we strike an excellent balance between
the workout and the party because it's a
shorter race. It takes you know on
average an hour a little bit more to
finish. People are are exhausted but
they're still exhilarated. Do people
bring alcohol? No. Would you sell? No.
Yes, we sell alcohol.
Alcohol outdoor festival. Pump piled
puke. Right. Exactly. It's a It's fun.
It's a fun event. So, what are sales
going to be this year? This year, 4.2
million. How many? 20 cities nationwide.
How much out of the 4.2 did you profit?
Million dollars. But next year, without
investment, we're projecting 6.5 million
in revenue, 2.2 million profits. Talk
about the industry. There's some
monsters out there. You know, what's the
difference? So, basically, you've got
you got two kind of at the top. The
Warrior Dash 5K, Tough Motor 12. And why
have they gotten so much bigger than you
guys? First movers in the market. And
how big are they, Rob? How big are they?
They have like 40 or five events. In
terms of revenue, take a guess. How big
would they be? I think they're about 30
million. So, would you guys say this
industry is about 100 million a year?
Much larger. More than that, Rob, what
what are you going to do with the 1
million? We've uh we've taken that money
and invested it in other brands that we
own. Um what? So, wait a wait. No, no.
What are we going to do with the $1
million that we would get from you?
Sorry. What million were you talking
about, Brian? I thought you wanted to
know what we did with our profits. Well,
we want to know that, too. Great. What
did you do with the 1 million in profit?
Let me show you exactly what we've done
with that other money. Okay, let's see.
Let's see. Here it is.
[Music]
Oh, you guys are doing these things?
It's so
stupid. That's a great idea. Rob,
explain to me what I saw. You saw
Running with the Bulls. Okay. Here in
the US. Anybody get hurt? We had some
minor injuries, couple concussions, a
broken arm. the injury rate.
People paid for this. Oh, yeah. About
the same price as his rugged maniac.
About $50. But is that part of this
deal? Separate company that separate
lawyers. Have you never seen the show?
Greedy pig. I give you a million
dollars. I don't I don't get to wet my
beak on the bull deal. No. Of course we
get. Are you guys kidding? Of course
that's not going to work. Can't be
serious. They're full of I give you a
chance to change your mind. Okay. We
would want more money if you get
involved in the bull. So the bull run is
is a separate entity. All right. Why
don't we entertain it? How much more
would it be to $2 million for 10% of the
bull run? 2 million for the bull and 1
million for the rugged. Yeah. So 3
million bucks gets 10% of both. Brad,
what are the sales in the second
company? 280,000 at the first event. But
do do you realize that your expertise is
not rugged maniac? Your expertise is in
putting on adventure events. The bull
run is just another variant of this same
thing. That's exactly right. And so the
growth potential with this company is
not just within rugged maniac. Guys,
what's the cash flow going to be next
year under your optimistic scenario for
both companies?
We think it could be a $20 million event
this year. Guys, I like the business,
but if I come in and give you money and
all of a sudden it's like, where's Brian
and Rob? Oh, they're chasing the bulls,
right? What am I going to say to you as
an investor when I'm not getting your
full attention? I want a piece of the
bulls. No kidding. No, that's not what
I'm gonna say. I'm gonna say they can
die, right? I want a return on my
investments or I'm suing your ass
because you have a conflict of
interest. No investor says, "Oh, the
existing business is dying. Sell me a
piece of the new one." Well, you don't
do that to investors. You align your
interest with them 100%. When you start
talking about a million dollars, you
don't screw around, right? That's a real
investment. The other the element for
me, I love the idea. I also really love
the fact that you're building a customer
base for the other events that you can
hold later on. For me, they're together.
Here's an offer for you.
Sure. Both businesses
combined. I'll give you 1.5 million for
25%.
Okay. Is that the only offer that we
have?
Mark, you said you were interested. No,
I'm very I I love the one business. If
if I didn't know about this other
business, I'd probably make an offer
right now. Sure. Right. But I want to
hear what you say to Rob. I think I'm
giving you a fair offer. I think the
business is worth what? Six times Ebida,
1.5 times revenue roughly. And I'm
pricing in. I think that's generous. I'm
pricing it in because I see the upside
in the other business. Okay. Asking for
$1 million for this business was already
challenging. having another agenda and
another business on the other side. My
gut feeling is my instinct is that no
matter what, I would be screwed working
with you. I wouldn't trust you. I'm out.
Okay. Thank you for your consideration.
You know, a funny thing happened to me
watching you here today. Uh you came out
here, I thought, "What good-looking
guys, man. They look the part. What a
great video." But then somewhere along
the way, the surprise of the bulls and
oh yeah, we'll wrap that into the deal.
And I don't think maybe you intended it
that way, but for some reason, you lost
my trust.
[Music]
But either way, I'm not sorry to hear
that, but we thank you for your
consideration. Well, guys, you have you
have a you have an offer on the table.
Yes, we do. Uh, what are you going to
do? An offer that's
lower than what we had wanted, but No,
let me make you an offer higher than
what you want. Well, yeah, of course. I
Anyone else want to throw an offer in
the ring? I'm still listening. Well,
Mark, your concern is that you you want
us to focus all our energies on one. No,
no, it's not that. You came in and you
tried to sell us one business and you
separated the two. You're overvaluing
the other business in my opinion. And if
you have such an a high opinion of that
business, that's probably where a lot of
your attention is going to be. And as an
investor, I don't think it's worth the
the value that you're assigned into it
because you've had one event for
$200,000. Mark, are you saying my value
is too high? Yes.
[Music]
Wow. Now Mark's making me nervous about
am I overpaying?
Two sharks are out. Robert has made an
offer, but Mark's concerns may have
caused a change of heart. Mark, are you
saying my value is too high? Yes.
Wow. Now Mark's making me nervous about
am I
overpaying? 1.5 million 25%. That gives
you about a $6 million value for the
combined businesses. The longer we wait,
the the less comfortable I'm starting to
feel. Let me uh cloudy the waters a
little bit here and maybe give you a
Hang on, Robert. You may want to hear
this.
I think your offer should be for 33 a
third. You become a third partner with
these guys and then I go in 50/50 with
you.
Hm. I'm good with that. I like going up
to
1/3. 1.5 million for one/3 of the
combined businesses. I'm with you, Uncle
Kevin. Yeah, I thought you might be
because I think you did overpay. Rob,
isn't it interesting what's happened?
You had an offer at here. Now we're
here. Sure. The longer we stay here,
So, what I would be willing to
do is 1.5 million, but it's for 25% of
the two companies
combined.
Okay, we're going to go discuss this,
consider both offers, and come back.
I think there's a lot of benefit here to
partner with these guys. I'm not sure
what there is to discuss. Mark, you made
a better offer than we did. Yeah, Mark
made the same as your initial. The
challenge is when they come back, do you
drop this dead weight right here and go
back to your initial offer? Then you're
overpaying. I don't think they're going
to take either offer. Oh, I think they
will.
Okay, gentlemen. Let's summarize what's
happened here. You have two distinct
offers. The first to Mr. Cuban is for
1.5 million for 25% of your company,
which by the way was the exact same
offer I made and then he spent half an
hour telling you how bad your business
is. I know. I know. The other offer is
for the same amount of money for 33 and
a third of your business. What are you
going to do?
We went out there and discussed it. We
we'd like to eventually strike a deal
with you.
We wanted to come back in and say,
"Listen, we do 2 million for for the
25%." Instead of doing that, we'd like
to split it in the middle and go 1.75.
[Music]
Deal.
Deal. Going to work, baby. Looking
forward to it, right? Looking forward to
looking forward to it. Absolutely. We'll
make some money. You lose out. But
Robert, why do you do that? Thank you
for your consideration. Thanks, guys.
Thank you. Fired up.
We are very excited. We took that offer
from Mark because we realized that Mark
offers more than just money. Mark offers
his experience. He offers his
connections. You know, only great things
can come from. Well done. 1.75 for 25%.
I'm actually surprised that they came
down from that.
Next into the tank is a business that
aspires to make unmanned flight
accessible for everyone.
[Music]
Hi, I'm JD Clarage. And I'm Charles
Manning. Our company is XCraft. We're
looking to seek $500,000 in exchange for
20% of the company. Much like when the
Wright brothers first took flight in
1903, we are witnessing a new dawn of
aviation, the age of unmanned flight.
The X+1 is a drone redefined. We've
combined both the hovering precision of
a helicopter and the fast flight of an
aircraft. You can soar at speeds of up
to 60 mph and climb as high as 10,000
ft. And you can seamlessly transition
from high speed back to hover. How cool.
Xcraft is breaking boundaries and with
your help, the sky will no longer be the
limit.
JD, how is it different from all the
traditional drones I can buy today? So,
the fundamental difference is the
ability to transition to forward flight
and it does that with a
wing. This is the wing right here. This
this main area is the wing. Okay. So, so
uh it's hovering and then when you want
to go into forward flight, it rotates
like that. Now, it's an airplane. Why do
I care the fact that I can go so much
faster? You can capture a fastoving
subject like a car or, you know, a
motorcycle or something like that. And
what's the range on this? Because if
it's going 60 m an hour, uh, you would
have to probably be in a helicopter to
accompany it, right? Or or you can be
stationary. You can be stationary. Yeah.
I mean, it definitely it's maneuverable,
so you can stay within visual range. But
one key part is that this system
actually can run entirely autonomously.
You can build a flight plan on a C on a
on a software system on a PC and have it
go do those things and come back.
Charles, am I allowed to create a flight
plan for an unmanned drone and just lay
it out there? Yes, that's a good
question, Robert. There there are
regulations and and rules right now and
and primarily uh if you're flying for
recreational purposes, uh you need to
keep it within line of sight, stay away
from other aircraft and airports, uh as
well as personal property, and then you
can't fly any higher than 400 ft. How
much does it cost you to make? Uh, it
cost us $400 to make it. And what do you
sell it for? It retails right now for
$1,800. Have you sold any? Yeah, we've
got uh 173,000 uh right now in
pre-sales. And that's Kickstarter then?
Uh yes, Kickstarter was 143,000 and then
we've done about 30,000 cents on our
website.
Guys, what's your what's your
background? Are you uh engineers or?
Yeah. So, uh, I have worked, I'm an
aerospace engineer by trade. I started
at a school and worked at Oracle and
I've been in software my whole history.
Um, I was looking at some drones
yesterday actually because I have a
property with 36 acres and I want to buy
something cuz I'm getting a designation
of managed forest and one of my
responsibilities is to scan it every
year to look for diseased trees. So, I'm
going to buy a drone. Can I configure
the camera on a gyroscope below it so
that I can film from below? cuz I have
to turn it into airplane mode to use
that camera the way you've got it
configured. We're working on it right
now so that we can actually hover it
inverted and Oh, there's more. Yeah. So,
uh this is called phone drone. A what?
Phone drone. Phone drone. Bingo. So, uh
we can use our smartphones for all
different sorts of things today. That's
great. But never have we been able to uh
allow our smartphones to fly
until now.
I love this stuff. And uh we have a
little video that uh we can show you.
Sure. Would love to see that. Oh my god.
Oh, that is so cool. And do you use the
sensors in the phone to do the balance
and everything? Exactly. We do. So yeah,
uh smartphones today have, you know,
gyros and accelerometers. Uh they've got
GPS. They've got a lot of them have very
decent cameras. So really that's all the
expensive components in a drone. So So
we've leveraged that and basically
turned a smartphone into a drone. How
much does this one cost to make and how
much do you sell it for? This is not
currently for sale. This is in
development. What do you think it will
cost? Uh, we're looking at around a
price point retail of $300. Probably
less than $100 to make. Jade, answer
this for me. Where's the secret sauce in
your company? Like, tell me what
somebody can't knock off. You you know
what it is? It's really about the IP
behind the designs. The IP behind this
design is unique. The IP behind this
design is unique and also patent
pending. What we believe is that there
is completely opportunity around the
designs. We're going to license this
thing. Silly music to my ears. And do
you have the ability or the contacts to
go out and license yourself? Oh, we do.
So then I I'm trying to figure out why
are you here? You're asking for 500,000.
What are you going to use that money
for? Uh 250,000 we would like to use for
scaling production on the X+1 to get our
costs down. So inventory. And then the
other 250,000
uh is to finish development of phone
drum. Okay. Well, look, what value add
you? I've heard enough. I'd like to make
you an offer. I'd like to start things
out here because you I've been looking
at this market quite a bit for the last
month and I think you have some issues
around licensing I could really help you
with, but I think you need more money.
I'm going to give you 750,000 for 25%.
And Kevin, coming into the Cuban zone,
no royalty, no nothing. I was straight
up turned over a new leaf straight. in
his
heart that day. So 750,000 for 25%. Wow,
guys. He increased your value to 3
million bucks. I appreciate that. You
know what I smell? I smell a nasty nasty
shark fight. It's about to happen.
I'll offer you a million dollars for
25%.
I'll I'll raise mine to a million as
well.
I'll give you a million for 20%.
What? Damn. Yeah. So, your value just
doubled. All right, I'll do the same
thing. A million for 20%. Wait, slow
down. Slow down. Hang on. Maybe we
should go step out in the hall. We
should also step out. Before you step
out in the hall, we contemplated this as
an opportunity and it's a fantastic
opportunity. We believe everything is
about team. That's why we are a good
team because talk. So, let me just
unpack this. I want to do a team deal
because I know that there is a big
nasty vulture somewhere here being
quiet. So if you guys want to talk about
what he's going to say, here's my
suggestion. Is there capacity to do a
syndicate where we get each and every
one of you participating in your own
unique ways? Oh, I'm interested in that.
I'm interested. I'm interested in that.
For what value? That's very rare in the
Shark Tank. I need enough equity to make
a difference. Charles, what would you
say that dollar is for you and the
equity?
[Music]
So, so I think a 10 million
valuation. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa.
Guys, how did you go from 2.5 million to
million? I smell greedy people now.
Charles and JD came into the tank with a
$2.5 million valuation for their drone
company XC. But with interest from four
sharks, they've increased the company's
valuation to 10 million. I smell greedy
people now.
You know, I used to tell my daughter
this this uh little story. Why didn't
the baby crab want to share his food?
And the answer is because he was just a
little shelfish. Right. I I can't
counter for everybody here, but I don't
I don't think this is worth more than $6
million. I don't believe. So, he that's
good feedback. He got a ceiling and
that's helpful. I think that ceiling for
me is 5%. I got to have 5% minimum.
That's the smallest position I've got in
anything that I'm working hard on. So,
let me ask you a qualifying question. Is
there any one of you that is not
interested in participating because that
will help address that problem pretty
quickly? I I'm interested. But I see a
lot of oil and gas security, all kinds
of applications for I'm interested. I'm
not interested. Mark, are you
interested? We all get Well, I don't
know. Mark's not saying. He hasn't said.
We'll see.
Um, I think it'd be good. Let's step out
the chat. Okay. All right. Thank you.
Just want you guys to be clear. There's
a lot of privacy issues. This isn't a
slam dunk. It's your call.
I think we should try to get them all at
a 6 million valuation for 25%. If
there's five of us, simple math, we each
have to put up 300,000.
Mark, I don't know. What's your
reservation, Mark? I don't know. I want
to hear what they have to say.
All right, we're excited. We're mostly
excited about doing something together.
Okay. Do you have something to propose
to us? We do. Yes. We would we would
like to
propose $1.5
million each at 5% equity and bring all
the sharks in. You're willing to give up
25% of the company. We each put up
300,000 for
5% 25% total. That gives you a $6
million valuation. I'm okay with this
deal. I'm one shark. I would do that
deal. I'm okay with that deal. I'm okay
with that deal as well. Okay, Robert.
Then I'm in on that deal, too, Mark.
What are you doing? You guys are smart.
Did anybody else offer you money prior
to this? For sure. Okay. Yeah. And so
when someone's come to you, what were
the discussions?
There's really two categories of
conversations. One is strategic and one
is kind of pseudo institutional. A lot
of the institutional guys want to kind
of shape it like a early stage VC
structure. Not something we're as
excited about doing. You all have a lot
more operational execution experience
respectfully than many traditional early
stage VC guys and you also cover a
spectrum. You cover a variety of
different areas which is really useful
to the business cuz that's the whole
model. Charles, I think that's so smart.
I deal with a lot of VC guys like we all
do and I got to tell you they're all
super smart. They're all great theory
but they don't get their hands dirty in
running businesses. That makes a lot of
sense. All right, Mark, are you in?
[Music]
That works. All right.
Really excited.
We should do a special party where we do
a little flight party. Absolutely. We
got a Shark Tank syndicate. Can you
believe it? You guys are going to own
this market. Thank you guys. Thank you.
We're thrilled. All right.
Well done, man.
[Music]
Next up is a modern version of an
important health
[Music]
accessory. Hey Sharks, my name is Justin
Wang. I'm here today to ask for $500,000
for 1% of my company,
Lark. Have you ever noticed that funky
smell coming from your reusable water
bottle? I bet you have. And if you're
like most people, you do what we call
the sniff
test. Wee. The average reusable water
bottle contains more bacteria colony
than your dog bowl or toilet seat. No
wonder they stink. And it's no wonder
it's so tempting to reach for a
singleuse plastic water bottle. The
result, over 1 million of these guys are
consumed every single minute. And that's
no good for your health and even worse
for the
environment. That's why we invented the
Lark Bottle. The Lark Bottle is the
world's first self-cleaning water bottle
that purifies water on the go. With a
simple press of a button and in just 60
seconds, the Lark Bottle activates our
patented UVC LED technology, Pure Abyss,
to eradicate
99.99% of harmful and odor-causing
bacteria, viruses, and mold. The result,
pure water from a pristinely clean
bottle. So, Sharks, who's thirsty for a
great deal? Just want to be clear. I
heard you properly. 500,000 for 1%.
That's correct. Robert, congratulations.
Highest valuation ever requested in the
Shark Tank. You seem like a reasonable
human being. Tell us why it's a By the
way, in all I have a couple of these.
Oh, you do? Great. That is awesome. I
do. But what's the market opportunity
that justifies this? So, it's a huge
market. Big water is a real thing. It's
a $300 billion market worldwide of which
reusable market is only 7%. It is
growing. I tried to swear off of
single-use plastic water bottle several
years ago. I bought several reusable
options and sure enough they ended up in
the back of the cabinet or in my gym
bag. They would collect mold. If it sat
in my car, it would get stinky. So, it's
the self-cleaning part. Self cleaning
and purifies. It looks to me like you
have a UV light in the top. Can you
explain how this works and what it does?
This is actually an optical system
that's designed to reflect the UV light
inside. So simply you press this button,
the UV light turns on. My co-founder is
a PhD in physics from Caltech. He's
engineered this to bounce the optical
light throughout the bottle. So then how
many minutes does it take to do that? We
have two modes. Our normal mode is 60
seconds and then we have adventure mode
which is 3 minutes. So if you want to
take it to a developing country or
camping or you're just somewhere where
you don't quite trust a water. Justin,
is it safer than boiling water? It would
be the equivalent of boiling your water
for like 20 minutes. Really competition.
Are you the only one that has UV
activation and cleaning? We launched in
October of 2018. We're the first one on
market. We have about 10 patents, both
utility and design around this product
and other products, but there are
copycats out there that we're pursuing
potential legal actions for right now.
So, Justin, why is it worth $50 million?
So, we launched this product in 2018.
So, we've been on the market for a
little under two years. Two years, huh?
Under two years. And in our first full
year in 2019, we did a little over $5.5
million in sales. There you go. In the
last 12 months, we've done over $9
million. This year, we're planning on
doing $14 million. What you going to
make on the 14 million? So, we brought
on our first outside venture capital
round earlier this year in January, and
we leaned into growing the business. So
this year we're expecting to lose about
a million dollars. Justin, how much did
you raise? 6.7. At what valuation? At a
$31.7 million valuation. So Justin,
let's talk real business. You've only
raised 6.7. How much do you have in the
bank? Uh, I have about 6.5.
Okay. So you really haven't had to spend
anything. Good for you, right? Yeah.
What do these retail for? The one you
have right there is 95. I paid 95 for
this. Yeah. See, even Holy crap. It's
actually not bad. It cost you what to
make it. The land. ended cost is around
40. You said you had a lot of patents.
What are those other products you
already have? Well, some of those
patents just cover some other
applications, but some of them do apply
to the new product. Uh, this is the lark
pitcher, which is our first foray into
the home. Let me do that real quick. And
while that's going, I'll show you a
video of how that works. Traditional
water pitchers use a filter. And the
biggest problem is that they only trap
contaminants where they could quickly
accumulate and multiply and actually
reverse contaminate your water. Why do
they reverse contaminate? Because the
contaminants are being trapped and
collected there and as germs are growing
there. It's a wet porous environment
that's dark. So imagine all the things
that could be growing there. So we take
a two-step approach. The first step you
see it go through and it captures things
like lead, cadmium, mercury. In the
second step, you simply press this
button and it'll purify the water that's
gone through. And as you can see, that
is a clear water that we poured blue
water in. That's contaminated. Clear
water. But is anybody else doing this?
No one's doing this. There's a million
people on planet don't have access to
clean water and 1.5 million don't have
access to electricity. So I don't think
any of those people are getting this
bottle right now because they don't have
$95. 1% of all of our proceeds go to our
charity partner, 1% for the planet,
charity water, wellare where we build
wells in Africa. 1% of profits. 1% of
revenue we pledge of revenue. Oh, gross
revenue. Gross revenue. 1% that that is
that is impressive off top line. I mean,
you're committed. I get it. That that is
important. Damon was going to stick a
skewer through you. No, I I might still,
but I want to just lay it out where I
am. Okay. I think we're at a time where
people are really angry. They're they're
looking for hope. Mhm. And when I signed
up to this platform, the platform didn't
start off as the wealthy helping the
wealthy with 6.5 million in the bank. I
I just could not do this cuz I just
think that I'm here for a different
reason. I think this is crazy. I'll let
the other sharks discuss it, but I'm I'm
out. I also come from a background where
I didn't have a lot. It's unfortunate
you won't take that journey with me, but
I respect what you're saying. So, let me
take a shot at it. I support a charity
called One Drop. making sure everybody
can drink fresh water around the world.
It's something I can get behind. Love to
be involved in this, but I'm not doing
it for 1%. I bring too much value. I've
never done a deal for 1% for obvious
reasons. I'll do it for 4%. I don't care
how you structure it, advisory shares,
whatever. So, you want him to do it at
almost onethird of his I understand. I
didn't say you would like it, Mark, or
you would. I'm just telling you what I
would do. Is there other offers out
there where, you know, to give you half
a million dollars for 1%? I I feel like
I'm not making anything. The category
that we're in is gigantic. It's a $300
billion industry and it's so ripe for
disruption and so ripe for innovation. I
think I'm willing to take offers and
listen to it offer, Lori.
I would love to work with you. I would
love it. 500,000 for 5%.
You keep on going backwards, Justin.
Justin, the problem with 1% is you're
priced for perfection. And yes, I would
love to own 1% of Apple and I would love
to own 1% of Tesla, but the odds are
just so low. To make it easier for your
investors, I'll do 500,000 for 3%. We
can work out the other 2% for from your
advisory pool. That's my offer. And
Mark, are you anywhere? Yeah, I know
where I'm at. Um, so look, there's
different platforms for different
reasons, right? This is a place where
people come where they just need a
little bit more fuel. They need a little
bit of help. We're not here to evaluate
companies that may be billion dollars in
sales over a trillion dollar market in
20 years, which is possible, but this is
not the place to do it. So, for those
reasons, I'm not. So, you have three
offers. What do you want to do? You
know, the the offers are all great, but
even without the advisory shares below
my last valuation of 32ish, right? To be
honest with you, that's really my bottom
line. What about we got you all in for
half million each for $1.5 million total
at 4.5%. And then I will also throw an
advisory share of 1% split between the
three of you. So for a total it would be
5.5% for that money. 2%. Yeah.
Okay, here's something we'll do. Would
you consider a million and a half or 6%
and each shark gets
two? If you get three sharks, huge value
for you.
Two sharks are out and Justin has one
offer on the table from Kevin, Lorie,
and Robert for his water purification
company, Lark. Huge value for you. 1.5
million, 500,000 each for 6%. Let's say
you uh I could accept the offer with one
condition that the structured in a way
that $1.5 million for $4.5% and the
remaining 1.5% would be advisory shares
to be divided among you. My question is
do I get 2% for my $500,000? You do. How
long is the vesting period for the
advisory shares? 24 months based on
what? Forget the best. What are you
basing? What do I have to do to get my
advisory shares? I I think we just have
a conversation about what we could do
with the business, how we could build it
together. Maybe it's QVC. Maybe it's
make it very simple. It's too
complicated. You know what? I'm out
because I've worked really hard to get
to this point. I don't need you to
interview me.
I I don't want contingencies on it. You
know that we're going to be involved. We
don't want to see that just evaporate.
Absolutely. Absolutely. I'm in for 2%
for 500,000. I'll do a million dollars
for 4% split between you and Lori. I'm
in. No advisory. It's just straight.
Advisory would just no contingencies. So
half a million dollars each for 1.5%
plus half a percent in advisory shares.
2% total. I don't want advisory shares.
I I like Can you do that? Look, I want
her part of the deal for sure. I see
lots of value here. Whatever it takes to
get her on board, I want the same. So,
are you putting a stake in the sand here
on the Yeah, I would go 2%. Okay. Well,
that's what you got to do, but not
advisory shares. Um, what if those
shares are invested up front because I
have to structure something where I'm
not going below my last valuation.
There's 2% up front. Done. Done. All
right.
Let's light up the world.
[Music]
Next into the tank is an entrepreneur
who believes there's big money to be
made from big scares.
[Music]
Everywhere I go, there's zombies. Hi,
sharks. I'm Melissa Carbone from Los
Angeles. My company is 1031 Productions,
and I'm seeking $2 million in exchange
for 10% of my company.
Wow. 1031 Productions is an
entertainment company that creates,
owns, and produces live attractions in
the horror space. Our most popular
attraction is the Los Angeles haunted
hay ride. And it is not for the faint of
heart. Sharks, when you take our
hayride, you are entering the pitch
black woods where demonic forces, lost
souls, psychopathic fun are waiting
around every turn.
[Music]
He bites.
And just when you think the terror is
over, think again. Oh god.
Oh, he likes you. Don't eyeball me. I
will kick your tush back to Texas. Mark,
get him. Okay, Melissa, you know what's
really scaring the crap out of me is
your valuation. So $2 million for 10%
imputes a $20 million value on this
scary hairride business. Tell us why
you're worth $20 million. We do
attractions all year long. We have the
Los Angeles Haunted Hayride, which is
our seasonal attraction here in LA. 17
nights. We sell out every single night.
We do about 1.8 million dollars right
now per October.
Wow.
1.8 was really good in 17 days. 17 days.
We have another attraction called the
Great Horror Camp Out that we just
launched, which is a summer attraction.
The Great Horror Camp Out is our way of
not being a seasonal company. It is an
overnight completely immersive camping
experience, horror themed. Oh, no. So,
it's 12 hours. We b we take 2,000
campers, we put them in tents, and we
have an incredibly interactive
experience that includes everything from
a hell that's basically summer camp from
hell. Yeah. 1.8 20 million in at the end
of the 17 days what's left. It cost us
$1.2 million to produce the Los Angeles
haunted hayride. So So I'm left with
600,000 free cash afterwards. Yeah. I
mean it varies year to year because
right now we're in a launching new
attractions mode. We're launching a New
York haunted hayride which is what we're
seeking some of this money for. The
great hor camp out. We're launching it
next year in 10 cities up the west
coast. And therein lies the rub, right?
Because they're very very very expensive
to to produce and create. Right. Well,
camp the camp outs are cheap to produce.
How much advertising and promotion do
you do? We spent about
$300,000. We do a ton of radio. My
background is I I ran Clear Channel Los
Angeles for 10 years. So, my um
advertising marketing and one of and my
other business partner is actually still
with Clear Channel. So, we know how to
make a dollar go really far from a
market. How many unique individuals come
through the hayride? We have we have
50,000 people. We sell out every single
night. So, this year is our first year.
where we increased our max capacity to
100,800. We actually are doubling our
max capacity this year. You sell out
every night for 17 days. Every night.
That's amazing. So, can I extrapolate
and say that the it's going to be 3.6
million in revenue this year? Yes. If we
sell out. So, that means this thing will
generate just over a million bucks if
everything works, right? Mhm. Okay. Now,
you're an intelligent woman. I'm trying
to make the leap now. We have to get
back to reality on your $20 million ask.
Yeah. Let's give you a fair chance of
making a million bucks before tax. Okay.
Yep. That's about 700,000 after tax. If
I gave you a 10 multiple, you're worth 7
million bucks. How is it that I am going
to pay 20 for a $7 million business if
everything goes right? Mhm. That's the
horror story you've brought here. You've
overvalued your business.
We've had major entertainment companies
in LA who have already given us offers
to buy our company and this is about
what they're valuing it. Why are you
such a greedy pig?
I not greedy. I have lots of lots of
high hopes for the company and I want to
grow fast. Just because a Hollywood bozo
offered you a $20 million valuation. You
know what the horror show is? Listen to
you argue about valuation all the time.
Well, then why don't you just give her
$2 million for 10%. I am projecting for
the New York Haunted Herid, which hasn't
happened yet cuz it's the same model in
LA. We're just plopping it there. Let
go. Let her go. Let her go. But
geographically, it's a different model
because it never rains in LA. Melissa, I
I I don't agree that your risk analysis
is correct. It never happens that
everything you roll out successful day
one. That's ridiculous.
For me, it is not hard to get lots of
people to come to the attractions. The
hard part is to make it a great
experience so they want to come back.
Look, this is all fun and games, but
we're talking about money here. I can't
I can't get there. I'm out.
Melissa, for you to come close to your
projections for next year, everything
has to work perfectly all the time. I
don't see you getting to those numbers
next year. I'm out
for me right now. how to give you $2
million. I feel it would take a really
long time for me to see that back. So,
for that reason, I'm
out. The risk is not as great as you
probably would think. I mean, we will
launch these attractions no matter what.
I know that we can launch them faster by
having this money. We can launch them
now. I'm an expert in high octane scare.
You are? Yes. I can tell you a way to do
this much cheaper. Wear a piece of
jewelry and walk around where I grew up.
Yeah. That will give you a high octane.
Fair enough. Uh I would just have to
insult you with my offer. Um go ahead,
insult her. That's about what it's
worth. Throw the offer. Yeah. Okay.
Well, then I'll give you $2 million for
40%.
[Music]
Okay, Mark. Come on, Mark. Is that a yes
or a no to him? Um, can I counter? Of
course you can counter.
Um, 2 million for 20%.
I'll take that offer. Done.
Really?
Yep.
Awesome. Good. We have a deal. All
right. We have a deal. Wow. Easy breezy.
I love it. Thank you. Oh, I'm so up for
Holy crap. You owe me 5% for helping you
on that. Totally. You can have free
tickets to LA haunted hay ride. Thank
you so much. Good luck. I don't know
what just happened. Wait a minute. I
lost out on a deal. Come to think of it.
Yeah, you just did.
I think that the next generation of
entertainment is experiential
entertainment where people get out of
the house and go and get a unique
experience. I thought for me to get my
money back if I did that deal for 2 mill
I'd have to rise from the dead and look
like that before I get You already have
Kevin. Are we excited? Are we excited?
Mark on board and $2 million. This is
the biggest deal ever. I'm so excited.
This changes the game for us. Wow.
Next into the tank is a modern version
of a traditional machine.
[Music]
Hey Sharks, I'm Brian Shimmerlick and
I'm Steve Bofield. We're from New York
City and our company is Veno. We are
seeking $2 million for 12% of our
company.
When you hear vending machine, what
comes to mind? Most people imagine
desperately shaking this old machine
trying to get that bag of potato chips
to drop out. These machines are huge.
They're old. They're ugly. And so they
get hidden in the basement. Veno is
taking vending out of the basement into
the spotlight with the latest
technology. So what's so different about
Veno? Everything. Let's start with size
and appearance. Our slim form factor and
attractive design is the ticket to
exclusive hight traffic areas. Veno
hangs on the wall like a picture frame
and requires zero floor space. Let me
show you how it works. What Veno does is
we bring video content to the point of
purchase. So Brian will go ahead and
browse the products. Looks like the
bottle breacher has caught his eye. He
adds it to the cart, clicks checkout.
Wait a minute, Brian. I don't see any
slots for coins. Veno is totally
cashless, totally digital, and very,
very fast. Once the payment is made, our
team at Veno back in New York is
automatically notified of the sale. And
that's just scratching the surface of
everything we can do with the valuable
data from each and every vending machine
out in the
field. It's that easy. Who's ready to
veno?
So, it's small in size. Yes. Does that
mean that anything that you sell out of
it has to be small in size? Absolutely.
This is about the largest item that we
can fit, but we can actually fit a 100
products. How do we fit so much and so
little is we have an amazing team of
aerospace engineers. Is he an aerospace
engineer? Yes, that's my background. I
was an aerospace engineer for about 9
years. What happened to you? And now
you're making vending machines. Now I'm
making vending machines. I saw the
opportunity. I quit my aerospace job and
I jumped to the See what happened with
the space program. We're not a vending
operator and we're not replacing vending
machines, but we are a software and
media company that manages this digital
network from the cloud. So, here's our
business model. We sell the hardware to
vending companies. So, let's go from
there. So, let's go from there guys. So,
let's go from there. What is one of
those cost for me to buy if I'm a
vending machine guy? What does it cost
you to make? Yeah, you're not going to
love this. So, bear with me. We build it
for 2500. We sell it for 2500.
Okay. So, you charge a monthly then. So,
what do you charge on the monthly then?
We charge you $20 per Veno per month.
And what do I get for that $20? You get
the front-end software that controls the
hardware. Do I Does that include
maintenance in case it breaks? Exactly.
So, then do do the different companies
that you sell this to select and choose
what's going to go in the machine? We
control the media rights and we control
a significant amount of the product mix.
And so you can get some of your products
in as the owner of the hardware, but
we're also managing this network
remotely working with really great
products to get them into the venos
across the whole network. What are your
total sales for this year? We're going
to generate a million dollars. Wow. We
just partnered with the largest vending
machine company in the country. But
Brian, you make money from the front of
the screen. You're an ad company.
Absolutely. Plain and simple, right? Let
me tell you what you guys what we're
doing here. We are changing the game on
retail and marketing physical products.
That's a stretch. Traffic into stores is
down 50% over the last 3 years. The
impulse purchase at the checkout at the
grocery store is down significantly.
Brian, so I'm an advertiser. I want to
advertise on the front of the screen.
How do you charge me? So, we charging
brands
$200 per skew per machine per month.
What that gets them is that's a lot. We
actually purchase the product wholesale.
We sell it retail. We make sure our
vending partners can make an attractive
margin and the product is a guys. Look,
I get it. This is a digital end. This is
a digital end cap, right? Which is
great. But here here's my issue. I
invested in a company called Oasis. Five
women out of Boston. They go into
women's restrooms. All the products are
women's. Now, we've designed our own
box. I see them as competitive. So, for
those reasons, I'm out. Understood. Why
don't you talk about this $16 million
valuation you put in front of the Sharks
here? 2 million for 12.5%. I'm going to
make the assumption that's not supported
by cash flow because you don't have any.
So, it must be some other reason you
think you're so valuable. It must be
that you have have you raised the money
or or we raised $3.4 $4 million from
some of the best investors out there.
The best investors in America right
here. Exactly. That's why we're here.
And we always get great pricing. I make
sure of that. I know you do. Just
explain to me how it's worth 16 million
today. You might do a million in sales
this year. Will you make any money on
that million? No, we will not. We will
lose about 300,000. Uh and then next
year we will break even. And so why is
it worth that much? We've got an amazing
team and we've spent three years
building out this platform. I've
partnered, let's not forget, I've
partnered with the largest vending
company in the country and we've
partnered with the nation's largest
chocolate manufacturer as well as
several other big brands. It's very
smart to have point of purchase video if
you can have it in something. But on
here, do they have to be relative to
what's inside the machine or are you
selling advertising space to anything?
We're focused on the differentiator. The
differentiator is coupling retail point
of purchase with media, extracting tons
of data about how consumers behave.
Guys, the valuation is
insane. I'm out.
Thank
you. I I don't like
it. What I find confusing about it is
you're in the advertising business and
there's a lot of competition for point
of sale advertising, but you're also
selling product, but you're only selling
products that are in the machine. And
one day, maybe if you get big, you'll do
advertising for other things, too. So,
is it a display advertising company or
is it a pseudo vending? This business
model is just too complicated and
unfocused for me. I'm out.
Guys, can I ask if your balance sheet
has any debt on it? We have absolutely
no debt. How would you like some?
Three sharks are out, but Kevin may be
interested in Brian and Steven's
high-tech vending machine, Veno. Guys,
can I ask you if your balance sheet has
any debt on it? We have absolutely no
debt. How would you like some? I'm open
to it. I'm open to hearing what you got.
What about I lend you? This goes into my
venture debt fund. and I give you $2
million and I'll take 6% of the company
in equity, which is half of what you
asked. So 2 million in debt. Yeah. And
I'll loan the company a 36-month loan, 3
years. That's enough proof of concept
here. 2 million. And I want 6% of the
equity for providing the facility.
That's why they call it Mr. Wonderful.
And there's no interest payments on the
debt. And there's no strings attached.
Are you kidding? It's a fund. It has to
make at least 7% is my lowest rate.
Horrible. Here's Mr. advice with no
checkbook. Isn't that wonderful? No
one's written more checks or bigger
checks on this show than I have. And I'm
telling you, well, you already know it's
horrible. I have a venture debt fund.
This is what I do all day long with tech
companies. So, Mr. Wonderful, how did
you calculate 6% on the equity side? I
just asked for it.
It's just what he wants. I just want to
wet my beak in the equity and I deserve
to. That's a big old beak. I love my
beak.
I look at this and it's a little
confusing for me. If you're going up on
a wall, right, you're taking up that
space. So, the space below it now is
empty. I don't see why you wouldn't
lengthen that. It's a little odd to me
at the moment. Like, I I personally feel
it needs some work. Lori, is it possible
given that we're asking for a
significant amount of money, is it
possible that you guys would consider
coming in together? Have you guys ever
partnered up before? I think I'll bring
you in on that deal, Lori. I mean,
you've raised a lot of money. You're
asking for a lot of money. With 3.4
million, we've built a network of 150
machines soon to go to 250. We've
partnered with the largest vending
company in the country. The vending
market is a large, slowmoving industry.
It's 7 billion. So, there's a lot of
opportunity here to create retail. So,
if I go in with Kevin at the deal that
he offered you and I'd be happy to do a
debt deal with you, but the the 6% is is
Where's your counter? My counter offer
would be 2 million at a 7% interest rate
for 1% equity. Oh, it's not 1%. I don't
get out of bed for that. But also too,
we work really hard for our money. It's
huge to get hard for our money, too.
It's huge to get two sharks. You're
asking for a lot of money, though, guys.
1% is a no. Yeah, that doesn't work.
Ryan, another counter.
That's my last counter. 1% of equity.
That's all you're willing to give up.
I'd love to make a deal with you guys,
but it's got to be in the rain. Hang on.
He's about to make another counter. I'll
do the deal. $2 million, 7%, 36 months,
3% equity. You got to pay something for
two sharks. Well, hang on. Is Lori in on
that?
4%. Four. You do it. Two each. four.
Okay, here's the deal. We'll give you
the $2 million. I've spoken to my
partner Lori. You get two sharks. It's a
7% interest loan for three years, which
is enough to prove your concept. And we
want when we close the deal with you, 4%
equity, 2% each. It's a done deal, my
friend, if you say yes.
So, we we know the venture debt market
and what's market is a little bit
higher. The difference venture debt from
any firm is one thing. venture debt from
Mr. Wonderful and Lori, Queen of QVC.
Yeah, that has huge value to you. You
become the IT kids. You're a Shark Tank
deal. You've got two sophisticated
investors from Shark Tank who care about
you and you come into the Shark Tank
ecosphere. All of a sudden, you're on TV
every day. Good pitch.
So, I'm going to provide one more
counter and this would be our best
offer. We can't give up 4% equity.
What's your counter, Brian? It would be
2 and 12% of the equity and we'll pay
you back and we'll work to set the terms
that you guys are comfortable with.
Three and a half%.
Three and a half%. We're doing at 3 and
1/2.
Ooh.
3 and 1/2% is really too much for us. 2
1/2% is final offer. And we'd love to
have you guys.
We're going to make money back.
Okay, look. Last offer and you should
take this. You'd be foolish not to.
We'll do it for 3%.
You got a deal.
Wow. I didn't think that would happen.
Thank you guys. Very interesting.
Excited about this. Thank you. No
problem. Next project. Thank you so
much. Thank you. Thank you.
We're really excited to have two sharks.
Kevin's going to bring us his financial
wizardry. Lori's got her portfolio of
products. We've built a big business
over the last three years, but we're
really just scratching the surface of
what we want to achieve. And so, we're
ready to go to the next level.
[Music]
Next up is an entrepreneur who believes
he has a better solution to drinking
wine on the go.
[Music]
Hi Sharks. My name is Andrew McMurray
and I'm here from Scarsville, New York.
Our company is Zips Incorporated. I'm
here today seeking a $2.5 million
investment for a 10% equity stake in our
company. I'm here to tell you that our
single serve is like no other in the
wine industry. our company. It's all
about packaging, packaging, packaging,
and licensing, licensing, licensing. And
Kevin, I think that should be music to
your ears. You are our wise grasshopper.
So, the single serves that are out in
the market today, what you might be most
used to that you've seen on airplanes,
the little airplane bottles, little
plastic cups. We've got a wine glass.
It's got weight and it's got strength.
This glass is actually so strong that I
can stand on it.
Oh my god. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow is right.
To open this glass of wine, you're
simply going to unzip the outer clean
wrap. This recyclable outer wrap acts as
a UV protectant to the wine, which in
single serve wine, shelf life is king.
Now, to open the wine, you're simply
going to unscrew the lid.
Attach it to the bottom. Very clever.
Now, that's great. To open the wine,
you're simply going to lift and peel.
One of the best parts about this now lid
comes back
off screws back on. This glass falls
over. You're not spilling any wine out
of it. So, let me quickly give you guys
each a glass so you can hold it. In our
opinion, our package is going to become
to the wine industry what the aluminum
can became to the soda industry.
Cheers. Cheers.
So for viewers out there and you Lori
who weren't around when this happened,
Copa Deina was another single serve wine
deal that came in the tank twice. Both
time got offers and he never accepted
either of them. Andrew, why is it
different than Copa Deino? It's
different in that we own the patents and
Copa Deino assured us they have patent
on sealing a glass of wine this way. So
how have you not breached that patent?
Actually, the company that owns the
rights to that glass and to that
technology is a company based out of
France. In speaking with the owner of
the company, he told us that the
previous entrepreneur essentially he's a
like a franchisee. So, he had the rights
to use his technology for his glass. So,
what is the difference between your two
patents? The shelf life. That's you know
what it boils down to. Our glass lasts
for well over a year shelf life. We're
in shelf life testing right now with
three of the top 10 global brands in the
in the world today. One I can tell you
about which is Yellowtale. They do up
close to 10 million cases a year in the
US market. So what I'm trying to clarify
with certainty because been down this
road long time ago and by the way you're
doing better than the other guy cuz he
was sweating like a pig by this point.
The point is you're telling me after
having visited the owner of the patent
that there is no breach. They have
agreed that you do not infringe on their
patent. That is 100% correct. Is your
patent unique not only to the form
factor but also to coat the glass with
that plastic? Correct. The mix of the
plastic that's in here is proprietary to
us. That's with the exterior package.
The exterior that's also a part of the
patent is the UV wrap, the shrink wrap
on the outside. So those two things
Okay. Okay. Let's put the patent aside
for a moment. You you have no desire to
make your own wine. You want to license
this packaging to other big wine
manufacturers and let them sell it? The
answer would be no and yes and yes and
no. So we actually have our Zips brand.
That's what's in front of you right now.
That is our brand. Is it in Costco? Is
not in Costco yet. And that's a big
piece of why I'm why I'm here talking to
you today. What are your sales? Okay.
The project started about 16 months ago.
We were working with Fatser Winery. The
deal with them was to get into six major
league baseball parks for opening day of
2013 and we did $130,000 with them in
licensing fees. They took your
technology and put their wine into it
and sent it over to the arenas. Correct.
We got the license. Correct. What was
the percentage on that license? It's 15
cents a glass. How much money is totally
invested in this venture right now? $8.5
million. Oh, wow. And where did that
money come from? We got about 25
investors total. We've got six retired
Goldman Sachs partners, three of which
own a professional sporting franchise.
And the rest of this group, these are
all Wall Street professionals. But the
question becomes, if you have all those
team owners, then why are you asking us
for the money? I want all five of you
guys at the table with me. What's the
sell through? Or what's your total
sales? The Zips brand that you're
holding in your glass right now. We're
currently done about $650,000 in sales.
What does it cost at retail? A glass of
Zips. $2.99. Look, per glass. Very few
people will buy a glass of wine for
three bucks. We're already in,200
stores. We just got Walmart this week.
What's it cost you to make? It cost me
95.
Look, in America, 97% of wine is sold
for under
$9.95 a bottle. So, where this packaging
idea has so much merit in terms of its
delivery, it fails on its pricing. When
the average consumer says to himself, I
can get five and a half glasses for
$9.99 and I have to pay $3.99 for one.
That's the problem. Yeah, but this is,
you know, but the you can't dismiss like
650,000 in sales, my friend. That's
nothing in the wine business.
I mean, everyone we've spoken to is
comfortable at the
299 point. They haven't tested the
market. They haven't sold it through.
650,000 and 1,200 stores is poo poo poo
poo. Peep poo poo. Let's not get hung up
on though. We're now I'm hung up. I know
it's getting delisted. It's not going to
work. We're talking about my brand.
Look, I'm not a wine connoisseur. But
even
then, I would take MD 2020 from a
quality perspective over a brand with a
zipper named Zips. Huge mistake. I'm
out.
Let me tell you a very brief story that
I think will be sobering for you. I went
to see Costco and talked to them about
wine. They're the largest buyer of wine
on earth. 5.2 billion in wine. I said,
"I'm going into the wine business." They
said, "Who cares? There's 5,000
applications a year to put wine from all
around the world into Costco. Go prove
that means something in the wine
business." Took me 2 years to do it. I
go back to Costco and she says,
"Impressive. But now you have to deal
with a new price point. We talked about
single serve. We talked about 750ml
bottles. We talked about my brand. Did
you get your wine into Costco? I'm
negotiating it right now. It's not in
yet. That's a good question. That would
be a no. Okay. What is your loss going
to be this year? We I don't want to look
at it as a loss. I want to look it as a
reinvestment back. Why not simply
license to the big manufacturers, to the
big wineries, and let them take all of
that? You're putting up enormous amounts
of capital. That's not the purpose of a
licensing deal. Why do any of it? Well,
I mean, hindsight is always 2020. That's
the answer. Now, is it Now he's too far
in. He's got no choice. Okay. So, at the
price of 299 that you want to sell it
at, if you don't get the sell through up
to call it 10 million units in the next
2 years, you're screwed. You've run out
of runway. So, the real issue is getting
back to how we started our conversation
today. When we know everybody in
America, which is
97% buy wine at
under9.99, that's 97% of the market.
And and where's that fact from? I
Everything I'm telling you is a fact.
You're going to go find this out on your
own. My gut feeling is I would not feel
comfortable investing this amount of
money with this amount of risk. I'm out.
But to obviously I respect that and I
appreciate it. But you know to open a
category that's never been done before
isn't easy. It's been done before. The
guy's been standing there twice. He was
here twice to clear the air in that
sense. I mean we're not a copycat. I've
been doing the single serve wine since
2008. I think brilliant design. I love
it from my perspective. I think that
there's a great use for it in certain
applications. But all the rest of this
is so complicated. You have so many
partners. so much money that for that
reason I can't see my way through this
and so I'm out.
You know when Copa Deina was here I
really like the product then I like the
better product cuz I think you have a
better product but my issue is exactly
the same as it was. I don't care that
you've raised 8.5 million for me it is
very very fundamental. It's a licensing
deal. I don't understand why we're
having this discussion. Kevin's going to
beat the crap out of you because you
can't get below a certain price point.
But you can't get below a certain price
point because you've taken on all the
risk. If you were simply licensing it,
that would be somebody else's problem. I
don't like the path that you're going
down. I'm
out. All right. Look, Costco is the
number one buyer and reseller of wine on
Earth. Period. Everything about selling
wine in America is known by their buying
team. Which brands, which varietals,
what price point, what packaging,
everything. They know
everything.
Everything. They don't like this price.
If I team up with you, I can get this
into Costco, but not at that price. You
want to do $12 million opening order
from California alone, it's $149. You
want to do a $19 million a year business
with Costco, it's $149. I can make it
happen. I can get you in Costco.
Four sharks are out. Kevin is Andrew's
last chance for a deal for his single
serve wine company, Zips. So, how do you
get the price down so that we can sell
to Costco for
$16? How do we do that? You've got to
get the the packaging down. And like
anything, when it goes to scale, we feel
we can keep driving it down. All right,
I'll make you an offer. Here's the only
way I'm doing your deal. I'm not
interested in going down the path you're
going down trying to prove out a 299
product cuz I know it's not going to
work. I'm two years ahead of you. Okay.
I want to go launch it in Costco. Do you
understand the value of the offer of
getting into Costco? Absolutely. Okay.
So, what are you going to do? I'll give
you $2.5 million for 10%. But I want the
option to buy another $2.5 million worth
of equity at exactly a $25 million
valuation in the event of an exit.
[Music]
Which means if you sell the company for
50 million, I still get to buy it at 25.
You get
it? I've got to have some upside for
making your company so valuable that you
can sell it. And of course, all of this
only happens if we get into Costco, so
you have nothing to worry about. Do you
understand it? Yes, I do. I'd like to
have an opportunity to make a quick
phone call to check with the investors.
All right.
These wine guys drive me crazy. I think
they're nuts not to do your deal. It's
just a potential deal with Kevin. Kevin
only. Kevin only for Okay. for for a 10%
equity stake in the company. And here's
here's the twist and the kicker. So,
obviously, we need to discuss this. Do
you see this as your way of you getting
into Costco? Yeah. But, this is the best
offer Kevin's ever made to somebody.
Okay. So, in speaking to the partners,
they were intrigued. It wasn't the angle
they thought that you would be coming in
at. I deserve to buy stock at a $25
million valuation, Andrew, cuz I brought
Costco to the table. Because we got into
Costco, all of a sudden, you're way more
valuable. Your partners know that you
should do this deal. You have no risk.
Just say
yes. Trust me,
Andrew. It's actually a very good deal.
Andrew, are you going to take my deal or
not? Don't be a fool.
I'm on board. I'm here. All right.
Cheer. Yay.
Grab me a very expensive plastic glass
and toast me. Cheers. Thank you guys.
Oh, ho ho.
Hello, Sharks. My name is Ethan Tucker
and I'm from the beautiful Green
Mountains of Brattleboroough, Vermont.
And I'm Pat Boon, aging singer and like
you, a lifelong entrepreneur. Our
company is Zero Pollution Motors and we
are seeking $5 million in exchange for
50% of our company. Our goal is to give
to America the leanest, cleanest,
greenest form of auto transportation
ever to hit our crowded, polluted
cities. So, Sharks, it is my great
pleasure to introduce to you the air
car. The what? The car that runs on air.
Wow. That's right. Air, but highly
compressed air.
There it is. Air, of course, is the
least expensive, most readily available,
and the most environmentally perfect
fuel there will ever be. And the AirPod
uses compressed air to drive the pistons
in the engine. It is far superior to the
electric car because of its price. And
it eliminates the need for batteries,
which are expensive and inefficient.
Look at that thing go. Now, this is a
picture we took, which is not totally
life-size. This is just the first
prototype. And so, how many want to join
us for a dazzling ride into the future?
Look, Pat, I know you've sold over 40
million records. They say I didn't get
paid that many, but yes. What was your
biggest hit? I'm just curious. Love
Letters in the Sand.
You know, I love cars. I do. I race
cars. What made you think I wouldn't
want to get in it and try it? Well, why
isn't it here? I know. We would like you
to be in it. And there's several
reasons. One is that a car to come into
the United States has to meet safety
standards. It has in Europe already. Oh,
so this is already a production car. It
is moving into production. That's You
bought the license to it or you want to
buy the license? We have the right to
build the first plant in the United
States. So, Ethan, where explain how
it's powered? Is this compressed air? It
is compressed air. It is not a
combustion principle. It is a propulsion
principle. Now, a crude way to
illustrate would be blow up a
balloon, it takes off. Pat, how how fast
does a lunchbox on wheels
go? It will go about 50 mph tops. Is it
self-perpetuating? In other words, is
there a certain amount of compressed air
within the vehicle to last a certain
amount of time? You plug in the AirPod
to any outlet. Okay. And takes 4 hours
to charge. The motor charges it itself.
It compresses the air. How long does it
last? You have 100 miles range. I'm a
consumer. I'm coming to a store to buy
an air car or a battery car. Tell me why
I'm going to buy the air car. There's
one big difference other than the price.
Tell me. I'll tell you. The difference
is if there's a compressor at a gas
station, just like you fill up your
tires, you can fill up your car in 4
minutes. 10,000.
10,000 for the car cost $10,000. The car
cost 10,000. That's it. That's it.
Something's wrong here. No, because it's
very simply made. The inventor, you may
know the name Ghee Negra. Yeah.
Titanium. Isn't he the guy who developed
the titanium piston? Titanium for the
lighter motor. He's got 150 patents. He
knows. He's a real car guy. He loves
cars, right? What will it cost for you
to bring a car here? Manufacture it
here. I thought we're going to
manufacture in Hawaii. Yeah, we're going
to manufacture states. The 5 million is
for a plant to build regional plant to
build the cars. Why Hawaii? Hawaii is a
sort of enclosed community where they
have pollution problems. They have high
cost of gas and and it's more of a
controlled place. Part of the concept of
the company is not a big Detroit type
plant. It is regional plants, small
plants building cars for that area.
Okay. Pat, can you share what it's made
out of? Fiberglass, polyurethane, and
resin. You can jump on a door and it
won't bend like a regular car. But what
about um in a crash test? So, we can't
pass a crash test until we've crashed a
car. And we don't want to crash a
prototype.
We only have three prototypes. So, we
would be crashing testing some a car
that was built from scratch. $5 million
to build your factory in Hawaii. Then
you have to market it, right? And you
not only do you have to let people know
it exists, you have to convince them
that they can trust it. Yeah. That's
exactly why we're in Hawaii because we
want to do it slowly. Okay. So, your
license is not for all the United States
on an exclusive bas. The company's
called MDI and they've just made a deal
with Tata Motors for India, a $30
million deal. So, they wrapped up India
and the MDI company has all of France.
So, they're only issuing a couple plants
per territory, areas, regions. Yeah.
Just so we can be crystal clear on the
opportunity. Yeah. I'm assuming that I
become a 50% partner in a plant in
Hawaii and that I own that entire
territory. Every car sold on every
island in Hawaii is coming from that
plant. Is that true? Yes. No. But if
somebody builds a plant in San Francisco
and ships a car into my territory,
cannot happen. Cannot. Guys, guys, I'm
going to simplify things here, right?
The smart thing as an investor is to
just watch what happens with Tata Motors
in India. See how it sells. Look at
their experience. And then if it goes
good, watch somebody else open up a
plan. You're too late. This is happening
right now. This wave is If it was
happening right now, you wouldn't be
here. You'd already have the money and
have the plan open. Guys, I'm out.
The strategy of trying to buy a license
for a single plant is almost ludicrous.
If you can't tie up an entire region,
you're buying the right to become a
dealer in Hawaii. You've got to lock up
all of United States. Do you have $200
million you'd like to plop down for
that? You become the pioneers. You
establish a region for 5 million, prove
the model, and somebody else scoops the
rest of the country. That makes no sense
to me as an investor. We will be the
first. I get it. The inside connection
to MDI. I can go to MDI and simply do a
deal right now without you for New York.
Well, here's here's my answer to that.
Try because they don't want my car in
New York or my money. No, they don't
want to be double crossed. There's a
there's a trust factor. You could not go
directly to Ghee and say, "I'm going to
plop down $5 million and and completely
double cross us." Yeah. You know what?
Push comes to shove, their company gets
in trouble and Kevin comes along with a
$5 million offer for the rice. $5
million to to ghee is small potatoes.
The way to make this work is to sit down
and come up with a national strategy for
the entire US market and then package
that up and bring it to investors.
You're trying to build a bakery before
tasting the cake. That's right. But
we're going to allow others to taste the
cake. That's what they've been waiting
for. I know the challenges of all the
legal issues bringing product to market
like this. It could take forever and
it's too early for me without your
ability to actually get clearance uh to
have this operate in America. So because
of that, I'm out.
You know, I like green products. I think
that this compressed air concept could
be a hero. Um, but for me, you would
have to have had the rights to all of
the USA for me to really be interested.
I'm
out. Your deal doesn't make a lot of
sense for a shark at all because the
return expectations on this are far in
the future. It's a monumental task.
Nobody wants to launch this in Hawaii.
I'm certainly not going to do it. I
think I've articulated why. You may have
a shark who is so ingrained in the
automotive industry, he may be crazy
enough to do it. We're going to find out
right now, but I'm out.
Four Sharks are out. Robert is Pat and
Ethan's last chance for a deal for their
airropelled vehicle, Air Car. I've
invested in a lot of things and I'm
willing to invest in this, too. Look,
I'm interested. I'm I'm really
interested. Annie is full of hot air.
Yeah. It's a lowcost commuter car for
$10,000. Big market for that. Mhm. The 5
million isn't that much considering the
size of this market. This is not
something you're going to sell one state
at a time, my friends. The minute you're
successful in Hawaii, somebody is going
to lock up the other stuff. I don't want
to make air cars in Hawaii. I want to
bring this to the American market.
I'm happy to give you $5 million for the
right to go and sit at that table and
negotiate a distribution deal with the
people who own it. So, I'm giving you $5
million for 50% contingent on being able
to negotiate an Americanwide deal. And
if you don't get that deal, what's
contingent on that? Cuz I don't think
the 5 million goes away. Gee, Neg would
be thrilled to have you make a deal with
him and I feel very certain that that
number could come down because
ultimately having the US rights is the
golden goose. Why are you even
hesitating? Well, I want to add one
other Phillip that you you you would be
purchasing and that is the golf cart.
Pat, you got to stop selling. Don't talk
yourself out of a deal. You got to make
a decision.
Deal. We have a deal. Oh my gosh. Yeah.
I want an honor to meet you. Thank you.
You are the perfect perfect person. I'm
the perfect person for this. I love
cars. Thank you so much. Congrats. Thank
you.
When you're dealing with the reinvention
of the motor, that leap of faith is the
leap that people who are on the ground
floor have to take. And we've been
proven right for our for taking the
jump. High five, Robert. I like that.
Awesome. There might be something there.
I hope there is.