I want to pet that I'm so sick of that
salmon oh that [ __ ] and then what you're
saying how you miss me yeah you miss me
and all the things
[Music]
all right I think I've had enough
you guys are not on first video that we
filmed back from tour
Jimmy but I think we're gonna move
and we're sitting on a car video with
Jade Swizzle yeah well that's oh really
that's this is gonna be the Friday
before that
okay if it's an update I feel like why
not okay so video with Justin coming out
soon and with Jimmy coming out soon wow
but the one with Justin was filmed
before our tour the one with our dad is
filmed after our tour but we figured
we're since we're back from tour we
might as well
yes okay so let's talk about tour okay
so basically [ __ ] I enjoyed meeting
everybody and I'm so very grateful for
the experience and I'll remember it
forever yeah Taurus was pretty wild like
we were just like in and out of a bunch
of States we went to a bunch of places
that we never knew we met some new
friends we
experienced a lot with friends we
already had that I did not think we'd be
able to experience like just wild wild
things yeah I never expected myself to
go on a tour ever in my life and I'm
just like damn girl you really did that
that's wild no yeah I did not think I'd
be able to do that at all whatsoever I
had no idea like the like what it was
gonna all be about this and that and I'm
very happy that we did it and I will say
a lot of people were like oh tour's over
no more tour content no more of this no
more of that like Malcolm and Trill with
that tour experience with them was such
like a like keep in mind we're living
with every single people that we went on
that tour with it was such a bonding
experience person
talking about this is a tour recap video
I don't know where he went yeah I'm
following with what he's going I'm so
confused now I was basically trying to
say that like oh people are like oh I'm
devastated the Torah error is ending
like no more Malcolm and chilling the
triplets together and Matt's saying like
they're going back home so it's gonna be
difficult to make content together but
don't fear because we will be with our
friends eventually and we will continue
to make contact with them and we're
great friends even though we're not
gonna post it for a while that's what he
was trying to say yeah I was so confused
I got you man I got you I'm putting ice
on this little thing I'm proud of you
but anyway yeah I had a lot a lot of fun
on tour
um yeah with let's recap it let's recap
it no that's it that's the whole video
no we're gonna add some fun that's
exactly what I'm saying let's recap the
[ __ ] Tour all right recap it Chris
start no I wanted to say first and
foremost oh yeah while we were on tour
oh there was a lot going on and we were
so busy my thoughts yeah we are all so
busy that we couldn't really do much
like and put our full effort into enough
no we could do a Nick I don't give a
[ __ ] well no I said first and foremost
oh yeah and then went on a crazy
different care go ahead I'm just telling
them basically since we are so busy on
tour and everything yes we forgot to
thank you guys for four million and like
a bunch of other stuff that we wanted to
just say it just didn't seem like we
were like we were very connected with
the people that we were meeting in
person obviously because we were like
meeting fans in person but like we
hadn't filmed the video in Forever
obviously because we were on a tour so
it was kind of like this weird
disconnect from like everyone we didn't
yeah like all the content we were
posting was aged content that was filmed
like a month prior yeah so it felt a
little weird but now that we're back we
can formally thank you all for four
million subscribers which is insane
shout out to us we can all we can thank
all you guys for coming to all the shows
yeah which I feel like we were doing a
lot but again thank you she's crazy
because I've seen so many like there's a
fun like it's fun to recap the whole
tour and we have a lot of stories to
tell you guys we have a lot of just
funny reactions and like moments that we
want to talk about but at the end of
every single one of our q and A's on
tour we were talking about our podcast
and a podcast update so I'm sure that a
bunch of you guys have seen clips of it
on
um Tick Tock and such of like people who
recorded that and posted it obviously
but basically me maker has been hinting
at a podcast since July
I've been hinting on a podcast since
July because I really wanted to do it
but our podcast did not happen obviously
and we went a whole different route with
it but it's going to be spectacular
that's a good word to use that's a great
great one but our podcast is going to be
amazing
um so when this Friday video comes out
we're going to already be back in La
hopefully if our flight goes according
to plan we're safe
um no I'm just saying like if we don't
our flight if nothing goes wrong I don't
like speaking like oh we'll be in La I
don't know the world I don't plan you
know the world plans me I'll see what
happens yeah you know what I mean
because then I feel like it's bad vibes
I'm like oh well yeah okay I'm trying to
predict the future and I can't do that
go but if everything goes according to
plan we'll hopefully be in La when this
video comes out so
um and it's a Friday so we're gonna post
photos of what our podcast studio is
looking like right now
um hopefully so basically that's gonna
come as soon as we can get there we can
unwind we can relax we can unpack our
amount of suitcases from LA and we can
just like really really take a week off
man we can set in like what we want our
podcast creative to be who we want to be
on our podcast but that also comes with
our content we aim to make the viewer
enjoy the content obviously such as
everyone who ever makes content ever so
with that being said is our podcast
being something new what do you guys
want us to talk about because you guys
are already our fans so you're gonna go
to the listeners you guys are gonna
consume the podcast before anyone else
probably because you already know who we
are so we want just feedback from you
guys in the comments tag us and tick
tocks whatever do your thing but just
tell us who you want to see as guests on
the podcast
um
what you want us to talk about on the
podcast just kind of what you guys are
expecting or wanted to look like so that
we can try and deliver like podcast
content that you guys want should we go
down the list of states and like say our
favorite memory no podcast yeah but just
a quick little thing nope that's not a
quick little thing we went to 15 states
like something so quick
no really quick Nick it's a car video
all right overall funniest moment that
you experienced yeah we can tell one
memory each that we should get two
memories each a funny and a good okay
funny and a good okay my favorite funny
memory was when Nick fell off the bed in
New Mexico no that was in Van Horn Texas
probably my favorite memory was probably
I want to say a formal nice thank you to
Mr Landing Cube for coming to the LA
show because that was a 10 out of 10
experience that I got to witness in my
life because that's another thing I want
to talk about for the tour recap video
is I've been a fan of Landon and skies
since like freshman year of high school
and to be able to do our own tour with
our fans in the crowd but then have him
perform for our fans and our fans know
the words to that song it was just a
very full circle yeah it was kind of
like the Matrix
not even close to the Matrix Red Bull
sugar-free
camera's gonna die any second so okay
that has been our recap and we hope so
that's what we're looking forward to and
kind of our recap on things we're gonna
do another podcast episode completely
separate about tour so we can't really
get into the details on here because
these are allotted to 20 minutes and I
don't want to bore you guys because
these are supposed to be comical and fun
so we're gonna save a lot of tour
memories all right cool so get ready for
that what's comical tonight
how are you guys feeling I say the only
thing comical about this video is next
[ __ ] sunglasses
I think he looks fan gave me these so
you just made fun of our supporters I'm
sorry no they're they're nice I like
them I just I don't know I couldn't pull
them off
that's a new juggle water no what the
[ __ ] could you ever juggle water yes in
bags or water balloons correct [ __ ] you
yeah but no that was my little trick
[ __ ] you
couldn't juggle water bottles you could
but that yeah that wasn't the [ __ ]
question
okay next question next
um if you could have any historical
figure as a best friend who would it be
and why
mine be Abraham Lincoln I knew you were
gonna say that
um took me months to get those any
historical feature bad question I mean
what did I just say any historical
feature what are you rapping
um
yes he is or person no it's not if you
could only speak in song lyrics which
songs would you choose to communicate
with in her mood by I spice she and her
mood like damn [ __ ] I don't [ __ ] with
you by Big Sean oh
um no what's a good one
um
mine would be stir fry by Migos
so awful it's like uncomprehensible
that was the worst answer I've ever
heard in my life but you can just use
the ad-libs I would say mine would be
hmm I have to get really I'm gonna be
Sweet Caroline
East Coast song
yeah people on the west coast don't know
about that song no if you know about it
it's just a good old East Coast ballpark
I'll probably be breathed by Lil Skies
your love I guess so I can just tell
y'all to [ __ ] breathe that's all I
need breathe breathe
why or that's I don't like this question
that's a terrible question I don't like
this question if you had any superpower
but it had to be completely useless what
would it be it could
like like like it'd have to eat I do my
vegetables through my belly button like
I'd be completely useless but it'd be
super power
I
could like
never mind what do you I don't want to
say say it sharpen sharpen pencils like
really quick nope because that'd be
useful
you need something that's completely
useless like you could do it anyway and
just like laser eyes but they only work
with my eyes shut
that's valid actually because it'd be
useless because you could not see the
what the [ __ ] your lasering that's a
valid answer thank you of course um I'm
gonna go with like
I could I could steal any two shoes with
their different sizes you can get away
with it wrong
I would just repeatedly steal the same
okay whatever I don't know
it has to be useless okay I would use
super heroes I could only enable it when
I'm listening to music with max volume
headphones see that's so good
you're not understanding um um mine
would be be able to push be really good
at carving pumpkins but be allergic to
pumpkins
yes I
super fast but I can only run super fast
if one of my legs are broken yes yeah
like you just couldn't do it mine would
be like I'd be able to push a shopping
cart really really quickly but I can't
push it really quickly if there's
anything in it oh that's a good one so
it's like you could push a shopping cart
really quick like what's the point yeah
yeah that was so good yay they
advertised like fire fire pit logs when
they call it like fire pit logs like no
[ __ ] obvious like I wasn't gonna put
it in my [ __ ] whoa
living room yeah okay when our podcast
starts I'm gonna be 100 real with you
guys on 100 of the time that's good Nick
because I just feel like there's a lot
that I just need to there's just a big
disconnect in social media world that
people just don't understand and I feel
like our podcast is going to really give
us the outlet to connect more to deeper
level and understanding of us see I like
I like keeping our car videos fun
humorous and a good time correct and for
the fans that want to see more real life
stereo low triplet [ __ ] where it's like
Amazon and it's like we don't we
mentally drain it yeah I want them to
see that too but I want to that's why
these are always but I also feel like
fun this is a good car video to watch if
like you want to know what our podcast
is going to be like because we're not
really joking around right now we're
having conversation so this is fine Nick
I kind of feel like this is the place
with the good old house
but I think we should keep this video
kind of serious because I want the
people to know like this is what our
podcast is gonna happen like this is
what we're gonna actually do in our
podcast starts you know what I mean I
never made that Tick Tock which really
we're gonna do loose screws and here's
gonna go you have time what I'm saying
is kind of just along the lines of like
if you guys enjoy this video like our
podcast is kind of going to be serious
conversation still
we're not grown but we're growing up
like we started YouTube we were 17. yeah
I'm also really so it's like I'm like
just to have more like grown-up
conversations like and I'm also really
excited because a lot of you guys are
kind of like but hey we're still us oh
[ __ ] you let me speak a lot of a lot of
you guys are like or my biggest fear
with starting a podcast and I told Matt
and Chris this was like what are we
gonna do in an hour-long formatted video
that's different from the car videos
because the car videos are kind of like
they're our source of entertainment you
guys know that like where they're funny
and they're quick it's all quick comedy
in the card I feel like so oh my God
sorry guys what I'm saying is kind of
like our podcast is gonna be so
different because it's gonna not just be
that quick humor that we're making car
videos yeah and another reason I'm just
really excited Matt shut the [ __ ] up
another reason I'm really excited for
our podcast and to get like more on a
serious level with you guys is I feel
like there's kind of a skewed perception
of like who me Matt and Chris you did
whenever there's a skew that I think
it's just like a skill I think of a
kebab yes there's like a skewed
perspective of like who me Matt and
Chris are as people as individuals
because it's like you're only seeing us
shut the [ __ ] up shut the [ __ ] up leave
the car you guys only see us like joking
around like getting really angry about
something Nick yells at me so I feel
like I'm really excited for you guys to
like have to like you guys are gonna see
an hour long of me and I feel like I
feel like it's kind of like I'm a
different person a little bit nickel
than us I feel like I'm kind of a
different person like funny car videos
I'm excited first yes I see more I
actually believe it I [ __ ] hate you
both and I don't want to deal with this
little stupid little act that I'm making
you guys upset it's not an act
you can literally just literally [ __ ]
yourself that was weird
so bizarre
good you're in the luxury Lounge Grim
days or something
I literally thought this was all black
it's not
do you guys have anything to say since
you [ __ ] keep interrupting me kid you
look like the AC thing on the ceiling of
a car you look like your mom all right
and my dad hey she's the place with the
helpful hardware folks
let's see how many Jingles we can sing
um
k-a-r-s cars for kids
for kids
donate your cars today
I'm loving it State Farm repairs
safe flight repair safe light replace
um
what's the other one ace is the place
with the helpful hardware folks what's
Progressive with flow oh oh oh oh
O'Reilly's Auto Parts
I feel like there's another there's a
few that were missing
um what's oh cinnamon rolls
that's a good one we know a thing or two
because we've seen that they were two
farmers
like we're not so crazy to me what every
single person in this world right has
their own experiences and has their own
opinion on everything and has their own
version of like a truth in a situation
and has their own version of like things
that they've been through where every
single person's unique experience is
completely different
so do you think there's like one defying
like
right and wrong or like the truth versus
the false in every situation like in
general I genuinely be like oh that's
true it's like how the [ __ ] do you know
you can say oh that's orange but it's
like what is really Orange
I mean I I kind of know what you were
saying until you said some dumb [ __ ] at
the end but it's like I think like it's
just crazy it's just crazy how different
everyone's life is because like me you
and Matt like bro we users stick
together so much and we're always
together for 19 years yet there's still
so many things that I've experienced
like that you guys won't you know what I
mean yeah so that just shows like if I
have certain feelings about someone or
something or something bad happens in my
life and I'm affected by it negatively
and you two aren't even like that just
blows my mind how everything is a
difference oh it's also so crazy down to
like everybody because bro we literally
I legit oh my God what's so crazy I
spend every moment of every day with you
guys what's so crazy on the same exact
point as you is like week the three of
us could be experiencing the exact same
thing like exact same thing but like one
of us is like slightly different in that
situation which leads to a completely
different feeling about it I also feel
like you know what feelings feelings
about like what's going what happened
before that situation at least with the
helpful hardware folks I feel like how
you feel about us like going into a
situation can really affect how you
leave that situation for sure
that's so weird like how are we
perfectly time Cardinals
oh
hello
[Music]