chilean's up
suitcase coming outside
oh he's strong
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
I need to go honestly me too honestly
they're not
thanks for being a gentleman
excited some of us
like that
boom backflip
because what are y'all doing I'm trying
to like I'm trying to open the curtains
and then he's gonna be there
I'm not used to this it's a rocky
sensation
Rocky Sensation that sounds like a fan
when I come back
I'm gonna need to buy like a mega
vibrator
Nick's gonna have to buy what
it's not that funny ever
okay
I didn't either no cool fit Maddie Oh
yay
I'm scared there's a movie Watcher here
tell me that's not a good that's not a
good idea
right there but you can't really see
this
yeah you can't but you don't have to
touch it or nothing you need to watch
that he said I found a good bug pack you
change it before you go on stage I said
I hope you change it before you get on
stage
Nick literally has pajamas on right now
what what is she being serious
like
like damn it's like a real sense
don't make him be on cue
Joe do that thing again be like
raspberries in The Green Room
oh
my God you're way too loud come on let's
go downstairs look at us we're in the
Green Room Chris is walking today you
know okay let's take a look guys
what is up guys
I'm surprised to see you here ah I like
that blue wall it was just red actually
believe it or not believe me really but
here's the stage let's go show them
where we're gonna do our first small
talking okay
if you're wondering how this is gonna
work this is our backdrop here for
yes
let's trip
so this is gonna be our backdrop for the
meet and greet photo lock
telling you this picture of you and
Chris
yay and then we're super excited because
it's just like
it's crazy how many different little
experiences we'll have in such a quick
time yep let me do the meet and greet
afterward and then we hit the stage and
rock out and answer some questions live
q a
intro kill it right oh yeah yeah yes sir
hey Maddie hey
y'all good yeah we're good
right here yeah Landing Cube live right
now
let's not landed cute no it's not but
Landon's coming to the LA show hold on
they don't know they know they don't
know it yet that's hilarious special
guest what a crazy little secret I know
right Landon legit my high school
favorite artist bro human Skies got me
through high school so it's a full
circle experience right now full circle
moment yep
[Music]
no oh my god look live action my BLT
coming in where where where oh right BLT
comment oh it's going up to the roof VLC
cotton movement
VLT on the Move Nick oh my God pancakes
you got pancakes yeah I'm very happy
with my decision
wow that guitar looks crazy on the
camera it's like reflective reflecting
welcome to Sam
pearly whites trolls pearly whites look
extra pearly on the with this light
do you want to go on stage when Landon
does red roses with all of us everyone
can go every single person [ __ ] it why
not every single person is I'm not gonna
like and it's just your mouth
we should just everyone everyone
yeah everyone for red roses they're
crazy that would be nuts yeah and have
Landon recruit us all be like I need
some help for red roses everyone gotta
come down boom so let's choke Cassandra
what's going down she gets the first
access let me explain what Cassandra is
for those yep
um
I think so high as followed yes
Alexander runs through the news account
a lot of you know what that is might not
know who it is so this is her in the
flesh
true but so we're gonna show Santa the
small talk area
is so scary
bro just like bro just sitting there
excuse me
[Music]
yeah
oh
[Music]
never even wanna change
It Off
yo hey hi how are you
yeah next one say hi to the Vlog
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
yeah
it was crazy it was lit when and Johnny
came which are crazy because we've been
watching them on YouTube for how long
like since freshman year of high school
Nick you're not even on me buddy sorry
wants to Vlog but doesn't know how to
Vlog it's crazy yeah but that was
awesome they performed Trill and Malcolm
did their thing that was like the
craziest live q a video for 20 minutes
technically so that was awesome that was
insane why is why is Maddie even there
because Maddie is a Maddie's the [ __ ]
a r Maddie who's Works behind the scenes
get [ __ ] [ __ ] done
okay yeah and she got my clothes on so
she's like an ad for yeah this is a
walking advertisement she hasn't slept
it's still
asleep
but yeah we're on our bus and we're
going to our first destination ever
other than the event which is a Walmart
whoa
subway surfers real time
I hate how many mirrors are in here I
can Vlog you and me wow that's crazy
what up Squad
we're at Walmart y'all on the floor
we're getting our Lifeline of supplies
in this Walmart yeah like do we do it
yeah [ __ ] huge bags oh make sure you
don't get sugar-free though
we're good we're good let's get pretzels
yeah
I need pretzels
no problem
but yes we are we are shopping for all
the Necessities that we will need
including horrible gummy bears those are
the ones
[Music]
yes the honey twist the fungus the sour
this is the one we got at home yeah
family fun
Family Fun mix
put on I'm Vlogging this is equally as
important shut up
you know
this is crazy
[Applause]
back in here
hey guys so we're actively putting
groceries into our tour bus
as you can see it's raining Matt's
outside so he's panicked I'm sheltered
from the rain so I'm fine
it's not the last thing here's everyone
all right
go back awesome thank you
thank you
Jesus hey guys welcome back to the Vlog
we did not Vlog really at all in the car
did we at the what in the bus no we
didn't really Vlog out on the bus
because it was just chaos but we got all
the way here I was annoyed because I
didn't get woken up at a normal time
this morning
we are meeting a lot of fans so we meet
people in two different segments first
is small talks second is meet and greets
and then we do meet and greets part two
Chris come with me
so I know I explained this yesterday at
like the other show but we're doing the
same thing here again so it's Matt's
gonna have a table here it's it's
different because we're at different
venues every time so we've got to kind
of navigate it well but Chris is going
to be at a table there's gonna be lines
here of you guys which is crazy so I'll
I'll play pretend again like they come
on down this way I think you'll go to
Chris first oh my God hi Christina oh my
God that's good you interact with Chris
get your card and then you're done with
him because you should be quickly you
come over to the beautiful Matthew
sterniola sitting at this table mama you
look great here the lighting and
everything's great then you sign this
and you move along and I'm gonna be over
here then after you interact with me you
come on keep it going back and then you
get to go into like this area this whole
waiting area where we will then do
another red carpet yes so then you do
the same line but instead of me Matt and
Chris being at a table we're gonna be
right here in front of this we're gonna
take a group photo you're gonna get that
group photo sent to your phone
and live a happy life with a group photo
then way over here where we will then do
our q a on that beautiful stage up there
let's go Chris is down there it's really
high up
I'm following Matt
our sound people are on the stage hello
you guys all be down there we'll be
doing our QA from up here
crazy then Malcolm and chill will
perform and then we always will have a
surprise secret song at the end where we
will do a little like how we had Landon
it might not be a special guest every
time but we'll always have a special
song
and red roses which is like amazing one
of my favorite songs ever so but we're
gonna have a secret song tonight as well
which you'll find out later yeah yeah
look at Ohio
oh they got up there answering questions
and stuff and I'm down here in the
audience this is like what front row is
gonna look like can you take my photos
yeah I got you
my recording
hey guys this is our rating for The
Green Room today the bathroom was [ __ ]
because we couldn't [ __ ] because there's
no stall door
sorry I gotta like squish bye
this is the venue after we're done with
our show
how do you feel after performing today
with your mom here it was amazing thank
you Arizona Hometown Hometown
me too that was fantastic Matt's got all
of our fan goodies oh my God there's so
much
Maddie how do you feel after performing
today it's funny you feel amazing
you performed it's gonna be here in 10
minutes guys 10 minutes
okay
favorite song You performed today
gotcha
indeed where's Trail
[Music]
how do you feel after performing today
and then how do you feel what was your
favorite song You performed today
favorite song yes
paralyzed all right
right we're gonna go into the stage for
fun but
I really this vlog's gonna get posted
soon then we're gonna have a lot of
shows after this so even if you're not
coming to tour and you guys are
following the tour what do you think we
should do differently during our shows
or what do you suggest what do you think
would be fun for us to do on the shows
because we're all about fan interaction
out in Arizona y'all went crazy it was
amazing mountain control performances
were 10 out of 10. Malcolm brought out
his mom Hometown hero this [ __ ] was it
was such a beautiful performance also if
you were watching them perform here
then little did you know while they were
performing we were hiding all the way up
there yeah we were peeking our heads
over here
all right
that was our first and second show we're
heading to Texas right now
I think like three shows before we
should go to a Texas Roadhouse in Texas
they even got them there
for that one all right well we'll see
you Wednesday and Friday
say and then what you're saying how you
miss me yeah you miss me and all the
things
[Music]