The idea for your future ready mine
really started when I observed many many
people in this world to not being able
to deal with that uncertainty that the
future actually holds right and that
created a lot of anxiety for people
around the future. One of the
experiences I had a couple of years ago
really helped me to understand that we
have more control of our future than we
actually think was when the wildfires
happened in California. They came clo as
close as 1 mile to our house. So what we
noticed is that police came and gave us
an evacuation order, right? So we had to
pack our things in less than 10 minutes
and evacuate our house. Our family of
five. What I told my kids and what I
told myself is that we cannot control
the fires. So our house might be gone or
it might be still there when we return.
But what we can control is how we
respond to that situation. Do we respond
with optimism? Do we respond with
openness, with curiosity? All of that
really helped us to then start living a
life that was very different before the
wildfires, a life that is more aligned
with nature, where we grow our own food,
where we respect nature even more. We
were quite optimistic when we left our
house and uh after 14 days we were able
to return back and luckily the house was
still there and our op optimism about
how to live with the future was also
actually increased. So what I wanted to
give people is three things. First one
is a framework that they can use to
really build the future that they want
to see happening. The second thing is I
wanted to give them stories from
individuals that build remarkable
futures for themselves. And the third
thing is really practices that everybody
can use in their own lives to create the
dream future they want to see
happening. Hello, my name is Frederick
Fat and I'm the first and former chief
innovation evangelist at Google. I'm
also the author of a book, What's Next
is Now? How to live future ready.
Everybody is interested in their future.
What we mostly see is that people think
about the future as something abstract,
right? But I believe that predictions
don't really help when we think about
the future. So I want to help people to
have a clearer picture about the future
by actually imagining it and not just
imagining the future, but imagining
their future. Because the future is not
something that just happens to you. It's
something that you make happen. And for
most people, it's really coming down to
that question. How can I create a better
future for myself? And I want to give
people the mind state to really shape
the future they want to see
[Music]
happening. I've been the chief
innovation evangelist at Google for
about 12 and a half years. My role I was
really responsible on shaping the
culture of creativity and innovation at
Google. Really trying to train people in
things like curiosity and empathy and
experimentation. Giving them the right
methods and tools and also mind state to
really invent a better future. And
secondly, shaping the culture, trying to
create initiatives in the culture that
really brings the values to life that
Google stands for. Values around
creativity, having an ambition around
the future, but also trying to think 10x
and trying to think really bold and big
about the future. That was really um
part of of the work. And uh when you
want to create a culture, right, what I
really see is that most cultures in
organizations have specific values.
Values like creativity or productivity
or community. What I try to do is
activate those values through rituals.
One of the rituals that I included in
our culture at Google was what I call
the Penguin Award because the Penguin
Award really rewarded people for taking
risks. And uh when you take risks,
you're really trying to try many things
out, right? You're thinking not just
bold, but you're acting bold as well.
Encouraging risk-taking through a ritual
with the penguin award was something
fascinating because for me, penguins
really stand for taking risks. As you
imagine, penguins on an ice shelf, many
of them, right, a colony of penguins,
there's always one penguin that's the
courageous penguin that jumps first into
the water. the rest of the colony stands
back and really observes is that if that
little penguin comes back up with food
or became food, right, there's a 50%
chance. And so what I wanted to signal
is that when people really jump into the
cold water, meaning that they're trying
something new, that they're
experimenting, that they're taking a
risk, that should be rewarded with the
penguin award. Because we also know that
when no one jumps from that ice shelf,
no one takes a risk in an organization.
colony of penguins will disappear and so
will the organization. So I think it's
really important that we build cultures
through rituals in uh every
organization. I think everybody's able
to do
that. Yes, I think everybody can be that
courageous penguin, right? That jumps
first into the water in that metaphor.
Courage is something that we all have,
right? But usually our mind doesn't like
to take risks. I think what we can do is
instead of waiting for the perfect
moment or for perfection, just go for
it. Just give it a try, right? And see
what happens. And usually what we find
is when you take that risk, when you're
open to trying something new, you feel
rewarded, right? That creates a very
comforting effect as well. So what I'm
practicing myself is trying to not do
things twice, right? not to fall into
that autopilot that our mind loves to go
onto because that autopilot really
creates or saves energy for our mind,
right? And when as soon as we get off
autopilot and we engage in something
new, we take a risk or we try something
new. It might be talking to a stranger
or it might be trying out a new idea,
our minds need to be activated. That
energy, I think, is great because then
we see that we're getting off autopilot
and we actually we're trying something
new. and then that might lead to an
innovation then as
well. During my time at Google, I've
been able to work with tens of thousands
of Googlers and really trying to figure
out how do people not just imagine a
better future, how do they innovate, how
do they use their creativity to really
create something better. So in my first
couple of weeks I actually traveled to
really many offices connected with many
many Googlers around the world to really
trying to understand how do people
innovate and what I found is that it's
usually not a place that makes the
difference. It's also not a specific
framework and it's also not the
resources they have access to. What I
found is really in their mind state what
I call a future ready mind state. And
that mind state for me has five
dimensions. First, it's about radical
optimism. Thinking not just that the
glass is half full, but seeing the
potential to fill the glass even
further. It's about unreserved openness.
Being open to many ideas, being open to
perspectives, and also being open to
change your own perspective as well is
really critical because openness is
really supercharger to your personal
growth. The third one is about
curiosity, compulsive curiosity, asking
those big what if questions that allow
you to really think big. And then it's
about experimentation, perpetual
experimentation, these tiny quick
experiments that allow you to really
learning quickly, to really learn
quickly as well because the path to the
future is really paved with experiments.
And then it's about empathy. Not just
empathy for other people, but also
empathy for your future self. trying to
understand your future needs is really
critical. And then the last dimension is
dimension X. It's your personal
superpower that allows you to really use
whatever your superpower is to create
these uh incredible innovations, to
create something new, and to tap into
your creativity as well. So these six
dimensions for me really define what I
call a future ready mind. And with a
future ready mind, you can really see
more opportunities. you can take control
of your future and you can shape the
future that you want to see
happening. I think it's the combination
of those dimensions, right? It's not
that radical optimism is more important
that openness or empathy, right? I think
they're all incredibly important. And
the good news is that we all have a
certain amount of those qualities of
those dimensions in ourselves. We all to
a certain degree open. We all to a
certain degree optimistic. We all like
to experiment from time to time. But
what I also see is that when we take for
example curiosity, our curiosity when we
grow up actually goes dormant. That's
what studies actually show. So I want to
bring those dimensions back into your
life by actually trying to train
yourself in curiosity, in openness, in
experimentation, and in optimism. And if
you train yourself in these things, I
guarantee you're going to see more
opportunities for yourself and you're
going to take control of the future that
you want to actually see happening. So
I've been able to work with many
organizations range from the UN to NASA
to the NBA to the German Soccer
Association and many many more including
startups. And what I've seen is that
let's take curiosity. Startups really
use their curiosity to explore something
new. They're the best in asking good
questions and trying to really reimagine
what is possible. When organizations
grow older, right, what we see is that
curiosity is usually replaced with
scaling or other things that they want
to focus on. So two things I've tried
when it comes to training people
innovation and creativity was first to
help them to train specific things like
empathy, expansive thinking or
experimentation. And the second thing is
what we tried is we built environments
where people really could reduce that
friction from having an idea to building
your first prototype. And the garage
that I founded was one of those places
where a lot of Googlers came together to
try out some ideas, right? To really
start to push the boundaries on some of
those ideas and really started to learn
quickly how things work and what works
and what doesn't work. So it's really a
space around experimentation. We had um
projects like project lon was created
those stratospheric balloons to really
provide uh internet around the world.
Antennas and some of the the balloon
parts were actually um prototyped in the
garage and experimented with. What I
found is that also Google Glass for
example was launched out of the garage.
A project where we invited people to
test out this service uh a couple of
years ago and prototype it and
experiment with it. Right? So I think
for me it was really critical that we
take an approach to innovation that is
based on experimentation and empathy and
expansive thinking. Those three elements
that really allow you to not just
imagine ideas but really build ideas
that are meaningful to people that are
based on radical new ideas but also that
are tried out so that we can start
learning what works and what doesn't
work. Innovation doesn't happen by
itself, right? It's something where you
have to train people in but also you
have to create a culture and an
environment where innovation can
actually happen. Those two elements are
very critical, right? Trying to provide
the right training for people so that
they can literally train their mind on
how to innovate around how to imagine
and how to think expansively and so
forth. And at the same time finding a
culture where this is actually possible
with initiatives like the penguin award
that I just shared um as well that
allows people to take more risks. So
combining those two things where you
train people into in uh in innovation
and you build a culture around
innovation is really critical and that
was the main focus of my work. What I
felt is that when it comes to the future
for example and innovation sometimes see
that our mind creates four strategies
that really is not really helpful but
it's just um a natural very human thing
that evolves when we think about the
future. The first thing is that we have
anxiety about the future, right?
Sometimes we think about the future as
not desirable, as something that just
happens to us, right? That is not in our
control and that creates anxiety, right?
The second thing is that sometimes we
think we can just wait until the future
happens, right? So we wait until
something in our lives happens and then
we start to act. The third thing is that
sometimes we think the future is owned
by others, right? So we think that our
partners, our managers or our leaders or
the government or politicians or
whatever it is are owning the future and
creating the future. And I think that's
not true. And the fourth one is that
sometimes we just want to deny the
future, right? We want to bring back the
past. We want to say like, oh, you know,
past times have been better and and all
of those arguments. So having that
anxiety, waiting for the future,
thinking that others own the future and
denying the future are four things that
really are not helpful, right? Because I
think everybody has the opportunity to
shape their own future and have control
over their own
future. I think there's there's three
things that I want to share. First one
is trying to really imagine your future
and make that a practice every day.
Maybe the first 60 seconds in the
morning or the first three minutes in
the morning trying to really just close
your eyes for a moment and trying to
imagine your future self. Trying to see
a clearer picture of where you going to
be in the future, a year from now for
example, who you going to be surrounded
by and what are you doing? And then the
fourth critical element is how do you
feel in that future and what do you want
to feel in this future as well? very
important practice that everybody can do
every morning or throughout the day to
really build that muscle of imagination,
your future self. The second thing I
recommend doing is you want to turn into
a more optimistic person. There are some
interesting studies that show that if
you write down three things in the
evening and that can be on your phone or
it can be on a piece of paper that
really brings up the three things that
you're grateful for throughout the day
that you think that went well that are
the positives in your day, right? And
that could be small things. Note down
three things every day. After 21 days,
your mind actually changes and looks for
the more positive things in in your life
as well. And I think that's a very easy
practice that everybody can do.
[Music]