foreign
[Music]
experience and we didn't Vlog anything
because it was super hot but instead
we're just going to show you what we got
all right
triplets turning on triplet halt time I
got this cool hoodie with like mother
Mary on it or something okay you gotta
figure out what it is before you tell
them the Virgin Mary no it's holy I was
feeling very holy
at the um
has a flea market experience I got this
thing that has like crosses on it it's
like a hoodie thingy I got that hoodie
cool cool I got this okay they want us
you're like [ __ ] throwing things
around slow down let's show them I got
this US Army Air Force's thermal because
it right dude I like it's impossible to
Vlog you I'm like this like trying to
like show [ __ ] because you're literally
[ __ ] full of this US Army
Air Force thermal because it reminds me
of a vintage thermal that Matt has and I
was like you don't know what I like his
so I'm gonna get mine and then I got a
shirt from this guy who was really nice
I wanted to give him a big hug after I
bought it because he was like [ __ ]
really cool [ __ ] that guy
but it's like this clown shirt I think
it's really neat I think it's really
cool I'm happy with my shopping
experience today
and yeah your turn Matt
um I guess I'll kick it off with the oh
the shirt from the same guy because I
bought it first it inspired Chris to get
his so yeah and the guy was really nice
he was super super nice guy I love
supporting people that are kind I only
got two things so it's not as cool but I
really like this shirt it's like a
zipper and buttons and collar and
stripes and the whole thing I love it
you're gonna look great thanks yep
I bought the most but I got this first
of all I love this bag
thank you thank you this is the very
best like a little flower and a
butterfly I thought that was cute but I
got two sweaters from the same guy this
is one of them
oh Ocean Pacific I actually really got
this because there was an Ocean Pacific
bathing suit that I really want oh it's
that's what the op stands for yeah it
doesn't stand for overpowered you
[ __ ] gaming nerd
bathing suit that I really wanted and I
couldn't get so I was like you know if I
like well you could get it just sold out
before you got it no it just wasn't this
time so how so how would I have gotten
that then
shut up and show the clothes so as I
said I couldn't get it so I was like you
know I'm not gonna let another vintage
Ocean Pacific thing Pass Me By oh that's
a banger R5 like damn you could be the
one that can mess me up Maddie's have a
sweater like this that she didn't want
her anymore so she sold it but I was
like so mad that she sold it outside now
I have my own version of it I love that
sweater right I didn't even see you get
that sweater then I got this shirt it's
corny because it says California on it
and I live here but we can look past
that because I like the fishes I love it
I like the colors it reminds me of my
grandmother
Bernice and then this is my these are
shorts that I got oh those look like
underwear
they're shorts but I like them they're
mediums a little scared
they're mediums I'm a little scared oh
bless you
well you interrupted me I don't believe
I'm saying blush if you interrupt I
sneezed and then I got these three rings
which were probably not worth the value
but they're probably not like worth
anything but I was like you know they
look really fun oh they hitting right
now man right they look like they go
those diamonds dancing go crazy
or something guess how much I paid for
all three
a jillion dollars
30. I don't know
I'd hope like they were like ten dollars
each like 30 is like the max
I paid ten dollars for all three all
three wow
see good I see I was highballing really
high because I actually you took my
numbers I don't know what you're saying
you did anything last thing I got
love those they're Dicky shorts
they're way bigger than I thought but
I'm happy with that thanks for watching
our haul can we get tacos
sure
hey guys our house is [ __ ] disgusting
it's the next day
um we don't want to clean it so we're
just gonna leave
I'm gonna burp and throw out dude
why the [ __ ] would I type because I
don't tie it right and you tie it right
here
oh my God
grown man 20 years old ask me to type in
all right like
the [ __ ] just tie it
all right guys it's the next day
how do you walk this way just do what
you need to do like a classic gnarly I
don't know like a normal tie or like
what you usually do okay for me
but basically we're going to the
warehouse today
that's it I want a big excuse to get
dressed up all fancy I think Clyde might
have to make a comeback
fun fact every single time I put on a
dress shirt I feel like Clyde that
that's who I am deep down
quite obviously he's busy right now I'm
playing again Chris has been playing a
[ __ ] iOS [ __ ] mobile game for like
a week and a half and it's like the
craziest [ __ ] ever time to get off the
phone buddy seriously here Chris
don't scream the neighbor I don't give a
[ __ ] about you got a noise complaint
today at the warehouse
complaints to every aspect of life if I
had a dollar for every noise complaint
I'd be a filthy rich man literally come
do a reveal come on I can't
[Music]
just
like God I don't know what plans you got
okay oh yeah thank God he gave me the
camera he's just standing over there I
told you to record the cupcake
I wanted you to take the camera and
record us oh
open up no what is this dumb joke this
kid's making you're not a monkey and
you're not four get off I'm not trying
hey sprinkles
well are the ones in the backs
considered Sprinkles Cupcakes if they
don't have any sprinkles on them they
kind of look really bad the ones in the
back
like what's the eyeball on it it ain't
an eyeball what is it
whatever okay let's try oh the cupcakes
is it actually yeah ugly ass logo
well the frosting stays on well
okay wait let me go find it oh wow it's
red velvet oh the frosting doesn't oh
um I don't know what happened
I Feel Like You Gotta Give it like a
tear instead of a cut you know like open
it I'm not doing that this is already
falling apart I can just take the top
off
the convertible cupcake okay I'm just
gonna take a bite oh God such a bad joke
dude
foreign
chocolate red velvet cupcake ever
alright yo
sick so today's the day no sh what don't
yeah of one noise complaining I don't
give a [ __ ] [ __ ] talent show likes on
this video and Clyde coming back
wait hold on Christian said crucial news
no no they don't don't even reset it go
ahead Matt welcome to the stereo triple
talent show everybody Matt
one step and then come back down
I think I can
okay A little train engine
I don't know
[Music]
no yeah okay you have to go five steps
up
oh that was that was impressive I give
it a 10 out of 10. I want to go
consecutively no because of the soda I
feel like a little fizzy ball
Chris you're getting in the way yeah but
the whole Talent is like they need to
see it bro
foreign
you're never getting it in
yeah I hope you're hungry
[Applause]
you're doing this too fast for me to
vlog
[Applause]
ow [ __ ] off eat your words
that's dumb because it is it's not
though
where's the last pink one I don't know
bro
what the [ __ ]
the thoughts resistance here
[Applause]
she had nailed in the face of these ping
pong balls
thank you
oh
[Laughter]
no there's two more
that was wild man I think I hit it twice
in a row
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
for my brothers