your [ __ ] hair now holy [ __ ] this is
good
oh you felt wrong it did look good
okay guys put it on the dashboard please
let's get the video started
oh that was so cute for the edits
okay can we start
I know what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
[Music]
and we're live
today we're gonna be filming a red flags
about each other and then to finalize it
oh my God
oh my God you said that with his teeth I
like felt and then to end it we're gonna
finally we're gonna finalize the green
flag about each other to feel better
about herself awesome I have all my red
flags written down I've not won green
flag written down
reading it from a book makes it seem
like a Bible verse
we all start eating better but then also
suggest Cane's 20 minutes after okay
that's great that's insane that's
awesome that was great a lot but you
can't be yeah see my point is when I say
oh I think we should eat better it's not
that I think we should eat better like
fruits and vegetables I think we just
need to eat a [ __ ] meal it's like the
problem is we don't go get food so I
think canes even though it's not good
for you you can think you have to eat
better until indulge in canes like you
eat canes knowing like oh I should eat
better no I eat Cane's thinking like
this you know you better if it's better
than not eating
that's not the red flag though the red
flag is that the stuffed animal has
severe privileges over the swamp in this
bed and the rules of the bed so if you
sit in the bed but the stuffed animal
Falls you have to like pick him up
apologize put him back everyone away on
the left side with the stuffed animals
there Mr pugington has to tell you oh Mr
wrinkles has to tell you whether or not
you're allowed to sit there so the red
flag is not the stuffed animal itself
it's the fact that this stuffed animal
is literally a tyrant up the back that's
the problem
that was great thank you Nick Mr
wrinkleton there it is I don't think
that's a red flag at all I think that if
like here's the way I look at it if I
were to go into your room
I wouldn't sleep on where you normally
do like on your side of the bed well
it's a stuffed animal yes I know that
but it's like don't like walk over like
yes opinion sometimes weighs more than
you like I see you go to the opposite
side of the bed because he's already
there that's not true at all yes it is I
just think like you shouldn't walk into
my room if you want to sleep with me and
take my stuffed animal and throw it on
the floor I don't throw it on the floor
never sleeps in the same bed two nights
in a row either mine his own Nicks or
the couch true I mean I like to switch
it up I don't like to be I hate that so
then I wake up and I feel really weird
if I'm not like where I want to wake up
no I like wake up and sometimes I have
no idea where I am because you switch
every day like you literally zero clue
like even back home like I have no no I
don't wake up in L.A thinking you woke
up in Boston and wake up in Boston
thinking I just I don't know man I'm all
over the place especially with Tor I
feel like it's your turn
oh mg that was terrifying
oh car driving by slow I'm scared Look
Away hey don't do that mine's for Nick
he complains and complains and complains
and complains about stuff and openly
complains about it knowing there isn't a
solution he just wants his point across
that he's complaining so then you like
try to find them why are you complaining
why wouldn't there be a solution you no
you have admitted it to things like oh
there's nothing we can do about it and
there's no solution better than you
[ __ ] for an hour and a half just for us
but you literally complain about things
that literally you admit have no sense
sorry I've heard Nick say like there's
nothing I can do about it but I'm just
gonna maybe like complain I have a lot
of strong feelings and requests and okay
I wanted to say what are you doing
feelings and requests emotions and
desires
it's rather than like keeping them it's
rather than keeping them internal I
vocalize but here's the thing we don't
care like we don't care
no you need a [ __ ]
like what is grabbing the chair gonna be
scared okay Matt will like every once in
a while me and Matt will go to the gym
and he will work out to the point so he
literally hurts himself like like Matt
will work out to the absolute extreme
levels like no socks on or something no
he had socks on and he has his ankles so
he ran on a treadmill till like his
we're gushing blood and he looks like he
was gonna pass out the whole time beat
red like
all confused I think he's just so like I
don't think you guys go often enough
that it's routine so his body just don't
know what to do he doesn't
like work out and then like Bill build
up he goes straight for like power
workouts
I just want it more than you know insane
Matt would like that's so true though I
literally works out to the point till he
came no it's bad like I run on the
treadmill to the point where he's like I
can't even make it back home oh you're
like dying iPhone for that though would
let an entire African Stampede Run him
over and then apologize to them
and that's the truth Matt has like a lot
of really really sorry I'm sorry yeah
like he says I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry but he like literally puts himself
in the way of danger nothing's worse
than her I'm sorry I'll stop yeah
nothing's worse than when he um when
he's like tells you something's like
that we're do like come on let me learn
how to word it yeah please you're about
to do something and we all know it's
gonna be like good and we're gonna do it
and like then he'll let you know like
we'll be like oh tonight Matt we have a
Premiere so we're all gonna get dressed
and like head out at like five and then
like that's that works that's good
that's good
yeah
or you say that and then five minutes
later he goes guys it's we're leaving at
five for the premiere so we should
probably get dressed and get ready soon
oh like he says yeah opposite of this
makes it seem like he came up yeah
that's so frustrating okay
okay go ahead you guys both ask me
questions as if I work with a plan and
then you're asking questions like that
are ridiculous like you you guys know
like the warranty and like the [ __ ]
Apple care and I'm like I do not know I
do not work there I've never worked
there and I don't [ __ ] know the
answer to your questions Chris is like
Nick why is the Wi-Fi out and I'm like I
don't know because I also don't have
Wi-Fi then I use my critical thinking
skills and I go to the living room with
a Wi-Fi routers and Chris unplug it back
in and I'm like oh maybe that's the
solution to your Wi-Fi problem or we
could be like eating and Matt's like
watching this is like the restaurant I'm
like I don't work here I don't think all
the ingredients I'd tell you if I did
but I don't and it's questions that are
so specific to like you'd literally have
to work at The Establishment or for the
company of the questions you guys are
asking me also I'm still in the mood to
talk so I'm gonna read my next one which
is about you both again and you yell at
me for taking a long time to prepare to
get out of the car we're not done in the
car but I carry way more things than you
that's not true and it's always like you
guys are always telling me to go and
you're asking me oh where's the camera
as if our whole job isn't like it's all
of our jobs to bring the camera to the
car to film videos it's all of our jobs
to Vlog and you guys constantly yell at
me when I'm not ready to vlogger me I
don't have the camera when you guys
never have it because it's always my
responsibility for who knows God knows
what reason
that was good I do that I can keep going
the first one is just I feel like you're
a knowledgeable guy yeah and you just
can get it done more than I can look if
anyone has a chance to know it would be
you I know that that's true but like
when it's like we're at a restaurant
like Matt's worse than I yeah like he
asked me questions that you literally
cannot know unless you literally work
there or just like Insane luck okay like
insanity
okay
[Music]
Nikki gets proven wrong about a
situation but somehow still thinks he's
correct because I am no you're not
arguable like Nick will go oh my God
I know I'm wrong but and then try to he
then that's true
that's true yes exactly I know I know
that I was wrong here but we'll talk
about it he tries to explain why he was
wrong so he makes you think it out from
his point of view on why oh my God what
he did I haven't really so annoying Nick
is very clumsy that's not true so here's
the red flag ready Nick will fall and
then be embarrassed because of how
clumsy he is and how badly he fell so
he'll blame you for him falling even
though you have nothing to do with it
like I put this next stumble downstairs
and then go Chris and I'm like literally
across the room like I have no idea what
to do and then he yells at you and yells
at you like like why would you do that
are you kidding me are you serious and
I'm like I literally am 10 feet away
I don't know [ __ ]
nickel trip over his own boxes all right
well I think I just yelled that a lot
okay I have another one oh wait I have
one for Matt I have a quick one for Matt
Matt has an actual obsession with Liam
Neeson yeah I love Liam Neeson loves
them way too much but he's so good he's
such a good actor are you kidding he's
like two rubies that he said it doesn't
matter okay I have a theory on Liam
Neeson but I'm not gonna get into it
okay just go ahead no it's fine no a
little bit
oh I know what you mean nobody Matt has
a theory that he thinks Liam Neeson is
like an actual like trained assassin
killer in real life okay here's the
thing if he's getting all these roles to
be a killer and an assassin and like an
undercover agent or just like if you see
a Liam Neeson movie at this point he
might as well be one in real life yeah
because there's no you've acted out the
same thing 10 times that's part of your
personality now like I just like if I
meet Liam Neeson I want to feel like I'm
in danger of him like shooting me at any
second oh my God
okay Matt preps eating spicy chips by
putting them on a plate and grabbing
numerous water bottles before even like
trying to attack
like if we know Matt's like we he has to
allocate like a half hour of time to
eating like spicy what does that shape
mean how do you spell it alligator like
when you allocate time you like like
plan it out and you like make a
particular like oh this time how do you
spell particular
you know how to spell anything either
yeah you tell you spell it that's all
right literally okay wait what was it
yelling at Chris no shut up I have
another one let me defend no let me
defend let me defend I will we're not at
War I will agree yeah I did I will agree
with that delayed like the feeling like
I feel like I felt it once I leaned back
I will agree that the water is excessive
but I put chips in a bowl or a plate
because when you all right cool we don't
care next okay nickel asked for her oh
nickel nickel asked for help when in
reality he just wants my company so then
I'll go there and then sit there and
I'll have nothing to do to help him but
then he'll just like be mad Nick will
drop something in his room every single
[ __ ] night and I'll hear it from like
the kitchen or something like he'll go
upstairs but oh good night and I hear
like a smash like 20 minutes later too a
broom like what are you doing like and
then another thing I have is he can't
hang up anything on a wall properly like
whenever Nick put something on a wall it
has like a 48 hour limit until it's like
collapsing to the ground yep there was a
night where I was sleeping on the couch
and it [ __ ] she had a frame or
something and he hung up and it smashed
to the ground shattered broke [ __ ]
like three in the morning and I
facetimed him and he didn't answer so I
like ran upstairs because I thought he
like fell through his [ __ ] glass
shower door and was like gonna be naked
bloody and wet so
I ran up I ran up to his room to try to
help him so I literally thought like the
worst like I thought he like got like I
thought an FBI agent kicked through his
window and like was attacking him
upstairs and then I and then I don't
even know what happened I got it halfway
up the stairs you like called me back or
something but it was just insane there's
a red flag for Chris he never flushes
the toilet yes I've been way better now
you have been better but you always have
your own bathroom so you could go full
day and we didn't just don't know well I
don't use my own bathroom really because
my room's all the way downstairs yeah
you use mine he needs to go in a hot tub
or craves the feeling of one at least
one time every two weeks that's very
accurate and it's really annoying
especially when he craves at like three
in the morning it's like bro nobody
wants to like go hunt for a hot tub with
you literally that's fine
but I do really enjoy it I feel like
with the I was telling Nick the second I
go in a hot tub I feel like it unlocks a
new window his creative portal no
literally like I could I cut like I'll
go in a hot tub and just instant ideas
like so many new ideas okay I'm gonna
read a few off because I'm almost done
Matt will doordash every single meal and
force us to spend double the amount of
money for food when he won't drive and
then we end up having way too much money
spent in food when we could just be
reducing the cost by driving down the
street that's true and sometimes it's
good to go for the drive as well
whenever me and Nick need Matt's opinion
for a new idea or a new project he'll
wait till both of us express ours then
go oh yeah I agree oh oh it makes me
want to just drag them on like do you
know when like someone has like those
long conference tables and you want to
put you on the table and drag you across
and then throw you into the wall once
you're all the way like down like
yeah that just means I think you have
great opinions on things no because it's
just annoying because it's like we're
all and then he'll and then we'll do
something and fully format it and then
like an hour later and then like an hour
later we'll complain like we're like oh
yeah this is what we're gonna do we're
gonna move forward oh I agree and then
we move forward yeah I'm sure about that
Matt couldn't quickly accurately tell
you one favorite color when you ask
every single time I ask this
[ __ ] what his favorite color is
I don't know I don't have one I don't
know I don't know yes it is every single
time oh his favorite food his favorite
thing like simple ass questions he
doesn't have one or he doesn't know
right away like God forbid he makes new
friends like they ask you like this
simple like questions like oh like who
are your favorite music artist who
what's your favorite color I don't know
can't quickly tell you his answer to any
more way for me to answer and then go I
agree yeah like literally
um
another red flag where I'm at my last
one that I'm gonna share anyway is he
wants me protect not even creative but
is so easily distracted by his phone
like an iPad kid like the second he
opens his phone he's like sucked into
another dimension all right last one
last one about Matt for the rest of the
night because I have my last one the one
Clash of Clans crazy they're like dude
deploy me please let's go okay that was
great go Chris when Matt has a one good
idea you never hear the end of it for
the rest of time I came up with let's
trip yeah
I actually named Chris's brand but he's
not gonna say that that's not true no
you like are the first person to okay it
that's not true no he was the first
person to say it out loud because what
happened was
like togetherness because I was like
Matt my two logos are like a heart and
orange like what what's the [ __ ] yeah
when you think of orange he was like oh
fresh I was like what about a heart and
he's like love another oh fresh love and
he's like oh yeah this thing works out
well and I was like okay word like it
was more of like a team okay like he was
like hey your name should be this that
and I was like okay he wasn't like
pitched to you correct like Chris
listens to music at all times and even
if you don't want to and you tell him to
stop he never does but then he's
surprised if you're annoyed at the
volume listen Nick this is one of the
ones I wrote down Chris will play music
and jump and sing along with everyone in
the room until everyone has a headache
and then continue to do it yes but then
if yeah and then he's surprised when
people are upset okay
never go ahead is he'll pick an accent
or a character
and then not drop it for like three
hours like he'll pick like a British
accent that's the cartoon character and
then Chris is just embodies them for
three hours you can't get anything
[Music]
those are real good and very accurate
okay correct okay here's my my the music
like when I'm playing music I just feel
stuff I know you'll get on a table and
like take your shirt off that's okay
myself that's amazing yes but then after
when people like revert you out and
we're annoyed because we have headaches
you're like what's wrong like you guys
are annoying that's fine
just keep going I'm gonna start with my
green flags I have two each
um I have one each I have zero and I'm
gonna come up with it off the top of
mine okay
um if you go to Chris with any tiny like
um concept or something or like an idea
for a creative plan or whatever he'll
have it like a whole slideshow on how to
complete it in two minutes and then that
was good puts me onto a lot of good
music that's right wow those are awesome
for Christmas he knows oh we're gonna
like yeah we'll go Chris first gotcha
Chris knows what he wants in a sense of
like he will not let himself into a
situation where he will disappoint
himself or other people like if he feels
like he's gonna upset you by getting
into the situation he will not because
he already knows what the outcome's
gonna be
wow that was beautiful I feel very
honored right now all right Nick next
green flags we'll always order food at
restaurants and drive-throughs for
everyone and he will correct the waiter
if you if he made somebody else's food
wrong correct he'll let them know and
then he can make a good waffle okay but
I I don't I don't [ __ ] on the people
that work there I'm just like oh you
made a mistake yes yeah
Nick's a very good leader and can take
and can take control in a correct manner
all right
I said he's much more creative than he
thinks he is and claims that he can't do
certain things but he's definitely
capable of if he put like a little bit
more that was great yeah
Chris come on for Matt let me think Matt
you're always there when I need you oh
that's what I like that's it I need I
need to I need to show someone a new
song I'm going to Matt need to show
someone a new cool shirt I want she's
doing a mat we need to watch a TV show
with somebody I'm going to Matt you're
just like actually that one you're just
like the go-to guy I love TV shows you
know thank you you make yourself very
accessible to help me out well that was
Friday do the dance oh oh oh
yeah
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
[Music]