what's good [ __ ] gang [ __ ] gang I
thought that was a test for the mic like
I I didn't think that was a straight
video
Mar that was pure honest
reaction wow I'm surprised that
those Merry Christmas
I wanted this Donut for far too long we
caught your hand in the cookie jar
terrifying oh my
God and the time it took to just hit
record I finished that dut that's insane
that was less than a minute yeah you
breathe that thing in breathe me
in like the chemicals guys Merry [ __ ]
Christmas is the St triplets every
single year if you don't celebrate
Christmas it's still the season of
joy every single Christmas we've never
done a gift opening video ever never
have we ever done a gift exchange
because it's usually really personal and
it's like our parents are there
basically we're going to be this year me
Matt and Nick on each other gifts and
we're celebrating and doing a little
mini Christmas with me Matt and Nick
together before we go back home to
celebrate for our family but when this
video goes out Christmas is already
passed if you celebrate Christmas I hope
you had a good holiday with your
that's first gift and then we'll go home
and have our actual Christmas with our
parents and Santa if Chris is alive by
then I'm like in your burp bubble dude
get out of here freaky
freak
oh can we get the AC on in this [ __ ]
it's hot yes it's really hot oh my God
my eyes are burning nothing feels more
like Christmas spirit than like a glass
Coke the only way I could get more
Christmas if Sant was printed on it no
the polar bear with a hat I was going to
say if a polar bear came in here and
mauled us and just ripped us to shreds I
think I can start this off by giving you
guys something you you both really want
yeah wait hold on please tell me he's
oiling up what just kidding guys you
guys have to open them at the same time
but whatever if this is a
mow YouTu already own like 10 of these
yeah and now you have your very own of
me can you autograph it can you sweat on
it
what don't
shine that's a freaky request and I'm
going to poke it with needles and rub
its feet in its sleep I don't mind the
rubbing the feet in the sleep no like
tickle your feet tickle your
feet okay Dear Santa I want a million
reindeer I want carrots I want a tree I
want no one asked for carrots in a tree
those were a given I feel
I never seen someone ask for de S I want
Nick to shut up I want Matt to stop
talking about his ankle I have a gift
for Chris I have a gift for Chris move I
you I thought you going in the middle
you're opening the you want to sit on
your lap move the [ __ ] over a lot of my
gifts go together so I'm going to give
you guys a bunch of things at the same
time don't open anything yet okay don't
open don't open that
press don't open that and then Matt this
is you why is mine so much bigger hold
on this is for Chris but I'm going to
open it at the same time as you guys
open these because they all go together
really yeah you can open yours first
actually it's something you've been
wanting can you open it it's still in
yes open
it what okay
I know you guys don't really drink
coffee but I was like I should just get
them a curig cuz they've been wanting
one in the house I think so I got you
can I open mine so I got you a cure egg
okay this is a don't speak hold on okay
I'm listening yes like a amazing now we
own a curig okay a curig and a mug yep
and then Chris you can have this too
okay oh my God for the coffee
pods for the
curig we can put it all together and
it'll be awesome like Nick just got
himself a gift wait wait wait actually
wait I I all my intrusive thoughts are
telling me to throw this glass mug
across the room so somebody take it and
throw it across the room if this is if
this is kups Nick you're actually just
stupid why I completely agree like are
you dumb Nick this video is supposed to
be like good and like we're supposed to
get each other gifts I did get you guys
gifts
yeah I got the gift of you not
complaining that you don't have coffee
yet you guys sound ungrateful you should
be thankful this is a lot of money and
there's some people out there who don't
have yeah but we don't like coffee like
you got you're the only I haven't I've
never had I'm not the only person you
come on I I think thank yous are in
order I've never used a cure a day in my
life that was the worst Christmas gift
I've ever
gotten I'm never going to touch any of
these again the second they're there's
so much to be grateful for there's
nothing you got yourself a coffee
machine only thinge a coffee machine
it's like
a Matt you're actually going to break
something in house get this mug away
from me cuz I'll do it Matt what is this
a helicopter and it's a
Nick is this easy mac are these the
[ __ ]
nuts oh it's the Snicker doodle nuts you
sick free I saved them for you cuz I you
like them so much put these in the trash
no they're yours put them trash Take It
Easy Mac you love Easy Mac love easy two
times more it's a big cup best gift so
far oh my
God clean booty Shar whes what we're
number one in number
two clean booty sh
a in case you sh the word Shar is crazy
like I've never seen the word
Shar I've never seen the word shart on
like an actual like product you can buy
is this a prank no it's sh look at the
little cartoon ass on this it's in case
you shart yourself you can 10 stay fresh
after the surprise strip is literally
what it says with mud butt cleaning
technology to you Matt again
Ripple your closet space I need this I
have the smallest closet in the house it
turns your hanger into like multiple
hangers oh my God aren't you excited
yeah but my closet's going to be like
Nick it's just going to fall oh I didn't
think of that whatever be grateful maybe
here you go Nick all right it's my
favorite gift I got someone I think I'm
scared what is this
it's for
you it's little
costume I'm really
scared oh my go put it on God go put it
on Matt you want me to put this
on you said go put it on look at this
you don't like my gift this this is
horrifying get it away from my face this
look hor
shoulders oh my
God oh my God it's supposed to go
over Matt put it on no Chris you put it
on no you put it on it's your it on no
put it on no Nick hold on not on camera
perfect oh oh my
God here M come this
a calendar for the new year hunks in
trunks
yes you can have it I don't want this I
don't want this gay
calendar look
M you got me gay calendars open them oh
my God Matt we're on the same
wavelength this one's way more like
pornographic I no it's not
shirtless Cowboys 2025 we have a
collection M we I can't to countd down
the days with
you wait is this
firefighters this one's
exciting oh my God A Firefighter
Calendar a cowboy calendar and hunks and
Trunks we can eat which what's your pick
Chris I'm good you don't want one no I
like the shortless Cowboys one the most
sorry sorry sorry sorry I murder
him here you go Nick that's yours let's
see you freak nothing crazy who's that
this is for you Matt can I get it yeah
here it's a black mug if you fill it up
with warm water it reveals a secret oh
God should we set up the Cur guy for
this video probably okay
the candle that smells like bades
n perfect a b candle all right B smells
good it smells like caramel oh it smells
good yeah it's both of these nuts oh God
Chris here top one okay waa
Matt what is it what is this keep going
hold
on no way
and we can rollerblader on the city
together oh my God I haven't
rollerbladed in so long Matt used to
love rollerblading I still do love
roller BL wait this is awesome wow and
they're in our sizes and they got like
this they're sick black color D these
are hard these make up for the this
makes up for the coffee machine thanks
idiot fool who's the best big brother
ever yeah this one's for both of you
guys all right oh my God got some weight
to it it's like an Apple box with rocks
in it
nope is this a poker thing be careful be
careful why would you try to open it you
don't want it to blow up be careful blow
up yeah be careful I'm kidding a
grillin open it Grill art it says Idiot
grillin open
it it's that if we can get a new grill
we can have a bunch of Grill equipment
you b a grill equipment set before a
grill yeah it's just going to inspire us
I feel we want to start cooking at the
house more so I got us some Grill
equipment M Put The Knife Down this is
my favorite part we can do we can make
kebabs I've always wanted a
kebab I like that it's a briefcase you
really can mean business when you go
cook exactly you're going to look like
the coolest Grill in town here you go
Grill Master thank you Matt yep please
no more sh wipes come on let that crazy
out are these both for me mhm is this an
ice pack it's already freezing are you
serious yes just open it okay open it
freeze
it you wrapped a Kool-Aid
fresh yeah thanks you want a Kool-Aid
Jammer these are already in the fridge
Nick loves Kool-Aid it's freezing I was
like you just did this I was thirsty
that's why I did that and you are mad
that I actually got us a coffee machine
that you can make hot chocolate with and
you're wrapping me a Kool-Aid
Jammer I love Kool-Aid D like Kool-Aid
I'm going to jam it in
love KOA though I love
these what is it what is it sleep T yay
Nick sleep mouth T yeah burn these no as
you go to bed then that's my biggest red
I got them on Tik Tok shop did you
actually no oh my god get rid of it no
use it get rid of it are you dumb or
stupid I went to throw it that way it's
for you Nick it's it's for like to boost
your jawline
stop talking seriously it helps perfect
the Riz face this is disgusting put tape
on no put on yes Nick no Nick put it on
no
it's everybody thinks you're going to
wake up and be
like breedable this is my biggest red
flag ever if I Nick loves sleep tape
guys so that's I just imagine saying
good night to someone you're like in a
relationship with and then like them
being like okay good night and then like
taping their mouth shot for bed like are
we dead ass yeah it's cuz it's good for
you what the [ __ ] does this even
do [ __ ] stupid I can't believe you
can talk of it you can literally fully
move your round I can't
talk I don't think it does enough of
obstructing like I could still breathe
if I wanted to I wanted to fully
suffocate me oh my God yeah clearly
you're going to pass out this is stupid
stupidest invention and the stupidest
thing that people are falling for in 202
no it's you it's all yours it's mouth
tape it's trash it's a [ __ ] trash
filler this is for everyone he's oh it's
going to become a part of the family I
Matt is match it open it it's for
everybody if it's an orange cat stuffed
animal I'm going to L it's
not what is that what is it it's a
little bowl oh my God it's scar isn't he
so cute wait where's he from I don't
know I just thought of him I saw him and
he was like a little a little cow and he
looked like a big bull and he just
looked super cute he looks like you need
to find a home his name is Benson Benson
is that like off The Dome Bon the bull
okay isn't he cute I think he needs a
little bit of a brushing like he looks a
little um he came vum sealed than you
can kind of tell hey Merry
Christmas did I get the same thing open
it
up oh my God M I don't want any nieces
or nephews anytime soon I'd rather you
have these then and do I hear you're
welcome thank you man thanks
man his face face of me was
terrifying oh my god of course I opened
him like that jump scare part two he was
like this [ __ ] the other day we
went to Walgreens and I bought this cuz
he was
cute and I was sitting down at the
kitchen table and Matt put him on the
back of my seat like this and then said
my name so I turned around and locked
eyes with him and it terrified me oh my
and so the exact same thing just
happened again creepy [ __ ] dude I
regret buying him is this the
same no
way oh my god grow grow these are grow
capsules now I have to take a a bath
soon you're not supposed to B yeah you
put these in like the sink yeah no you
take a bath dude this is a bunch of them
Mt we can make a bunch of different
things
M wait wao wo they're all different Matt
thank you that's awesome what a blast
from the
past what is that one of a new
sweatshirt is this oh my God this is the
best gift ever is that wait is that new
sternol merch this is unreleased stolo
triplet December merch that dropped on
Christmas
wow Matt you're welcome I didn't know
you were that cool thank you so much
Matt of course I've never wanted
anything more on
Christmas if you want something like
this or similar go to story yellow.com
first link in the description below it's
for you guys from this is a really
thoughtful gift I thought that this
would help with your guys' brotherly
relationships in so many different ways
and help bring things possibly to the
next level it's a black box jewelry box
no it's better than
that okay it's Dungeons and dragon dice
are you serious no oh that was hype oh
it is Dungeons and dragon dice no it's
not what is it come on open open it open
it open it open it oh my God okay this
is a little crazy they're intimacy dice
toes
nipples
lips my
CHR it's a it's a vegetable
why do you guys think we cook you keep
getting it's just start cooking I'm
trying to I like this I like this energy
thank you m I like it yeah [ __ ] your
coffee maker exactly oh I need caffeine
and I'm going to be all unhealthy like a
little work we going to be e salads and
vegetables this isn't for salad oh I
hate that one the one with the the yeah
it has a slider no we can make cucumbers
though really
nice this one's for both of you okay I
feel like I can't contribute yeah you
can't
Big Brother no
way stupid no it's not
stupid let me see it's big brother
necklaces no it's not what is it one of
them says big brother oh hold on do you
want to say Big
Sister Big Brother little sister who's
the little sister who's the big brother
Matt's your big brother am I big brother
and little sister why the [ __ ] am I I
think it's so funny if you have a
necklace that says little sister I'm not
ever rocking this come on little sister
this was a I put a lot of thought into
this
song an HDMI cable just feel like you
never know when you need one of these
and next time you go to ask me oh Nick
we need an HTMI cable you have one now
that's a really thoughtful gift right
now next time you're setting something
up no questions asked you can just go
right to this I got this for I I liter I
legit don't know who this get this I
want it I want it I want it get it to me
little F what if that was like something
like no idea what's in there just crack
me up the Dome with it this one I put so
much thought in here what the [ __ ] is
that blueooth a Bluetooth headset a
Bluetooth headset with one ear yes like
it's like um I don't know what we would
use it for
but you can keep it it was like Prime
day or something
no look Mi saw 80% off and he's like
yeah
look it's a yogur
mat oh my God it's a yoga mat Chris what
is good with you you want to know so
good okay so this gift is cuz like I
know Matt's been wanting to do push-ups
and situps in the house so now he'll
have a comfortable place to do it why
doesn't smell like
fish and they smell bad they smell like
theep
I knew it
yeah I think it was just important that
we all had somewhere to like do
something to yoga it out yeah exactly I
might lay that lay that in my bed little
memory phone you
good giant Grandma underwear a super
cute are you dead ass wait put them on
no put them on put Giant yeah I love it
Chris can you put them on for us what
where's the front this is you put your
body in here and then you put your legs
down there all right here you go is it
also for me
yeah I love this game ren noodles yes
this is so you can you can eat those and
I'll eat my Easy Mac perfect oh my God
and I can make a
coffee I can feel it you don't know
oh yes a nice new polo shirt
ooh baby blue baby blue this is a nice
gift Nick of course wow one actual good
gift wow I don't really wear polos but
I'm going to give this a go actually
like the one polo I've been wanting
really I'm dead serious bow sniped it of
course I have no idea what this is
either
Legos wo you're right wait no I forgot
what I got you oh my god Matt that's
really good I like these isn't it cuz
it's like I like these it's Christmas
themed is it no it's not yeah this is
like a Christmas plant this one I put a
lot of thought into it I got I put a lot
of thoughts into this map this one
includes a special note as well that you
have to read before you really I know
what the last gift you got Chris is Matt
open it up and read the
note because in sick because I'm sick of
hearing it I'd rather look at it Merry
Christmas L CSE it's going to be a
sports gambling shirt oh we'll
see what does it say
man my ankle hurt
[Laughter]
[Applause]
I was picturing coming out of his room
in the morning with like a disgusted
look on his face face and that's a shirt
[Applause]
okay I just figured like now you don't
have to say it anymore I put a lot of
thought into that one I need you to wear
that mat out of the house every day my
did they sell a shirt that's no I had it
custom made oh my God even better
okay these I actually got you guys based
off of your
interests oh that's so nice I am [ __ ]
so excited for this song
what is it Chris T tell
us it is a Max action hunting series
archery set yeah and why is this
significant because when I was young I
took archery lessons really and I
actually had a whole Instagram account
for it really should we shout them out I
guess should we shout them out my uh my
plan is to that's more embarrassing for
me me I was dancing and stuff it was my
plan no I had a [ __ ]
Mohawk your your hair quiver I had a
quiver on oh my God yeah and this I
actually think this is just cool that's
kind of part of the reason why deers are
my favorite animals cuz I thought I I
liked archery and then I saw people like
killing and hunting deers I was like I
could never do that well in modern time
we use guns no one's really out there
with a bow and arrow anymore I know yes
they are like Hightech crossbows people
100% crossbows yeah but a bow yes Nick
like not like a yes people can use these
it's actually like the primary item of
what people use to H yeah scary if you
miss you don't scare the others wow I'm
amazing yeah then I saw I used to watch
videos on archery then it it led me down
like a Bad Rabbit Hole of like hunting
real animals and it made me really sad I
used to have everything I used to have
the arm guard dude so goofy and fun
don't call it goof here's the thing I
tried things as a kid I did gymnastics
ooh cool I played I did parkour I did
skateboarding I did archery I did hockey
I did soccer I did lacrosse I you paid
to jump off a ledge this one is a
trap what a trap yep and I should open
it yep I like that you had the headset
on this whole time I'm just waiting to
see if I hear anyone come
through I'm still not playing wait Paul
that's the coolest thing ever Nick Rupal
Monopoly Nick this is a double-edged
sword and you think that it would excite
me but all this does is anger me because
he's dangling a [ __ ] Berry in front
of my face that's what he's doing is it
your favorite Berry or just any Berry my
least no a good Berry but he's dangling
it off a cliff Chris Nick loves RuPaul's
Drag Race so much loves it so much won't
ever stop talking about it I cheated in
Monopoly when I was 12 years old and
Nick said if I was on my deathbed he
would never play a game with me ever
again and I've held that Grudge I've
held that Grudge successfully for 10
this is my only way back Nick this is
really cool if you guys will play this
I'll play even as a I think Matt has I I
will I think you've done it it's been 9
years it's been 9 years since we've
collected play Monopoly too look thank
you Matt this would be so fun we can
finally play monopo oh where's Chris I'm
a crab all right Matt we're going to
reveal what the mug
says I'm gay is that all it says watch
why is it so
low full rain yeah of
course I'm
gay that technology is
unbelievable see that hold on I'm like
trying to get the top of it hot it's
going to over it's going to overflow
it's going to
overflow dude really
mad good [ __ ] switch it out pH
dumbass I'm Do It For
Fun Matt you are the CU Pro that was
[ __ ] that was just a little dribble
too like that was legendary thank you so
much for watching this week's Friday
video we will be back at it next Friday
at 5:30 if you don't C celebrate
Christmas I hope you still enjoyed this
video and I hope you had a good holiday
season and enjoy the New Year cuz it's
going to be awesome spread some spread
some holiday cheer be nice and kind to
others it's the season of joy and hope
and and Merry and
mariness that was good man you going
[ __ ] throw make me throw up
thank thank you guys so much see you
guys next Friday at 5:30 where we're
going to light ourselves on fire oh jump
through a small oiled up ring time to do
that
[Music]