are you ready to get hooked up to the L
detector test Nicholas I don't think
I'll ever be ready but I'll say yes all
right let do
it and what you saying how you miss me
yeah you miss me and all the things that
we did to from the island M we had a lot
of plans but they
all why because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
saying would you like some water
he
[Music]
yeah the blood
monitor my base
here yeah it's like a seat belt but
new I like the little finger it's like
finger
mittens keep them nice and warm
are you ready to get into some of the
questions here
yes that's
true let's do it all right that's
perfect all
right we're getting deep right off the
bat would you're not going to ask me the
test question okay that was your test
question is your name Nicholas
yeah true why do you seem so like on
edge cuz I thought about what if today
Wednesday March 29th but I don't even
know
actually so
true is it yeah oh God okay are we
inside of a warehouse right now
yeah true okay are you ready for your
real
questions you're ridiculous
okay getting deep right off the bat
would you risk your life for one of your
brothers I was going to say that no it
was insane see I'm the worst you lit
went prob no probably
not true oh my guys listen let me that
is so you have to understand no you have
to understand my biggest fear is like
bleeding and like being injured that
like when I think of risk your life I
think of like getting hit by like a
sword right and I'm like honestly I know
that matter Chris love me so much that
they know that that's my biggest fear
that they'd rather get hit by the sword
than me so I'm just like no okay anyway
that's my next question do you think
Matt has good work ethic
no
true respectfully awesome thanks he knew
my answer yeah are you actually afraid
of birds
deathly yes true okay
yeah do you genuinely believe you're
always right yeah I do why okay my God I
I can't believe it but do I think it's
it's true now okay oh I see form the
question okay is there secrets that you
have that you won't tell me in M
no not that I think not that you think
see cuz like I don't
know okay the whole keeping my sexuality
secret forever kind of boggles with me
okay it boggles you're ridiculous oh my
God cuz like okay would you date someone
with the same name as me or Matt no at
least I try to not true yeah try to
avoid at all cost okay do you want to
relive your first kiss Nick
no
true do you have a favorite brother
crew that one I thought was going down I
did too have you kissed more than 10
people no oh my god wow true that let me
read some here you know what brother you
would want as a best man at your wedding
no why have you ever lied to us about
where you were going or what you were
doing no oh yes yeah
true wow that's crazy I think of like I
don't think I lied to you but I think I
might have told you I was going
somewhere and then like got in like the
car at Michaela in high school and like
she went somewhere before and I just
never updated you like I think it was
like lying maliciously but I do think I
told you I was going somewhere and I
didn't if needed would you give me your
kidney
no a li a deep down deep down he cares I
think it's more just because I'd say no
cuz I'd be too scared to go through that
like surgery but you would if it was
like if you really needed it but if you
could get a kidy from someone else I'd
be like yeah them first okay have you
ever had a boyfriend
yeah true
wonderful are do you think a good driver
yeah
why I just think everyone's a bad driver
cuz always scared that's just ridiculous
cuz I'm probably like the only person
that's J you around that hasn't gone to
a car accident do you actually like my
brand
for why
Wow I like
it have you ever eaten our food from the
fridge knowing it belonged to us no
look at the smirk on that face you know
this it's rumaging and ring is such a
great phrase to you use for Nick I
really rummage I kind of Stand By stand
at it for a good while and just eat okay
cool great have you ever cheated on
anybody
no
true nice have you ever said I love you
and you didn't mean it
yeah true I it's easier that way
sometimes there's no like way out of it
have you ever wished you were not a
triplet
no true I thought I answered it okay
great have you ever tried drinking or
smoking
no
true have you ever lied to Mom and Dad
yeah true usually see like a lot of the
time I lie it's like by accident so I do
remember like yeah I lie to them but it
was like I think you just use that as a
Divergent for a bigger situation no
there was like there's sometimes I lie
cuz like the truth is so far behind that
it's like you know it's like it's like
opening an 8mon wound it's like there's
really no point are you gay
yeah true yay I would you kiss a girl
yeah true I was thinking for like if I
was like in a show or
something not for any personal
benefit have you ever gone through mine
or Chris's phone
no true no need I don't want to see
anything on that
okay did you enjoy being on tour
yeah true do you feel closer to one of
your brothers
no
true I do think me and Matt argue more
but that's not the question that's not
do you you think I would be a better
boyfriend than
Chris
no true think he'd be pretty
even I think Chris is harder to get into
that situation but once he is I feel
like it's fair even even playing field
if you're both would be great that's
very kind than you do you think you
would be a good driver once you got your
license
no true that was a very that probably be
horrible driving would you confidently
let me search your phone
[Music]
no true that was a
m yeah i' let you like go through it if
you needed to but it's like sometimes
it's like I don't feel the need to go
through anyone's phone for any reason
good good point yeah few more
left would you feel bad turning on
someone who did you wrong yeah you oh no
no no God no I answer the question no I
wouldn't feel bad
true if you've already done me wrong
it's fair playing field you're getting
everything back at you full flames and
fire all right last one do you love me
more than Matt
no true oh beautiful great yes that was
the very last one you survived do you
feel good with your
answers yeah do you feel like an open
book yeah awesome I feel like his whole
demeanor changed once he was hooked up
to the tester what do you mean by that
like you just behave differently I agree
weird I feel we should really take
advantage of this moment I know that's
hooked up to a light test is your
birthday August 1st
yes true and are we actually triple
siblings
yes Pro great so we're on the same page
okay all right Chris you want to go
first ready do your brother's rude
comments in videos actually hurt your
feelings
yes that's a lie all right first lie of
the day wow explain yourself M
um no okay okay I just like I I feel
satisfied at least they know
now say we're sad at it's a m do you
actually think out of me Chris and you
that you have the best style
yes that's
true a crazy thought wow have you ever
actually eaten a tomato
no why thank you this kid claims that
he's never had a tomato and I've
witnessed him have like 50 tomatoes in
his whole entire life I've had tomato
related chooses to like forget it and
then it's like oh I didn't actually have
a tomato do you get jealous of your
brothers
no that's
true just proud
a nice thanks man yes do you think one
of your brothers makes better decisions
than the other one
yes true wow okay is that brother me
yes true so you personally Mato think
Chris stolo makes better qu or wait
better decision makes better decisions
than Nick yes I think that that's valid
wholeheartedly true wow you consider
yourself a lover boy
no that's nice true that's good I feel
like you got by with that one have you
ever read fanfiction outside of our
YouTube channel no no no no why why
why which ones I don't I don't save them
are any of them
like wait I previewed them outside of
our videos to try and find more content
not for
personal do you ever feel guilty for
your lack of work outside of our YouTube
channel it's a lie so you enjoy it you
enjoy playing games and doing nothing
all right have you ever had a girlfriend
matola
yes okay true did you enjoy being on
tour yes loved
it
true nice you have a best friend Nathan
yes love him to death we would you risk
your life for Nathan
guaranteed prove that's cute that was so
100% do you think we're the best
YouTubers on YouTube right now
yeah crew oh
wow stir answer do you believe that my
Pepsi addiction is out of hand
yes CW try to help them every day I
think we're all on that
page knowing person needs to be your did
you say that your mental health has
progressed in the in the past few months
yes true oh that's on the man of the
truth that's nice Matt spitting bars do
you think you could actually live on
Strictly chicken and rice yes chicken
and rice everything nice
crew love chicken chicken and rice
everything nice everything do you have a
favorite
brother
no true that's good thank God i' been
really disappointed in you you have an
older brother Justin is that true very
true
true do you think he's better at playing
video games than you
yeah true I really thought you'd say no
I really didn't think thought I think he
is do you love Trevor yes love that dog
true would you love him more if he was a
pug no
why wow that's like severe betrayal so
you would love our dog more if he wasn't
who he was that's not true that's it
literally just said it was a lie no yeah
um I have a I have a thing for pug pugs
mhm special place in my heart beautiful
this question I also put down I really
need the answer to do you think your
temper when it comes to Nick is quicker
than your temper when it comes to Chris
no why
okay like that we'll let that steep for
itself that that gets too angry at me
constantly you're just so easy to yell
at and if you ever deny this again I
have video updates now so that was good
whatever that was good yeah yeah that's
just information I need to bank and
I'll tucked away for the future you're
so
ridiculous have you ever hid anything
from us
no true that's awesome wow
congratulations M you really didn't lie
much