Home Depot
grass
Target
Ralphs yeah you miss me and all the
things that we did we said we going to
travel from the island to Madrid we had
a lot of plans but they
all why because that's some but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
saying nothing when I post it with other
[ __ ]
yes I saw that loaded up good morning
campers
welcome we are here we are ready it is
time for the camping inhouse 24-hour
challenge is that
what what is we just went to threee
stores and bought a ton of supplies
about $1,000 worth of stuff to camp
overnight in our living room I can't
believe this what my life is com it's
time to camp in the kitchen
camping in the kitchen it's got a ring
to it I love when things got rings to it
we'll be right back when the
electrifying Camp setup is
together confusing we got it what did
you say looks like a giant sting right I
was about to say that it looks like a
man oh Nick come on oh brother that's
your
duty duty it stays like that I think
that's in the way no it's not it's
supposed to it's the support come on
Nick it's like our supporters this is
you
guys Focus [ __ ] emotional talk we're
all one big tent you guys are the
support what type of knot did you do uh
okay just [ __ ] tie it no you [ __ ]
tie it what KN did you do the
fisherman's Loop nope what a boy scouts
a classic tent
knot got okay all right everyone after a
long after a long day of setting up the
sun is finally almost
set put the sun back on just a little
thanks um the sun is almost set we got
it just in time and now it's time to
feel like a flee on [ __ ] right now going
to go outside and scoop tons of dirt and
sticks and throw them in the tent well
we need to get fir with it I don't even
want a pillow I don't even want a
blanket I want pure grit and muscle to
get me through the night I know I don't
know where it went oh my God there's
smoke coming off that
thing is that supposed to happen I don't
know what the [ __ ] I don't want it to is
it still
smoking can you read up on this I shut
it off it's time for me to kick my boots
off so I don't walk all in our home with
my dirty shoes after a long day of work
and preparation take them
off what is
that it's a bear I'm taking my vest off
but that means no more hard labor
tonight okay no problem I'll ask you to
put it on before I ask you to do
anything else yeah you better okay you
know what I've done in this vest what
stories you and believe Maul a bear in
this vest killed the tiger with my bare
hands in this vest made one of the best
t-bone steaks ever in this vest I killed
the tiger took the meat rubbed sticks
together kill my Knuckles
blend I'm so hungry me too I want a hot
dog a hot dog I'm
starving oh my God you have to realize
that that chair was built in with 30 the
most sturdy chair ever I can use a drink
right now okay
drinks Nick almost fell through the
chair what' you get baby shark Pepsi
baby shark thermos Pepsi Cola Dr Pepper
Pokémon Dr Pepper Pokémon thank you
yep and the nipples oh look at the
little sippy got this suck okay there's
paper stupid thing hey don't litter in
the forest I'm pretty sure you're not
supposed
to add carbonated drinks to this m yeah
cuz I think the second you suck on the
straw it's going to be it's going to
squirt out yeah no I don't think that's
like what happens with carbonation I
think that like you just never get the
taste out of like anything but water out
of the thermos well guess what I don't
drink water cheers of
that you're supposed to use the thermos
[ __ ] be saying anything but
Theros the thermos Theros the Theros
theas in the forest where is the third
toas the third
toas my face I told you I told you what
did you do that it squirted closed it
I'm telling you dude it literally just
blasted all over me bro like my face is
soaking wet stupid
thermos you dumb [ __ ]
thermos my
couron hold the nipple reminds me of
when I was a
kid was
like when I was in Middle School I used
to have one of
these I was going to say
how young yeah that's insane y'all
hungry mhm hot dogs hot dog hot no I
need dude the windows open I mean
there's other campers I want all our
neighbors to know how [ __ ]
adventurous we
are I want them to walk by see the tents
and run okay hot dogs yeah let's um
let's get firewood and get the fire
going yeah let me put my thermos in the
co
welcome we got the fire started and now
we're going to get the [ __ ] hot dogs
and we're going to cook them up dude
where are the scissors Nick we don't
have
scissors where's the was that a was that
a bird I think we're just going to do
one dog slowly impale the dog yeah I
think we're going to do one dog even
though it's can do two we're not risking
it no no no no why cook two mediocre
dogs when you can cook one to Max
potential okay relaxed I want to see
your dance in that fire how do you know
it's done I'm going to shut this one off
you cook it till it's done there is no
time get that one oh wow wow that thing
burning that [ __ ] you burning your
Glizzy I knew that stuck my thermos in
there
oh did it squirt my thermos squirted all
over M that's like crazy that you
pointed it at
I'm in I'm in a different colored shirt
because my Theros shot on me
[ __ ] you're sleeping right there no I'm
not yep and I'm going to add some dirt
and mulch in it no one Clos the Theros
again so we can avoid
squirting I'm going to go get a leak to
seriously go put that in the sink cuz if
you're you're going to ruin this whole
video if you open it cuz I'm not
sleeping down here oh yeah
yes on my whole life I won't I'm not
going that close to you I'm not going to
I know you're not but it's going to
probably go
it's probably going to go this
far I told you I told you dry it off
holy [ __ ] you guys saw we got the what
are you sad about it tell them we cook
some hot dogs we cooked some hot dogs
and with the fireplace oh I'm stepping
in your [ __ ] thermos
spill it was technically your thermos no
it was Matt stupid idiotic spill what
are you scared of touching the dog no
real campfire [ __ ] you grip the dog and
you throw it in the pond I have the
mustard hold on dick all right what's
your favorite hold what's your favorite
okay what's your favorite summertime
activity M probably [ __ ] [ __ ] how
much is it GL you think you can eat one
bite okay probably the rest
this I Cana get the whole GL okay so
what's your favorite summertime activity
when you're not [ __ ] [ __ ]
I like to sit at the campfire okay with
some friends cook some s'mores I just
think it's like being out like the
feeling of Freedom with your
friends love night sky MH American food
M yep my favorite is just
driving down a long road that's ironic
but like with okay like you really don't
like that that's ironic for you cuz you
don't even have your driver I didn't say
it okay
whoa B alert someone call the fire call
Smokey the Bear [ __ ] I put an extra bun
feed it to feed it to the raccoons
yep away from Camp can't have them
interfere why does the camp counselor
quit his job why it was too
intense I like it all why didn't the
elephant hack for the camping
trip he had it all already in his trunk
oh my God
yeah you got it I don't know why you
yelled I couldn't believe
it is that
skunk oh my God oh my God a skunk in the
tent it smells like
skunk so what's your camp counselor name
mine yeah let me read it like your C you
made a cam yeah W KGW a o
h we killed Grizzlies with our own hands
what's the wonder where kids camp
nowadays Best Buy waiting for the new
Call of Duty when I was a teen I would
be outside in the wilderness surrounded
by
logs
dirt and the peaceful energy of mother
God bear and black bears don't fight
what do they do
run at least for
[Laughter]
me a chrisly see sees me and they act up
you know most of the time people see a
grizly bear and oh you got to get big
you got to get tall scare them
away that's what they do to me I
go God you guys hear that there's
another skunk
coming all right s'mores let's see if my
machine doesn't smoke up this time I
think it will I've had her since
1984 we just don't cook
it's not hot I was scared it was is it
really not how you going to react oh
yeah all that because then it's not even
hot oh the top is the top is
okay just leave it just leave
it this is unreal this thing actually
works really well what the s'more cooker
yeah yeah I know look at my golden brown
marshmallow I'm a little in shock right
now yep I told you had her for
years sick she never let me down
marshmallow I trust this more cooker
more than I trust most of the women I've
been with okay that's like always the
old timey line you know what I mean yeah
like she doesn't fail me like you're
will never run
out here I think I should tell a little
Campfire story
oo yeah chill out no leave it on just
don't let it
smoke the kid fing in the back of the
classroom when we were growing up we
would go to Maine for Labor Day with our
godmother and everyone and there was a
big fire pit someone smoking it's Chris
and there was a big fire pit you're
smoking and we would always make s'mores
at night with the fire P dude guys I'm
scared Nick it's fine what is just the
world the longest story ever well I'm
being interrupted anyway Nick got a
marshmallow and
[Applause]
it I wasn't looking Nick got a
marshmallow and it was on
fire and he was on fire and he hit me in
the face with it and I got a third
degree burn on my face did you make up
the degree or is that what the doctor
told you he didn't go to the doctor oh
told you you made it up yeah I make it
I'm
smoking wow
if someone edits that I'm going to lose
my mind look at that
SW sweet
baby I'm going to be the person to eat
this for in the house you're way too
excited right now no I'm not I'm just
eager
excited you slid right past me he set
that up without either one of us see it
that was sneaky with the most Grizzlies
I've seen in my day fcking
you move like a serpent in the grass big
fire oh my God guys what that's like us
what chocolate marshmallow and gr
cracker what was your favorite activity
of the night tonight mhm I don't
know I enjoyed hanging around the
campfire mine's being with you
guys should we go get our sleeping gear
I think so I'm tired all right we've
eaten our food we've done our camp
activities for the night it's time to go
to bed I'm going to really embody the
camp mentality I'm not even going to
brush my teeth E I can't what the floor
it hurts no it does hurt a lot it hurts
more than every Grizzly I've ever fought
it is really like
hard I'm going in my
room you have to stay here no I oh God
it's just knowing how close my bed is
good night everyone I'm going to go up
to my bed thanks for joining us for
camping if you want to have us bring one
of your favorite influencers camping
with us let them know we're going to run
some camping in the future also if you
want us to go camping again also let us
know we can camp again for you guys and
I really enjoy maybe actually sleep in
the tents I don't think I can sleep in
I'm not I don't know
I think we should try like like camping
where like glamorized camping oh yeah
bro I know you're pump I want a
temperic sleeping bag no I want to just
face every Big Challenge see
H it's easier to be real camping because
you have like the soft grass under you
right now we got floor
backs well I'm going to my room see I
think what it is for me is I can't feel
the wind no twigs and mud it's almost
too comfortable right now I want the
challenge of the pure Wilderness goodbye
everyone see you next Wednesday and this
Friday we going to travel from the
island to Madrid we had a lot of plans
but they alled
cuz of some but it's okay cuz I'm moving
different don't be saying nothing when I
PST up with other [ __ ] P for my
brothers