that was in the chat
why am I echoing because you're [ __ ]
screaming hey guys welcome back to hey
guys welcome back to another Wednesday
video today we're playing fortnite and
we're gonna see if we could drop 20
kills as a trio and win the game
is that the overall challenge that's the
goal yeah [ __ ] um looks like I'll have
to put up like 15.
shut up guys
oh why did I jump what yeah what what an
idiot I am I'm like a decade away from
Mega City Nick looks like we're gonna
have to carry at the beginning here like
what an idiotic move terrible well no
it's an idiotic move
what no never mind it took too long I
want to know I don't at all
one two three four four people that I
see gliding in with us here I thought
you were just counting and I'm like
what's the point of this I have a shield
keg if anyone would like to keg together
one too we'll bathe in the blue juice of
God
you're insane by the way if you have no
kills yet
none
we gotta push some people
[ __ ] [ __ ]
that's gonna help there's a kid up here
there's a kid up here dude dick I'll get
him
I'm up
is he up up or is he down down
where right there
help me Nick
I got him I got him I got him
he's dead let's get Chris's reboot card
Nick's asking Who's Who and Chris is
literally a card on the ground like no I
was confused who he was telling that
they were right there there hold on let
me I'm spectating I was always expecting
dude we have one kill there's a kid
right near you
puppet shooting make it back and get
back in
dude
in for a big tree I have an idea
back three white nick so we shoot not
yes
let's [ __ ] go Matt that was me that
was me Nick you have no kills bro
Chris Chris Chris
here we go baby
I miss you Fred the bunny is back
oh that's so cute
meow
that's crazy
snipe that hoe
um for those of you who are viewers that
don't know how to play fortnite or don't
know what's going on those henchmen drop
a gold card which leads to the Vault
Matt is at right now
which you can bet open there's a bunch
of good stuff to help you win the game
yeah but you gotta kill the henchman to
access it brief intermission for what
we're at I'm at three I'm at one but
zero
sniped one
not he's the worst he's the worst he's
the worst
not dead terrible nice
no one left oh I'm about a [ __ ]
where is he at oh oh
my kill nice work
you need to get we need 13 more we got
it we got it bro I wonder what like a
chill pot tastes like
probably Pepsi honestly no it's probably
like blue Gatorade
ew that's like the worst am I right in
the car it was right in a car this way
you're driving over that bridge see them
I see someone right there right in front
of me
knock them DJ honey bun see you later
oh my dear great Heavens I'm behind them
right in front of you
50 white pushing I'm getting in almost
kid I'm getting in on him
who's your Daddy come here buddy what
God
gosh I got him like in a tree that isn't
actually there okay other kid near me
50. she's a baby I'm on his ass like
[ __ ] ants had a picnic I'm coming
after you
where is he I don't see him where'd he
go cause the neighbors are gonna think
they're dying in front of me no is he
I'm Matt [ __ ] [ __ ] I just took like
80 million trillion fall damage trying
to chase this kid
let's go buddy you're weak
see uh hit the ground
where is he Chris more kids more kids
driving over
no in my box Chris I need help need help
me help me help me help me
Chris get him get him get him get him
yes I just got killed by [ __ ] Santa
Claus
I gotta move
Santa
no
because she had a clutch where's clutch
it
oh there's more kids gliding in just one
more one more
oh
Santa's down where is this kid
where is he he's in the water
oh my dear great heavens
no oh [ __ ]
[Laughter]
I thought I was totally falling to death
he's terrible
so mad Chris
freak out freak out thank you push it
get him nice he's gonna do
is this Santa again it's Santa
Chris grab a legendary slur please
you're making me nervous
good job
[ __ ]
there you go
I hate talking I get scared
yes Chris
oh great then
I almost said great Betty but I didn't
know who Betty was
oh [ __ ]
see y'all set the [ __ ] finish him come
on guys finish him good shoot
oh real careful my friend
I Believe In You Chris I trusted did
someone just reboot right here they
rebooted at the one in the storm
steps in front of me
thanks Chris
he's so bad Chris you got it
you got him Chris he's in your books
[ __ ]
Chris get over there
I'm so scared how many kills we have we
have 16. oh my God it's so possible
sit down sit down
you're crazy Chris go to the booth go to
the boat
please run
no Chris don't know
oh we need to kill everyone I think
oh and we need to kill everyone left in
the game I think
oh my God I can't
you could have
Chris
[Music]
no
okay try again
this is it this is the game I'm feeling
it in my bones let's go
why did the chicken go to Mega City
to [ __ ] kill people
bro I'm trying to become a fortnite
YouTube channel [ __ ] car videos I was
gonna say to lay an egg but that's cool
oh buddy oh don't you regret that
decision oh [ __ ] I'm dead Chris
call damage fall damage fall damage fall
damage now I'm down here on the balcony
oh my God
who's your daddy
Matt come on bro don't say weird [ __ ]
we should be a good boy and let me
revive you all right what are you saying
right there
yes oh there's a kid on me where
I don't know but he's on me in the
street
in the tree in the street kill them
one in front of me
we're coming
literally almost got killed by anime
got him
victory
oh Footsteps in front of me right here
in the street
there [ __ ] this building go Nick
go
go oh he's coming back to you Matt
what he pushed me
he's so good at the game bad he's dead
are we kidding the window
right in front of me Chris up 46 18
.
oh my God I'm weak
bro another one Heavens dude
right below me
the [ __ ] did he go
I don't know
good job help me save me
please
um shots um West West
275.
I'm camping out right next to the entry
right now
I don't see us oh my good God
Rose
ah what are you are you killing henchmen
dude yeah all right let's make that note
inside I'm like pushing on them because
I'm thinking they're on him
where is he on this Ruth I'm pushing off
get up there
dear great Heavens he's so [ __ ] weak
oh I'm dead
Nick Nick it's all your fault Nick
that's crazy where did I go
so [ __ ] bad
where are you I'm Reviving Chris he fell
onto the ground because he's an idiot
oh he's gonna kill me
Nick what are you doing knocked him
um Reviving you
you're welcome is a better thing to say
no you need to just build next time I'm
not even happy I'm up right now
I'm pushing I'm pushing these kids are
mine
come here kid get over here you're dead
where's your friend
you're dead no
what the [ __ ]
oh
dead oh
my God
the storm's coming
oh shots to my left oh
knocked on knocked one knocked one push
up push up my shot push up push up I put
myself in a cone [ __ ] egg launching
he picked him up
no
get my get my kill back
oh yeah
no
he's going up
come here kid come here you're terrible
you're terrible I'm carrying I'm
carrying you I'm carrying I'm carrying
over in front of me
hundred
yes Chris oh my God
back up
he's one shot dude I'm so scared
oh another kid where the [ __ ] is the
lizard I want him right here Chris
he's going up I just got sniper
headshotted oh my God
but I got killed almost okay box up
please where the [ __ ] is a blizzard
lizard's on me Chris
lizard's dead I got [ __ ] on me I need
help just beam Goku littering his big
[ __ ] yellow mullet
somebody help me no
I'm with you I'm with you
we gotta back up and Survey the area
there's a lot of kids here oh [ __ ] right
here oh see you later
oh no I just got snipered
right there it's Goku
another kid
on my wall Chris
I need help
got him shotgun save me save me save me
save me save me save me Shut the [ __ ] up
you sound like Spy Kids right now you
know I'm crawling in from help us save
us I don't know I know what he means
I don't know oh my God
we have 16 kills we can do this we can
do this we can do this they just came to
get up there go go go go go go go go go
go
going straight in probably a bad move oh
my God I don't know if I'm gonna make it
to that
you have to they just washed off
not all of them nope hit one the more
kids zipping up [ __ ] we're Dooms there's
a lot of [ __ ] going on Mario
what do you mean get up stop fighting
down there and come up here
I was already dead
man I hit a majilian hit him a Jillian
literally a Jillian I'm about to sneak
up on his little [ __ ] ass
and I did and there he goes down
another kid right here 130. we Chris
got him dead
oh my God we need one more kill Chris we
can take it slow take it slow
Matt you cannot count
we're at 19 are we not team Nick oh I
can't count look at that idiot no we
can't run through it yeah we can it'll
alert hold on right here zip lining
oh if I hit that I would have pissed
myself
we are going where to the reboot fan
I thought you're pushing the kid I'm
like on him
Matt this is probably a bad decision I
agree
wait did you just not kill this kid no I
didn't don't make me regret that dick
don't make me regret that did that kid
did he get sniped oh my God he did I see
them I was about to kill somebody and I
kill got stolen from these kids with
snipers over there
they're Katana over in that sniper
oh 120
oh my God
knocked one
should I add glittery to play if you
wanted to kick it with the big guys
you [ __ ] loser
oh my God hit the other one funny push
push push push push push push I want you
to push like a nine month pregnant woman
push
uh
95 almost
not
no I hit him
no I'm not I'm not
stay safe Chris get up please don't die
on me I need you
knock on
crack the last one
Chris
oh
right here right here right here right
here Chris you have to win
popping [ __ ] right here on this
[ __ ] loser [ __ ] you
oh my God I'm so scared
Nick you have no reason to be scared
unless I am and I'm [ __ ]
yes yes yes yes
come on Chris please
no
right here Chris he's low he's down low
I have a legendary slurp if you if you
want me to
yes
[Music]
yes Chris yes
and we got
23.
[Music]
nice work
and we got 23 kills I did nothing to
help but
nice work
bro that hey
I want to talk about my final gameplay
so go ahead
I thought there was one kid left and
there was actually two so I like like I
knocked one of those kids and like
almost celebrated because I thought we
won and then and then I realized there
was still one left I was like oh [ __ ]
and then I like dropped all the way down
and I thought for sure he was gonna be
in like a full box so I dropped out with
my heavy sniper and literally shot a no
scope like right in front of the kid as
he pumps me for like 180 probably I saw
that oh my God so that I built a wall
and then I felt safe enough to edit and
try to kill it was crazy but that [ __ ]
was [ __ ] hilarious all right guys
that has been this video we got our
Victory Royale with 20 kills as a trio
let us know what you want as the next
goal for the next fortnite video if we
ever do one or if you want us to just do
the exact same goal again but it's in
adios and see you later from fresh love
disco Ruben to math the Munch and we
will talk to you soon