as if the events of my life in the past
few weeks have not been stressful enough
we're going to torment ourselves For
Your Entertainment
you missed
did you say I know what you're saying
how you miss me yeah you
Yeah
[Music]
so basically
basically we have this here
fun wheel that we've yet to use that we
said we're gonna use but today came in
perfect
what I was gonna say perfect handy but
that's like perfect time perfect time to
use it we have
we have 14 slots on this I think one of
them is positive and the one is spin
again oh none of them are positive and
they're all punishments and we're gonna
take turns spinning this wheel until
every single the wheel of two
every single punishment has been cleared
off spin it I start unfortunately until
every single one is cleared off correct
spell oh [ __ ]
oh Lord
It's gotta be the easiest
okay
yes okay
I was gonna say chugging time Ready set
go oh you better make it worth it chuck
chuck
Chuck
this is oh my God come on
if you get more than a minute you're an
embarrassment
go go go go go John John John I can put
a gallon of milk faster
shut up
drink
good that was faster than you did in
that one video 30 seconds I don't see
Chris let's see the timer
good 37 seconds
all right Pepsi complete
whoa now
please be the
what's for water for a week yes
yes yes
Loki just did that last week yeah that's
my first soda all right today's
Wednesday the video is coming out and um
Matt cannot drink soda until the next
Wednesday video comes out
wow
clean Nick's dirty ass room yeah
yeah
yes let's go so I got a bunch of trash
here on the stairs that I need up there
damn that's right that's right I don't
know that's the stairs
wow it's dirty in here
there's no [ __ ] anyway
[ __ ] gumball machine
all right that's gonna go in the hallway
thanks
you can help no okay and then yes what
are these
um one of them's fully recycled because
it's empty the other one has shoes in it
well while Chris does this I'm gonna
just put the camera down for a minute so
what have you done
put all your dirty clothes in the closet
in the laundry
it already looks a little bit better
yeah let's make the bed next
let's get some [ __ ] manners in that
system how about a please you're lucky
the wheel gave you the [ __ ]
day off hey let's just move like the
problem oh is this yours oh that was
Stevie oh
no it's not it's way too all right just
keep cleaning be right back yes super
clean
all right
okay let's go back to the wheel
boom boom boom boom you can see me in
the reflection of the wheel
lucky duck that's not lucky
[Music]
post any embarrassing pic of you
Brothers Pick yes
yes you do almost passed out holding my
breath for so long
that's it
that's so important like a laugh ing no
no that's [ __ ] almost passed out
here's the thing people are gonna see
this
[Music]
it took me to post this I held my breath
perfect share
oh my God posted that's [ __ ]
atrocious okay
wow that was a great thing I was so
excited
again oh you wanted an X that's the best
thing because X is the best thing okay
Matt's safe
stop you're altering my skin
I don't play these games
ready whip for 30 seconds yeah
[Music]
oh God
we should have bought a new ready yeah
we're out
ten more seconds
honestly I think I think this is enough
that was more offensive than [ __ ] if
I got foam for 30 seconds I just got the
wasted whip
[ __ ]
[Music]
others post on your Instagram story yes
okay it's a mirror selfie that matters
before we went to the scream event but
I'm gonna write a caption no just went
to the scream event didn't scream one
[ __ ] time the movie was 10 out of 10.
but do I look like the type of guy to
get [ __ ] scared no that's terrible
that's good that's
that's terrible that's funny that is
terrible and then I'm gonna assume the
confidence is like insane
please give me one other option I can
pick okay yeah no because you have to go
equally as harsh as I did because
so you guys heard Nick's idea so now I'm
gonna say I'm gonna say mine and you
have to pick one of the two yeah we're
gonna go with this photo from tomorrow
oh no Matt and his bunk from the [ __ ] me
Matt and his bunk on tour
and we're gonna go
just found this pick
from the film
camera
why so direct hold on from the film
camera and I'm gonna spell camera wrong
on purpose no c-a-m-r-a F feeling very
vintage vibes
#Hashtag 80s
which one's worse you can explain
yourself when the video comes out dude I
just realized I found variety whip all
over my pants
um yeah you can post that one but can
you spell camera right okay in
negotiation
I would have like oh no I dropped this
for behind you're posting mine tomorrow
when the video comes out I look like 100
from each brother
[Music]
you can't get any worse than this yeah
thank you God I just came up on 200.
what do you mean there's one up spin
again oh
[Laughter]
bro it just did I know that but just
making sure that that's a rule I don't
want to see no half-assed oh yeah
absolutely
no good
[Laughter]
Brothers pick outfits for a week yes
okay we're gonna do daily Nick outfit
checks yes yes 5 30 P.M
California time for the next week
we're enemies so the wheel of Doom is
over okay you don't sit again oh he went
on actually wait you know it counts yeah
for real we're not listening okay stupid
pouty face that I'm gonna see in the
Attic oh he was so cute when you walked
by oh my God
don't pamper my spin I didn't
DM anyone on your account oh my God oh
my God I have a good idea I give you
your phone I don't actually have a good
idea but I'm excited to look we are
gonna go with Nathan thank God we're
gonna say
I'm screen recordings to send this to me
hey Nathan
dot dot dot
I just watched a movie
Dot
that doesn't matter though
holding things down
in Boston I hope
I really hope nothing bad happens
nothing nothing
happens backspace backspace backspace
what do you have Nate be like bro I just
watched scream like actually let me know
if you need any help make it no no he's
really like no hey Nathan I just watched
a movie that doesn't matter though
holding down in Boston I hope I really
hope nothing bad happens that sure would
be a shame this isn't insane I have to
poop
God text me and then
and then I'll do fresh love with orange
emotions
[Music]
foreign
again yeah 100 push-ups Jesus Christ
one two three four five six
seven
eight
nine ten eleven twelve count on Rhythm
eleven I'm at 11.
12.
okay
25 for now he'll do the rest in a minute
well nice job
spin again
[Music]
nice
oh
thank you Jesus
[Music]
nice
oh
what do you want to do first 75 push-ups
for the ride
okay
only 60 more that's not bad of course I
land on that
land on every negative [ __ ] thing
well they're all negative shut up okay
good job shut up no no no no they'll all
be on camera okay nevermind
Matt
oh my God
so I suggest the egg before the mountain
I agree
I hate this week to myself ready whip
all over me well like I'm confused why
you keep saying that as if like that's
not obvious I'm just clarifying for the
viewers can I do a 30 second plank
instead yeah I honestly a lot of that
but your butt has me lower
28 29 30. yay
I'm so proud of you I'm so itchy last
punishment I'm so itchy bro that's
[ __ ] stupid thingies last punishment
is eat a french fry with ketchup but
that's only really a punishment for me
and Chris here because me yeah this is
honestly the probably the worst one on
this whole thing again for now yeah I
can't do it that's why I'm very scared
oh literally cried
okay
[Music]
yes
yes yes
oh my God yes
yes
I don't think I've ever seen that eat
ketchup in my life oh my God
what are we pick your poison basically
Chris has two punishments I only have
one so I think I should do the um
intermission in between mirrors I'm
going right away
right after another right away
are you sniffing in an empty Pepsi can
stop
yes that's exactly
all the good sweets well at least check
if this is pasteurized
[Laughter]
do it for the fans bubbling up dude for
the podcast
come on Matt stops
thank you
mouthwash challenge 30 seconds let me
start a stopwatch oh my God you're at
like 10. we'll give you a 10. hold on
yeah 20 seconds to go keep going keep
going without listery keep going
you gotta keep going you got 10 more
seconds
five
drink it
yes what a crazy consumption of food
holy [ __ ] oh I forgot
how do you throw away an egg
I don't know maybe we should go get it
that's cheating okay what do you do
[Music]
well Chris is done with his punishment
let's put the amount on
here this is no no this is Matt's anime
one drag yes
oh my God camera's gonna die you gotta
move quick I can't you got this
it ain't no egg brother
here you can even dull The Taste here's
a bigger french fry that you can like
put with it you know I feel like I feel
like I'm going pale like come on come on
here this will make it better I swear to
God the more food you add the less
ketchupy taste
you have to go quick the camera's gonna
die okay I have to hold my nose do it
you got this Matt it's literally I can't
it's just a wet french fry ten no no no
it's gonna get on your finger so hurry
you get me a couple mouthwash for after
it's right there I'm not you put that in
your mouth hurry up we're at 10 the
camera's gonna die
swallow follow it swallow it swallow it
swallow it swallow it swallow it
yummy ketchup
I'm gonna go crying
don't do that six years in his eyes is
unreal
oh yeah
good night everyone I'm going to bed as
the triplet that's most capable of
holding a conversation right now I'm
just gonna out for the video and say
thank you guys for watching and also if
you want us to use the wheel more often
we will you try to let us know what to
do then if you want a part two of us
torturing ourselves let us know we can
do more creative punishments so I'll
post an Instagram story eventually about
hey well more punishments do you want to
see from us but thank you for watching
thank you for seeing us toward ourselves
and we're excited to use the wheel more
and make more videos for you guys and I
love you all and so do Matt and Chris
and we will see you soon
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things