hey guys welcome back to the serial
triplets Friday videos
Matt was on the roof
that's actually really cool
I'm gonna close this though because
we're definitely gonna scream
I know what you're saying how you missed
me yeah you missed me and all the things
that we
the trouble
but it's okay
bro what do you think the strongest
animal is
oh
I feel like a good healthy gorilla is
not [ __ ] around we've talked about
this yeah like we've already talked
about this no lists like top five top
five strongest animals ready to go
elephant elephant elephants elephants
getting stomped on by an elephant
giraffe okay I know no you're just
listening big animals
giraffes in the wild if like three lions
were attacking a giraffe oh it's [ __ ]
their legs are so strong that if they
like kick the line to stop it it could
break its spinal cord with like one kick
you know I feel like bugs don't really
count
bugs aren't strong I know I'm just
saying as animals like bugs don't really
count for me
no you know when people are like people
I don't know like what's the most
populated animal and they gotta try to
throw like oh my Ants it's like
come on ants don't count what's like the
really that's absolutely no like but I
think of animals like bugs are on the
last of my phone I'm just gonna let you
I don't know yeah no it's like when they
throw bugs in the mix and it's like you
just want the statistics about the big
animals
sorry
I'm confused because bugs are random no
no no it's like world's strongest
animals
world's strongest animals and it's like
an ant can carry like 80 of its body
weight
it's an ant obviously we don't care
they're small like I want the big strong
animals like when it's like top 10
strongest I feel like bugs should be
excluded I completely disagree that's
insane would you not be more shocked to
find out that like ants are stronger
than like animals you might think are
stronger
but it's like the comparison the
comparison of strength is just stupid
it's like oh Nance real strong it can
carry 80 percent of his body weight but
I can kill it it doesn't really you're
not that strong I got it I got it it's
like strength of perception
sure if everyone it's like an ant that's
that big like the size of an ant it can
carry 80 of its body weight but you
could not do that so that why that's why
that's impressive because but the ant is
strong at the end of the day you can
still step up damn stronger than me but
he's a little [ __ ]
whatever I don't know it's two different
like whatever next topic let's go it's
two different categories what's your top
five strongest animals I feel like a
good healthy this word we haven't even
introduced I know the meat and potatoes
we were in an arcade tonight right okay
the skill crane with like the candy in
it yeah had me thinking how long has
this candy been in here so long and I
saw a worker watch us playing it and
like generally like look a little like
really like he knew that the candy in
that machine probably I had a tootsie
Rollie
how often did Tootsie Rolls expire
that's what I'm saying but that's just
stuff what am I eating Tootsie Roll
what's what am I eating anyway that's a
great question you know what are the
main components of it maybe one
ingredient beside sugar of a Tootsie
Roll
you're telling me it's a Tootsie Roll
with no Tootsie the [ __ ] going on that
was like me how I usually yell but I
just said speaking but you know yeah I
was like the guy said it yeah but like
dude like tootsie roll like that's such
a weird one like what am I eating that's
true like a like a Blow Pop I know what
I'm getting into I feel like you really
still don't what sugar the gum like it's
like it's just kind of like so you know
one yeah it's gum in the middle no but
like like lollipops make sense to me
it's like the crystallite like it's like
a kind of like a rock candy like it's
crystallized sugar essentially is but
all right
I mean honestly lollipops and like rock
candy that's all just sugar but like in
a different format of sugar Chris listen
it's like an upgraded I hate when Chris
is in I'm being so for real I'm not in a
mode what is Tootsie Nick give me one
ingredient of Tootsie [ __ ] rolls
Google it no I don't even care like I
don't
like grow up I have to pee oh my God I
just sneezed and it hurts what is it a
Tootsie Roll oh yeah available in many
popular sizes and varieties oh my God
no nothing outside you saying that made
me remember do you remember the long
thick Tootsie Rolls like the [ __ ]
fatty thick ones oh god dude I haven't
seen a fake Tootsie Roll in a while hold
on I missed those Sugar Sugar
corn sugar sugar corn syrup palm oil
condensed skim milk cocoa
um I don't know what that is whey
do you know soy artificial and natural
flavors oh it's all fake it's all bad
stuff for you Tootsie Pop It just be
called unhealthy okay but imagine going
to like the local CVS to like say
trick-or-treatings coming around I don't
know why I didn't just say Halloween
that was so bizarre
Halloween's coming around and like you
need to buy candy for the
trick-or-treaters and you buy like the
variety pack Tootsie Rolls yeah you're
the worst [ __ ] person ever no it's at
least it's not toothbrushes no remember
that lady that was just giving out
individual candy corn like you like it
was like oh my God I just had to take a
handful of candy that was scary I didn't
take anything so they're getting like
recalled candy corn I'm pretty sure
they're like like really bad for you
like like
terrible let's search it up I'm pretty
sure Candy Corn like you should not be
[ __ ] with candy corn I love candy
corn oh me too it's great delicious
better than Tootsie
I'm just thinking of like candy corn
though it's still suss
candy version of a corn
plastic container and a market it's not
about the Candy Corn it's not the
plastic packaging whatever either way
I'm not really it has nothing to do with
the container you know and they're like
hey salad leak or like don't mess with
lettuce for a little bit I'm not gonna
have any lettuce I'm sorry I'm not gonna
get like I'm not gonna risk it rate the
different flavors of Tootsie Rolls are
we gonna get into like a different topic
or I don't know yellow yellow is good
Blue Blues are no so good the blue is
like the white though when you open it
right I never understood the cream is
the blue toads are all open the
Bluetooth opens into a white Tootsie
Roll yeah make it make sense the blue
packaging when you open it it's white
the white Tootsie yes you know this you
know it's blue no it's white no there's
like a blue and white and then there's a
blue blue
yeah there's like a neon green Tootsie
Roll wow okay so it's blue but it's
vanilla flavored yeah what who the [ __ ]
did that oh blue vanilla
I love blue vanilla who made Tootsie
Rolls we could make them I'd rather just
buy them seems like a hassle oh that's
me that's me go down where right there
okay I actually thought it's been a
while and we haven't even talked about
what the actual topic of sorry I kind of
that was my so we're gonna get into it
today oh you wanna know I have a really
bad habit I have to admit it to the to
the camera first every single time we've
drove by something that has like letters
I've been like just making up like the
phrase in my head I don't even know like
like the car for us has like a sticker
that says UD
and I just was like oh under diapers
like in my head I just I just Associated
to two words like this license plate is
seven rhww don't read the whole thing
let him be no I'm not gonna die
okay
I put like seven riding horses wild okay
seven riding horses while
and then that's it seven yeah so you
just made not gonna read the whole thing
you just make up little story yeah but
like it's so much cooler when there's
like an and a c or like an m and a CM oh
my God Matt and Chris like there was a
building yeah and it was like it was
like MC Plumbing or something and I was
like oh my God Matt and Chris it was
just a cool moment I don't know I don't
know why I do it okay siblings or dating
is gonna be the second part of this
video so welcome
um
they haven't really updated their
account like at all since the last time
they've only posted six more photos what
since that last video because I think
they kind of gave up on their account
like when we looked that's so sad
remember this is the last one we saw
yeah yeah I don't even know right I
don't oh I remember they're dating
first one
oh
I think they look nothing alike
yeah I agree but so that's gonna throw
the wrench in the plan I think that
makes it I like his shirt I hate it
honestly I kind of want it I was
honestly gonna talk about how much he
definitely needs some like some
sunscreen on his neck she looks a little
scared I'm trying to judge if they're
siblings are awkward dating
I accidentally swiped because it makes
sense though why am I so shocked I was
going to say dating yeah me too
yeah I see it next one
okay okay she's fully leaning on this
dude that has to oh look at their feet
oh they have matching sandals not even
close to matching but that's well it's
like they're like well they're just
really close together for me they don't
even look like this has to be a dating
if this is Siblings going to be really
Disturbed actually no no I'm not trying
to push you away I'm just thinking
she's fully leaning on them and they
look yeah you and Matt would stand like
this for a photo
uh
um really strange yeah no no you just
stand like oh that's a joke no like you
wouldn't say no no no no no no and like
[ __ ]
yeah that one's strange
Civ blocks siblings gets me every time
so I guess it's a common mistake that
they make okay next one oh terrible
photo well it's like they tried to go
portal why does it look like their hair
or like morph together it looks like her
hair it looks photoshopped in this it
looks like her hair is like going up
that has to be dating though no this
looks like no no no no no no no no no no
no no no listen I love it hold on back
up we need to can you stop touching me
because you were crowded okay this is my
thought process behind it I think that
they're like oh I'm trying to crack my
wrist it's like Grandma Tina's wedding
and like it's in the uh it's in the
mountains and like we're gonna go oh you
should go with your brother and like
look really nice and oh take a photo
with your brother like portrait mode
they're dressed really all right look at
no no I'm just saying it looks like
they're going on a hike dating
no dating I think it's siblings I think
it's siblings yeah like it looks like
they're going like that it's giving
family Excursion because there's no way
you're in the mountains dressed like
this unless all right go okay ready
three dating two siblings
wow Matt you want all the chips thank
you you don't have to say that you know
I thought they were siblings for sure oh
my God they're 35 seconds they're clones
that's a sibling Duo hold on same
glasses
same everything I mean they're clones
the only thing about them because
they're the same hair and glasses their
eyes and they're making the same
position eyes look nothing alike yes
they do same exact color his face looks
so different than hers ready they have
to be dating I mean siblings I think
that they're they think they're siblings
okay siblings we have the same forehead
bro okay three two
dating what dating
why do they spell it wrong on purpose
I don't know what's going on
[Music]
yeah
behind his left head his left side of
his head left head there's a like
bouquet of flowers in their drawers
they're at a funeral yeah yeah they're
at a family funeral
why are they smiling so much there's no
way okay I understand like okay listen
since we think they're at a funeral my
thought process is like if you're at a
funeral there's so much like family
there because someone are you gonna take
a selfie with your sister like no no
what I'm thinking is like you're more
likely to take a photo with your sister
rather than someone you're dating
because someone you're dating you're
like dragging not dragging along no no
I'm not trying out
hey we're dating drag you along the
funeral
you know what I mean not drag you along
but like you're going to like you're
going in support of like your love I
love how we totally just guess there
Adam no they are look there's a mint
thing in the back too they're for sure
at a funeral that's terrible but listen
think about it we have to think more
critically there's no way you're gonna
post up with like a selfie if like
someone you're dating like think about
it you're in a relationship stop telling
me to listen your own problems
someone in your family passes away super
unfortunate someone you're dating like
they the family already knows them they
kind of are gonna feel like
uncomfortable you know like they're
going to support you but like it's not
their time or place to shine it's
someone's funeral you know what I mean
no one's supposed to wear like siblings
what I'm saying is Siblings would go and
like oh the other grandmother that like
like gets there is like oh my gosh I
haven't seen you two in so long because
like at a funeral trying to like to make
the boat the most of it you know what I
mean and you're like
deeper and deeper yeah it's like a sad
thing so you want to just think about
what's positive and like you look at the
siblings and you're like oh like you
guys are so cute like oh I love you guys
I'm like totally I don't even remember
you're trying to like now go so I didn't
get siblings because I can picture
all right can I see it okay what are
your thoughts I think they're
siblings as well because of my reasoning
sure thing Matt dating just because you
guys are both saying siblings and I go
Nick
oh oh my God
I was wrong
hold on let me see it why do you want to
see it I just want to see the comment
section let's see if anybody else thinks
they're at a funeral what I really want
to do what the new fiber we just
stiffled at the same time with the new
Five Nights at Freddy's movie coming out
I'm really like interested in going to
watch the movie but I don't know [ __ ]
about it and I don't want to be one of
those posers like I wanna I wanna watch
and like devote my life to it for the
next month I hate when you do this [ __ ]
there's also a game and we don't know
the format of the game
that's my [ __ ] no but it's like
know what's going on yeah but before I
go to this okay the game and the thing
is different the movie the movie
the game and the movie can't be that I
have a bright idea okay when before
watching stranger things did you play a
[ __ ] whole trailer of Dungeons and
Dragons no but there's like a storyline
a plot character it really really can do
the same thing think about it it has to
do with Dungeons and Dragons but it
really minimally right like relates yeah
it's a whole did you play Dungeons and
Dragons before going to the Dungeons and
Dragons Premiere no and I wished I did
that's true
you I really wish I didn't know what you
mean you're not actually validating what
I'm saying more and more as you speak so
keep guys
Channel what do you think like a new
channel dedicated to fortnite I don't
think it's not just foreign
I hate when escalators go like this
why
like this one's going down this one's
going on
yeah you walked in you always go to the
one you just don't want to be at and
then it's like you got to go all the way
around it's so awkward too like you just
kind of oh I have to show everyone that
I made a mistake later but you wanna I
really don't understand either what like
a little metal fruit baskets in like the
fridge and [ __ ] no clue what you're
saying not the fridge like do you know
how like the little metal fruit baskets
that people have on like their counters
and stuff put your fruit in the fridge
no thing with like the
like oh
I feel like there needs to be a better
way to store food fruits like those
aren't in there can I tell you what I
actually don't get that makes more sense
than you not getting this what the fruit
like the fact that there's compartments
for fruit and vegetables and
refrigerators and depending on which
which way you put the level like there's
like we'll get a load of this spice
cabinet no listen come on you got 80
other cabinets let's just put them on
that listen no listen listen you oh you
need a whole little cabinet
in the fridge
vegetable how does that change so much
ask the scientist bro I know oh God here
we go well a vegetable is more of like a
rough inside I feel like every fruit
like the shell is more valuable than
what's on the insides
this is gonna be one of Chris's no I'm
saying like I like like no no no like an
orange has like a hard rough shell then
the inside is all gushed and [ __ ] and
the same with an apple the apples the
hard [ __ ] and then the inside's like the
soft mushy [ __ ] that goes bad I feel
like a vegetables what strawberries yeah
same [ __ ] it's like the outside's normal
but like the inside goes I feel like a
vegetable is more like all the way
through type of
like I know what you mean actually
because like like a vegetable is like
I'm a vegetable from like the outside
all the way out of vegetables through
and through yeah like but then a fruit
is like all sensitive on the inside
I have to be more chilled and then like
leave me out for an hour I might throw a
tan okay zucchini my bad you can see the
most [ __ ] up okay
you can see the most beat up green bean
of your life and then go to like the
like most mediocre Apple that's kind of
like a stage three and I bet you the
apples
bro what would happen if one day the
whole government just issued like
everyone has to play laser tag now
everyone just had a vest on and you
would just see like like the beams of
light just
like like instant laser tag everywhere I
don't get I'd love that
why because it'd be fun like no I feel
like each like the government should do
a thing where it's like City Mini game
day and they're like okay City minigame
in Boston paintball everyone has to have
a paintball gun ready and like you step
outside you're in the [ __ ] well they
should give you like 48 Hours of like
preparation evacuation if you want to
like if you don't want to participate in
the city games you go to like Vermont
yeah or something like far away yeah I
don't like this I love it okay
um what if it was just Capture the Flag
State like state by state and like every
like like state had their state flag
like hung up in the center and like get
to like steal other state state flags so
we even have a state flag yes every
state has a flag flag news to me you you
know this
right now like the red star in the
basement oh the Bear right yeah yeah
I've never I don't know what masterton
says
Bay State Massachusetts is the Bay State
I don't know if that's a factual sense
that or like lobster or clam chowder I
think he's correct Massachusetts
okay it's called the base State refers
to one of the most famous bays Cape Cod
where the pilgrims first settled yeah
we've been there for the whole point
oh my God we literally have a place
called Plymouth obviously the pilgrims
went there first why would the Pilgrims
go to Plymouth first they both start
with a P oh my God I love Cape Cod
Plymouth Plantation is where the pilgrim
that's like why no the Plymouth
Plantation nothing beat when we used to
go to political Plantation with like our
school and it was like in Plymouth and
it was about like the pilgrims oh my God
it was like the most like surreal thing
ever no I remember we used to go I made
it so far the actors that were there
should have won like [ __ ] Emmys like
I'd go in and talk to the lady when I
was a little kid and I'd be like what
are you doing here and she'd be like oh
churning butter for my family this week
she was like okay she was churning
butter for her family insurance I'm
gonna be totally honest with you I had
no idea they were actors so you just
said that you thought they were pilgrims
I thought they were like living in
Plymouth Plantation I just realized like
fully in my head that those were all
fakes they're all phonies
genuinely think that I want to go hold
on one of the most mind-blowing
experiences of my whole life was seeing
Plymouth Rock with my own eyes
but it was surreal because I felt like
the moment like I it's like dude when
you go to places that's in history you
only have to really know what's going on
you know it's deep like you know like oh
my God like I'm being for real you're
like where the Boston Tea Party well
dude we live in such a history based
State it's insane dude oh
Paul Revere one bit
I'm like pretty sure that
was dirty work and he did like the last
leg and we gave him the credit because
he like finished the job
deserves all this credit
I hate talking about history because I
just don't like I feel like I'm an idiot
and I don't want to like [ __ ] something
up but I feel like we give Paul a credit
to someone I feel like you always know
the most random [ __ ] ever
I did all I know is like seeing I'm not
even joking around like I know you oh my
God if you uh if you Google who was Paul
Revere's writer like co-writer it says
while Paul Revere rode into history on
April 18 1775 his fellow writer William
Dawes galloped into undeserved Oblivion
yep he's literally at zero credit
come on that's [ __ ] up bruh do you
know how many people and like what I
don't get is like we know so many people
in history but there's probably so many
more that we just don't even know about
well you have to think of like I played
he was just documented they shout out
the horse too
for real like bro like let's oh yeah oh
yeah Paul the credit shout out to
Horseshoe galloped all that way and like
dude yeah Paul is just riding the horse
for my brothers