hey guys welcome back to our YouTube
channel and welcome to today's video
today we are going to be doing I need a
haircut but that has nothing to do with
the video I just need a haircut yeah
today we're going to be doing something
we've never done before we're going to
go through our liked Tik toks and show
each other we don't I hate Tik Tok it's
my least favorite app of all
time throwing that out there before we
even began no need to be a hater bro
it's just like just stop being don't
make it your I just I came with the no I
just came with the brain rot like it's
like if you're if you're on like when
Livy done and skibby RZ oh I
like it's like that's the Tik Tok that I
hate no it's a lot when it's like
everyone's just talking about skibby RZ
and it's like what the other with our
friend like an 11year old walk by and
they were like should I relate to them
and I was like what do you mean they
were like skibby RZ Ohio and I'm like
the fact that that's like actually how
like like if I walked by a 12-year-old
instead of saying Hi how are you I'd go
like skibby RZ like oh yeah skibby
anyway we're going to show each other
our lik Tik toks and see if they differ
or if they're similar after we open
after we do this I don't think I'm ever
going to open Tik Tok again we send each
other Tik toks but I'm curious to see
how our humor differs I can't show you
guys all of mine yes you can fine oh my
God wait I have the perfect one to start
off the video I think we should be like
hutman
[Laughter]
something um that moment when slam down
touchdown touchdown pass Mikasa so there
ain't no going back singing flid he just
he didn't sing anything
one of my favorite words finess oh
finesse
finesse see the
[Music]
hatler oh my God what I did not see that
I was looking at the chick the the
cheese puffs by rewat
rewatch
take I'm the rler on the what is
happening to the Youth of America the
fact that this is the first one makes me
sick oh my God in Las Vegas is crazy
that should be in Ohio skibby
RZ oh that should be in Ohio skibby
rizzler dude what about today we were
talking about how Logan um I always just
said Logan Prime instead of Logan Paul
Logan Paul we were talking about how
Logan Paul is about to have a kid and
Nick goes what do you think his kid's
going to do besides drink Prime and
wrestle that's what I'm I'm waiting to
figure it out I can't wait no hate it's
just like those are I feel like his big
two things and it's like you you have to
age up into both of those you know what
I mean I really love Logan Paul all
right are you guys ready yes can we get
horny I got something wait should we
alterate wait should we like take turns
this one this one didn't have a lot of
views when I saw it and then I reposted
it forgetting that I'm like a public
figure I hate
it um but every every single comment
like let me show you the comments yeah
you guys don't have to tell people if we
repost this let me show you the comments
before I show you the video this is
getting out of hand why did Nick repost
this show us okay got
[ __ ] my
DNA wait
wait you're really weird come on man ray
that is the craziest you're really weird
it's tickling my DNA he said no like
that's the craziest thing ever like they
were lowy edging on
SpongeBob what they were lowy edging on
SpongeBob it's the way the belt is like
shaking like it's like it literally
looks like it's like it looks like
someone is going like like man ray is
standing there and someone's behind him
like knocking on his nut sack that's
what it seems like what like the speed
bags I can't I like
I like someone behind man someone steps
in I
like damn get all the [ __ ]
[ __ ] I love that isn't that so funny
the only reason I didn't laugh hard cuz
I saw that already
[Applause]
that's my biggest sick
makes my biggest fear is being in that
situation let's like annotate like look
at him like
just J like
slicing look look at like this guy with
the pink phone where' you get that a
full it's a case no that's a pink
phone Chris that's a pink cell phone
it's a it's a phone case it's a phone
case there's like 10 people there 10
people there in general it's like a stab
convention stab e [ __ ] stabon what's
going on literally stab St I can't watch
that he's just slicing it's throat it's
like what is this this should be
happening in [ __ ] high contained
prison yes so yeah here's your activ you
can slash up dummies here in in in jail
in jail cuz why else would you be doing
this why else would you be
massacring like that isn't even this is
not literally it's like go cook choping
onion we're well packed make soup you
know this is crazy we are we are well
past self-defense this is
premeditated oh come to this little
self-defense class yeah d double
arm cut off I didn't like that Lit it's
like I didn't like that he put his
fingers in the shoulder oh look at his
[ __ ] chop I did here look at his
[ __ ] cut it's like he's talking Mor
Mortal Kombat finisher he just he's
talking about the knife he said he said
oh look at oh don't even touch me like
that freaks me out bad he said oh this
was the B drag dude look at that
combo look off rip I can't pause it fast
enough wait let's count let's count one
across the neck another coming right
away from the left hand side another
it's like it's like yeah so it's it's
chop right right to left both back chop
right to left left again and then
another
Le wait okay another right it's like
this it's
like fo fo yeah yeah another right
another left I that was too quick that
was like two moves and then and look at
this poor guy and look at this poor guy
in the back yeah he's like oh my god get
this man to a high containment prison
facility insane and
then after it looks like he's jump
starting a car and
after like what and then after gutting
the poor gummy gummy or D he's slicing
the dummy up he goes you know what
ripping your shoulders off your
shoulders are too intact right now oh oh
oh you're bleeding
out he literally thinks he's
like boom like what my arms literally go
like this boom shrugs in the
ground standing there and your shoulders
go like this you're just standing there
and they go oh no more shoulders where
are my shoulders he said um I just
sliced your neck eight times gutted your
chest no more arms boom just like
massive that's called a shrugger you're
never going to go to Shug again I'm
ripping your shoulders out of your body
and then look at this cut look at this
big cut look at this cut right here it's
like what this isn't the Viber going for
for guys I'm like
sweat oh God pick it okay hold on um
this was a really good
one I love Pop belly I didn't know pop
belly got an ed wow it's the fact that
they have like no comments no no
engagement on the pot belly like what
are we not engaging the pot belly ated
for the pot belly
sandwich oh my God I [ __ ] love pot
belly sandwiches I had to eat a whole
one right now I swear to God if you
become a fashion ion I'm going to kill
myself I knew it was coming I've never
seen this boy before he's the man I've
never seen him before he's so fly I've
never seen this kid before I've seen him
so many times and it brings me pure joy
I love suspenders yeah me there was a
phase in eighth grade where I tried to
wear suspenders to school every day you
guys remember that oh of course I had
them in every color I was clipping them
under your back every day oh I love
suspenders I never wore them to school
yes you did I think I wore purple ones
once Chris a Florida man trying to do
his best tan impression when
things wait I feel pain in my back
oh it's his legs it's his legs Nick it's
his
[ __ ] when the branch he was on
collapsed see it's his leg his leg is
broken oh my God you can see his broken
leg broken leg no you can't see no his
leg's not broken I think it's just
inertia when the branch he was on
collapsed well get me his GoPro footage
he has a go
strapped to his chest oh get me that
footage get me that footage um if you
listen closely you can also hear that
his goal was to get into the water
anyway yes he took the route I don't
think he had planned but it's like you
were up there you intended to get the
ground you did want to jum doesn't shock
me this happened last month the man says
he usually jumps from another branch and
this was the first time he went that
high I shouldn't have tested this branch
out slit my mind maybe I shouldn't climb
60 ft in the [ __ ] air did he did he
do the wait I need to hear her
question I don't think he ever got it
out he started and then then it turned
into cut off turned into a different
call and I have a feeling he'll see I
can make fun of him cuz I'm a viewer
like from home news anchor ah ouch guys
mine are all just hot men like actually
these are my f these are my favorite Tik
toks I've been seeing recently look
Chris showed me these for like a
day they're so cool kind of scary
they're so cool cuz look look look look
look hold on kind of scary hold on
there's no there was a Scooby-Doo one
that's what I
have that's what I'm looking for
yay I'm
creaming I'm creaming is that AI it's
artificial intelligence that's so weird
[ __ ] AI
AI pisses me the [ __ ] off cuz it's like
why why am I on AI get me out of AI I
want to be a part of it I can't I don't
want to I don't want to allow myself to
be duplicated by AI I just think one day
when I walk into a grocery store and
it's legitimate robot chaos and they're
all like good greetings may I get you
Mayo may I get you eggs like leave me
alone you're acting like this is an
issue now I'm more worried about Lally
started that sentence by saying one day
okay listen what I'm saying all I'm
saying is literally see Robo Bots
delivering food all the time I want to
kick those [ __ ] over [ __ ] those
stupid little what is the Mars rover
doing on this side literally get out of
here go away you should be orbiting a
different [ __ ] planet get this
literal Rover off the street correct
like why is Mars Rover 1874 working for
[ __ ] door Dash and why we put why do
we put eyes on it and let it like blink
you're a robot you should be finding
water on [ __ ] Pluto and literally get
away you should be looking for new life
forms and you're bringing fat
[ __ ] a his meal you should be on
another planet okay whoa whoa whoa
restart
[Music]
already oh Jeremy you're a
beast joury
[Music]
beast do you want
it
jery do you
want jery dresses like SpongeBob jery
fragrance is my favorite I think we need
to dedicate a whole video to Jeremy
fragrance Jeremy fragrance goes me and
Matt love quoting this video he this guy
if you don't know good for teen teen he
can he can smell any fragrance and know
what it is it's like he can smell a
fragrance and tell you what it is where
people go up to him and they're like oh
my God Jeremy fragrance like they
recognize him in public and they ask him
and he whips his phone out no yeah he
the second people start interacting with
him I'm going to start doing this if
people notice me I'm going to start
whipping my camera and he he brings out
his camera and starts making content he
goes like I'm going to show you guys
exactly what he does there'll be like
there was a teenage boy next to him and
he goes up to the guy and he goes the
guy goes sniff me he go he goes I'm just
kidding teenager
musk he's like why would you ask Jeremy
for exist to you if you don't have a
smell on and he goes yeah I'm not
wearing anything huh and then at least
Jeremy was right it was just teenager
teenager musk and then he goes up to a
girl and he goes nice he I don't
recognize this fragrance and she goes
it's Cloud by Ariana Grande he goes ah a
good teenager fragrance and he looks
like a good teen a good frag a good
fragrance a good teenager fragrance and
it's so funny need to review him
interact with some human beings I yeah
pull up another we need another Jeremy
FR I want him like literally look up
Jeremy fragrance Cloud perfume no just
get like Jeremy fragrance best moment
this
one this little K he just grab him is
that his
hand no it's no what's the brand it's
lemon lime shows me some Niche lemon
lime okay thank you bye
Goode that is not a fragrance that I
expected on him man lemon
lime he goes home pissed he goes home
and kicks his dog so
mad he
go he's just tell me some Niche [ __ ]
[ __ ] Niche lemon lme he's so pissed
it's my favorite thing ever it's my
favorite thing ever it's my favorite
[ __ ] thing ever what is happening why
is he dressed like it's his first
communion every day I [ __ ] love him I
love Jeremy FR it's so
funny yeah we don't need to watch Nick
edits we're
good can you hold the [ __ ] light
straight oh don't be mean to
him straight he's
like it looks like that light is like a
crushing weight on his back
can you hold the [ __ ] lights like
look at his his arms are buckling he's
getting away he's so [ __ ]
[Music]
cute it's not even funny for the video
yes take the dog off right the turtle
stress
like [ __ ] he thinks he's think he's like
what he like what the [ __ ] is on my back
and then the dog takes one step off and
he probably feels the the relief of like
I I feel like I'm in like the dog on me
position cute what and I feel like I
need to remove that stress C God it's
cute but it's stress this is not worth
it I feel induced with stress watching
like my belly the scraping of the belly
oh my God he's like and that's like
that's like the Rost part of a turtle
you know just like straight up like skin
the ground God God my God you got to tie
me up and drag my my ass across that's
how that Turtle feels think if you threw
a Frisbee with like a a turtle like a
frisbee it would have the same inertia
no like I think you could I think you
could quite easily frisbe a turtle I
mean yeah it's just not going to be like
safe oh my
God obviously what thank God you're here
this was so Nick's
[Music]
VI please tell me wait wait please tell
me someone green screens this no come on
let's put this girl on lava in water
this is like you're telling me someone
doesn't see this and immediately think
how can I manipulate the green screen I
don't know Nick how are we not this
being a trend in and of itself where
this girl is just being green screen
this is [ __ ] hilarious how I can't be
the first one have that it's not that
funny they just push the fish off I feel
bad for the fish yeah whatever
no no does he
die
no I don't think we see anything happen
but it's
what it's just him like giving up and
like the you can see look look look you
can see the peacefulness in his eyelids
he's ready he's like he's just like yes
I feel bad for him cuz I've been there
you know you're just like you can
literally see all guys the allergies are
so
bad bottle can you stop can you stop all
you do is talk about these all you do is
talk about every night before I go to
bed I I like am too lazy to like hire a
masseuse or go get a massage I watch
Like chiropractors or massages before
bed and I just like imagine that it's me
and it's like a form of Med
and then I genuinely can sleep easier
like look imagine
just feel this I think it's just getting
later so you're tired no no no feel no
no feel it like just
imagine
Bott I don't know what's the oil what's
the oil like massage oil I don't like
that in my hair I'm sure you wouldn't
but I'd love for this to be happening to
me I don't think so oh oh yeah yeah
on the forehead I don't think I oh
oh he's like motorboating the air the
guy
like I have to cover my face I have to
cover my face I can't [ __ ] leave that
I'm covering my I'm bluring myself out
[ __ ] you guys that'd be weird
I nick nick for your own sake and
everyone else is in this world stop show
me your bad dog I don't want to see any
of these like good boys and good girls
sitting for a cookie show me that who is
filming this audio
get good want to see I don't want to see
your good girls or your bad boys I want
to see them little doggies dog like what
are you saying let me see so true look
at that look at that webbed
[Music]
paw that is literally perfect can I tell
you Matt so weird we're doing we're
doing the laundry upstairs together like
he he asks my help to fold the clothes
and he goes he goes once it's full it
empties out once it's empty it fills up
again I was like what who's reading
who's doing poetry slam right next to me
welcome to cognify a facility designed
to treat criminals like patients instead
of spending years in an actual prison
cell prisoners could finish their
sentence here in just a few minutes
cogi could somay create and impal
memories directly into the brain welcome
to I'm done no you go to jail if you
commit murder no [ __ ] AI
Bots like can we can we be over this on
POV your brick in public but it's only
semi so it looks like you have an
absolute
Chopper
what oh
[ __ ] instant headache oh I feel I got to
watch my Indian head massage my [ __ ]
head hurts that was bad instant pull
P [ __ ] God damn it watch it watch
imagine your mother does that to you
Matt punch in the face watch
[ __ ] don't touch me like that
idiot
[Music]
okay go go I need to shower he just
yelled at me it looks like in like over
bedtime never yell at me again
[ __ ] like looked all around like
weird
kid lock no I'm locked just watch it
B I didn't even he a noise listen just
listen
a oh my God just watch just watch just
watch please give him a
cookie
overnight T's daughter
Kik had her first
cat this is B only a few hours old I
don't know it's just a story about baby
elephants I just thought the intro was
insane I'm ready to call CPS someone
said oh that was really sad the noise
thing it so much worse it was funny at
first and then like the The Cry for
Help a few hours old right in this
CH oh you're a few hours old here this
will set you to [ __ ]
reality I'm just like what hey let's go
to the bar beer smack like so beer that
is so night
out did you just eat an entire carton of
eggs
e with the
shell get that wasn't me [ __ ]
that was someone
Elsey
fken no there it was physical as well
yeah
they're all in no one's touching each
other at the moment but they're still
screaming
yeah the caption being Bakery brawl
emergency call bagette fist like the
rhyme and then the Emoji really I love
that video Yeah someone comments I just
know my son would have yelled you made
me drop my croissant in the midsts of
yelling
[Laughter]
[Music]
can we be [ __ ] for
real can we be [ __ ] first real all
right thank you guys so much for
watching this Friday's video make sure
you follow each of us on Instagram
follow St triplets on Instagram for a
weekly photo D and we'll see you guys
next Friday we love you all so very much
we're excited to talk to you I love
filming that video so much so if you
want a part two of us reacting to Tik
toks if you get this video to 300,000
likes which is asking a Lotz that's nowh
near so much 250,000 250 yeah if you get
this video to 250,000 we'll do a part
two um I had so much fun that was so
funny that was really good oh my
goodness
[Music]