stolo Nation we are about to embark on a
journey of which has never been seen or
done before on the stolo triplet Channel
and the stolo triplet lifetime
experience hey everybody Nick speaking
me Matt and Chris have never been apart
for more than 24 hours in our entire
life the longest I have been apart for
Matt and Chris is 5 days the longest
Matt has been alone is 2 days and the
longest Chris has been apart from us is
under 24 hours but all of this is about
to change being triplets we grew up
together we went to school together and
we have done everything together so far
at this point in our life as we've grown
up we want to become less dependent on
each other and start to do more things
as individuals so we can learn from it
being a triplet is amazing but sometimes
it's unhealthy how much we rely on each
other as we become young adults we want
to learn more about functioning
completely on our own and we are
starting by spending a week completely
by ourselves in this video we all start
in Boston then me and Matt go to La for
2 days then I fly to tour with my best
friend Madison and that starts our week
apart and all I ever
wanted is something I
can't Nick it's 6:00 in the morning I am
going to leave Chris for 20 days and I'm
about to go to eight different Madison
viewer concerts she's my favorite artist
seeing a little like a sheriff like shut
the [ __ ] up get that goofy hat off [ __ ]
okay everywhere I go I'm trying to Chris
I'm going I see you for 20 days we're
going to die what if we die what if I
die die I'm not going to die like you
need to stop mentioning I'm you're going
to die love you I'll see you so soon
I'll see you later rub your belly every
night you're taking this camera remember
yeah I know all right Matt he's taking
that yeah you're taking it I'm not
taking it I'm taking a nap all right see
you later have
fun on top of not being alone from each
other this and it of itself like the
past two days has been an experience of
its own because I've never been alone
with just Matt for this long and I bet
it's a dream right and it is it is a
dream it is just crazy cuz I was talking
we we went out yesterday and I was
talking about it and I was like I've
never been with just Matt for this
amount of time it's crazy mhm well we'll
be back we got to go make Gooseberry
pies that yeah we're gonna go make a
gooseberry pie what's up guys quick
little recap um I'm still in Boston Nick
and Matt are back in La they've been
there for about like two days I think so
I've been home alone for two days but
the week hasn't started yet because Matt
and Nick are still together but it does
definitely feel weird being alone and
away from Nick and Matt um but I'm
feeling fine I'm about to make this Lego
set right
here and watch
[Music]
SpongeBob guys I'm about to leave um
Matt is not with me Matt fell asleep
yesterday and so I said bye to him last
night before he went to bed but I'm
going to make the hardest decision I'm
going to have to make
within the next segment of time and it's
which socks to wear cuz although to you
guys they may look and seem exactly the
same this will change the trajectory of
the 12-hour flight I have to be on cuz
if I get a pair that's snug and comfy
and doesn't like make me feel dry and
gross like sand it'll change my
life instant regret I just don't think
it's going to do the trick but
we'll be
fine hello Vlog what's going on today is
my first day alone I woke up at
um I woke up at like 9:00 in the
morning and uh I feel violently ill took
a covid test and it's negative but I
have like the worst headache I've ever
had in my entire life and um
not really sure why been at home
watching every single episode of Gravity
Falls and now I'm about to take a break
and eat multigrain Cheerios and listen
to the neighborhood all right all right
all right let's see what we
get
101.1 that can't be good all right just
got into the hotel room is this a light
switch should I twist
it that's the light switch guys so crazy
but yeah we're GNA get ready it's the
first day I'm alone I don't know if it's
like accurate to like Matt and Chris's
first day alone cuz I'm like technically
a day in the future cuz the
flight we're going to go in one of the
60-minute sex shops and then we a
60-minute hotel room together yes stay
tun don't say that and then we're going
to get candy after as a celebration
reward we really want Tang I don't know
how to say it tangu tangu tangu yes the
sugar covered
sugarcoated fruit and we and we already
have it videos what videos look at the
videos that playing on the that screen
the Instagram reals live on the street
oh my God she's throwing ass throwing it
back we're going to look for we already
found it ate it and we want it again so
we're trying to find a better more
convenient place to now yes yeah hey
world we are in the hotel room I'm about
to throw on the fan noise I think that
was officially day one without Matt and
Chris and then explored Japan I had an
absolute blast I took
14,000 steps I'm exhausted the second I
hit shut off on this camera my body is
going to fall asleep how much should I
miss my brothers on a scale from 1 to 10
honestly and I'm going to be negative
honestly like a one is that rude to say
that I like it's something that I don't
miss
[Music]
them hello everyone it is day two of
being alone I woke up at like 9 in the
morning today in a pool of sweat still
have 100 something degree fever so sorry
you're not getting much Vlog out of me I
hope Nick and Chris are recording a lot
because I am just living a very boring
life and very sick right now so there's
not much to record and I look a mess
yeah that's it for me it felt like I had
a [ __ ]
paranormal experience last night I'm
trying to go to sleep my [ __ ] fan in
my room I have a box fan right here box
fan it was like spinning and then it
like slowed down it was
like and then it picked back up and like
[ __ ] max speed and then my door kept
like creeping open like this
like I don't know if it's cuz I've been
sleeping alone for 3 days that I'm
starting to like hear everything that
happens in the middle of the night and
it's just normal and I'm just like being
dramatic but I literally couldn't sleep
last night cuz it kept sounding like
someone was like coming into my room but
I'm going to naths today which is good
to see my friend um but I had to ask my
mom for a ride and that felt extremely
weird cuz I haven't had to ask my mom
for a ride to a friend's house in like
probably like 4 years disgusting
disgusting disgusting disgusting in the
middle of the road and we're at a bunch
of Street vendors I bought nothing I
have water and I got a little a little
cute little thing I'll put on the screen
are you saying you tried nothing no I
was saying I bought pretty much nothing
but I got a little thing I'm going to
put on the screen it's like a i I think
it's for Chopsticks but I just thought
it was cute so I bought it anyway insert
insert here Madison has tried everything
which is good everyone's eating but me
but I'm not really like a he tried a
piece of steak I did try steak it was
very good it was delicious other than
that angle that you film from no
sometimes I'm up here
hello sometimes I'm down here sometimes
I'm up here we're really it swaps it up
it's so hot we're disgusting I was
convinced up until 5 minutes ago I
wasn't sweating I'm like I'm not
sweating and then I'm like I'm like I
felt it roll off my face how do you how
much do you miss your brothers on a
scale from 1 to 10 um I would say I miss
them pretty much like a 10 already
because I haven't seen them in like 4
days or 3 days because am I feeling I'm
feeling great do I miss Matt and Chris
of course I miss them but on a scale
from 1 to 10 I'm at like a one stale
like I'm good I'm chilling I'm having a
blast it's just I mean there's just so
many things like I go to tell them [ __ ]
and they're not there and I'm like oh
[ __ ] I noticed also all of the clocks
here or most of the clocks here are in
like mill military time so that's fun
it's
22:45 it just feels really strange there
was like a time where this needed to
happen and I feel like this is like
perfect timing in like our life I got a
necklace that's in here and I'm not
opening it and I got two little
Chopstick holders that are in here and
I'm not opening it that's the boring
start of the haul and I got this shirt
for matte I got this shirt and it has
little bears on it and it has snowflakes
on it
and it's just so cute like tell me you
guys wouldn't like die if Matt wore this
I know what the Matt girls want and I
also know what Matt looks just so super
cute
[Music]
in hello everyone I'm literally
recording the wall because I've been in
my underwear for the past 3 days
sweating my [ __ ] ass off with a 101
fever we're to
98.8 so gra
fever I'll talk to you guys again later
feel like mini pizza is my life feeling
bad mini pizza feeling happy mini pizza
can't sleep mini pizza slept fine mini
pizza going over to a friend's house
mini pizza friends come over here mini
pizza most importantly I'm
hungry mini pizza I eat breathe and live
this [ __ ] it's not a game got to make
sure you get the one with pepperoni
though I know if Matt was sure' be like
you chew so loud
Nick would be like let me have a bite I
just saw a video of Dave pornoy doing a
pizza review while I'm eating my mini
pizza here he takes a bite and he goes
solid slice of pizza but I'm not doing
jumping jacks and I think that just
entered my top three sayings of all time
guys it's so easy to spend Yen cuz I
have no idea like how much USD I'm
spending I'm like yeah sure I'll add
that on you you um oh my I'm a little
terrified how do I get away from this
one hi
guys hi um how much do I miss my
brothers on a scale from 1 to 10 I'm
already going with a
10 um I really just miss going out with
them and doing things and like saying
good night to them and being able to
recap my day with them
[Music]
um I literally rewatched all of Gravity
Falls I rewatched all of Wednesday cuz I
I knew I liked it I just kind of forgot
what happened and I do really like that
show but I finished all of Wednesday all
of Gravity Falls and then I didn't think
that I was going to watch Big Brother
this season but I ran out of things to
to watch it and I saw it when I was on
like when I was like bouncing through
the streaming services so now I'm also
so caught up on this season of Big
Brother I actually feel the best I have
like in the morning today than out of
all the other mornings so I have hope
but um even though I am sick and still
have a fever three of my friends did
come over they don't really want to talk
much or say anything but I'll just show
you who's here it's um my boy's
here if you don't get this reference
you need to do some research and make
yourself familiar I got a haircut today
with my mom we went out to eat and now
I'm at Nathan's and we're about to be
trying whatever the [ __ ] these Donuts
are we got a bunch of different ones and
we're about to go crazy the moin nut the
mo the mo nut oh wow this is like a nice
little thing and I know I'm going to
like these I'll try the stick all right
I'm going shove that stick in
there all right ready
Ready
Set M it's a nice strawberry flavor yeah
it is pretty good M it's kind of like a
munchkin it really is it just feels like
a little ball in your
mouth hold on this one this is um
coconut
oh wao I like that one
m more of a crunch on the dut I
feel it's got to be like the little
shaving or something mhm dude I like
Dead series every time we went to Hawaii
I started to like coconuts really it
changed it for you changed my life wow
that's beautiful honestly it's like a
good
story the time the time my coconut
changeed my
life I'm [ __ ]
the
time
the change
my what about the banana bread is that
the same or I don't f with bread at all
no the OG the
OG okay to me it seems just like a
powdered donut it looks like it um looks
like fried dough it does oh I hope it
tastes like what it is all right let's
go it's a nice flavor very classic very
boring yeah I love that you could just
get a group of nine friends and each
take a little ball and enjoy one that's
how it goes that's how it be this is
delicious very delicious I love it I
give be number one for sure really mhm
all the way to one oh yeah a top wow
well you like cereal you a breakfast
cereal
animal I'm a
warrior not my favorite but it's still
good it's it's better than Cocoa
Krispies whatever the [ __ ] those things
are [ __ ] those should we split one of
the matcha ones yeah I know I'm not
going to [ __ ] with that yeah I don't
think I will what is
that I hate
[Music]
it [ __ ] I I need no water bro what I
just eat bro it's like minty bro if you
like matcha I can like kind of get
behind it but that just's like a
one zero I'm headed to a coffee shop
that everybody's already at but I slept
in because I had to upload a YouTube
video
yesterday hello trying to Vlog I was
just in the elevator and two people
walked in and I did not think anyone was
going to show up okay I live guys I'm
not going to a coffee shop because
everybody's already done and they're
going to meet back at the hotel but I
want to show you guys these vending
machines oh none of these take American
dollars well obviously not but they
don't take Visa or Mastercard either
they so I can't get anything but there's
vending machines everywhere like Chris
would be so excited it's just like
there's immediate access to drinks
literally everywhere something I've
noticed that I'm genuinely blessed with
though is I have amazing sense of
direction like if we go like One
Direction and hey I will know how to get
back is this an
ATM this looks like an ATM to me oh no
that's how you pay for parking obviously
brain dead idiot brain dead idiot
walking through Japan and his name is NI
stola I'm literally next to a [ __ ]
parking garage and I think that the
thing to pay for your parking ticket is
an ATM how much do you miss your
brothers on a scale from 1 to
10 um right now as crazy as it sounds
I'm glad that they're both not here and
experiencing me while I'm sick because I
just know that they would just like if
this if they were here right now I
wouldn't see them they would go go out
and do things while I was sick and then
when they were home they would like help
me out like get me the meds and stuff
and the stuff that I'm ordering to the
house but
um I'm I'm honestly glad that they're
they're away I miss not being sick and
hanging out with them I'd
say
6.8 out of
10 how are you feeling terrible terrible
terrible terrible sickness wise but
mentally I'm doing fine great I think
the strangest
thing about being alone is like going to
bed and waking up and not like
immediately talking and like debriefing
with them about stuff that's like that's
definitely the craziest one especially
Nick like because he's in like a like
Chris I'll text and [ __ ] before I go to
bed and when like I wake up but Nick
being in like a complete different time
zone is like he'll wake up and answer my
text in the middle of like of night time
for me so it is really really weird and
the strangest thing so far is just Nick
and Matt not being with me at like when
we go out to family dinners and stuff
and then it's like just me my mom and my
dad and like I'm like the center of
attention and they're like talking to me
cuz normally they talk to all three of
us us but it feels a little weird when
it's just me I am in the nicest hotel
room I've ever been in in my entire life
um I had an amazing day today today was
Madison's first show had a blast it was
phenomenal we took a bullet train to
Osaka so that's where I am that's where
I'm going to bed tonight I don't miss
Matt and
Chris that much I feel guilty every
single time I say it but what is going
on I'm
fine I think all of this is just me
learning to cope with being an
individual human being and I'm enjoying
it but I do miss them like I'd love to
have done some stuff with them while I
was here um and this hotel room I'm in
is amazing but it has like compartments
where doors don't close and I'm deeply
afraid of sleeping with like open
hallways um so I'm a little terrified
right now and I wish I wasn't alone but
I had an amazing day today I'm going to
have an amazing day
tomorrow and I love you all
[Music]
hello everyone more boring Vlogs for my
end here I think we're like at the end
of fever town here um all I really have
right now is a headache and a like a
pretty bad cough um today I spent
watching professional lacrosse all
day and I also
spent some time when there was was a
professional lacrosse games I watched
the first Harry Potter I want to see I
feel like I could potentially be a Harry
Potter fan so like I'm trying to watch
those movies because I really do think
that it's in my potential to like those
movies um also no shock but I did a
bunch of laundry this is just like all
my stuff because obviously I've been the
only one here I just threw the blanket
on here I'm not really good at like
making my bed but I made my bed and
washed my sheets and everything because
I've just literally been like sweating
like a pig in them so I accidentally
washed this guy because he was under the
the blanket not sure if I was supposed
to but he's actually much softer so
maybe it was a it was a benefit Red Bull
shout out they sent us a bunch of [ __ ]
sorry guys the table's a mess cuz I
haven't cleaned it right by the lily
pads hold on ready Jimmy's the bro
oh [ __ ] Jimmy we might cross here oh
we're crossing Jim oh no he's good he's
out of the way yeah dude it's crazy I
was here once Nate and someone let their
dog like swim like out there look at
this kid got some more seaweed all right
hold on I got to get that fish back on
my
line Nate I just got a sick moment yeah
you were cat you were fishing and then
the birds flew by in the Flying V yep
look at that that's a beautiful thing
this could be your your uh your
wallpaper oh what the [ __ ] scared the
[ __ ] out of me I thought I was going to
get
hooked dud forgot to flip it oh right in
the lily pads oh watch out hold this oh
Nate right by the nature got to love
it oh right by the red bush oh yeah
don't don't cross lines here
nice cast Nate somebody I'm not going to
name names kind of made a bubble in the
in the rail I don't know who it was the
current cameraman no now we
have the the master the master
beta and his
trainee we need to get shirts that say
say that that say master like we're the
mastur baiters around here yeah no right
there oh I got to be quiet I thought I
saw something he's following oh he's
right behind you shake it shake it shake
it shake it he's coming what the [ __ ] is
that there's two of them oh yeah it's
hold on hold that here I got it I got it
I got glasses I can't see [ __ ] yeah give
CSS what the [ __ ] is that too bad I
can't there's two of them right there I
knew the bubbles look at that [ __ ] look
at that [ __ ] take it take it Dad lock in
for the Vlog it's too ter you see get
good content get good content dad you
got to get it oh my God I wish I had the
the uh the fish thing there's one right
there yeah get it do something make it
come closer make him come closer I'll
grab it with my hands if it gets close
enough I no dude you're just going to
bite your finger off if it's a snapping
where is it it's right there iar that's
a turtle right there oh don't hit me bro
I'm not I'm going to go
underand all right that wasn't far
enough n definitely not he's further
than that it's chill it's chill no yeah
I feel you bro we found a [ __ ] I
think fix we found a [ __ ] mini Shield
bro is it it's a mini shield from
fortnite a nice little B hold up
yeah to in a
fish yeah bring them over there bro
dancing look at that is that the one
with the teeth no that's a that's a bass
y yes sir oh I need to touch them it was
really just chilling Nate you got one
buddy yeah I'll fix this way in a second
wow that was quick
dude boom there he goes swimmy swimmy
I'mma catch him again just like that
catch and release Nate how do you feel
feel like a million bucks uh today is
sumers Sonic day two I think Madison
broke her
toe which is awesome I I obviously can't
Vlog this but I need everyone to know
how much I'm enjoying this experience
once Chris gets here I'll I'll be
relieved but I don't have like a feeling
of like damn I really miss them right
now it's kind of just like damn I I I
wish like Chris was watching this game
with me stuff like that but it's all
good um feeling way better on all
aspects today so great I feel super
super strange that I haven't seen Nick
and Matt it just feels like a part of me
is like gone but um yeah I'm having a a
lot of fun I miss Matt and Nick probably
at like a 10: now um I can't wait to see
them and just like exchange stories and
like tell them what I've done and what
and just talk about [ __ ] but um I mean I
think this is a great experience I'm
definitely more or less reliant on them
than I thought I was like emotionally
like I've been fine like I'm not like
devastated or sad or upset I just had
the best night of my life I'm not
explaining myself good night
[Music]
I woke up today and I wasn't feeling
like sick at all whatsoever just like a
a very very slight little bit and now
that it's later in the day I feel
perfectly fine I think today is my first
day without sickness which is so amazing
and I'm so happy just went out and got
gas for the car because I didn't get I
didn't leave the car with any gas when I
left for Boston I dropped film off
because Nick had a space camp photo
shoot before he left for Japan that's
what I did today I've also eaten the
same too like I've eaten soup for lunch
and chicken and rice for dinner from a
restaurant every single night um which
probably isn't good but I'm I'm
literally just like eating so
repetitively when Nick and Chris are
around I don't have enough time to like
actually like think about the things
that I would normally think about
throughout the day but now that they've
been gone for multiple days it feels
like I have like two too much time to
think and it's all just like hitting me
with like negative things and this and
that but it's it is strange it's it's
such a weird um weird feelings to have I
can't believe that I've haven't seen
Matt or Nick in person in like nine days
it genuinely blows my mind
like I just can't believe it I really
can't I think because I had Nathan it
wasn't as hard as I thought it was going
to be I'm very excited to see Matt Nick
still with Madison running around doing
whatever they're doing um breaking toes
and whatnot the girl's toe is purple
sent us a photo it's purple yeah I hope
they're having fun I know Matt was sick
so I hope he's feeling better I don't
want to get sick from whatever he had
[Music]
hey good morning everyone I'm about to
go zip
lining that was so fun I just did the
zip line and a bunch of people brought
their phones but I didn't cuz I think I
didn't think I could oh my God I just
got the [ __ ] scared out of me it's a big
ass bug right
here hi buggies big news I pick Chris up
from the airport tomorrow at
1:15 I think something like that but I'm
very very very excited to be with him
again and I would tell you the all those
stories about my day today and what
happened but I'd be lying if I didn't
just say that I watched two Harry Potter
movies lied in bed watched other content
throughout social media platforms and
ate powder
[Music]
Donuts what's up everybody I just took a
I just woke up and took a
shower um I have 45 minutes 45 minutes
in until Chris lands at the airport so
I'm going to get dressed and I will see
you guys then driving to the airport to
get
him good morning
everyone I'm walking to my gate at the
airport and it's surprisingly peaceful
and I'm actually enjoying myself which
is rare cuz I normally hate the airport
but this is like weirdly enjoyable right
now
all right guys I'm at the airport I hate
driving alone
especially in the circumstances that I
am in right now but we're making it work
like walk to 5f right now
5f I'm right it's right next to yeah
walk over here I'm right behind this
white car yeah I see it yeah I see you
okay yeah this [ __ ] sticker of 5f is
peeling it looks like 5 l okay you're
good all right chat I got Chris I've
been watching so much like live stream
stuff that I'm just calling everyone
chat here we
go there it
is what's up what up oh my God your
hands are cold yeah I'm
freezing
bro wow you're really like a uber you
got a water bottle for me that's for me
but you can have it well there's one
right here no I know I've been taking
like six everywhere I go I have to make
sure I'm hydrated mhm seat belt
buddy I hate the
airport hate the airport my least
favorite place in the world I think this
is vlogging I don't know yeah I don't
know if the mic is working
though I don't know man I don't see like
what Nick says he looks at as like the
mic thing you know what I mean let's
just pause it and replay it did you
slept the whole thing I slept two hours
at home last night and then I just slept
like pretty much the whole flight I
probably slept it's like annoying but
like I probably slept in like nine half
hour intervals that's like a half hour
woke up to something half hour woke up
something car but I was yeah I do but I
was sleeping like a good amount that's
good though
mhm I literally haven't done a thing by
myself I I know the flight attendant guy
was so lit he was like he was like do
you want something to eat bro and I was
like I'm good dude I'm probably honestly
going to like sleep the whole time he's
like all right if you change your mind
let me know that's nice I said I got you
I fell asleep pretty much the whole
flight like I was laying down and he he
like woke me up when we were descending
cuz I like I like slept through the
descending thing like he had to like
wake me up to put my chair up that's so
funny yeah and he was like damn bro I
didn't believe you but you really did it
I said that's how I do it bro I locked
inny was so funny and then he like daed
me up when we left he was a really funny
guy isn't it crazy you'll probably never
see him again in in our yeah that's like
how you think
bro dude I just said no we don't need to
Vlog me and Matt are together for the
first night in a
while so we're having some classic
brother
conversation it's 3:00 in the morning
all we did what did we do today Matt we
streamed yeah we did we streamed
together and we ate In-N-Out Burger mhm
and it was delicious but yeah we're
happy to be back back together yes we
are so much stuff to get
[Music]
done good morning everyone we leave
Singapore today Hard Rock
Singapore um I am going on a mini walk
by myself this
morning this [ __ ] is ass it's like hot
poured on
Ice oh God
not
bad it not red so they're more of that
Bluey gray color and a bit smaller oh my
goding oh my God she's so perfect he's
not just like a big tough male actually
is really really strategic and is like
body and makes things really sorry is
that him that was
insane he said [ __ ] that
ring hi big Angry
shim wow
this video for Matt and Chris only
lasted a week but for me it was like 2
and a half weeks of being
away and I'm packing I have to leave for
the airport in like 3 hours and I'm just
really really blessed really happy um
and I'm just really thankful and I'm
really happy and I'm proud of myself and
I've learned a lot about myself in an
individual setting and I think it's
amazing and I'm just really thankful
that I was able to do this and I'm
really thankful that I was brought and
welcomed into a team of people I'll see
you guys back in
La what's up everybody it's Matt and
Bucky here and we're here to tell you
some good news for those of you who are
confused by the Bucky that's in our
living room right now us and our tour
driver have built a very fond
relationship and he is driving another
artist around La right now for their
tour but they had a stop where there was
a Bucky so he bought this and surprised
us and put this in our living room and
it works perfectly because now not only
do we have party time Bucky we also
have this which is a giant welcome home
we missed you
sign and we also have six confetti
cannons we also have five people from a
mariachi band coming to our house at
7:00 in the morning
tomorrow all right guys we have some
friends with us now and they're here to
help us welcome Nick on this beautiful
what time is it on this beautiful
Tuesday morning at 6:43 in the morning
[Music]
what is
going I don't want Oh My go how are
you holy
[ __ ] I don't want that I don't want to
see her
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
luy
Dan so apprciate it thank you thank you
thank you wow welcome home Nick I just
had a heart attack I [ __ ] not anymore
our neighbors are going to hate us yeah
why are you guys awake so early we
didn't go to bed go get my suitcases you
didn't sleep no why we excited we so
excited we we have to wait for our
friends and everything oh my God welome
back welcome thank you were you
expecting wow I'm so tired I'm so
confused I was just in a different
country now I'm here that's it amazing I
heard the buck event I was like what is
that noise that's why I peaked over that
I was like what is
that oh my God welcome home thank you
thanks
everyone thank you very much
thanks I'm so confused I'm so
tired what the [ __ ] is happened that was
insane well just had heart
I had a heart
attack that was insane we've had that
plan since I was in Boston I figured I
knew you were going to do something I
just thought it was going to be like
later like I thought it was going to be
like when you woke up no Mariachi on
arrival bam that was so loud and insane
I heard the vent of the
Bucky and also why is Bucky here like
none of this adds up that is the
question of the hour we have Bucky and
Mariachi and confetti I wish I was more
like attentive to what was going on was
I me like dis that was like the first
ever total Blind
Side we've ever hit you in I wish I how
[ __ ] awesome was that that was really
insane that was all my idea by the way
my brain is like
super I thought I was awake enough for
the day but after that I guarantee you
I'm not because I am feeling like so
disoriented by that
I just can't believe there was five
people playing the Mariachi in our
living room a moment ago you can't
believe
it I can't believe I'm here I can't
believe I'm even in this house I'm so
tired too Memo's here too I know I said
hi how awesome was that that was not
until it says welcome home like that
entrance right there that was insane
that's never going to be T Nick Nick
texted me earlier and he goes he goes
you guys should be vlogging or like pick
me up from the airport and like we can
do something fun and I was like [ __ ] no
I'm going to be dead asleep that was so
intense imagine that that was so intense
I was like so shocked I thought I got
shot I was like debating like the whole
time I was talking to L I was talking to
Matt I was like should we just tell him
we have like a little surprise and then
like but we were like let's just like
really dude the poers I literally told
all the Marchi guys I was like these are
a little loud but like the second he
gets to the top of the stairs and see
something I crack that you guys
play yeah I'm sitting there Chris is
sitting there they're all around Bucky
the sign I was like what I hi guys what
do I do it's like that was like that was
like you know the awkwardness when
people sing Happy Birthday to you it was
that times a million like I'm like what
the [ __ ] do I do it we were like we were
like I'm still TR like we're triplets
and like there's two of us I literally
told them I go I go me look just like
the kid we're about to surprise so the
second you see someone who looks like us
hit the top of the stairs you I promise
you won't miss them that was you play I
hope what they were singing wasn't
copyrighted no they're good
[Music]