what am I getting a 12pack of tacos can
I
[Music]
get 12 packs of
tacos I want a large Pepsi Pepsi sh I
get two large Pepsis okay sorry I'm like
struggling right Now give me like one
second I accidentally drank detergent at
the house my tongue is actively going
numb Also may I just say I hope Taco
Bell never takes away this amazing party
pack
packaging why is it called a party pack
and not a fiesta pack Fiesta is like an
easy Spanish word to say I miss when
everything at Taco Bell was just Dorito
themed like I feel like every you could
Escape it you got cinnamon twist they're
slapping nido's thing we need a
soundtrack can we get that can you stop
talking I want like the Sam from I Carly
like blue box like Stern yellow triplets
and then Nick you just edit the Sounds
in I can actually do that really for
sure anyway anyway today's video me and
Nick or Nick came up with um and then
Matt doesn't know what we're filming so
I'm going to explain it okay today'll be
there the TV's on it's muted okay
clearly you can well light like it's BAC
and blue like I'm like kind of like this
right now basically Matt you're going to
be served your three tacos per usual and
you have to eat them as fast as you can
not happening yes yes it is well no you
don't have to eat them as pass yeah you
can take your time but here's the thing
every minute that passes while you're
eating we're going to ask you like an
relatively invasive I wouldn't say
invasive but more of uncomforting and
you have to a personal question that you
So the faster you eat the tacos the less
question questions you have to answer so
hypothetically if you do a minute perac
the minimum am amount of questions you
answer is three mhm okay yeah you go
first yeah can I have The Notebook I
want to ask the first question okay
ready what are the odds oh my God like
close your time
starts
now oh I shouldn't drank Matt Matt oh
wait did you start a timer okay yeah
thank
God this first question is going to
weigh a lot how fast let's talk more eat
let's talk more
like how uncomfortable this first one is
Less Talk More eat also like all right
Taco down Taco down t t down swallow
can't eat anymore you can swallow but
that's it your first question at the 1
minute Mark is have you ever had a crush
on a teacher yeah no you have to hey oh
my God time resume time resume tell us
about that though you don't want me to
go to
detail okay okay
okay one taco down two to go there's
really not much to elaborate on in that
in that sense guys I'm really scared I'm
like not hungry at all you better eat
kid you're 30 seconds away from your
next
question all right 2om minute Mark Taco
down but you can
swallow and then I'm going to look for
your next question while you finish that
what is your guiltiest pleasure song and
when was the last time you like listened
to it and got into the groove
um
I got to check I'm not like guilty about
any of the songs that I listen to I'm
really
not like the song that you'd be like
embarrassed if it was playing on Ax Matt
you don't have like a guilty pleasure
song like Fergalicious or something like
that not really boring well I don't like
I don't know come on you don't don't
sing like a girly pop song in the shower
I do actually bags by claro is not like
a guilty pleasure song that's a that's a
really good song well it's not something
like you would see me listening to okay
well Matt we need an answer still it's
not like a guilty pleasure song that's
not embarrassing that you listen to that
song I want something about like sheer
embarrassment if like you hit Shuffle on
all your songs and this plays in the car
it's not guilty though I would put this
on aux and I'd be everybody in the car
is turning up with me can you just
answer the
question don't you wish you were us on
the lemonade soundtrack lemonade
absolute Banger of course this one hold
on hold on hold on hold
on I can't even that song's awful oh my
God grow up all right resum all right
[Applause]
resume all right 3 minutes in Taco down
let's get this next question you had a
taco and a quarter left I'm having a
really good Pace what are the first
three things you look for in a
significant other that they have a
sibling oh that's a good because because
not only do do I think that some sorry
to all the only children out there not
only do I think that some of the only
children out there are are like a little
weird but also I I want like whoever I'd
be talking to to understand like like
your relationship with me no one ever
will though and that's the beauty of it
they won't but it's like the closest
that I can to get to that point CU then
it makes everything else easier cuz it's
like that's like a big thing about oh
yeah you like if they have a good
relationship with their siblings like oh
that like you'll understand that Dynamic
mat that was such a beautiful
heartwarming
answer yay thanks bud I said this to
Chris the other day really strange
really strange I don't remember this yes
you do okay if they can rock like a
men's polo shirt okay okay yeah you did
something like wear a men's polo shirt
and look cool with it on yes I love that
and then just I guess goals and
aspirations of their own Matt you're
such a
good I just love your answer it made me
so excited to hear that I don't know why
a yes it's okay is that
good he's like checking out his list
yeah he's super thrilled about this all
right eat that taco
resume all right time's up is there
something you feel guilty about right
now stupid question no no it's not Matt
you have to answer there's not much that
I feel guilty about right now okay you
don't have to feel guilty right now what
do you like most recently feel guilty
about doing come on get a little deep
with us stop like talking the side of of
you you we've never seen I just
stuttered so bad that was insane yeah
what's like the most recent thing you
did that you feel guilty about it I
don't really feel guilty about it but I
guess sometimes when I'm like in my room
half awake or like in my room on my
phone or something like that one of you
guys will scream my name from in this
room and I'll just pretend like I don't
hear and then you have to and then you
have to walk into my room and then like
you'll still be like hey and then I'll
be like pretending to be asleep cuz I'm
just like I just really don't care oh my
God and then you'll wake me up and then
I'll be like what you pretend you can
pretend to wake up like that if someone
walks into oh I pretend to wake up all
the time I can pretend to be asleep but
I can't pretend and then I relist I'm
going to start tip toing your door like
Santa like this and
then and then I and then I relisten to
what I already heard you say in the
other room you're such a weird kid all
right you have 1 minute to finish this
taco and you escape your final question
stop like go quick there's clock started
I got
it all right three tacos down for Matt
and 4 minutes and 30 seconds he only had
to answer four questions I'm proud of
you Matt all right ready first
bite all right get it last bite in you
like 3
seconds oh my God stop stop
no you're not real all right Chris is
done the biggest bite known to
man question what is the most romantic
thing you have ever done oh God I don't
think tell us about it what's the most
romantic thing you've ever done I don't
even think I can answer this question
yes you could what's the most romantic
thing I've ever done think about it most
romantic thing ever this is a
w forgot about you got a [ __ ] no
second penalty
forut 5c penalty are we serious dead
100% serious oh I hate this question I
don't
[Applause]
care stop
touch Matt you're going to give me a
[ __ ] concussion that's the one spot
that little MMA fighters aren't allowed
to hit the back of the head to me all
the time you're going to like I think
the most romantic thing I've ever
done can you [ __ ] answer the question
I don't I've never endured that probably
like hand handwritten
letters course got no Riz clock it right
now basically no Riz basically I've just
never dated somebody I've never been on
like a date in my life like at like a
dinner that doesn't mean you can't do
romantic things what why why did our
sink just shock in water the Gremlins
are coming out one time after one of our
shows I I knew which room Matt was
staying in in the hotel so I made like a
rose pedal Trail all the way the
room
question from the tour bus I made a rose
pedal Trail let's answer the question I
I just I know that there's a deeper no
there's avoiding it no there's not the
most romantic thing you've ever done is
it is probably handwritten letters to
somebody that's like the most romantic
gu from
cholo slow down like it's not worth it
the question's not worth the hospital
trip [ __ ] oh I'm not hungry blah blah
blah you're
you're going to Lodge tortilla into the
back of your you're taking care of these
fall the back of your
neck no eat I was going to You Make Me
Laugh 2 minutes 2 minutes Taco down Taco
down Taco down okay Chris's second
question how long have you gone without
showering real answers only I mean a
weekend is like obvious though like
that's like I feel like anyone's answer
would be like oh like a weekend okay um
there's been times like if we go
somewhere like cape for the weekend or
like Vermont or whatever you have to
keep in mind says weekend he means like
long weekend like get there I mean
Saturday and Sunday I mean the two
[ __ ] days of the weekend idiot well
you've showered you've gone without
showering longer than that like I think
on a road trip I know the oh my [ __ ]
God I know the answer so you didn't ask
the peanut gallery like dude I haven't
even answered the question I would say
like we traveled somewhere on a Monday
didn't shower that night Saturday Sunday
didn't shower and then like showered um
no Friday Saturday Sunday on like the
Monday morning it's like shower Friday
morning and then not showering till
Monday
morning yeah okay I feel like I've done
the same like 4 days probably that's not
days that's a different but that's like
if I really don't have shower you
sugarcoated that well you almost snuck
that
PN that's okay that's is the weekend
yeah Friday morning to Monday yeah like
4 days no that's like if I really didn't
have a shower around you do you just
don't use it I understand that and like
traveling and Stu sometimes it's just
like access and yeah I also like don't
stink ever no none of us would ever
smell bad I'd clock you guys immediately
if you smell like [ __ ] I agree I agree
but like I if I'm not sweating and like
dripping sweat I'm like I don't if I do
nothing for 3 days what's the point in
showering yeah I don't smell bad I still
apply deodorant every day like brush my
teeth all the regular [ __ ] but like I'm
not going to like fully get in the
shower and like I know the stank
allegations yeah I don't smell bad you
know no Matt really set you up for
constantly saying you smell bad and
don't shower cuz like it's like that's
he's like he's a kid you know so like
little kid and you going me a tough guy
so it's two things that we least tough
isn't attacking your sanitary needs yeah
like you're you're saying something
that's not real you act tough and I get
called tough and get pissed about care
all right time
resume
third question okay give me the inside
scoop on what the perfect Chris yellow
date night looks
like if I'm dating somebody they have to
get along with all my friends and peers
okay so ideally maybe maybe I'll go to
like dinner all not like all like all go
out and do something like me and like is
this like a super like intimate like
just being the first it's a first date
it's on group hang out really what's the
perfect date you've never been on a date
what's your perfect ideal date probably
like an activity of some sort that's fun
together like what's the activity oh my
God can I get to the [ __ ] can I have
a millisecond like bowling or like Top
Golf cute fun mini golf something along
what you guys getting a top golf like
pretzel bites the share biting them in
half you wish no I don't I can care L
bowling or like how are you get in there
you ubering or she picking you
up hey relax well no top golf serves
food and so does bowling so I feel like
we'd have probably a couple like
appetizers there that's all right and
then so we're not going to be like full
like we're not going to be like hungry
but we're not going to be like full okay
so like probably like somewhere where we
can just like relax like for food no
like after
after no we already ate at the activity
as well so then probably like maybe like
the beach or like a walk in the park or
like somewhere to just walk in the park
if we're hungry again go to dinner again
W oh my God what timer I thought that I
thought M said Date Night Like This is a
full day for me like an Excursion I like
booked the driver we might as well
utilize it all day I so like maybe
dinner again but if she's not hungry
then like we'll just go get ice cream
and then go if she's not hungry get ice
cream
okay good job Chris Chris beat Matt's
time and he got 3 minutes in 30 seconds
and only had to answer three questions
wa knock
knock who's there salad salad l
[Laughter]
in 1 minute I already know which
question all right we got it all right
you're getting a two for one lucky you
when in your life were you the happiest
and when in your life were you the
saddest
I'd say it's so hard to say when in your
life were you the happiest cuz the true
answer is probably when I was like eight
or something oh my
god when I was like a little kid I was a
very happy little kid yeah like I loved
being a little kid y i loved hang out
with Mom and doing with stuff with Mom
all the time like going to the zoo with
Mom or go shopping with Mom so probably
when I was eight but Nick I'm like
really sad no I'm so
upset oh my God yeah probably I was 8
years old a loaded
question start
crying that's so crazy I instantly
started crying talking about being 8
years
old I did not expect to cry I just got
really emotional cuz I really agreed
with you oh my God like I really just
like f that was the first first time I
think that was the first time I think
emotion has ever just like come up to me
like that choked me out I fully agree I
feel BR I think it's the vulnerable
state of
it I'm literally right there with you
like it's you this is the first time I'm
like crying in content this is so
embarass that was a lot I literally just
like my
eyes that was a lot my eyes started like
watering and [ __ ] like that was cuz I
have like baby photos in my head
yeah like
dude it's like funny but it's not you
know you're the cutest kid ever I know I
was adorable oh my god dude that's
crazy that was
shocking I wrote that question down
earlier
too oh
my God so wild dude happiest part I was
eight I'd also say like our birthday we
turn 19 was like one of the best days of
my life with Nathan and MADD white
through tears I know I'm like really St
too I just think like instantly related
like I would have said the same yeah and
then I'd say sadus is
probably like junior year like but no
cuz it wasn't Co it was like I'd say
when things were normal again after Co
yeah senior year yeah like things being
normal again after Co I like loved my co
life you have the identical response
that I would have had cuz I loved my co
life cuz I was like I was gay and just
like at home and didn't have to deal
with anybody or anything and then
leaving like the safe haven of like Co
at home was just exhausting no being
going to school for like senior year
with Co like and Co being a thing and
like just that whole I hated senior year
so much I would I regret every single
thing other than YouTube I age us three
pursuing YouTube was the only beneficial
thing that happened that year in my
opinion check K agree yeah I agree
shocking first Taco I can't believe what
video we're filming and that yeah like
dude I was just crying right with you oh
my God that was so much but I also think
of like senior year and I think like for
us three as a core brother best
Brotherhood and like like grouping
together starting YouTube together and
like chasing our dreams it was like also
the highest point of my life so it's
like weird to say that's the saddest but
I think it's just cuz like I learned the
most about like the reality of life and
that's what was sad about
yeah but like other than that like the
journey was super like exciting like
graduating high school is always going
to be sad and like moving on not even
graduating high school it wasn't even
that that I cared about yeah I was so
happy to graduate oh my God I was ready
to get up and leave bro all right ready
Nick we're going next taco okay I'm
Ready set
go Taco
down when and where did you go on your
first date ever I'm trying to think cuz
I I feel like actual date was like a
pizza
place and it was
like I don't even remember when what was
that Junior sophomore
mm- what is one memory you really want
to never forget our 19th birthday
yeah and I'll say I don't think this is
a memory I'm like actively trying to not
forget but hitting 4 mil while we were
on our first tour and like randomly
being in Texas like the way that all
lined up is something I don't think I
will forget yeah like four mil in Texas
on our tour at a meet and greet yeah
that's something I never saw I do agree
like you have 1 minute Nick to clear
this
Taco 3 minutes and 51 seconds to clear
three tacos all right well that was
today's video all right guys the
questions that we avoided a answering is
what is your worst memory from your
childhood what triplet brother has
annoyed you most this week um how many
times have you been in love with
somebody when was the last time you
cried and why what's the what's your
grossest habit and what's the last thing
that you lied about and how long have
you gone without brushing your teeth and
none of us have to answer those because
we ate our tacos F I'm definitely down
to do a part two of this video with like
a different style food or something and
we are on the road to 6 million
subscribers we have a special video
planned for 6 mil that includes a
special merch drop So the faster you get
us there the faster that will happen
make sure you hit the Subscribe button
if you're on the channel we have a big
percent of people that watch our videos
that don't even subscribe so make sure
so make sure you subscribe so you don't
miss a video um we post every Friday
Wednesday for
now and um thank you for tuning in we
love you dab on them dab on the haters
dab on them dab on them dab and remember
when things go right when things go when
things go wrong stick by people you love
and support spread kindness spread
positivity and think twice before you
act negatively Amen
[Music]
period