all right guys almost a year ago we
filmed this video which is insane um but
yeah almost a year ago this pretty viral
clip was birth of me crying during the
last time we filmed this when in your
life were you the happiest and when in
your life were you the
saddest so probably when I was eight but
ni I'm
like I'm so
upset start
crying that's so crazy I instantly
started crying talk about being 8 years
old so basically what we're going to do
today is a video series that we do
called Truth or eat and it's becoming a
video series with this video because
this is the second part correct um and
what we're going to do is we need to eat
three tacos like we did last time but
Matt wanted in and out so he's his
challenge is a little different he's
going to eat an entire [ __ ] burger
and fries and fries bading already going
to suffer with questions so I need to be
pleased in in a food manner of things
and I did not want to eat you're setting
yourselves up to eat to answer more
questions I wanted to eat Taco Bell last
night and I did tonight I'm eating
In-N-Out you fatties are eating Taco
Bell I did not have Taco Bell
yesterday who are you lying to I did not
eat Taco Bell only I did
[ __ ] who are you lying to no I'm
not lying every single minute that
passes while you are trying to eat your
food you you will be asked one of the
invasive questions we have printed out
on this piece of paper and however long
how many minutes it takes you to eat is
how many questions you will have to
answer until 1 minute one question 10
minutes 10 questions so on so forth
until your you have to eat all your food
in front of you in order to stop the
question asking all right the second
Matt starts eating this video is going
to start you want to sit in the middle
yeah that's the point now you you look
very patriotic
today here I'll make it easier for you
yeah I do all right well what are you
doing ready waa start
it
you where you just like start scarfing
down the food like a [ __ ] wolf scarf
that reminds me of the winter retire
item you can
wear okay freak chug jug CH such a weird
word if you think about it
chug and oh my God we're weird that was
me being you that's why we said the same
thing I like we're like doing this like
thing here all right 1 minute minute
burer down question number one what is
the worst piece of content of you on the
internet that if you could erase
entirely you would get rid of I uh I
have like five Instagram accounts that I
made when I was like anywhere between
the age of 8 to I'd say 13 14 and I
would probably banish those off of the
internet just another day at baseball
just another day not fun yeah it is I
know that this question wasn't for Chris
either but I feel like if you were to
answer it he'd definitely say his like
archery Instagram
account and You' say the Dark Horse
music video and the Super Cuts video and
your entire YouTube channel that you
have that has almost enough for a
YouTube plaque now of people us playing
the piano you know all those yeah like
we' all have really good answers to this
question me and Nick when we were
younger some lady in the mall came up to
me I remember and she asked she's like
oh my God like she told my dad she's
like your kid should be a model like
that'd be awesome and it got me thinking
I was like wait like I low key could
probably do that and then me and Nick
went home and he was in the like
photography oh my God and I was like
Chris like I got you like we can do the
whole photo shoot and we did a photo
shoot and I the photos never hit the
internet but they're in like one of my
like on my drives or something and I
like a full photo shoot of Chris like
hardcore modeling like 10 different like
seasonal outfits and they are insane wow
I'm waiting for you guys to be done I'm
H it's crazy I L we set up a blue
backdrop and it's like me with like a
bucket hat and yeah we had like summer
winter it was amazing here wait you get
question number two okay get ready he
has 15 seconds till question number
two I have one of 2 minutes oh you're
smart you're smart why cuz the rules
that you can finish what's in your mouth
and at like a minute 59 seconds he
[ __ ] pile drove a full [ __ ]
quarter a burger straight into his
[ __ ] hole I hate the last piece ni
come on yeah I'm ready can I get a water
yeah you can you want to grab me one or
what can you ask him question number two
what's going on oh I thought he was
going to get a water I thought so too he
thinks I'm going to I don't need the
water right
now I'm not getting it out I'll get it
share the last 10 things you Googled
okay I did this cuz I'm genuinely
curious like what this kid like started
I don't want to know it's probably like
weirdo that's the weird the weirder part
of this yeah this is like personal to
chy wants to know your Google search
history tell me tell me big booty
[ __ ] stop Wordle words that start
with e r Supreme best protein shakes cuz
I was in the store looking at them and
didn't know which one was the best
snowfall Bazookas
bazook what I wanted to hear can we
share a story or not yeah we were
talking to one of our friends and me and
I were yeah we were having a
conversation and friend was fully con
that they that they saw somebody in
their apartment building with a with a
bazooka like you mean an RPG
like said that is not possible yeah we
promise you no one did like an armed
robbery with a bazooka yes Booka in La
nothing oh that was your seventh one mhm
bazooka and bazooka in La Little Miss
Sunshine is a movie that I wanted to
watch that's cute that's sweet that's
really nice what's the movie about who's
in the movie Nick I'm going to kill you
um and then houses on Zillow why not
Robert Paton Batman showing love him I
love him Zoe kravit in that movie with
like the pink wig that's a good that's a
good Google search 10 can we get a round
of applause for the Google search I
don't know what
yeah stop question number three hold on
like you didn't do a good like Stop
fries down whatever go
ahead go trying to arrest stop minute
three put down the prize all right Nick
new question time question number three
too many Beast games let good who is
your least favorite person one of your
brothers have ever introduced to you wow
that's intense actually one of your
friends from a couple years ago who why
would I say on the inter yeah like what
do you want me to say to answer this
question the guy that you brought over
once
I love him wow that's a lot if that
that's the least favorite want that's
least favorite no that's not least
favorite I don't know okay we're going
to ask you two questions because I want
to it's I want no he has fries still
yeah but I want to ask him another one
for this one we have to see if it gets
to that one wasn't a good question
you're ask a different one yeah what's
the [ __ ] point of this game have you
ever felt your brothers didn't have your
back oh here we go with some corny
[ __ ] and when yes with Nick never
ever bringing in groceries ever a day in
his life every single time that's having
your back yeah what against the grocery
monster no against who uh the groceries
for 14 years you against the groceries I
didn't have your back is name get better
at this I didn't have your back I didn't
know the groceries were calling you name
I like that he said you though like I
would no I would say any time I'm in an
argument most of the time it's like with
anyone ever that's not you which is like
kind of because you're most of the
arguments I have but most of the time
you like agree with your siblings or
like oh yeah I'll help my siblings out
here if you're opinion is against mine
you won't help me out with any against
who any argument I ever have or any
person I disagree with whether it's
Chris whether anything you say if you
argue with someone I'm not going to
agree with you not at all very wow Nick
that's like hurtful I don't believe that
okay you don't have to believe it that's
actually crazy like an outside person
yeah just anybody that like if I
disagree with somebody Nick actually
instead of being like Oh that's my
brother I should agree with him plays
the logic C well you're not going to get
that you're right if you're just my
brother correct and I don't expect to
you just don't if you're wrong in a
scenario and someone else is right
they're right never wrong
okay 10 seconds stop his very little
fries left so probably isn't going to go
to a question five last question for
Matt what's a moment in your life that
you are most ashamed
of
no I don't want to
know I'd rather eat a brick than answer
that question that's why that's
literally why I asked that one I knew we
didn't want to answer what are you most
ashamed of I don't think you're filled
with much shame don't rub my no I'm just
sad are we going to have a crying part
two now
no I wouldn't say I have a specific
moment but anytime that I just lacked
confidence to do things that I wanted to
I didn't like that answer
that really didn't clarify a moment of
time I want a specific moment that you
are ashamed of what Mato did I've never
been ashamed other than
that is this guy the worst at answering
questions or never been in a car
accident never got arrested never did
anything bad growing up um oh you're
perfect Disney movie not saying a
perfect just don't really know what to
say what about being a [ __ ] ass [ __ ]
sure that could be it
you should be ashamed of not answering
this question sure I am I don't have
anything that I'm all right I'm going
nexted watch out good job Matt give me
get a round of applause for
Matt I am such a good Clapper like I can
make a
clap you're a freak no like if there was
like a crow and you're about to get
cheered on I'm what are you say like if
you want to get cheered on I'm your guy
like I can make it clap you guys are
about to be blown away at this point I I
am like my goal is to only answer two
questions shut the [ __ ]
[Music]
up oh my God
disgusting 45 seconds
down 10 seconds left just get something
in your mouth whatever you got whatever
you get in your mouth you can swallow 5
seconds left big fight all right stop
[ __ ] I shouldn't have gone last cuz
literally looking at you is making my
stomach like turn like it's gonna be so
hard for me to
eat kid kid ate so much his posture fix
he
said he's got to make sure that
esophagus is straight narrow it's a
straight shot question number one what
is something you have done that you
don't want your future kids to
know oh my God I would probably say with
was terrible in school ditched like a m
a ton of classes and got like a bunch of
failing grades like I want my kids to
know that I was like a high school loser
boring you know your kids know you were
a high school Loser yeah like I
literally got like Fs in every single
class I barely passed every single class
I was ever in not true boring answer I
graduated high school but I barely made
it through every single class like
literally I got like you don't think
there's anything else you don't want
your kids to know I'm thinking I was
thinking something way more juicy and
crazy than that like yeah like I was
thinking like I know you haven't met
your future wife so you I would say
slept with a woman that isn't their mom
how about
that I mean that's like a given in my
eyes though like I don't care about that
[ __ ] thought I feel like every kid has
to know their parent like has been with
more than just their mom right no we
we're waiting till marriage and I mean
yeah that's like a decent one but that's
like nothing
crazy I don't want my kids to know how
much money I have why because I think
grow you going to be
expector oh I hate expector I tell Nick
this all the time I hate when people
expect things I don't want your kids to
know that I'm the Easter Bunny cuz I'm
going to be hop hop hopping around and
giving them gifts okay weirdo I'm going
to be no but that's true like I want my
kids to grow up humble and appreciative
for everything and even if I'm not like
what are you going to do your kids why
does Uncle Nick have kids he does not
want kids and he cannot buy a l of his
own so if he if he wanted kids why can't
he biologically have kids because he gay
so that means so what does that mean
that means when a boy meets a girl and a
penis goes in a vagina that's how a
child what's a vagina a vagina is a
woman's
[Laughter]
penis
oh vagina is a woman's penis is
unbelievable
what the
[ __ ] that's the craziest thing I've ever
heard Ready set
go
hey those shoulders can
move SL down 30 seconds it is so unfair
that you guys make me laugh when I do
this it's going to be easy for me cuz I
don't find either of you funny so wrong
oh I'll make you laugh I'll literally
tickle your butt I'll I'll TCH your
butt stop question number two what's the
weirdest thing you have done in private
when nobody is around you um I don't
want to know to answer this question I
have full formal conversations with my
stuffed animal chip yeah but you're
[ __ ] freak talk to chip yeah like one
day I was downstairs with chip and we
were like sitting down and I asked him
something and he obviously didn't
respond and I go you don't talk much
Chip Chip he doesn't talk much yeah then
he looked at me like
this is that what is that the same face
he's always making yeah and then I was
like all right all right chip it's fine
and then I like be playing video games
and I like be playing fortnite and then
I'll die I'll go [ __ ] and I'll lean back
like this I'll see chip on my bed I'll
go and then I'll turn back around
actually that I give W like chip a wave
sometimes if he's looking at all right
because on Matt's second question or
because on Matt's third question we
asked him two questions we're going to
ask you another question for this round
too okay what is the most awkward fan
interaction youve you ever had anything
that's right outside our house always is
very awkward cuz I'm like trying to like
not give away that my residency uhhuh um
so whenever I'm walking outside like
right outside my house and someone's
like oh my God are you Chris and I'm
like yes and they're like can we take a
photo and I say not right now please cuz
I actually live here it's a very hard
thing cuz I never like declining fan
photos but when I live in where the
background of the photo would be I just
don't I'd ra I take a safety precaution
if I don't want my house on the internet
one time I literally had some girl
literally go no it's okay real quick and
like took the selfie and like our house
was like in the back and I was like okay
I was in the store and I was like
shopping and I hear
like and I'm like I I jumped cuz I'm in
a store and I literally like flinched
and went like this and I like look and
this was just some nice girl who like
asked for a photo and stuff you got to
eat that meat you got to eat that meat
scoop that meat up and eat it
and you're done eating but you're still
chewing at the 3 minute Mark so you have
to answer another question absolutely
only 3 minutes is good that's impressive
yeah get out of here Chris question
number three almost missed
your zip it out of his chin for a second
how many times has Chris sto ever been
in love with somebody I literally like
hate you so
much it's not even a bad the girls want
to know the girl girls want to know the
world wants to know all right shut us up
no I feel like I should have like a
[ __ ] like a satchel a newspaper and a
bell be like Chris turn YOLO stop doing
that and I can't change even if I
tried even if I wanted to drink a Tik
Tok to that
song I Can't
Change she can't
see shout up my being a
friend my love my love my love she keeps
me little when I was little as a gay kid
and I heard that song it resonated with
me cuz I was like okay I'm gay but then
when she was singing like oh she keeps
me warm I was like I don't get it I
don't get it cuz it was like since it
was a lesbian but the songs about being
gay it was like confusing me cuz I was
like I know I'm gay but I don't I don't
want to like it was still it was gay but
it was talking about women and I was
like I'm like not I'm not with this side
of it yeah but I was just like confused
you know what I mean can't be said skip
I love this song it's it's a great song
I just like couldn't believe I was still
confused listening to
lesbians I love lesbians anything else
Nick El
[Laughter]
lesbian any need more lesbian friends if
you're lesbian and you live in LA hit me
up I saw a Snapchat are you going to
answer the last I'm I had something to
say based on what you're saying
how you say how many times has Cho ever
been in love you just say one and then
we can move on we'll Edge everyone we'll
Edge everyone because you want to answer
the questions in a different order flash
themed flash them I'm not at one Matt
like dead ass like why would it be one
what one what person that I've ever been
in love with mat how many people have
you ever been I think I met like three
three yes that's news to me in love with
three people can I get a list off camera
like an itemized but why I am the way I
am as Chris YOLO is cuz I think that I
can be in love with somebody but still
be fine with not doing anything about it
oh yeah that's horrible
yeah no actually I've definitely been in
love
once there I love
him
not even if I
tried even if I wanted to
and I can't change all right guys it's
my
[Music]
turn what would you do if it rained
ground beef and then like it was like a
lightning strike and a huge
me you meatball fell from the sky boy I
got the movie for
you cuz it's like Cloudy with a Chance
of Meatball
so it's like the meatballs are that
chance like the lightning strike
chance they're spaghetti everywhere and
then there's a talking monkey with a
black hat on instead of a
headband three two one stop Taco down
Taco down that's good PA that's good
PA you said I'm going to eat these slow
you just crushed the taco in 60 seconds
I wasn't
trying I wasn't trying to go
fast
Taco do it do
it like a chimp question number one what
is the dumbest thing you have ever cried
about uhoh no I'm not going to cry for
sure in the cad I'm for sure not Cadence
of I'm for sure not going to cry okay
guaranteed it takes a lot for me to cry
usually that's why last year when we
filmed this video it was so shocking to
me that all I had to do dude you have a
gray hair like a really prominent can
you take a photo of it cuz this just
shows that I'm really stressed out I'm
really stressed out like a really Matt
you're on the opposite side of my
head look for more cuz I thought I saw
one but I was like oh I'm tripping
unless it's just a hair that's like
falling out of your head Chris can you
please not say this I
see this might make me cry you need to
just calm down that's like a full solid
pure white
hair that's like [ __ ] crazy Nick I
need a vacation like I'm not trying to
be corny I need to like destress I need
to all the stress you have in your life
you put on yourself we just hire a big
strong man to dstress Nick Matt what do
you think that's the craziest it takes a
lot for me to cry for sure so that's why
I think like the stupidest things that
make me cry is like Instagram real
sometimes like if it's like 6:00 a.m.
and I'm like in my bed yesterday I was
literally crying last night because I
saw a video of a little kid and he went
back to the school that he used to go to
and the kids lined up to hug him yeah
and it just reminded me our youth and
when you're kids there's so much less
judgment from other people and it
matters to you less what other people
think of you and that you're not
thinking about like other people in like
such an intense and deep level you just
know who you like like to be around you
love going to school and you're just
like a happy little kid so that's why
it's like seeing videos of kids like
happy to be around each other is so
devastating cuz they're also going to
like not go to that school anymore like
not be friends at some point and it's
like
sad 3 2 1 Taco down Taco down question
number two what is the biggest lie you
have ever never told your parents I'm
straight cuz Mom and Dad have been
watching too many videos recently so
like they're guaranteed going to see
this don't know if I've told this story
on the Internet or not before I'm really
scared me too I like chills I know when
we were younger whenever I would log on
to Clash of
Clans I told this story I owe mom money
for that then I still haven't paid her
back but I used to every single time I'd
log on to Clash of Clans it would like
give me gems and I'd be like yeah like
it's a hack like I like I I jail broke
the game like it's a hack and every
single time I was going on I was going
to the store and then hitting gems and
it was like charging my mom's credit
card and then actually she got like a
$700 bank statement from like iTunes and
she showed it to us three and she was
like is this you guys and we were like
no that is none of us and I didn't know
like that's absolutely not meh no I
think you're being
hacked um and then we all went with her
to the bank and I remember sitting in
the room seeing her tell the person who
works at the bank that it wasn't any of
us and that like her cards got hacked
and then fully canceled her cards and
got new card numbers and it was me who
spent the money on it I owe my not only
did I do that and cause that stress to
Mom but I also owe her like 700 bucks do
you think she knows I have no idea I
haven't paid her back how old were we
like 15 oh my God old enough to know
better for sure what is the gayest thing
you've ever
done you don't want to
know you're [ __ ] weirdo what if your
taco was like secretly going to explode
in your
[Music]
stomach that be horrible like IM imagine
all sitting here and we like just
talking you really think we're cartoon
characters
question number three what's a memory
you wish you could erase forever my
genuine and honest answer to this
question is nothing because I think that
your memories and like like I would have
the same answer if like oh if you could
time travel to the Past would you
absolutely not like I think changing a
erasing a memory or changing the past it
[ __ ] with like the butterfly effect
like if I forgot something that I like
want to forget all right all right all
right kill this [ __ ] what's the real
answer the real answer is probably when
I was probably like seven or eight and I
thought I had to fart and I probably I
[ __ ] in my bed and I crab walked out of
it and I had to throw my pants away or
that or I was in my favorite that one
won't affect the butterfly no it won't
that one get rid of that one later and
then another time that one actually
might crucially affect I might [ __ ] my
pants later by accident cuz I'm not as
cautious but one time I was super sick
as a kid and I was like probably like
nine and and I was wearing my favorite
Scooby-Do matching pajamas set and I was
[ __ ] my brains out I was sick and I
was screaming and crying I was like Mom
I'm going to throw up and she came in
the room while I was [ __ ] on the
toilet and like held the barrel and was
like sitting by me and like consoling me
and I threw up all over my pajamas and
her while while I was [ __ ] I wish I
could erase that memory for me and mom
cuz it was I was a disgrace what's the
hardest goodbye you ever had to say
to Tik Tok okay goodbye everyone see you
next Friday my neck my back
[Music]