[ __ ] you in sign language dude I've been
saying because my whenever I shave my
name
and then what you're saying how you miss
me
[Music]
that's the intro
you know today we're gonna make each
other cringe or try not to we're gonna
start try not we're gonna try and make
each other cringe challenge we're
actually doing to start and then we're
gonna switch into something else Yeah we
actually doing it what do you mean boy
what are those
like I actually can't do that what you
mean bruh I don't know like I want you a
baby you little baby goo goo and Gaga
what are you gonna do one about a credit
or Mom
where my hug at
oh
Luis should give me a hug
bro where's my hug at dude bro
no bro what the hell man nah you ain't
gonna give me a hug
foreign
[Laughter]
guys hey mamas
for real for real can we like frill
where my hook at
give me a squeeze
that one's bad okay wait what's the
worst you mean boy
what's the worst what's the worst like
pickup lines or [ __ ] like that that
you've heard like in real life like
somebody actually try to use
what you're doing over there besides
looking good
that's really [ __ ] I've heard that
one before have you yeah when um give me
the rundown
actually
someone use that who
can you bleep it out well like go like
this
that's who
um
oh somebody's sprinting through the
parking lot full speed where what the
[ __ ] bear
this person has been scoping can you
forget something I'll flock the car
doors okay for oh my God should we leave
that's not I think we're good no they're
running why is she running if she was
gonna attack us shooting right running
at the car
what the [ __ ] okay are we done trying to
make each other crank should we move
into the next no definitely not what's
like the worst pickup line that would
that was yours yeah I don't I've never
feel like scooter man on a scooter oh
love is fit dude what is good what the
[ __ ] is going on I hope this car's
driving at us I feel weird we choose the
weirdest places I think it's just weird
Mama's hey hello Nick don't wait well I
was just like goodbye you waving someone
that makes it we just we choose the
weirdest places it's just like a lot
happens I don't know okay anyway because
I've never heard a pickup I'm not
acrobatic I am flipping on my Bros
nothing's worse than Disneyland line
couples
what's your favorite thing to do like at
the Disney line now because there's
always oh you jump through the whole
like stand on the metal pole yeah
there's always people playing heads up
on them like jump up and down we were
heads up people yeah we were I refuse to
ever go to Disney again though no yeah
that [ __ ] pains me she asked me with
my hoodie well then say something funny
bro
say something funny man
make me cringe cringy default I'm a
renegade Raider
Brooke you didn't build in [ __ ]
fortnite bro you're dog water Bro you've
never beaten talk to me when you've beat
in Minecraft
how do you [ __ ] beat Minecraft slay
the Ender Dragon you don't even know
like you win mine
okay that was Goofy you don't even know
how to you don't even know how to craft
what you mean boy
uh he literally loves video games okay
no I can't do this I can't do that there
are 10 but they wear skinny jeans oh
zero
well I feel like it's different for
girls men and skinny jeans it's kind of
like no anybody in skinny jeans I feel
like there's anybody in skinny jeans
well when men
what is going on
honestly it depends because truly wears
skinny jeans and we leave
you know what I mean we go to our other
parking lot no we're good here okay you
know what I mean like oh you truly can
pull off skinny jeans Patrol's the only
person I've ever seen pull off ski jeans
I think it's because he's tall I agree
there were 10 but they have a terrible
music taste someone will force you to
listen to it zero absolutely zero who
puts [ __ ] like this what there are 10
but they're weirdly attracted to his or
her cousin
such a severe problem that I'm not even
raiding them yeah I'm like I'm in a
minute
administrator I'm
you got it I'm submitting them to like
the psych ward yeah or go get that fixed
or like you and your cousin need to move
far the [ __ ] away yeah I agree or a
conversation is that that's not even
like oh rate them on a one to ten like
they like their cousin that's like let's
have a cousin that you like forget your
cousin Loki
no we have cousins that like I remember
or my cousin I'm like whoa
like you know like those thirds no it's
more yeah but it's also there's more
it's actually I found myself more in a
situation saying like damn that person's
not my cousin but they feel like my
cousin oh yeah you know my brother
facts Nate Dog Nate Dogg bro I can't
some of them some of the things that
people put are like impossible like what
like there are 10 but they're from
Poland like girl I if there are 10 and
they're from Poland there's still a 10.
in Poland yeah from like volcanic ash
like it's a different story you know
there's no idea
which origin really matters to whether
or not they're a 10 or not if they're
like they're 10 but they're for Mars
it's like I don't know they're still a
batty ass alien
okay next
bro what would you do if you like went
to Mars and just saw them it was like
double cheeked up batty alien you've
ever seen in your life I honestly feel
like that's exactly what I expect like
the most attractive person ever just
like on Mars
but like they're green
honestly I don't even want to think
about that I love that makes me laugh I
feel like that'd be really cool I love
that like imagine you just go to Mars
and there's a ton of aliens but they
just look like us but significantly
cooler
what oh this is terrible there are ten
but they say I'm okay with anything but
then get upset in what they've done Matt
that's you I agree so I don't know why
you just grunted so hard yeah I'm okay
dude this car is like circled us yeah
we always go to parking lots that are
just like way too sketchy I don't know
why we decided to do it but we always go
to parking lots at 2 A.M we expect it
not to be spooky and scary I pretend but
they don't wash their hands after the
loo what
happened
but I feel like it's kidding me what are
you gonna say he's gonna say it's not
that important to wash their hands
cool okay there are 10 but they claim
that they don't do normal things like oh
I don't sweat I don't sneeze I feel like
that's kind of like valid
you would he would be one because it's
like if you don't just like you don't
it's what everyone [ __ ] sweats okay
sure you can have that if you want I'm
really uncomfortable but it's the people
it's the people that make it Chris
people that make it like a big jab that
they wanted no I guess it's like when
someone says like oh my God I'm sweating
it so oh like I don't sweat like ever
so it's just those people that want you
to know something about them that you
just want to [ __ ] curb stuff oh I
just love to see your buck teeth fly out
of your mouth someone said the craziest
straight to the pavement they go there
are 10 but they have a criminal record
that's okay it depends their background
but it totally depends how like if
you're like if you like didn't if you
got caught up for stealing a candy bar
like okay like we're chilling I ain't
acrobatic I ain't flipping them out Bros
yeah I saved that one there are 10 but
they don't have tea with their biscuits
no tea no tea with no biscuits yeah no
tea no tea for their biscuits I think
about that one written down no way yeah
that's like a beach with no sense
biscuits no tea with their biscuits this
is unbelievable I can't move forward
shut the camera off no tea with biscuits
zero tea with biscuits and croissants oh
what about scones no no teeth yeah no
tea they have no tea with any breakfast
good even muffins bagels
there are 10 but they make like kid
noises when eating like
everything everything
kind of fire like I'm really entertained
they're gonna be eating like
I think watch something
next yeah
[Music]
no more we need more than that you're a
second
like that okay there are 10 but they
talk with the baby boys
I say it's zero that really scares me
that's the most foul thing in the world
especially like imagine imagine because
like nobody should be talking like that
no one like even unless you're talking
to a baby I still I don't yeah it's
still corny I love when people just
straight up talk to kids like they're
like grown yeah like a little brown like
Fish Box I love it it's like a kid in
there it's like oh you like that and the
kids like sucking like a pacifier
you know what I meant
you guys are insane
that was awful
[Laughter]
it's not that funny
no not even exaggerators but people that
like lie about situations where it's not
important to lie at all like uh all
right that's just exaggerators like make
yourself sound cooler is like kills me I
agree like someone could literally be
like like pay to go to a billy eilish
concert and then be like like last week
like I was hanging out like Billy and
you're like who and they're like like
Irish like Billy eilish
it's like bro you paid to go to a
concert you weren't hanging out with
Billy Island correct you know what I'm
saying yeah
when little kids are in like fifth grade
and they think it's super funny to be
like my cousins like
my cousins like my dad owns epic games
yeah like my cousins like in the NBA oh
like it's always like her cousin there's
this one it's always the cousin that's
distant there's this one girl that was
younger than me and um me and one of our
do you think these people are saying
like they're our cousins that are just
aren't hundreds yeah probably I remember
when we were little me and one of our
cousins like legit one of our cousins
we're a big fan of this one band and I
remember this girl like just fully
claimed that every member of the band
was her cousin like the band was like
assembled of like a group of strangers
so I'm like you're literally look at
that such a [ __ ] it puts me in physical
pain biggest [ __ ] pet peeve on the
face of this Earth please please do tell
absolutely gonna share it what I was
gonna share my biggest pet peeve and I
forget well obviously it's not that big
but yeah it's not that oh my god when
people don't say like thank you in
situations where it's like so warranted
that it creates like awkward silence
because you didn't say things oh my God
you know what I mean like if someone
holds the door and you just won't blame
them no no not even just ah just like
you walk straight the other day like
that's like disgusting the other day at
the in and out and the lady goes Nick
was ordering the lady oh my God this was
so funny Hi how are you doing are you
there no
oh he wasn't there in and out where was
I okay let me say it and then oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah
so the other day you know Nick starts to
order What In and Out in and out [ __ ]
in and out Chris
the lady
goes Hi how are you doing what can I get
you to eat and it goes oh yeah it goes
can I just get a play oh my God I'm
sorry how are you it looks nice I'm
doing good like how are you doing
because she said Hi how are you but she
didn't you said it wrong she didn't ask
Hi how are you what can I get started
for you she was like hi how are you and
I said plain cheeseburger and I was like
he's stuck
that's how rude
I'm like a rude like that loud oh my God
that was good
um what's the world it starts with a P
personification no that was good like it
could have been it's like oh that was a
good like um
it was like a good describing okay it
was great thanks I liked what you did
there awesome and yeah I felt so bad and
she like fully interrupts himself
she like was giggling the whole time
what does some icks you guys have when
people chew and they're like
oh I have a really bad one go when you
get to like the airport and you run that
you're a friend and like bug in the
airport like yes yes oh my God you
already wait I ever saw someone in the
airport that I was like a meeting with
and they sprinted toward me and like
gave me a hug
I literally like literally like I don't
think it's like like it's like
[Music]
yeah you look like a forget
when people show excitement under any
circumstance
like when like you get a Christmas gift
oh
I don't know I don't like that I don't
really like a touchdown on a team I'm
like
Anything could happen
like why do I even try to talk if you're
just gonna you're like you talk yeah
interrupt you yeah like I haven't yelled
at you for injury
you
talk about how you can't it's quiet
dumbass look you're an idiot
as [ __ ]
oh I just they think it's nothing could
happen in which my body has a physical
reaction of excitement like I just don't
think that's just a personal preference
that's not you can't it's a personal
experience not preference it never
happens okay well okay what I'm saying
is you can't like hate on what we're
showing they're excited about things I
can okay yeah oh let's go
oh my
okay do that I can't I've seen you it
must be so free and instacart got to the
house
but I've seen you get like excited
that's not true yeah
you ordered an Instagram to the house I
forgot what you got it was like you
needed like batteries or something and
like I'm saying let's go because two
Double A's got on my doorstep no [ __ ]
chance I'm like I know
I initially sound sarcastic in every
circumstance like that's why I felt bad
no more and I literally posted on my
story a full like announcement because
I'm like on Christmas my birthday you
could get me like I've been alive for 19
years on my 20th birthday you could get
me the gift I've been dreaming of since
the morning I was born I don't know you
could get something I was so looking
forward to and be like oh thanks this is
awesome I love it so much I can barely
contain myself how excited I am this is
great this is phenomenal I just can't
wait to like this is awesome and this is
naturally how I sound and speak can I
tell you how I saw you excited
go ahead continue There was like
something instacarted to the house and
it got there and he ran down the stairs
I'm just telling you like before you
didn't get there that I know that this
isn't true you were there's no way you
were Barefoot I remember and you had a
shirt and shorts
a sleep shirt on and like sweatpants and
I literally saw you run down the stairs
like this
I just don't like freak out
okay that's that's what I was saying
like you didn't let's go or anything
that was good that was hilarious you're
just a weirdo don't call me a weirdo
like you're a weirdo
just burped tweet it