in honor of Valentine's Day and all of
us being alone
we're gonna um all of us being in love
because I love each other yes yeah
and then what you're saying how you miss
me
and all the things
[Music]
with water and try to make each other
laughing teams with um Valentine's Day
pickup lines yeah that's the point
should we pick teams yeah throw the pork
or a spoon Ready Set Go
Set Go
oh it doesn't work try again one two
three
one two
okay
we're a team okay are we taking turns
yeah so let's do Matt and Nathan fill up
with water first okay
so basically hey if you spit water on me
I'm hunting so basically it's okay
I've decided to do team Matt and team
Chris because me and Nathan have the
same first initial so I don't know well
I know I made one okay he's Nathan do
you have a name can I just call you mine
[Laughter]
foreign
spits out water you get a point yeah and
everybody don't want points yeah yeah so
right now it's like one zero hold on I'm
losing let's do that if I had a nickel
for every time I saw a person as
beautiful as you
yeah
I have five cents there's only one of
them I don't think
so like laughing I put too much water
like now because I couldn't hold it in
anything all right hold on is this the
Hogwarts Express
because it feels like you and I are
having somewhere magic
headed somewhere magical
come on get back in bed laughter when
the second water comes out of your mouth
you might lose
that's what it should have been so we're
at both at one point all right guys so
we're changing our point system so that
you don't want points
and if you laugh you get a point if you
laugh at your own teammate so remote
that one because Nathan laughed at Chris
and Ryan laughed at math regardless of
who you laugh at the second water comes
out of your mouth you get a point and
you don't want points if you are a
vegetable
you'd be a cucumber
speaking of a fewer things
if you were a flower you'd be a damn
d-lion
amazing
you are you guys Australian
[Laughter]
that's so bad
I would punch him in the Box
straight down and see you I need to
finish my joke you didn't even get to
say anything I didn't see you I swear to
God are you Australian
because you meet all my qualifications
are you French
yeah
because I fell for you
like the Eiffel Tower
no no like
for you
so funny you and I are like nachos with
jalapenos
I'm super cheesy you're super hot and we
belong together
okay
all right that was good all right now we
switch Chris you're good I must be a
pirate
because I'm looking for some booty
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's bad it's strong
man no
oh my boss
if you were a Transformer you'd be
awesome is fine
who's there
when where when where who tomorrow night
my house me and you you guys I blew it
on the Atlantic Ocean and I don't be I
don't mind being lost at sea
I'm not that good at holding
conversations
can I hold your hand instead did the sun
come out or did you just smile at me
would you like to see a picture of a
beautiful person
don't look at me
you like Star Wars
because you're the only one for me
did I ever mention what I said God bless
you after that sneeze but damn it looks
like you already did
um
I don't consider myself
what happened Nick
what the [ __ ] happened Chris I don't
consider myself a hoarder but I'd like
to keep you forever
okay watch in a matter of losing really
bad right now matches left we're killing
it and I just left one of Chris's jokes
off camera so I don't know why Chris
told it but yeah damn
you must be jelly
because Jan don't shake
[Music]
a good holy [ __ ] yeah
David do you happen to know the
difference between jelly and jam
I cannot jelly this dick in your mouth
stay strong
oh okay you're good you go straight in
the water where's the Swamp right yeah
swallow it
well here I am what were your other two
wishes
such a good one
are you forced because ever since we met
I can't get rid of this Rosy feeling
this is even in the dark you still know
how to shine
you must be magical every time I look at
you
everyone else just disappears
[Laughter]
Matt doe he did like that doesn't count
you shouldn't be allowed to walk all the
way over there he didn't spin it out
though I just can't walk away
nickname by the way his dishes because I
want you to get me wet and do me
wait
that's foul wait that's a tie again
[ __ ] are we yeah sure who should do the
tight breaker give us the tiebreakers
this is for all things hold on
foreign oh my God
[ __ ] me if I'm wrong
yeah yeah
that's terrible
yeah wow what are we going to end oh man
oh
that was crazy yeah well that's better
oh I knew he was gonna get that was
crazy
hey oh Nick that's your shirt
well that has been this Wednesday's
video man that was amazing that was very
fun
happy Valentine's Day everybody
because now see you Friday and next
Wednesday
[Applause]
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things