why is our couch like dispersed we
should probably have that back don't ask
just leave it alone don't ask our house
is a mess
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
we put this mirror here so now our
YouTube clocks are on the floor
which is honestly really sad those
shouldn't be on the floor yeah put those
somewhere nice and high
yeah it's really heavy you guys wouldn't
know you don't have the million plus
that's really okay
um okay you guys are gonna kill me why
it's dead
it's about to die yeah of course it is
of course
oh
Nick you're gonna get in the video you
[ __ ] idiot well it's also not dark
because I don't know what this idiot is
the drink itself glowing no not the
drink Chris what the [ __ ] is even a glow
Berry like what is that even I don't
know move
Nick I'll kill you sorry y'all my camera
died look at here move I'm gonna plug it
in right now I'm gonna document myself
plug it in you don't care don't touch me
don't touch me remember when me and
Christopher sitting here and doing I'm
gonna try it Matt are you [ __ ]
hitting it
ugly shirt
I'm always sends us up early and they
sent us glow Berry whoever the [ __ ] that
means now if you're cleaning my doorbell
no I'm not sure
what was it it's glow in the dark if you
charge it in the sun who the [ __ ] the
drink or the bottle it says glow in the
dark Dash charge inside the drink or the
bottle
the bottle glows and that's cool but
okay you're wearing a white shirt it's
not gonna work can you just be like a
black whatever in space shut up dude
what if you get the big blanket
it's all the stuff that's green on the
prime bottle I knew it wasn't the drink
I don't like the smell of it I can't
open this one it tastes like toy some
people smell
I think good or bad
I mean it's not bad but it's not my
favorite product it tastes like you have
like cologne was a beverage am I crazy I
don't like it that much it's all right
doesn't it taste like cologne it's not
the best prime I've had but it's okay
it tastes like a watered-down cologne
smell you're crazy that's what I taste
it's all right not the best one but it
actually does taste good though
I enjoy it it kind of like green apple
heavy on the green apple yeah yep for
sure I got that green apple candy that
tastes just like candy apple
well no it's so festive one okay and two
limited edition wow everything is there
anything it's a sucker for like 11
limited edition like he just loves it
but like why not like let's give it a
shot I don't know why they only had
family size like I wouldn't want to try
something for the first time and have
like a gigantic amount yeah you got a
sample yeah are you standing Like A
Fistful and no we're getting a bowl and
we're getting milk no we're not I
actually think I eat in my days they're
gonna be more dry cereal and I have what
what is crazy take a couple
add some more Dry Cereal to your
repertoire Ready Set Go
I need milk I need to know
put the milk in here
putting it in my mouth
[Music]
should I get like a oh I used to do
shaking your head after it's crazy
good
you'll never massage you like that
I just heard the crunch me too
it tastes like an apple cinnamon
I was gonna say that but I want to sound
crazy it tastes just like the other
Cheerios lame lemon Edition my ass guys
are just doing the same [ __ ] it's no
different than the cinnamon I'll show
the box it's green let's put on the
screen yeah
so I think it's
[ __ ] lousy I love the green ones
growing up so I'm gonna give this a high
rating because it's the same thing yeah
but it's like an illusion like I'd
rather just bought the green ones and
read it than how I wanted rather than
get something I thought it was new and
it's not but it still doesn't do a
little like but these are good yeah
too much spice not enough pump yeah
most people use this to make Shirley
temples that's like the thing yeah right
okay
this is like a lemon lime drink we are
out of ice so oh it's a lime Rick that's
what this is whoa that's a lot dude no
it's not that's a lot that's the perfect
amount you're drowning in it dude
you gotta add a little bit you know yes
that was a splash he went crazy it's
raspberry oh wow can't even force him oh
wow oh this looks so good it's so it's
Barbie pink it's about like the Barbie
too much leaving the thing too much
[Music]
sharing this drink on the internet
forever but we'll see
um yeah so Matt hold on to your socks
because this um might blow them off for
me what is it like groundbreaking
discovery I made today
fully grounded freaking like could
change everything for us
but I actually have to
have to hold no I mean they might blow
off but like this might blow your socks
off and Pharrell okay
like I'm good forever
my socks are very well on I don't want
that
I'll start the car yeah let's get going
we have to get that necklace it's
[ __ ] insane literally insane it's
crazy I saw it and I was [ __ ] very
well prepared to go give it a shot
um
everything mixed with soda like I'm
totally game for Baja Blast it's like
I'm gonna at least try it Nick we go to
get Baja Blast all the time we did try
and yesterday in the Vlog we tried a
bunch of [ __ ] a lot of other things
you guys trying to convince me standing
like this like the funniest thing Matt
take out the recycle because he never
does
oh yeah those are fighting words
why do you got
over there whoa we should go look I love
like emergencies and stuff I love
snooping on them Chris I'm being so
honest like terrible well everyone
agrees like if someone everyone does
agree if someone's pulled over you just
want to know if like they totaled their
car if they're smuggling drugs you gotta
know you gotta get curious a little bit
100 feet Taco Bell pardon me I'm still
acting a full part of me Nick you ready
if they don't have it give me a Pepsi
actually just give me a large Pepsi
anyway please thank you
oh I don't see it
no do you see it at all hello how are
you I don't see it
you guys happen to have the Baja Blast
gelato
gelato oh we don't carry that here it
was only at the Irvine store no problem
that's all right yep I want a large
Pepsi and like a bunch of those Cinnabon
things with the cream in it
um can I get
um
six crunchy tacos with just meat and
cheese no lettuce I want a two tacos
and I want a Pepsi and I want to watch
those tacos
can I get two more of those I'm sorry
large Pepsi
um I mean can I get two large Pepsis and
then the cream things like the cream
like like eight like eight creams
12 cream things and then can I do a 12
pack of the Cinnabon Delights okay
imagine anything else nope
I love the cream things um and then I'll
just get do you like the mat the cream
things can I get them
medium white I call them little cream
little cream balls what did he just get
yeah
thank you so much what did you eat in
your order bro
same move
well Chris just keeps talking like
there's nothing to do I'm like not done
over there and I feel like I feel like I
just got like that was insane well what
else did you want to order Nick
someone's right there I just tried to
[ __ ] I tried I tried
why is he knocking on the door like
they're gonna like let him in
go around [ __ ] idiot get a car buddy
there's another door yeah why is he
knocking at the Taco Bell door that was
pretty insane
house and playing friends house either
cream balls yeah like I was trying to
order I ordered six tacos oh give me two
of those it's like hello your hair looks
insane holy [ __ ] the mask
well I said that at the very very soon
yeah you told me that it was a
reasonable time we believe they don't
have the gelato I'm like so [ __ ] mad
it's only in one store did he say yeah
that's [ __ ] ridiculous he said it's
only at the Irvine Irvine's so far away
we'll see you guys at home where instead
of the gelato we will be trying the
strawberry freezy creme Delight that's
not what it's called yes it is I write
it off the menu yes crazy well I don't
know who put the [ __ ] Baja Blast in
one location like a [ __ ] numbskull
but did you try it already no oh my God
yeah it looks Grody if it ever comes to
the one near us we'll get it and we'll
try it or if we ever met you don't have
to let it like before if we ever make it
to Irvine
we could go to Irvine one day and just
get it and now what the [ __ ] are you
doing
well if it goes hopefully if it's a
Smash bro hopefully if it's a smashing
success at Irvine they bring it
everywhere Matt wake the [ __ ] up India
we're trying the [ __ ] cream machine
here
oh
it's because you're sipping the syrup on
the bottom you gotta up a little and
it tastes some just like something I've
had I know [ __ ]
it's always like just like right on the
edge or something I feel like I'm like
changing I feel like I'm 12 years old or
something what it's like I'm 12 and I'm
sick that's what that tastes like okay
you're a [ __ ] kid
okay
you don't know how I feel about this
well I flip the camera
like what like that
in the sink Gone Forever that's a great
throw by the way I hope it's in frame oh
yeah you wanna know what's crazy Taco
oh my God I know it's insane it's
Tuesday no right now and it's Taco
Tuesday neck oh it's like literally we
got and we had tacos this morning
we literally just spent a whole day on
Tuesday eating just tacos like today
start to finish was Taco Tuesday holy
[ __ ] did I say something yeah yesterday
I had three tacos for dinner so this is
I've had three sixes where were you nine
I've had oh I have those tacos too wait
where we ordered them to the warehouse
I've had nine tacos oh my God isn't that
crazy yeah I need to chill and Mexican
food for real but it is Tuesday yeah of
course we get it it's Tuesday guys what
I'm also thinking of is kid [ __ ] you
like we get it
yay it's like okay dude we get it we're
also going on tour soon we're eating
tacos at every day at every stop every
Tuesday we're eating tacos on tour no
we're not talking Taco Tuesday actually
I'm so excited for tour and soon we
might give you guys a little sneaky peek
of how things are gonna run in an
upcoming video
no stop he just looks like just like a
little
bit
and all the things