California
girl we're in San Francisco today before
the show so we're gonna go eat my God
Matt do you send our fans a hearing aid
and they subscribe so they can hear you
and you [ __ ] whisper behind the
camera
ah there's like absolutely no reason for
you to be doing all that there's two
pulled pork sandwiches just hurt you
only had two dude they were so like I
had four so well they were sliders
everyone I had so much food today
there's some candies we're gonna whoa
Nick almost took a big old spill this
one is hold on we gotta restart the
camera
why
I don't know is it out of focus here
nope it's actually in pristine Focus
I'll stay right here
okay we got
oh nice patch bro please
it says bubble lick and I'm really
freaked out by it because I was reading
the instructions we got together and it
says flavored bubbles but the
instructions say adult supervision is
recommended
okay don't drink the solution okay lick
the bubbles only in bubble form
I'm drinking it that's what sucks me out
like you can if you can't drink it
confidently hold on best use that room
temperature what no we should freeze
them and if the solution gets into your
eyes rinse it with water now I'm gonna
put it in my eyes man you don't like it
kids just saying everything
I want to go first I want to go first I
want to go first I want to go first I
want to go first I want to go first Matt
take the camera I'm gonna look and I'm
like oh
looky looky looky looky was it good was
it good
oh great it's the cotton candy it has to
be gross
was it good it was like mid
I can't even get that it was weird blow
it like directly onto my tongue okay
okay no Chris no no no no no no no no
wait can we do this oh do you know how
to blow bubbles
you're dripping everywhere oh my God
oh what are you doing
oh
please there's not enough like you it's
like
you got that one did I yeah I like your
like blow it at you technique that was a
good one
oh it's awful because eat it just eat it
Chris stop stop you're coughing like a
threesome
no [ __ ] I got on my lip bro get
you're such a weird kid we can throw
this out all right I I deeply hated that
but we're moving on to the next one
candy foam whoa see here's my dilemma
here uh blueberry
flavored like what are you upset about
just let's get straight into it
don't put it like that far into your
mouth it didn't foam
oh maybe there's like a capital I'll
[ __ ] grab [ __ ] stop being a yanker
just yanking it put it back I don't want
to put it on like a plate oh I hated
that noise did it taste good no
I'm good on that for life
forever I'm not even gonna try it all
right this is how we're gonna test it
it's like shaving cream bro
why did we do this yeah oh my God that's
disgusting
some people need to get their ass beats
for Imagine goofy [ __ ] legit it smells
like spoiled milk get the [ __ ] out of my
face I put it directly in my mouth
no way sniff it Matt I'm not moving I
suggest you get that sniff out of my
sniff sniff Chris what are you doing I'm
not sniffing that Nick please no Nick
please no boiled milk right oh oh my God
I will kill you all right Bubbles and
the [ __ ] Super Phone whatever it is
it's all getting thrown away this [ __ ]
is terrible don't buy it
where the [ __ ] we at
Seattle Washington where dreams are made
of what is that like a slogan or
something
well I liked it it sounded really nice
you ladies all right
didn't iCarly take place in Seattle yeah
oh my god let's go to The Groovy
Smoothie
they probably got a greasement ew don't
move ew now my Reflections in the TV I
just wanted to get these bags that we
can eat these candies unless something
to spit into because they're gross
um so why are you eating it you
literally just said it's gross
okay let's do it okay ready guys let's
do it
whoa um basically we've had one show so
far we went to San Francisco we had our
show in San Francisco Chris won the show
in San Francisco and then after San
Francisco we drove to Oregon we spent a
day in Oregon we drove from Oregon to
here today and our Show in Seattle is
tomorrow well technically today this
past two yes and then after that we're
on the road again which is Wednesday
which is when this video comes out so
this video is coming out while we're on
the road to our next state after the
Seattle show that is tomorrow yep
hopefully that makes sense I just want
to make sure you guys all know what
we're doing where we're at even though
some of you can't go to tour and some of
you are on tours want to make sure we're
all updated and that's it that's all I'm
gonna talk about for tour now we're
gonna try these candy fruit messes these
pop it popping fruit jellies that were
puppies
that were a trendy treat on Tick Tock oh
my God this is insane
ew bro my teeth almost broke
oh
my God
I feel like on my stomach a bag in here
yet
[Music]
you guys ready
Chris ready dude it's all over my
nipples
in the back of my mouth and I just had I
like sucked the bag
okay oh that was yummy
all right let's get out of the hallway
brother
[Laughter]
and you're gonna choke
these scared
he's like actually scare me dude just
eat it the whole points to eat the food
Matt oh my God take the camera
was that a hit or miss Matt
it's in my no one took the camera here
I'll take it one second
where is it in my eye and on my arm is
it on the lens your haircut is so cute
like I really do like it yeah I got it
cut real short he looks so cute I knew
Tor was right around the corner I said
oh I'm shirtless don't body shame me oh
Chris gaining weight
I don't think that I
oh great it was crazy to me I just
couldn't care less about a single hate
comment because what you guys are saying
you're typing your your little fingers
away and you're going oh you're clicking
buttons from the loneliness of your own
bed when I'm with my friends living out
my memories and my dreams
[Laughter]
I mean haters are gonna naturally come
when you have any this is true because I
was thinking about it because I'm like
because I was thinking about it because
I have so many friends that do social
media and this and that like so many
people in this world every single person
no matter what you're doing you'll be
the highest of high giving back to
people doing the best you can and people
are gonna have something to say that's
so negative and wrong about it so it's
like just
zip your lips and continue on being
anyways
eat the jelly eat the jelly you eat the
jelly
um
it's good right
do you like it
yummy here's the bag see it's like the
fun like the sensation is good like the
tactile like part of the experience
there's a whole another demon
you're disgusting
oh it's on my arms
okay we're just gonna put it right in
the bag it's like a poop bag
itself
I can't believe this hotel room it's
like the scariest place ever like what
is going on like this Vlog nightmare
Hotel
there is
nightmare Hotel
what are you doing don't try and put it
at me lunch is crazy
yeah I saw you look I should have the
back you thought ho
jelly you couldn't pay me a million
dollars Nick eat the jelly I would do
anything boss take it take a bite put it
in this bag for the Vlog Nick you only
live once for the Memories you were just
saying it jelly jelly jelly jelly jelly
no I don't like the jelly it's tactile
experience dear Nick one more tactile
experience that's all we got left
hand
it's not like rain
good job the world doesn't revolve
around mine don't miss any spots really
get in there
I love doing that when Nick's like
cleaning or doing something we're good
the [ __ ] people like the housekeepers
after I feel terrible like I'm gonna
clean up to the best of my ability but
they're gonna come in here and see this
purple jelly Rag and be like what
Seattle is
show 10 9 correct no it's not it's 9 20.
oh I'm looking at the wrong thing oh
someone's not using their brain this is
being annoying all day but it's time for
the show here in Seattle
get used to that one metal you're not
gonna have anything else
[Music]
how are you feeling today
oh God someone's not gonna win it's a
lack of energy I see
energy conserving versus lack of what do
you guys think drop in the comments down
below your opinion
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah