what I like you like what you do
chees so funny something happened that
was funny I don't
remember all right everyone we are back
to the holiday spirit holiday cheer oh
my God cheer it's that time I want you
to should you do a Christmas intro just
for this video drop drop a body like
just like just like like a death drop so
last time we tried holiday snacks we
with our friend Madison and I can't
remember what we had or not so I'm
trying to like look back at that video
all I remembers I had the big meat stick
yeah we didn't get a meat stick again
this year no I know that these videos of
us enough I know that these videos of us
trying food are going to be good when I
literally actively feel sick while we're
shopping like Chris is picking [ __ ] up
and I was like like holding my chest
yeah n goes that looks so bad I go get
it it looks like you shaved a [ __ ]
like Min Jack why cuz just like are
bleeding everywhere like bleeding
everywhere you're not you're not like
bleeding everywhere but you have like
little spots that like it looks like
kind of rough like it looks like you
like you're not look like you shaved
with a chainsaw in [ __ ] Home Depot
all right
thumbnail first things first we going to
start with Junior mint peppermint crunch
Junior crunch crunch I thought that was
an egg Junior Mints peppermint crunch
Junior Mints made with a sweet outer
crunch
dude I saw this video this guy at
In-N-Out and
um this I'm going to go like this and
you guys can see how whoever catch
whoever catches more wins are you guys
ready instantly got ready just go the
[ __ ] oh I way more way more way more
count count 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
13 14 15
my let's
go 1 2
3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 oh
no [ __ ] go with my bare hand I went
like this like I was [ __ ] praying to
God they all landed in my hands [ __ ] you
[Applause]
m [ __ ] go we need to eat those sck
three on the table they're all over the
place let's give it a raining are you
eating it of course okay Chris Chris
what why do I get the mush it kind of
just tastes like a peppermint Jack it
tastes like a standard Junior mint no
it's way more minty than a junior mint I
don't know if you're right I didn't get
Junior mint the junior mint with a
little bit of can we pick these up off
the floor and try can I try a different
one it's not like go I have table
infected Junior Min but worse I agree
like a five out of 10 I'm the six day of
Christmas my true love gave to
me one who wants to die who wants to die
next person to stand right next to me on
camera behind this table is going to
[ __ ] bleed to death I'm not standing
I'm sitting
[Applause]
oh better is on the right side of the
peppermint worse is on the left side I'm
really scared to face Little Debbie's
wrath what do you guys want to do next
Little Debbie's wrath is a little
dramatic Snicker doodle blue diamond
almonds and his cousin and frosted
brownie almonds Nick saw frosted brownie
in there and he I think he almost threw
up on I'm really disgusted at this at
this even
thought do you normally like
almonds
who who remember the last time I had a
nut was at um on bies on our tour I had
an assortment of nuts it was so good oh
this smells like real good put that down
get it out of my [ __ ] face all right
Snicker doodle or fudge brownie first or
sorry frosted brownie let's do frosted
brownie first to like destroy our case
buds for the rest of the video oh my God
I feel like I'm chewing a rock
my fingers are going to
break oh it has a lot of winter inside
it like a lot of Christmas
taste it's not it's not that bad not
that bad one is good one is enough you
know one zero it tastes like Cocoa Puffs
kind of it tastes like tar scker
noodle way better
does this get born to be dramatic or is
it just a new thing he's
[Music]
doing you guys serious oh that's
awful are you serious the sugar coat was
good but it was just like an
attack I could eat I could eat 10 of
those I hated it I could eat 10 eat nine
more oh it's worse than the other one I
don't want to watch you do this I'm
putting trick
no hey I'm doing something
don't way is better than better way
better tastes more like a nut the other
one tastes like a sid tastes like hell
tastes like Mortal pain like are there C
Altoids in there or something so I can
get rid of this [ __ ] in my mouth please
get something
else some nitive coffee beans or
something quick I
know okay we have first two kisses we
have cherry and we have sugar cookie do
you know what happened to last time I
had a cherry holiday themed treat what
no roll the tape oh God roll the tape I
don't remember what was it I almost had
a heart
attack oh my God I'm getting sick all
right Cherry let's
go oh are you in the whole thing I mean
it's a h want to see your
face
okay what whoever decided to mix Cherry
with chocolate like deserves to get each
one of their toes cut off like by a
[ __ ] their own children or something
it's like the match up of like like a
[ __ ] big strong eight versus a
gazelle like it's the it's just not
meant to be it's not a good match up
it's not going to look good coming in I
have to say out of all the chocolate
cherry themed candies that they have for
the holidays I think that this is the
best one I've had would you rather eat
another one of these you tra you grab
your neck like trapped with flavor I
don't know it's like just I need it to
to
end you're just like so
stupid Mi better than here yes I agree
are you [ __ ] literally twisting my
you're not allowed no I'm not no I'm not
I'm raing terrible Hershey Cherry [ __ ]
Snicker doodle time again hold on it's
not like go sugar cookie let go what are
rating out of 10 for these [ __ ] zero
sugar cookie kisses
oh oh my God that's even
worse come
on it's not that bad oh my God I can
just picture a little kid that would
love these like this gross old
kid it tastes like solidated
frosting if you let frosting sit on your
kitchen table for 4 days and then licked
it that's that's up actual perfect
description thank you yeah it tastes
like really chalky like I think eating
five of those in a row would like put me
in a hospital better than
these yes no better than thisuh it's
like here yep oh you guys are twisted my
ranking right now would be number one
number
two number two yes get the [ __ ] over
here we don't need to hear the rest of
what you have to say this would be a
really good weapon a bag full of shitty
flavored Hershey Kisses don't
Sour Patch Kids coal Sour Patch Kids
ornaments don't Nick don't no like
you're yeah these are these are black
raspberry I've never had those black
raspberry why are you so blown away by
everything cuz what is that black
raspberry Sour Patch Kid
first now these are good to hear me out
I think the reason Sour Patch Kid sees
the success that they see is because
they have a diversity in their bag you
have the orange the blue the yellow the
green like people can pick up favorite
flavor when you're buying the coal ones
you're getting strictly Blackberry
flavored sour Pat kits which are good
but I'm not going to finish this bag I
don't need the whole bag [ __ ] like
think of sour Pat did watermelons like
that whole bag is all watermelon like if
this is your ideal flavor I I will say
these are the best thing we've had I'm
with that let's go sour patch gets
ornament
M
delicious green M
delicious yep those are just
regular all right I'd say number one I I
like the uniqueness of the coal I would
put this just a little under the no
number one really yeah exactly what it's
like a let's see the
final next let's go okay guys I'm going
to throw a Hershey Kiss a nick
[Laughter]
we are going to try these Little Debbie
snacks we have Christmas tree cakes we
have Nutty
Buddies wait that's like
us nut bues don't call us the Nutty
Buddies We have tree brownies and we're
going to try them all right now first
thing we're going to try is the tree
cake oh wait no this is what I think we
do all silent no reactions nothing I eat
the tree cake you eat the Nutty Buddy
you take a bite of that we rotate no we
could eat this one at the same time no
I'm not do not on
camera get over
here no one's going to Nutty Buddy with
me no no Nutty Buddy I have no Nutty
[Music]
Buddy no one with naughty budy with me
you got some naughty budy on your lip
you
wish really good I love the peanut
butter taste m
I don't like
it I like it no no no where do we hang
the decor
no I like that move I like that move all
right guys next is the Christmas tree
cakes Nick's
favorite don't make that face before I
bite it no do I have to eat it do I have
to eat it do I have to eat it do I have
to eat it please man please please
please please Nick oh oh oh oh oh
not
bad my bite tasted kind of like sour
that's why it freaked me out why don't I
taste
anything tastes like I just bit am like
I'm chewing on a deep
breath that was
good I don't know it's like in that area
let's move on yeah like here yes
oh look at Santa he looks so nice go
like go
like go like that way so we have more
space Oh
yeah I'm not taking that big of a bite
you psycho it's a cosmic brownie I love
cosic brownie you got my finger a little
did I I don't like that I hate that I
don't like the green on it I don't like
Cosmic Brownies at all we disagree
doesn't taste like a cosmic brownie
all here
too not all right I can do
that you st on my toe big foot my God
can I can I ask for something get the
[ __ ] out of my way then okay
listen oh my God I'm going to make a
move and you guys need to let me know if
we agree or disagree with this
move agreed agreed agreed firly agreed
firmly agreed are we good there I like
that okay I'm going to make a move as
well not
[Laughter]
my stop cing before you clean
up we're going to do the re's big cup
fun fact last time I had this I [ __ ]
hurled
no I always say I'm going to grow up but
like I for real might go down this time
no the
last
sugar what milk chocolate and peanut
butter this pass FDA stuff with sugar
cookie bites look at his face oh I'd
rather eat a banana I love banana I'd
rather eat a banana for sure right
now dude you are brave
[Applause]
rees's enough you do good with the
peanut cup get out if there's one thing
bro bro hit him with the oh my God if
there's one thing that I feel figed out
this video is that I am not a fan of
sugar cookie I'm not a fan of sugar
cookie Nick no nick no it's better than
it's worse than this okay yeah the we
don't I don't think we ever needed the
big cup I would rather die than get eat
a big cup in completion the other day I
saw reesei sell something called
nutrageous that is nutrageous you got it
right that is [ __ ] absolutely
nutrageous okay nicer jodle white
chocolate truffle cook or truffle choc
guys I feel like laded no me too I feel
like I'm a [ __ ] sugar high like I'm
with [ __ ] P streets in my brain you
should see my head right now it's like
unicorns and rainbows and [ __ ]
fairies doing fencing court with candy
cane yeah with candy can licorice
fencing right now in my head
insane and and guess what I'm going to
add to it a [ __ ] Snicker dooodle lior
meteor shower coming in
hot let's go
[Applause]
wa
yeah yeah I would have loved this an
hour
ago but I've eaten enough it's good it's
not bad at all it's pretty bad like it's
like here to
me very Christmas Vibe it's good like if
grandma gave me one of those i' like oh
I love that Grandma that chocolate that
grandma gave me around Howen time right
here I had a very serious Christmas kick
to it like very yeah like that would be
fun on Christmas Eve like around in the
corner the fact that that's like limited
edition is fire like they did good that
was good I I actually really liked this
good good job good job Chocolate Company
peppermint CH or peppermint cookie this
is going to be good this is going to be
good this going to be good what
peppermint cookie let's go
mine's
broken very good though very delicious
you I can stomach this one I think it's
here it tastes just like when you go to
the it's better than the junior one it
tastes oh my God Andy Andy chocolates
cut this out I just farted so bad that
tastes just like when you go to the
Olive Garden and it it's like they put
the little mince in the checkbook right
there all right Grandma let's go no ious
what do we want next the so last year we
had last year we had the milk chocolate
version of this this year we went to the
to the dark chocolate version that's
good for your ab give me two more two
more no the blood's rushing into my
head I like
it I do like it come here I hate come
here
thanks I hate that I like it I don't
mind it I'm going to throw up today yep
you guys are I like this cuz it is like
a graph peeps marshmallow trees awful
awful awful I hate peeps I've hated them
my whole [ __ ] life and anyone that
enjoys these needs to get [ __ ] away
or
something EA it
together she tasting a
peep yeah okay well you're going to
die
yeah like like like like what do I
do how does one bounce back from
marshmallow
bitching
seriously oh
dude
FU oh my God I got it got it the
reflexes Prevail once again that was the
best catch I ever made it no
out of all my reflex catches that was by
far the best one and I can't wait for
you to watch it back oh God Ritz fudge
this looks good like a salty one that
looks
fun oh that classic R smell
ooh oh my got they're slippery I like
this rather have a regular R but it's
not bad cover
fudge hold on CH I like this this goes
here I think that goes go there I think
this goes here and I think that goes
there and that goes there I like it
that's what I would say I don't like
Nutty Buddies that much all right two
more reps one one more one more come on
scorpions there you go hey all
right J me a
million pass
out upside down that scaming if these
are a little mangled this is what caught
me earlier when I caught you no the
table caught you this took most of the
blow PE slic you
ready
delicious Prett good good an amazing
tree oh are these even different toasted
holiday Peanut M&M's let's see if this
even has an alter alternated oh they're
M&M's yeah
a they're not no they're
[Applause]
[Music]
not got assaulted by a coffee like a big
coffee came up and [ __ ] slapped me in
the face
like he was eating it so confident like
it was just going to get peanut M&M to
the background of coffee like boom
uppercut the coffee Undertaker just took
me all right the camera just cut so we
don't know what the last thing you just
saw was but we just tried this reindeer
[ __ ] and it was
ass keeping it th up it's coming it up
what happened to holiday cheer take a
look at the wall this is our F everybody
get down
down take a look at the wall hold on
look what do you look take a look at the
wall both of you look at me
now I can't I thank God it's going to be
a year till the next time I have to do
something like this that was our final
rating take a look behind us thank you
guys so much for watching this holiday
video another holid holiday video coming
your way and more starting a trip of
content no matter the season 5:30
Fridays on your YouTube on your TV and
and one two ready go left right
side jigle these balls [ __ ]
[Music]