us all right everyone last time we were
back in Boston with our with the fam not
last time months ago idiot
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you missed me and all the things
that we did
a lot of plans
[Music]
we did foreign
taste Japan Japanese snack pack us three
and the parents are in the tribe also
stay tuned to the end of the video
because we also have these which are
Japanese drinks that didn't come with
this box but we've had them since we
were little kids and we're gonna be
having them at the end of this video lit
Matt let's do something for an edit yeah
move at the same time move at the same
time let's do um back take like a step
back and step forward like
um
get one foot back come on ready ready to
meet ready set let's look at me
[Applause]
why do you guys
no it's just they like movement like you
need to give them something
you can stand still this whole video so
take peas outside all right go get wow
okay not toward me this is too much I
always looked in the box yet but here it
is
Japan yeah yes are you ready why'd they
smell oh
say hi Oh mom look they gave us one of
the drinks
it's a little scary
Blackberry though no because they didn't
pay me money
yeah last time we get out last time we
were still in English territory this
time I don't even know what I'm getting
myself in yeah let's do it okay oh it's
called Texas corn where do you see that
Texas corn
Texas corn from Japan
visit Texas
[Music]
it smells like sweet and sour from
McDonald's really yeah no don't eat it
okay ready
I'm ready
to taste it I did it this tastes like
that's just really good like um Puffs
yeah they're just little Puffs it tastes
like um Pirates Booty yes yes that's the
U.S oh wait there's a couple more I
don't know it's a rice crackers
Set Go
okay
oh I didn't get any other um
like garlic um
there's no garlic in it Mom
okay I like the outer shade I like the
outer yeah I like the outer I didn't
even get the end I didn't get the inside
and I'm terrified is that cheese I just
felt the garlic in my chicken
what'd you say all right worse than that
yes worse than that they're good but oh
is it is it yeah don't you go right like
yeah this is worse it's worse okay yeah
no definitely no Chris here behind us I
didn't need it it was awful okay this
one is chocolate cracker oh I like
chocolate yeah I don't know let's go put
it in here can I stand on something no
no eat you're good here all right
everyone already sorry okay
oh these are gas okay it's light and
fluffy inside it's like it's like if a
Rice Krispie hat did tastes like Cocoa
Puffs okay so cereal they're way softer
though yeah but some chicken flavor
they're not very satisfying I like the
chocolate definitely okay
like I
where do you eat these like at the
movies or something yeah I think I think
I'm putting I think they're better than
they might take that yeah they're moving
into first place this is going number
one for me okay that's good well it was
very light to eat
oh this one you can't go wrong here man
what is it looks like oh
yeah they look like little graham
crackers
oh
hit the cup that my Invisalign was yeah
okay well that's that's
[Applause]
it oh my God you didn't look in the car
she's giving me like symptoms
you know what
and you
from the boys okay from the let's trip
merch okay good enough you gotta say the
website oh I I don't know what it is
no you guys are going to send them www
we don't have to know I don't know I
know
that's true you're gonna send them to a
red bubbles ah no don't do Redbubble
because [ __ ] a friend of mine did that
yeah
you seem very confident in that number
one number one
number one
you're the most like Oreos number one
okay you want some more
yeah
like Oreos no I think these are better
than Oreos yeah they're lighter they
don't taste any different to me lighter
feeling like this
because it's packed in a box like you
know what I mean I think this is number
one actually when I say like it is what
I mean
Airy like like it doesn't make you feel
like okay
I'm scared this looks like the these pop
stuff liked but as Pizza [ __ ] taste
instead see I think I might need that
cup of water without the invisalignment
okay go
very good
the worst one yeah
really bad it tastes like pizza Goldfish
now this can go in the trash next one I
like the other colors of the Italian
flag
that one's awful what didn't you like
the most about it it was just like the
tasted bad I think they're better than
these I don't like these oh I actually
agree I don't think I gave it a chance
throw them away these were 100 they're
not treated like dirt oh more corn
snacks oh enticing caramel flavor oh my
cake
that's all right
oh those look good those look like
no did you put never mind
yeah it's full immature
all right everyone grab one
but it's okay oh wow smell delicious
wait I didn't have one yeah so great oh
wow this tastes very familiar mom you
gotta let me know here because you work
in a school they tastes like the school
snack I used to have yeah it's like rice
cakes
a rice cake yeah very nice this is a
rice cake it's going number one for me
yeah yeah and Tyson caramel corn snacks
not better than these three are better
yeah
I think it's safe here I agree it smells
like a marshmallow Okay
it does smell just like a marshmallow
good old father construction too
yeah marshmallow to my face I hate
marshmallows three right on the bottom
for being uncreative
I'm putting in here so
on the left
taste together
British thank you but I don't smoke
okay let's go
you guys love describing what's about to
happen
you guys know Pocky inside the chocolate
covered things yeah it's like that
without the chocolate sauce I like them
over there they're better than
everything on this side though no that
100 okay wait trash what who put this
there because this is not better than
that okay you're crazy all right that is
dude this is soup [ __ ] puffy thing
those were better not true I don't like
those at all
oh these look good
that looks like there's one for each of
us what's it say are they like oh it's
all in Japanese or something rice
crackers okay it's a rice cake
rice cake I like rice cakes there's like
some okay
all right no Mom it's okay oh is it um
what's that smell like
something
I know this smell but I don't know what
it is you're gonna cry about it like
it's very hairy again
dad
that hasn't stopped
really I agree I'm with them I agree
might be better with a couple
times
oh
this one has
oh it's crazy no these are good probably
gonna be my favorite how do you know
what is it green tea is it the green tea
mama
you guys tried them no so how do you
know they have these one of our friends
used to like always have these no
Invisalign in this right they're kids
they'd always have these in mint form
they look like so this is the gummy
version of that they look like gummies
they're not there's no way these are
wheat gummies if they are [ __ ] it we
ball yeah we have to try it I like the
all the highest [ __ ] yeah they are very
squishy okay they're fine food ready one
two three all right food
I don't like gummy [ __ ] this one's good
it's a gummy but it tastes like a
spamint leaf or something no no
spearmint Leaf has got to be the
furthest away oh Dad's gotta spin it out
no
I want someone oh there's a mint leaf
right here wow that did not take it it's
a mint leaf gummy candy musk cat awful
you're not gonna get information
you were trying to read Japanese all
night and you can't I don't know it it's
okay in the trash no it is better than
these two no it's not in my opinion dad
what no need all right we'll we'll give
it to death no I can't
need to go ahead of it that pizza is
awful I agree it's so similar to these
um no it's not
horrible horrible horrible
The Wizard of Oz what does it even taste
like better than these
I think it's good better than these
let's just read that
I think they're good really yeah what do
you like about them
please enlighten me I just think it's
good in what way I like the crunch okay
what's the tape Mom I don't know maybe
stop trying to read Japanese it's a
churro taste
you know what I would really like Mom
what if I had a cup of tea with it that
would make different mentee all right
we're down to the last two here this oh
it's looking like a laffy taffy then
there's a bunch of cartoon oranges on it
this is gonna be the top one I say we
saved this for last I seem to enjoy it I
say I start to make the tea for that
this one is a horror there's nothing
about it sugar cookie okay we're gonna
pretend no no no no no no we're in it
for all we're in it we're not it could
be the most outstanding thing we're not
leaving anyone out
oh not bad no it tastes like a plain
rice cake it's still come on this tastes
better than like I think it's a
vegetable
it's a mental thing in your head very
Bland so it has like a wow it's a
conflict though okay
where do we put this one oh I can't even
vote I think it's like there is salt
okay sweet but it just Blends
yeah not good yeah not good what smells
fantastic oh yeah this is gonna be the
one for me ready it smells like cough
medicine no but I just can't
it's good
I liked it yeah
thank God we answered with that what's
the best one
yeah it tastes like my favorite my
favorite I think no it's good all right
number one it reminds me of something ah
an orange
an orange okay
[Applause]
okay
listen with food with food I think
everything from
here on I'd actually eat again me too
definitely
for sure
where do you want me to put my hand like
two over three over
um
mom the Oreos are over there yeah no
from here mom's like how about this just
move that there [ __ ] right
oh that's very long
I like Darius but that's how it opens
wow
if they're like a marble in it or
something yeah marble forget it we're
gonna pass around like the chicken salad
see
yeah Dad's really inspecting the taste
yeah but never quite add anything
so that's a very unique it's good though
right can we try that one yeah
I bought that for you guys the honor of
tonight that's where the hole is and
then you sip it
I'm still here she's got a sippy cup
all right pass it along can I have
something
that's enough all right there's no
Invisalign in there either
I don't even think you can get the
Marble Outlet that's good right I like
that one it's good
yeah yeah all right we're good well yeah
decent little experience
cheers
[Music]