get in the video take those sunglasses
dude I'm on my way baby all right y'all
you've seen this on Tik Tok before or
somewhere before I don't know it's
pretty
self-explanatory from what what it looks
like right now Fair well explain it all
right we have 21 straws we're going to
and drinks we're going to take turns
exiting the room one at a time and then
we have all of the drinks in front of us
we have printed out on little pieces of
paper here and then we're going to take
turns sipping all 21 drinks and then
trying to guess if we know the orders
this is going to be the easiest thing I
think we've ever done no let's all share
what we're most excited for and what
we're least excited least excited for
those Gatorades [ __ ] that most excited
to get shocked by when I take a sip of
that kombucha I think it's going to
literally send my most excited it's
going to send my vitals into fight or
flight that's how I'm going to really
test myself is drinking that kombucha I
don't want to have this at all I don't
either and then I'm most excited for
really afraid of the Prime Dodgers
Dodgers yeah I don't know what flavor
that is that's why I'm a little
concerned probably like baseball fall
sweat gross as you guys know from our
videos in the past Nick hates coconut
water so me and Matt are going to put
this in one of them and take one of them
out all right y'all so here's the here's
the order for
Nick's
prank um so yeah we're going to call
Nick in and then have him start sipping
all right I saw I saw what are you doing
what did you just do I like clearly saw
him do what are you doing I didn't mean
he went to sip it and he fully lean I
didn't mean to see it I just was like
going to like that's how I take a sip of
a drink I got to like shut your eyes and
take sit we have to mix these up just
the first three first three serious
you're an idiot actually dumb here he
comes this is the New Order keep your
eyes shut it was a mistake actually
matter of fact take the glasses off so
we can see I'm not going to no
I oh my God his eyes are shut
what all right which one is
it what did exactly what I said it would
it's the kombucha I know it right how's
the taste not good I haven't heard the
word crayon in like 5 years I hate
people that say crayon or cray cray no
one says cray people say
crayon okay crayon let's see the
assessment Nick what are we thinking
what are we thinking it's the blueberry
Red Bull hold on
okay it's not good that's what it is are
we [ __ ] serious don't hit the boxes
idiot there's drinks in them I feel like
I want to say kiwi strawberry but I
don't like the way it
tastes why are you normally a kiwi
strawberry type of guy no never didn't
show the camera fourth one whatever for
it this kid's an
amateur that is without question
the sun kiss no it's not it's this
without question pineapple Fanta without
question number four number
five fruit punch stop moving the boxes
so much I'm not fruit punch six let's go
buddy number six is my baby Coke Cherry
number seven my baby my baby is
insane R beer number
eight God you're losing it let's go
buddy come on wait I broke they got
confused come
on how is it yummy it's
awful it's awful I'm skipping eight
number
nine it's got to be
Rosé okay that's the ultra Rosé or the
Pacific punch I'm not sure I'm putting
them both there number
10 over you overshot number 10 is the
fun Dr Pepper 10 11 here we're on
[Music]
11 number 11 is
horrid I think it's the peach monster
number
12 that's the
Rosé and it's not good that makes nine
the punch and 12 the Rosé there you go
13 that's the Cucumber Gatorade no it's
the Cucumber
Gatorade number 14 you don't like the
Cucumber Gatorade confirmed it hang on
no I'm just asking you don't like that I
think so number
14 I can like hear him sipping number 14
is
horrible why you don't like any of these
drinks well it's cuz it's like shocking
me okay tipping 14 as well all right
okay
15 how do you
feel
do we like 15 are we confused it's awful
okay and I'm confused we're skipping to
16 just 16 is the liquid death okay the
convicted melon 18 convicted melon is
insane oh my God so bad I want to say
the prime okay the Dodgers
Prime
18 come on buddy that's blue gorade
there you go 19 up he's on fire holy
[ __ ]
20 that's the sun kiss okay the um y
strawberryish sun- kiss 21 man get in
[Applause]
frame is it coconut water yeah where
didd you get coconut water oh
look we there's the coconut water all
right you have to go back in MA room cuz
we have to
put Shut Your Eyes Nick Nick we put that
there as a prank yeah I [ __ ]
obviously Chris
real all right close your eyes eight
strawberry apricot Red Bull okay
14 I hate that that is
awful Blue Monster I don't know I like
can't taste it I have to just say Pepsi
but I'm so confused okay next and then
that just leaves this for that all right
we'll tell you how move anything around
or you if you got it correct we'll take
your slip and put it in the bowl got it
I'll do it okay it's the P Peach monster
it's you're right it's monster wrong
flavor F this one you have orange red
bull it's Pepsi Orange Red Bull
stays it is Pepsi Next One wrong it's a
different monster is it the Pacific one
no no it's the Ros it's the blue one
it's the mango Fiesta the next one you
have the Ros it is the green Red Bull
wrong uh you are correct with the I know
I was correct with the Cucumber Gatorade
you have you have blue monster there
that is the prime my friend that is the
Dodgers Prime gone next one you have
Pepsi that is seven up incorrect what
yes next one you have seven up which has
to be wrong cuz that one was Seven Up
this is the sun-kissed watermelon
lemonade that means this one is also
wrong what you have a sun-kissed
watermelon lemonade is Pacific punch
monster this last one this last one
since that one's your green Red Bull
over there that would make this your
Rosé so you got one 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
11 12 wrong I got nine right n
I thought I was going to do so much
better yes all right everyone here's
your first look at Christophers aray
let's get him in here what's going on
you're having looks like you're telling
the straw crisis literally I want to
just say that's Pepsi but I feel like
you guys are pranking me by putting my
favorite first empty it out let's move
on okay you got Pepsi number
one also not too carbonated definitely
something like Fruity I'm going to say
that's that's like the kiwi strawberry
Arizona just for now all right I'm put
like my for now's right there Gatorade
which one there you go thank you next
wow that he's confident more for that
than he is
[Music]
Pepsi all right number five what could
it be stop making that [ __ ] noise
like oh God this is just a gross monster
literally thanks for the hint no it
wasn't a hint I want to say that that's
also like an Arizona fruit punch Vibe
I'm going to come back to it all right
okay pickle dill pickle whatever the
[ __ ] is W cucumber cucumber same thing
how are you not disgusted by it yeah if
it was next number seven
ooh that's going to be a gross monster
number eight really
fruity it is so fruity very like
hydration I'm going go withd Dodgers
Prime for number eight number
nine but it's giving like beverage it's
giving like um
oh [ __ ] piss it's not a solid how do
we feel I want to say that's one of the
arizonas that I'm not getting Sun kiss
strawberry watermelon definitely could
be that so I'm going to put that right
there number
11 that's number 10 you just have aill
literacy this kid wrote a one for a zero
earlier that one's really stinky I want
to say that's fruit punch monster I
don't like it at all number 11
now my boy
DP
DP 100% that's Dr Pepper number 12
That's My Boy DP that's wow you're
really gross maybe this monster I don't
know number
you don't like it at all
okay it is shocking right sounds like a
baby it is like a little shocking now oh
my
god it feels like I tripped and fell ate
mud and also went bleeding in my
mouth that's the most disgusting drink
I've ever drunk most disgusting drink I
ever did drunk oh my God
that should be so are you locking that
in I actually can't even [ __ ] breathe
[Music]
14 I don't know what that is what I'm
getting a heaping load of of of fruity
flavor so I'm to skip 15 a heing load of
fruity flavor gross Monster again
heaping load of fruity flavor we got two
in one that's like the same drink I feel
like I'm being pranked let's go buddy
I'm just going to take these three Red
Bulls and just randomly assign them here
all right for now okay can I remind you
you've yet to take a sip of this one you
skipped it actually
yes that's fruit
punch for sure that's a fruit punch I'm
just going to go like that for now is
this staying here yeah wait that might
be the Arizona one though do you want it
no okay you're disgusting
18 liquid death I just I don't know just
gross 19 gross again that's like rose
like some corny
[ __ ] all right gross yeah 20 and 21 20
root wear
root what are you feeling on 21 wait
that that's the Gatorade this one yeah
all right
here I'm being pranked come take the SI
six some of these have got to be the
[Music]
same your taste do are shot what is that
I don't know Chris seven
up what's going I haven't put Coke
Cherry anywhere try 14 again it's the
only one without one all right all right
are you locked in yeah all right we are
going to go down the the line and we're
going to let you know whether you got it
right your second drink that you have
you have kiwi strawberry Arizona that is
blueberry Red
Bull what your fifth drink you said was
fruit punch Arizona but it was coke
Cherry
[Applause]
what oh that makes total sense your
sixth drink you said was seven up it's
liquid death convicted melon seltzer
water what's going on your seventh drink
that you put you said it was the peach
monster but it was kiwi strawberry
Arizona 12th you got wrong you put Blue
Monster it is the fruit punch Arizona
yeah whatever next one you got kombucha
you got that right oh I know I did
number 14 you said it was the blueberry
Red Bull but it was the peach monster
the next one you said was coke Cherry
was the mango
monster whatever the next one you got
right it was the Pacific punch monster I
knew that that was definitely fruit
Punchy the next one was the rosé monster
but you put watermelon Red Bull so you
got that wrong as well next one you put
liquid death but it was seven up yeah oh
I swapped them didn't I no yeah I did oh
yeah you did is that seven up yeah you
did you swapped them I swapped them you
spped that's what I did okay next one
you said was silly trick next one you
said was the Rosé monster it was the
watermelon dragon fruit um Red Bull yeah
REM me to never get that again that [ __ ]
was ass so I got all the ones that
matter right sure all these worthless
monsters and you didn't get Co you got
wrong and 11 right you did better than I
did I knew I would there you go thank
God all right guys last turn know why
I'm like actually nervous all right come
on in hold on Chris has all the logos
the wrong way all right 21 drink choices
as always one is all the way over there
21 is this way Matt is going to take a
sip of each one and try to identify my
stomach hurts my stomach hurts bad still
I know that
one I think that that's Prime because
it has the consistency that the other
primes that I've had in the future
have the other the other Prime that I've
the consist the primes that I've had in
the past and it tastes like a flavor
that would be Prime and it doesn't have
like a I don't know Prime that's my
guess number one prime all right second
one that's some type of monster cuz I
can feel a little Bub but not but not
but not that that that much so we're
just going to put all the my advice to
the bro I know I know it's a little it's
a little Bub though that's why I'm like
three I feel like that might
be no cuz i''d be more disgusted oh
that's melon that's melon that's melon
all right number three try two again how
does it make you feel see it could be
seven up it could
be the red bulls four wrong straw
yeah wait you didn't even get a good
enough sip you're supposed to I got
enough more than enough I got enough you
know what it is yeah that's bad it hits
you after doesn't it it kind of it looks
like once it gets here it does something
it kind of gets to your stomach and it
just starts to spread like a p it just
tells your stomach can I get water no
five all right one of the Red Bulls mon
one of the Red Bulls are monsters
or that's seven up
wow confirming number two is Seven Up
that's Coke
cherry
or it's some type of soda but it's not
my root beer but it's some type of soda
defending like six one yes this is I
think if I had to guess out of any of
the energy drinks is orange Red Bull on
the
seven wow Matt the way you're talking is
oh he doesn't like
it wow I don't these I'm locked locked
these ones this box locked I with my
life also bad these I'm thinking
monsters and they're not good nine we're
going to come back to these okay hurry
up nine no nothing's coming out of
it that's also a monster number nine
yes 11 is the way that's 10 Chris one
instead of a [ __ ] Z it is a z I just
didn't believe that is that right there
10 is Dr Pepper confirm lock in 11 all
of these are so similar 5 7 8 9 11 we're
coming back to all of these take a big
sip just take a big that is Cherry Coke
oh my God man you need to chill that
could be Pepsi we're locked in on the
sodas other than root beer I got to find
my root beer
14 and it's giving me kind of Arizona
Vibes number 15
easily pickle whatever
pickle my goal my goal is to get
everything that's not an energy drink in
these arizonas locked in and then just
Rego for those my main man that's ruit
that
Fanta 20 that's Pacific
punch okay wow you're the thing that's
shocking me is that I've had cool blue
Gatorade that's what's shocking me right
now to my core this is everything you
just have laid out okay we're going to
Rego through for the cool blue Gatorade
give me a second here this is
insane didn't take long did not take
long at wow you you just think you're
the boss huh I am who dude
that that no question is a juice to me
oh but it could be a monster okay we're
just blocking in this go with your gut
go with your gut how do I know not think
of this
before that I did really not think of
this before that I'm not mistaken is a
main ingredient in a Matthew serola
mocktail that's that's how I know that
20 I not done this before he says it's
also
Juice this is so funny to me it's just
your level of confidence making me laugh
this is this is the outlier to me so
this is out that's going red oh you're
so you have three monster flavors left
identify hey that's what a monster feels
like that's what a monster that's what a
monster feel crazy
quote Rosé peach
mango
okay this is some whack Rosé
[ __ ]
oh my God that mango peach it's locked
everything okay are you fully locked in
I'm going to just tell you people are
going to think we're literally click
baiting you just got all of them right
except for the three monsters that you
just placed wow everything that's
actually like you were almost let me let
me re you were almost going like 100%
And I was like he has to be cheating
like what's I'm not cheating how could I
cheat you literally just like almost
shot 100% from the field that was like
the most impressive thing I these two I
just guessed with juices those were
50/50s that was actually like insanely
impressive when you were going down the
front and you just like knocked down
these four I was like oh my God I knew
that box was lock I had that box unlock
this one that has been this week's BL
Day video we'll see you guys on Friday
thank you for watching us do this maybe
we can do this again for Tik talk I
don't see it as a full YouTube video but
I'd be down to do like small boxes of
five or something King right here yeah
that was crazy Matt is the Bev King I
did the worst and the
monster okay okay Loosely give yourself
that title peace out
[Music]
y'all