I don't think anything's worse than
lukewarm hot fudge it's like your
straight up line
what
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
that we do
no trouble
but it's okay
[Music]
uh I couldn't have said that anymore
clear lukewarm hot fudge you don't think
there's anything worse yeah why would
they make hot fudge what about
kidnapping I think that's worse it
should be warm fudge then if they're
gonna [ __ ] like if they're gonna lie and
say hot fudge make it at least
kidnapping no one's lying to you you
straight up getting stolen yeah you're
getting kidnapped
carry around or if you could be walked
around by like some mythical creature as
your personal bodyguard what would you
want it to be
Dragon easy
no dragging these nuts in your face
what was I even talking about before
this [ __ ] idiot kept singing
what were we talking about what were you
what would your mythical creature guard
be oh I feel like you would want to be I
would I would want it to be something
that I could ride like fly on and you
know yeah shut up and drive
shut up
yeah I like that that was cool Shut Up
and Drive okay
best serves and cold and revenge is
sweet then revenge is really just ice
cream
actually love Revenge I think I love
good I don't like okay listen
I like unironic Revenge imagine you
dated girl right oh
not you Nick I'm talking shut the [ __ ]
up I was scared
[Music]
stop what was the first person who tried
to milk a cow what were they doing
honestly what were they up to I feel
like Loki
like in the human in like the nature of
a cow like they're not their milk's not
for us it's for their babies so I feel
like the First Farmer kind of just saw
like a baby cow leech on to a moment and
then like oh damn
you could utilize that just like the
baby cow yeah I was on some weird [ __ ] I
think that was why he but also the weird
thing is in order for him to know that
if Cinderella's shoe fit perfectly why
is it falling off in the first place
[ __ ] her keep your damn shoes on like
why she's just trying to hook up with
some [ __ ] guy at the castle she
thought she was all that I'm sure of it
she thought she was all that her shoe
fit perfectly she kicked it off because
she's like ooh she wasn't confident
enough to go go up to the guy and she's
just like I'll just lose my shoes oh
I'll just lose my [ __ ] hope he finds me
back like she definitely planned that
[ __ ] and that's what I don't like about
it it ruins the whole story do I need
help oh oh you found it I love you like
awesome it's supposed to be like that
that's what you want the story to be but
the fact that it fits perfect is kind of
like damn girl
you're really planning this [ __ ] out not
as interesting well it would have been
better if she wore shoes that didn't fit
and he still found her and then realized
she was a great person as well yeah you
know what girl I'll treat you to some
shoes that fit
[Laughter]
for that person impression yeah you know
what girl I'll treat you because it's
like it's like it would have been true
love because it's like wow she couldn't
get shoes that fit her in the first
place no like she cut up the thing where
she just didn't and they kind of just
found each other in her eyes like damn
we work together this is good and then
he's like you know like those shoes you
wore fell off like as like kind of like
a start of their relationship like they
met because these shoes didn't fit so
he's like you know what I'll get you
some shoes that fit so that way let's
start our love Yeah and show that no one
else can get her shoes but [ __ ] her
she's on some fake show she was the fit
kicking them off ruining the story
yeah I don't know I just I'm not a fan
what would happen if Pinocchio said my
nose is about to grow right now
hold on
if he was lying my nose is about to grow
right now he'd have to say that after
lying because then it'd be the truth and
then his nose wouldn't grow but it would
have grown from the lie so him saying oh
my nose is about to grow right now would
be the truth because he just lied so
he'd have to lie right before saying
that for that to be true but if he said
that and his nose if he didn't tell a
lie right before it was his nose would
have grown because he'd be lying he'd be
like oh my God no if he said my nose is
about about to grow
see that's that's the thing it's not a
lie if it grows
[Laughter]
I feel like he died hey was he puppet my
nose all of his limbs would fall apart
hey hey my nose is about to grow right
now he'd die and then if it doesn't grow
he's a liar so it would have to grow but
then if it does grow he's telling the
truth but in order for it to grow he
means a lot
twice or something maybe that would just
break him who did it like grow twice or
grow not as long or gross I don't know
how long you should ask somebody oh my
God I think he'd kill him I seriously
think he'd kill him like if he made a
puppet team that you know that one audio
like the Roblox character I'm pretty
sure like dying not the oh but the Lego
like yeah like the crunches that's what
happened like Pinocchio would be like my
nose about to grow and then he just like
like his limbs at all but I think he die
I seriously think okay that's crazy
yeah stop breathing I'm not trying to
shut up and drive drive drive could you
stand backwards on a flight of stairs
yes yeah which way
could you stand backwards on a flight of
stairs you'd just be going down the
stairs
no you could be going up no if you were
standing backwards on a flight of stairs
it would backwards is technically just
the opposite of the way you were just
that's true like if I go down an aisle
and then get like brownie mix or
something and then I go back the other
way I'm technically going back from
where I came forward oh it could be
backwards that's not backwards though
because you're going straight through
so if you walk backwards down the stairs
it's the equivalent of walking backwards
after getting brownie mix can you stand
backwards on the stairs [ __ ] you yes no
you can't stick cause then you just go
walk them either way whatever Direction
you're facing on the stairs front or
back you could do something with that so
there's you like it's impossible same
thing with an out for the [ __ ] aisle
at a grocery store
if you went halfway down an aisle at a
grocery store and then turned around and
went backwards the rest you're going
backwards so if you go upstairs six
steps turn around and go upstairs six
more steps you're going backwards up the
stairs so if you go up six and then turn
around and stand still you are standing
backwards on those no but Nick here's
what you're saying stand there's no if
you go up six turn around you're
backwards like there's no movement
involved you're standing still so you
could be backwards at the the [ __ ]
eye the eye of the beholder like the
person watching you won't know that
you're backwards correct that's all it
is but yes you could
no you can't you can't because you can't
stand back stand backwards on an aisle
yes
incorrect now that one you can because I
always have an end to him wrong yes
wrong no aisles there's a start and a
finish to an aisle wrong yeah but either
way it could be the start right right
yeah [ __ ] you the same so it's the same
thing so basically shut the [ __ ] up [ __ ]
yourself the question is literally
the question is literally if someone saw
you standing could they tell if you're
going backwards or not the answer is
always going to be no unless you give
them a little bit of context okay next
shut up so [ __ ] that question literally
how is it even possible
that the world is in debt
I [ __ ] money I don't believe it I never
who do we owe money to
just like the government owe money to
itself maybe Mother Nature is like in
order for me to keep revolving around
the Sun I need a kadillion US Dollars
yeah but what is your crazy money's just
kind of like bartering with special
paper
like remember in like Mayan days like
Egyptian when they just like trade like
a jar for some cacao beans or something
and that would be it like when did we
get strictly paper and then this is the
most valuable thing this is what I think
it's because it's like point I feel like
it's like I think it's all a system yeah
we turn something that's so invaluable
so so valuable yes like what is the cost
of a dollar bill to make you want to
hear it you wanna hear the thing that's
a good question that is a good question
oh my God how do you pay for money
a dollar
watch out the chills oh my God because
that's the problem with the penny and
why they were trying to the Penny's
endangered and they were it was gonna go
extinct
because they were apparently it cost
seven seven point five cents to print a
one dollar bill oh so technically that
one dollar bill is
wouldn't that be creating that no it's
not Matt it's not whatever math you're
about to do it's a hundred no it's not
no it's not because the second you have
a dollar it is worth a dollar because
you're not paying the cost overhead to
make it you're not paying the cost of
goods correct the bill
well apparently it's a twenty dollar
bill comes 13.8 cents well I'm just
confused I don't get it dude get rid of
the penny because the penny costs like
more than a penny to make it costs like
a penny and a half
what yeah that's why the penny was
extinct how much it does it costs you
really care about the penny no it's just
like I remember this the penny was in
the customer they cost 2.1 cents what
so who's doing it like the government
that's why we're in so much debt we keep
making
pieces like oh so oh my God so if we
stop making pennies and solve a lot of
problems but I love pennies I feel like
Abraham Lincoln on the penny yeah I love
Abraham Lincoln I just love I love
Abraham Lincoln Matt what are you doing
I like his beard Matt
what are you doing look I don't remember
why is he laughing it's funny because I
know the only reason Nick likes Abraham
Lincoln is coming this [ __ ] Top Hat
true Nick loves Nick said he wants at
the same top at his area of like it I
feel like I've always ever since I was
young like just resonating
five I remember just loving Abraham
Lincoln
but not in like a weird way of like oh I
love Abraham Lincoln I just love the guy
[Laughter]
are like reincarnated
Ghost Inside My Child and like the kids
used to tell stories to their parents
about Like You Know Abe like didn't wear
the hat all the time yeah
yes he did no he didn't he did it hard
but listen do you remember that show
Ghost Inside My Child and people people
just tell stories like these little kids
would tell stories and like wake up it
like having a [ __ ] panic attacks and
Nightmares like like about like that
being at War and [ __ ] like that crazy it
was because rumored that they were
reincarnated because they'd go and
they'd tell stories
seriously yeah inside the show Ghost
Inside My Child
oh there was this one kid who literally
was like I don't know he was like always
like oh I just remember like I remember
going to like [ __ ] like at Sea and I
remember like all these crazy stories
about like boating and all this crazy
[ __ ] and then it was like everything
that he was saying he brought his
parents to like a spot in the woods and
he was like he brought them there never
been there before they've never been
there and he was like oh like I remember
being here like when I like fought that
one guy and then they Googled it and
there was like a legit [ __ ] war of
like this one yeah
I'm like yo there was this war like War
like I don't know what it was scared it
was almost like crazy crazy like War
like War like like fighting like
shooting at each other and [ __ ] yeah in
this [ __ ] place and they Googled it
and like the guy that he had like many
memories of like oh I remember like
killing this one person what they looked
like I remember the shotgun I had like
they Googled the guy no that's just
weird and the kid like was telling them
in extreme detail like what was
happening and he's like nine yeah
but no like on a way less extreme level
I just always felt connected to it yeah
I don't feel like I was him I just like
love him yeah I think he's just like a
cool looking dude like ever since I saw
it Oh my God I was like oh he's cool
what shape do you think your like Psych
is like your line of vision
what the [ __ ] are you saying hold on
like you looking right now what shape
like is your vision I feel like it's a
giant rectangle I was about to say a big
rectangle like a rectangle or it's like
a it's literally this it's like a
fisheye lens no I don't think fisheye at
all actually it's like a bean it's a
very shallow shallow fisheye
it's a shallow fish no look can you see
my finger look forward okay look forward
forward can you see my finger yes can
you see my finger yeah it's under your
eyeball so [ __ ] you it's not a rectangle
it's slightly fixed a jelly bean flip
the door can you see my finger
don't look for it can you see it and I
can see like your like finger okay it's
fish hide yeah I can go like this on the
side of my temples look can you see your
fingers he's my finger uh
yeah yeah look man you can see my finger
[ __ ] you it's been shot but I'm like
looking at it no well don't look
whatever dude like you need it together
a jelly bean right but like this way
like this way Jelly Bean oh [ __ ]
yourself Matt it's slightly fishing this
way jelly okay slightly fish-eyed Jelly
Bean my highlight of my life is meeting
all of it I agree like I think it's just
gonna be something here remember for us
and it's like it's gonna be something we
remember forever and there was like so
many fans that I would see and just
immediately want to like literally just
trade positions with and like be that
person for like one minute and just
experience it from their perspective
because they were just so cute and kind
and they're great lovable like there's
just so many people that are so sweet so
many little twerps wanted to kick to the
side but
I feel like we never got to thank for
four million subscribers and thanks for
like coming to our shows and stuff
because we were really busy on the road
yeah but now that that's over they're
kind of just all settled like we hit
four mil we had a successful tour and
we're kind of just super super we're
just like kind of getting back into like
normal life right now and also if you
think of our podcast doesn't exist yet
um it's gonna be really really soon and
we're gonna hopefully do a podcast
episode
check the Instagram story right now when
this video comes out because we'll have
um we'll post like the um how close we
are to our podcast yeah if it's not out
yet they'll definitely it feels so weird
like filming right now because we
haven't filmed in like months but I
thought you guys to know we're super
grateful even though we weren't really
able to express that on the internet
during our four mil and our tour and
stuff but we're back we're filming car
videos I'm excited to do a podcast
frequently so we can talk more often
it'll all be good see you guys love you
thank you
Set Go
do it again ready one two
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah