all right everybody we are going to film
a video this is probably going to be the
biggest video I regret on this channel
and this is probably going to be my
worst nightmare and I already feel
nauseous and I think I need a couple ad
bille I'm right there with you
completely completely agree yeah the
other day I walked into the store to buy
a bag of chips and I passed the baby
aisle and then I remembered in the
twitch chat I saw a video and someone
was like you guys should eat baby food
for a stream for a video this is fitting
just cuz Chris looks like a lot like the
Gerber baby so it's like it makes a
whole lot of sense right Nick if you
literally took your shirt off and stood
there you'd look just like the gber baby
like just like
him just for the full head of hair I
forget babies don't have teeth and
that's why this is a thing goag stop oh
carrots carrot sweet potato pee pear and
cinnamon oatmeal this one good that one
sounds Nick you're gross got banana
Puffs which these I eat regularly anyway
these are good as [ __ ] these are the
emergency see these are the the beacon
yes this is the emergency Beacon this is
this is Hope right here yeah then I got
yogurt
melt those look yummy those also look
good who's excited to try the baby food
me yes
me oh God be with me this is for 6month
olds what how many month olds are we
like what a lot I hate when people say
that it's like their baby like two she's
24 months today all right first first
one apple wait we should do like a
challenge and whoever this should be
perfect for you since you're acting like
a [ __ ] baby throwing spoons
interrupting people we should do a
challenge and whoever loses has to take
like a heaping scoop of it no and the
other two can have like a bite maybe
that's for like another video okay yeah
yeah thanks no heaping Scoops today no
no heing scoops I already feel sick I
ate dinner already I don't want to throw
up Apple raspberries and avocado let
crack her open that just doesn't sound
like an inviting
Bunch avocado should have stayed out of
the bottle I kind of [ __ ]
avocado smell it Nick don't ever do that
that's like a that's like [ __ ] up okay
it's very apples Saucy I feel yeah all
right all right first one apple
raspberry
avocado not bad wait it's kind of like
hot like it tastes like spice a little
it's like a poison like it tastes like
it a antifreeze in it like this tastes
like it's trying to kill the children
way better than I thought this is going
to go way better that one is doable for
sure I could eat that whole thing if I
had if I had a gun if I'm stra on an
island like zombie apocalypse fill my
thing with this for sure okay Apple
raspberry avocado right now is the
middle liver next up we have butternut
squash this is for stage one babies 4
months
old Stage One baby okay butternut squash
I forget like babies are like oh my God
God this one looks like sin it's like a
yellowy throw up get a heaping scoop no
that's enough 1 2 3 butter nut
squash that one tastes like Thanksgiving
sin oh it tastes like pumpkin pie gone
horribly wrong you're fine is this first
yes of course that's better than the
other sweet potato this is going to be
just as bad stop shaking it I can't hear
theise it has to be shaken and you need
to stop I had way too much way too much
that last one I'm going to throw up what
are you doing it's a one monther oh he's
off the
milk don't this one looks wetter like it
looks like
water I got to shake it some more this
one looks wet like this one looks watery
oh
God this one's like looks very watery
I'm a little freaked oh this one looks
like [ __ ] this one looks like [ __ ] this
one looks bad this looks really [ __ ]
bad guys I'm like sweating some oh [ __ ]
this one looks bad I don't know if I can
do this I'm kind of nervous this one
looks very wet oh my god did you smell
it can you hurry
up oh I'm dripping don't drip on me
[ __ ] you put your arm in it no I didn't
you cuz you're like hovering over me my
God what is it again sweet potato sweet
potato 1 2
oh no it's CL it's it's like butter
butternut squash it's same family for me
give me give me give me give worst one
worst one I feel it in my eyes don't
burp I like the color palette whatever
you do don't burp don't
burp um stage two six months on the
mango I don't like a six Monon like
that's this is as watery as the other
this is as water why does it get water
more watery the older they get oh
[ __ ] I feel I feel like it should be
more I feel like it should be more of
like you're growing up you can deal with
a little bit a chew a little bit of
chewing a little bit of like solid all
right mango
awful it looks like slime is this
expired it smells
sweet I saw a little bit of relief in
your eyes he SM he like smell smells
sweet smells sweet all on
three oh tastes better than it looks
tastes better than it looks tast better
than it smells not number one this is
not better than the avocado Berry I
think that someone should do like a big
scoop of one no [ __ ] no you can do that
if you want no we each have to do one
big scoop of one no okay I'll do a big
scoop of I'll pick you get to pick okay
I'll do and we can't repeat though I'll
not I'll do a big scoop of the the Apple
I'll do a big scoop of the oatmeal one
this one Matt then you got this is the
oatmeal that's banana okay yeah I'll do
oatmeal I'll do a big scoop of that and
then Matt how about you I'm not doing a
big you have to it's part of the
challenge the challeng the challenge is
you have to take one big scoop and you
can't do one of the ones me Nick just
chosen so you have to do banana not
happening it is happening you have to do
banana not happening veggie carrot sweet
potato pee let's peel this baby back
right M delicious I'm tell myself I get
a million dollars Ready set
go it's more doable than some of the
others that are there get it out of my
[ __ ] face where does it go there I
hate I hate that people even like can
know that I ate baby food as an adult
like I hate that this is happening right
now oh my God it's still on my spoon a
little get out of here I have that yeah
sure but like you're going to [ __ ]
hit my shirt with it dude which one do
you have to take the big scoop out the
one you just held all right I'm not
doing it first though cuz you have to go
first cuz I know you're going to cheap
out 100% you take a b scop of this no
you're doing give it me I'll walk out of
the video good thing good thing we're
eating baby food for real serious you're
acting like a big Garber baby he has to
do banana first he has to do he started
what are you going to say next nobody
has to take a big [ __ ] scoop of
anything it's part of chall you need to
take a [ __ ] big scoop of attitude toj
guys it's come on babies who are you
calling babies you're arguing like
babies I'm not you just told him to take
a big scoop of an attitude adjuster
that's a baby thing to say all right
pear cinnamon oatmeal cereal delicious
sounds like a perfect breakfast for
chis this would be the one I'd take a
big scoop out of but I have a che I
don't care I don't care I'm not taking a
big scoop out of this this is going to
go on YouTube this one's nothing happens
this one's
thick she's
dense nck
n it has like a jellish
consistency look what month what what
stage what stage stage this is for
sitters for what sitters like they can
sit up it's for babies
I don't know what age that they can sit
up all right if I take a big scoop will
you do the next one hair cinnamon
oatmeal
cereal
oh oh my God there's no bang an excess
off of this tell me I won't do all that
bang it down right
now 100 bucks 100 bucks if you do that
and a little more a little more your
whole face is starting R I'm like
nervous as hell wait a little more yeah
like that's tell me going to stop like
that like that 100 100 bucks hold on
your SC hold on I need to reeval no you
have to take your scoop I'd pay any
amount money take your scoop Matt
oh three two
one not that bad I'm sure in high doses
it's horrible
come on
baby are you
joking what happened this is the drama
is crazy it's not that bad this is like
that was pretty good it's it's better
than it's
here it's here
oh it's not yeah no it's I think that
that's a safe rating if I were to take a
big keeping scoop of any it'd be that
dude so far yeah it like got stuck to my
throat like the whole slab of it it felt
like it felt you're thick you know when
like the Habachi Chef put that slap of
butter on the rice that's what I just
felt like I ate like it was just like
like I felt it every moment of my throat
o ooh
gross okay you have to do a big scoop of
banana mat [ __ ] no I did it I don't care
I don't care taking a big scoop of
nothing dude take a big scoop of these
nuts Chris no de's not stroke wait I
know what's wrong what I know why this
tastes tastes bad why hold on don't say
some dumb [ __ ] Bro hold on cuz it's
we're crawlers and we're sitters no what
is this one for banana ready I don't
have a spoon yeah I know I'm about to
tell you why it tastes bad
why Nick get that's probably why you
need an airplane get the [ __ ] out of
here that's probably why it tastes that
you need an airplane do you want you
ready for it or shut the [ __ ] up this is
your spoon banana
o it's got that sour
kick this tastes the most like something
I'd eat as an adult I agree number
one it's not good did you take a big
scoop that was yours to take the big
scoop of no and I'm not going to are you
guys low key tastes like really wet
banana bread like if you brought banana
bread in a pool with you and ate it no
yeah it's it's like if you put banana
bread under water first yeah imagine
it's like oh what I wonder what the
triplets are eating for dinner tonight
it's legit legitimately baby food this
one's also for
sitters okay is this one for sitters
sounds like a breed of zombie like I
just feel like a crawling baby is going
to come at me oh my God how scary would
it be if a baby like ran in here alone
stop to try to like fight for his food
back no babies can't really run apple
strawberry exctly what I mean like
imagine how scary that would be if the
boss baby descended from our ceiling
this one looks just like applesauce this
looks promising as [ __ ] honestly it does
it does I you think about applesauce is
just for babies who never grew up I feel
like I don't need to plug my nose for
this one yeah we I don't think you do
either I haven't plugged my nose in the
last like four strawberry it's almost
worse when you do that cuz it hits you
all at once it's
applesauce literally applesauce number
one yeah I'd go ham on this thing this
one's good actually Nick no way crazy
the additional you're crazy no I could
do it it's [ __ ] applesauce literally
sauce if I'm a baby I'm Munch in that
it's when you give me the peas and the
sweet potato that sit me down and call
me a sitter I me you're [ __ ] gross
put that away seriously you're freaking
me out yeah it's like not wait do we
ever have the turkey one no it's
now what a transition what a what a
sequence of events now it's time for
sweet potato turkey all right this is
also for sitters we got sweet potato
turkey I I feel like I don't need to
know if it's for sitters anymore yeah
I'm good well just in case you were
wondering actually I am wondering what
the chunky like the yogurt and the other
ones are no no when we get there
crawler wait is a sitter more advanced
or less Advanced less advanced than a
crawler all you can do is
sit crawler's got to be like a crazy
level so wait crawler is more advanced
than a Sit see but it is weird though CU
you're moving do you think they have
walkers or no that's a
toddler looks
horrible I like my turkey the in me dude
the color of this is crazy oh the stench
is bad
let's go let's go yeah there you go oh
my God I just got a [ __ ] piece of
that stench okay
ready it's on my teeth oh my God oh my
God oh my God it's like hot oh my God oh
my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my
God having a Dr Pepper is a cheat I'm
not trying to be dramatic I'm really not
and I've had a lot of bad
things this is this is the worst the
worst food we've ever eaten for our
Channel ever ever it lowkey tastes like
like this is what I feel like that we're
going to advance to in the future is
just like liquefied meals cuz it I down
Loki no it scares me how much this just
tasted like [ __ ] like turkey dinner
like turkey dinner and it was just mush
do you think like moms and dads like eat
a little bit of it
no like do you think like when you have
a kid you're just like like you get a
little on your finger and you're like
like you know what I mean
e
ew all right well I guess we're
advancing past sitter and we're headed
to the crawler stage which is these
yogurt melts and baby puffs when when
you go from sitter to crawler I didn't
realize it was such an advancement but
such a luxury they peed you right as
crawler as a crawler you get the
amenities this is first class of baby
food good these are good gain and grow
banana PFF uh-huh these are delicious
these are really good my this back like
actually I would tell you guys like go
try these like they're good they're so
delicious like they're really good I
feel like these could either be really
good or really bad yogurt melts
strawberry flavored I'll take a hand I'm
taking my guest before we eat them right
here yeah that's a it's going to be hard
to it's going to be hard it's going to
be hard to beat that cuz that's a luxury
but it's going to be very easy to beat
mush I like the way that these feel
Portuguese snack yeah I for forget tell
me I won't go all in just for it wow
like 20 20 of them not
good
uh- not good oh oh I got all of
them I couldn't imagine where you're at
yeah one I feel like I got a mouthful
you're chew is sidewalk chalk at this
point you're eating like a walker dude
you're a crawler oh my
god it feels all like sand
a lot of these Foods I was like
flinching in pain while eating I all
right thank you guys so much for um
watching us torture ourselves and we'll
see you guys next
Friday and we we stream on Twitch now so
go follow sto's on Twitch because we do
live streams every here and again every
now and again every every now and it's
now and then I always say now and then
he says now I say now again you can say
either Link in the description below so
that when we go live you don't miss it
[Music]