what is up guys welcome back to the
channel and today's Wednesday
video wow that was like a AP noise or
like a like pterodactyl yeah that was
good silent PE baby I still can't
believe it can't believe there's silent
pee and pterodactyl I can't believe it I
wouldn't believe it unless I need to a
pterodactyle to come in front of my face
and
say say there's a pee in the front of my
name and then I'll believe him anyways
me Matt and Chris we got suggested by a
friend to go to this soda this place
that sells a lot of Crazy Sodas because
everyone is aware of our s fiend
Behavior so me and Chris went today oh
Matt drove us I hate when me and Chris
another thing hate to complain as well
but I hate when me and Chris say we went
somewhere or say that we were driving
how did they get there if we don't have
friends Uber [ __ ] walk whatever
anyways me and Chris went into the store
Matt was parked on his side I hate like
over slam myself but I know that they're
going to be like what was happening
where was that me and Nick went into the
store and we picked out I think it's
like 12 very very funky strange sodas
all right the first one that we have
here is alien snot and that one and the
other one that I saw the
Unicorn Yak or whatever I think that
like they sound gross but I think I
think I like kiwi blue and R yeah it's
just like named back kiwi blue and Ras
isn't it blue it tastes like blue I
guess yeah what is blue kiwi blue rasp
no Ki kiwi and blue raspberry oh and
blue
raspberry BL you guys are stupid holy
[ __ ] alien
snot oh Nick not my fault not my fault
not my fault Nick maybe we don't measure
it up no just don't be an idiot you have
to go fast when you por it like this
let's do it Down the
Hatch that's fabulous it's it's
extraordinarily mid I will never drink
that again that's like leisurely taking
a sip like it's like
wine give us a little walk kind of just
tastes like water to me I don't know if
yeah it's like it's also not like
carbonated it's like juice low key that
was more of a juice in a jar than it was
a soda I didn't like it at all no I
didn't either not bad though I think I
took it back when I said I said it was
good yeah you did but you're always just
like drinking soda oh this is great this
is great dude it just like I just like
Miss saw that
all right guys the next drink that we're
going to try is the Unicorn Yak I feel
like an absolute cornball thing yeah
like that's like I think Yak is like the
most lame way to say you threw up ever
but I I threw up my favorite thing ever
is that Meme of like the r yes yes we
know it looks like a purpley little
potion like I drink this I was like a
fairy in a
garden okay you know what I mean like I
be like oh I need to go to the watering
well for my for your green juice This Is
Not Great you can't sniff it ready set
go you guys are really like taking it
down like that
yeah bad bad bad bad tastes like purpley
it tastes like sweat like it tastes like
I someone's leg it is oh no throw up um
yeah just not good right oh it's
okay it tasted like the
I Fu I just saw that you want to know
why I don't like it I just saw that like
factory reset it tastes like what I
imagine like laundry detergent would
taste like yeah they don't they don't
they taste like juice they don't taste
like um no it tastes like when you like
it tastes like when you like when the
berry hits like the sour part of your
tooth you know what I mean the sour part
of your tooth you know no like you know
when you have like when you have like a
super fuzzy Berry and it's like soury
and it's like just gross no like the
really sloppy like raspberry I think
this one of one experience I don't know
like that was gross all right the next
one is probably going to be my least
favorite the ghost pepper one if this is
actually it says this soda is very hot
your mouth may catch fire drink it your
okay it's a joke is it yeah your mouth
isn't going to catch fire no but like is
it going to be like hot I we'll be able
to like smell the hot I feel like I hate
I think we should all just go straight
in and see what happens Nick no I'm like
a little scared that it's going to be
gross but this one is Ghost Pepper
soda Matt you you need to stop pouring
this out like it's your favorite drink
yeah like he's like like such a generous
portion he's holding this like it's like
poison and he's going to like get his
ghost pepper soda on
three it it is kind of
hot it's kind of like a ooh it isn't hot
until I swallowed it it tastes it has a
good flavor you know what I mean it's
like feel hot in my I feel it in my neck
no like in my nose I feel it more in
like the like it's not like hot it
smells just like something from the past
yeah it tastes like something I used to
have sniff it Cape Cod what is it it
tastes it's like a chewy it's like the
chewy wax bottles
yes yeah that's it oh my God that's
exactly but it's not like the regular
ones it's else no it's like the wax
bottles it tastes like that but it's
like it has a gross after feeling it
it's like sensation I feel it in my in
my like tickles in my sternum tickles in
my sternum that's what it is right all
right ghost pepper soda ass moving on
coconut cream lime soda is the next I
got it hey hey hey you're already going
at it wrong you're no he's
not let it grip the bottle first stop
mad I'll do it I'll do it big baby
coconut cream lime soda this one is
going to be [ __ ] this one better be
good it's going to be busting in your
mouth yeah this one's going to be
busting for
sure too much cream not enough coconut I
agree or I it tastes like o soap
sunscreen soap sunscreen sunscreen yeah
a it tastes like how a gift shop in like
the tropics smells wa no this is not
this is not supposed to be drank no this
tastes like soapy water no this tastes
like soapy coconut sin tastes bad it
tastes like soapy that's like my least
favorite one so far no I wouldn't push
it that I would that tastes like I'm
licking like a soapy coconut water stop
drinking it Matt okay the next one we
have is grandma's Apple Pie it's just
apple pie brother put it in your glass
if I'm the last one I'll drink it out
the thing oh
okay worse than I thought it tastes like
apple juice low key
it's kind of good it's like perfectly
Apple no it's like not good but it's
like still it on myself I thought we
were about to get robbed and shot no I
still myself I feel like okay it's not
good but it's what I what I
would this is a good one this is a good
one this one's good for the flavor yeah
it's good for like what like you have to
think of what we bought we bought apple
pie soda that's exactly what I want to
tast I just feel like all of these ones
that we had so far guys I probably
haven't done like mustard yet stop it
don't even say that buffalo wing soda oh
God we're about to get even
spicier I'm just going to pretend it's
orange cream SAU do you think there's
actual buffalo sauce in here don't even
say it don't even say it Nick you like
buffalo wings I'm a big fan of buffalo
wings only this came with tits like
Hooters okay
let's you good Ready set
go not bad
I didn't even try it yet I just wanted
to see if you guys I got like no flavor
it tastes like just wax
again that tastes like the other one I'm
getting like salt it tastes like Wax
like it tastes like a a prank like it
tastes like someone rubed a feather on
my
nose it tastes like a little it tastes
like a little like itch you know what I
mean it's not bad I could drink this
whole thing yeah it's not Buffalo I'm
probably not I'm probably not going to
but I could that one's not bad that we
had they're not bad every time I pass
something in my floor stop
you know what I me every single time
something passes Chris's throat he feels
the burn no but I get it it's like here
yes like yeah right there right here
that's like where I'm feeling it mustard
soda this one I hate mustard IRS I was
searching in there for a ketchup one
just for you that and that's the closest
that I actually this I'll give a shot
Mustard's my like one of my top three
cryonite yeah Nick you want know what I
was going to say earlier before the
other drink what Matt oh he got a he
caught a whiff he caught a whiff
it smells like mustard in here don't
this one might make me throw up no I
can't I can't no no no we should do a
little we should do this last we should
put this to the side and do it last last
We need oh my God I feel it like in my
in my eyeball when I snit we're going to
we're doing this last we're doing this
last we're doing the mustard last I
don't know if this is going to be any
better any better butter is one of my
least favorite things ever there's like
butter like too much butter on Rice too
much butter on like anything too much
butter on toast I'll throw up so this
one I I think there's nothing butter
than butter I hate butter I'm not
excited for this at
all okay weird noise butter soda butter
butter said butter soda v u d d e r
butter
soda pinching your nose is a cheat
[ __ ] let go
that this one they executed the flavor
really well it's like a melted butter
stick you have to take a you have to sip
it Matt I'll give you $100 if you drink
the whole thing $100 my got it $100 I'll
shake your hand I'll shake your hand
I'll shake your hand right now 100 cuz I
was holding my nose go that go mat go go
go chug ch ch chug chug chug drink it
drink it drink
it I can't be near you
oh it's the
worst it's awful don't drink the whole
thing I'll give you $100 not to drink
it I can't even look at you drink all
that what a terrible thing what a
terrible thing I think I got blindsided
cuz I tried to plug my nose and then
that made me unplug it so I was like
halfway down the hatch and it was just
like boom it hit me right in the face
like a ton of bricks guys I think if I
burp later I'm going to throw up just
don't burp it is cucumber
the time I feel like this this one just
has to taste like cucumber water
cucumber is like good way love this has
to just taste like cucumber water like
can't taste I just like I'm really I
hate the Cucumber Gatorade oh if like I
have like a traumatizing experience with
theator what happened to you nothing I
just took a sip of it yeah so now
like that one like body put a fight in
reject it like my white blood cells or
something were like no no no like it was
in my throat my body was shooting it
back out
instantly oh my God that one's actually
that one doesn't taste like cucumber it
tastes like they added this is like what
a cucumber wish it tastes like like it
yeah it's like a it's good for cucumber
it's just ass if you switched the labels
to the last three we had I could have
been like all right I'm getting like the
same thing a very slight difference like
I don't there's it's just all gross like
like okay let's name all of these gross
foods and just make them taste bad color
it's more the color than anything yeah
moving on if I went out in public right
now and I saw a baby getting burped I'd
probably be
jealous like actually be [ __ ] me I
need burped right now maple syrup soap
so excited maple syrup is like in my top
10 of like if this I I'll be really
upset if this disappoints oh I already
can smell it this is good I also love a
brown can it's like I'm just drinking
it's just like classic like I'm I'm I'm
looking at an
alligator you know what I mean like I
have no clue no it's like USA flag Jorts
and a suntan drinking a beer let's drink
it yeah oh yeah they perfected the maple
syrup taste I feel like I just had a
[ __ ] pancake baby call me breakfast
that was good if I if you gave me this
this is Jack in my flaps I needan flap
in My Jacks Jack in my flaps what if you
gave me a [ __ ] waffle and dump this
[ __ ] on it I'd think I'm having a I
agree I think I'd think I'm having a
normal breakfast it just tastes like
watery syrup that tastes exactly like
syrup way to knock it out of the [ __ ]
Park got way to go that [ __ ] was Del
want more moving on they going to go
pull Trigg in the
bathroom I'm just going to this one is
birthday cake I'm excited I was a
birthday cake ice cream kid like the
kids that get like the birthday cake ice
cream at friendlies and like they walk
by covered like blue [ __ ] frosting on
their face that was me I like cake
pops I like cake pops okay
baby wait I just realized all the sodas
are this couple the
fixen yeah ler and his lers are bad and
Melba are good fler melb fixen that's so
cute I [ __ ] hate them let's
go ooh that's delicious m i can get down
with that Melba what is funny Melba did
my fix
in I said ooh that's delicious ooh
that's that's delicious oh I'm good I'm
good oh I'm definitely good have some
more no thanks here you go this one is
the did you tell them what it is yeah
it's strawberry watermelon
oh my god do we know where
is oh nothing happened something bad
happen M
enough what is going on put this down
good yeah it's pretty good it's
like ooh the strawberry and watermelon
is like a little overpowering no dude
that's what it's that's the the flavors
that tastes like
2006 [ __ ] you don't know what 2006
tastes like no it tasted like that 2006
tastes like breast milk Chris you were a
baby no it tastes like
2016 you were off the tit at 3 no
way no way no that tasted like like good
like classic times like good classic
times no I felt like a kid right then
you should name like these like like
corny snacks like I feel like you like
Chris would Chris would be the type of
guy who owns like shop called like good
classic times and he just sells like
bizarre [ __ ] that reminds him of like
his kids life okay all right guys thank
you so much for making it this far in
the video we're about to try the mustard
soda but before we do go smash the
Subscribe button down below see you in
mustard
Town it tastes
burn oh oh my
God I know
exactly what they need it didn't hit me
until I tast burn it tast burn it's all
like it won't Escape me it's like in my
head it's like a nuke like you know what
it's like it tastes like it tastes like
I'm eating like a [ __ ] it tastes like
I'm being I can't breathe I can't
breathe I don't want to breathe I don't
know I don't know give me something
else I need something I need something
go go go get me whatever you get get me
whatever you get dude that was
disgusting that is this is what they
need to give to people who are in like
prison for life here's a new punishment
instead of going to jail s a mustard
soda they should literally in court it
should be drink a mustard soda or spend
the rest of your life in prison I'd take
prison over mustard soda a burn you know
what I mean what I'm what I was trying
to say but I couldn't get it out it's
like it in your mouth it's like a fine
like okay there's like liquid in my
mouth
and then the second you swallow it's
a like it's just like it's just like all
negative senses pounding into my mouth
like
wow well thank you guys for watching us
torture ourselves with 12 terrible sodas
if you want to see us do a new 12 sodas
the place we went to today had like
hundreds of [ __ ] like this so
it's good that's the perfect rank
perfect rank the way that I look at it
is these four are my could drink again
like I could have these with a meal once
after this we're looking South for sure
yeah and then it's prison after that one
then it's like take me to county jail
and leral federal
punishment could after the meal mid
Terror never going to see you again
federal crime yeah yeah great awesome I
don't know how it got approved by the
FDA literally I don't know how we
purchase this like an ID or my will set
up no literally they should be like do
you have someone you intend to leave
stuff behind to before you take this
literally you should be able to drink
this if you have a kid at
home thank you guys so much for watching
we'll see you guys next time we see you
guys when we upload on YouTube so just
subscribe and put your notification Bell
on and that's when you'll know that we
uploaded on YouTube so true and also the
first link Down Below in the description
is our merch link there may not be merch
live right now but make sure you're
fully aware of that because when we drop
merch at 10 to sell it super quick and
you're not going to want to miss it and
then you're going to tell your mom I
[ __ ] hate you you missed the merch
drop and it's not going to be a good
look for you so
[Music]