what Nick tell them what you just told
us and all the things that we did we
said we going to travel from the islands
to Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
alled why
because I was in mat why is that like
that I was in the car a couple days ago
and I just got flashbacks
cuz I saw a big billboard okay saying
the MC Rib was back uh-huh I think we
could go get a MC rib for the first time
and I don't want to but we have to get
one but for content and being like the
McDonald's
brother oh my God McDonald's brother
like that's what like people would say
oh my god oh cuz we were like thinking
like oh we should go try the holiday pie
at McDonald's has we always try what's
new at McDonald's and when Chris said
that it hit me I think the M rib's back
okay check can you check online yeah man
you get in this and check with
him is it back trying to
check back oh my God I
actually I have chills down my spot not
available after midnight it is not
midnight what time is it 8:30 oh we got
to move why does it say that okay we're
going to try MC rib oh dude
I have chills like my
spine R I really don't want it I'm not
going yes you are Nick we have to go yes
come on turn your turn your no I can't
turn your light on you stupid idiot not
until you play do I can't play the song
you [ __ ] until you play I can't play
the song if we're vlogging you stupid
idiot God shut it off actually you look
terrible M I know what to
do oh my God I wish I had a bulletproof
stomach for this I'm literally going to
grow up I'm goingon to grow up last time
we do this [ __ ] ever seriously the Grim
Shake last time you tried the Grim Shake
disaster Halloween pumpkin [ __ ]
stick Halloween pumpkin [ __ ] it was the
boo buckets dude the boo buckets the one
thing we don't get I probably would have
enjoyed a meal it was your chicken
nuggets and french fries and apple
slices and maybe a little thing of milk
just maybe you serious I feel like
they're bringing back to MC rib too
often the Rarity level's gone for me
like it's always here again my heart's
literally racing welcome to McDonald's
would you be using the mobile apps today
no hi um so what comes on the MC rib MC
rib
yeah it's just onion pickle and sauce um
can we take the onions and pickles off
yeah so could we get two plain
mcbs yeah get the get the holiday pie
sandwich um just the just the sandwiches
is fine the holiday Pi can I get three
of the holiday pies let me confirm that
we have
okay if you don't that's totally if you
don't have any that's fine MC rib
returns it's top left it's like
glitching it's
glitching God please don't have three
holiday pies please don't have Nick's
literally Crossing his fingers hoping um
what else you guys want I just want to
can't believe I'm going to pay some good
hard-earned money on Nic ribs this is my
favorite Tik Tok audio right
now Mr I have an idea idea dude you know
me and Chris were watching SpongeBob
last night and that was the episode yeah
that was the episode what episode is it
I don't know Mr Crabs I think it's
season 2 something I have an
idea
hello
oh
thank you have a good
one everything that everything I think
that's everything they forgot half oh I
can smell the MC rib like I can smell it
am I going home or are we eating home
home home yeah we need to be in a safe
space sa enironment saing correct Nick
take it no Nick take I'm not Nick just
take in the nick take the [ __ ] bag I
really don't want it Nick I really don't
want oh I can smell it Nick take the bag
I'm going to let go thank you Nick take
it this isn't even a good hot chocolate
what are they doing over
there imagine asking someone what their
favorite item is at McDonald's and them
saying the MC rib oh I love when it's
the holiday season I get to eat a MC
ribbon followed off with a holiday pie
said no one ever all
right
W look at it look at it look at it
why is it messy bro oh guys guys guys
get together get together get together
please I need to take a photo of
commemorating this moment I don't even
know how this is some lunch lady bread
too like look at it got the seeds on it
oh my God I SN is there no I'm like I'm
actually feeling the fear what if Nick
likes it I will not like it wait I'm
trying to I'm kind of confused cuz is
there actual like bone no way they got
bone in the MD no like can you just take
a bite out of a MC rib yeah there's no
way they can so casually have like good
rib meat from McDonald's no is there
ribs in the MC rib is there bones oh
yeah is there there obviously
betters no bones no bones I think it's
just a p pork sandwich oh that changes
everything right Nick can't be as bad
but still who's going first not me
those you were so last yeah you were
last this is your rock paper scissors
threeway it was your idea you brought
the MCB to life today even a even even
if you're the odd one out you throw one
or two if you're the odd one out okay
ready set go wait wait I didn't even
have my finger Ready Set Ready set go
ready set Ready set go set
go damn it I can't take a mind of this I
really can't you have to no you have to
now big boy bite my God I'm so nervous
guys wait I don't want to touch it you
hold it I'll take the first
bite Nick you got a big bite is it Nick
stay in the camera he does want to be
seeing chewing he's good no I don't want
you guys to see how I'm
reacting till you try it well Chris is
trying it
now
both look disgusted
so did you bite it mhm oh how gross I'll
give him this ready barbecue sauce isn't
that bad best part actually bread really
bad meat awful it's like so sweet you
know what I mean the barbecue sauce is
okay I don't think i' eat a full MC rib
but I can like they're doing good for I
never ever actually thought that I'd
have a MC rib in my life but it's
definitely not like my favorite
McDonald's meal you know what I mean God
that's like the last matter how imagine
someone's fully debating oh should I get
chicken nuggets or like a MC GB get
chicken nuggets no Nick stop no just
play it safe and get the McNugget as
much no the way that I'm going to put it
is no matter how much I grow in my life
and grow up
thing I'm never going to I'm never going
to stop eating chicken nuggets I'll be a
[ __ ] million years old eating chicken
nuggets I do think if the MC rub is your
favorite thing for McDonald for being
for that being McDonald's tast
banishment for that being McDonald's
cake on on ribs not bad it's good for
McDonald's not bad now good we have to
eat the holiday pies why' you get three
dude one
each what is in it what's the cream can
you read it can you read up on this it's
is like a sugary P oh it smells good I
wonder if this one will taste like
Trevor oh it does smell really
good Nick I think you'll like
it did you eat
it like my thought is I don't love it it
tast I don't dislike it but I never want
this no the outside is good I don't like
the
cream it's not that bad I just never
wanted it
it tast like a Funfetti cupcake it's not
bad do you like the cream I'm never
really like it's a bit of a cream
overload like I feel it's putting a lot
of
cream you can dial the cream back a lot
yeah I agree this way too much cream but
the outside shell is all right the shell
was good it's really me with the amount
the heaviness like there's a lot of
cream but it still tastes super dry yes
I agree and it's freaking me out I agree
like how there was so much liquidy kind
of cream in my mouth
but it feels like that's a dry thing you
know I agree I do agree it's like
there's way too much cream in here for
me to feel like it's
dry that's how they talk about things in
like cooking shows yeah oh so dry oh so
dry but there's a cream overload not bad
cream
overload okay I'm kidding I'm kidding
I'm we need to clean our walls I think
we should get our our house
painted cuz like these marks only only
appear because we have like an all white
home you know what I mean yeah like if
we liveed in like a gray house we'd look
clean as [ __ ] correct if white it's not
even offwhite it's like white yeah we
need it to be like that's for sure our
issue correct I think we should get it
all painted the house looks better this
is new shirt
no yes it is totally not wait when did
you get it it's like blue and and nice
I've never seen you wear it well I
thought that this was blue and I'm color
blind so no it is it blue or gray it's
gray it's gray but I put blue cuz I
thought it was blue and I was like oh
yeah that's a fun fact Nick's color
blind not actually but not like
clinically diagnosed but mentally
diagnosed you can never see people from
squid game pink argue the walls people
from squid game pink red pink red it's
okay ni it's okay we all have suits that
the people are wearing the other
characters green but like an aquamarine
green green
not green not it's more blue anyway
thank you guys for watching this
beautiful awesome Wednesday video we
love it appreciate you and Nick tell
them what we have in store for December
guys today is the 29th tomorrow March
the 30th we have an announcement the
same time that this video is coming out
tomorrow so make sure you're tuned for
that it's a Stern YOLO Christmas and
it's going to be bigger better and Grand
slamer than Christmas has ever
been account before so just prepare cuz
we're taking over this entire Christmas
season right now and some guests in the
videos some guests in the videos so
basically WR tomorrow at this exact time
head to our Instagram account Matt
stop holy [ __ ] tomorrow tomorrow this
exact time at at this exact time head
over to the sternol do triplets
Instagram account Matt I'm going to kill
you head over to the stern do tri's
Instagram account right at this exact
time cuz we're going to be going
Instagram live and talking about exactly
what Christmas is no we we we should if
we don't forget and if we're all awake
yeah Matt you need to stop you need to
stop yeah and keep your eyes out cuz you
never know who's going to be joining us
for any of our this going to be guest in
the
videos that we did we said we going to
travel from the island to Madrid we had
a lot of plans but they
all why oh because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
when I with other [ __ ] my brothers