whoa hello what's up let's go let's go
it's the first day of autumn okay no
it's not but it's it's Autumn Fall is
here and welcome to stolo fall fall is
here
[Music]
hey well we are going to try fall themed
snacks and goodies today and we're going
to rate them cuz we're the St triplets
and that's what we do and after we rate
them you're going to see best is on my
side worst is on CHR side after we rate
every single thing so we're going to go
best to worst and we're going to rate
them one out of 10 yeah and before we
start we have to ask each other a fall
themed question the table that we eat on
is
sticky okay that's all I have to say
this needs to be wiped out why you shut
your [ __ ] stupid mouth get get away
get away please get the [ __ ] out of here
and just like that the table is clean
the other day I was singing and I was
dancing on the I got up on the table and
I almost broke the table Yeah I have it
on video actually insert the clip
what's your favorite Apple from the
apple picking farm like the trees I like
a yellow apple yellow of course trying
to be different I I used to like Golden
Delicious remember when I was a kid and
I get them in like my lunch box what are
you um I'm a umpire Apple gu oh you know
me so well same here what would your
Nick this is a question for you I need a
drink Nick this Halloween will you be my
boo stop it uh Nick what would be your
desired donut filling for I can't stop V
what stop am I out of a joke I made a
horrible joke and Chris is trying to get
me to say it again what Nick said no no
no
no ahe no we the floor was gross in here
and I was like Chris wipe up the floor
and he was like I don't know who you
think I am I'm not wiping up the floor
and I was already vacuuming and he's
like well it just looks like a big Ogre
in here and came all the floor and I'm
wiping it up and I said that like a good
Halloween filling like in like a donut
or something like I feel like it'd be
like a funny like runchy little places
like little flavor of the week I don't
know I don't know but it's fine St it
first
item you saw that amazing the first item
is pumpkin spice rolls G my stomach
already hurts my stomach just drops
pumpin spice Matt stop it you think it
would hurt if you got hit by one of
these dust like fly
ready yeah that was a terrible
ready come on Nick get sick I feel a
little
sick bite it and pass it down no no no
hold on this smells good don't no no no
no no no cuz I'm not eating a third of
this thing it's huge [ __ ] idiot and
that's why we don't need to cut it it
looks gross just take a bite and get out
of my
city so much
filling wait it tastes just like
something I've had before
surprised you can taste it it's all over
your
teeth it tastes like a cinnamon poptart
it tastes like a Christmas snack it
tastes like a cinnamon poptart what is
it a Christmas snack Chris gingerbread
yes how did I have to put those pieces
together for you it tastes like a
Christmas snack seven out of 10 that's a
five for me what
wa five he's five six six out of 10 the
final score median all right
this one's for the ruling and we are now
on to nerd's rope which we all know and
love but this one is spooky Edition it's
spy I'm going to hold it like no I'm
going to hold it like this and you guys
rip the other ends you
ready
perfect I'm not cleaning that I'm not
cleaning that perfect go
eat tastes like a nerd's rope 8 out of
10 out of 10 10 out of 10 okay n out of
10 so spooky
[Music]
next all right B well well item number
three disgusting pumpkin seeds I love
pumpkin seeds Okay pumpkin seeds go so
everyone have eight eight eight no I'll
have two I'll have three I'll have five
three for triplets three for triplets
three for triplets okay ready set
go it's so godamn loud next to me wait
these are these would be like a really
good salty snack what are you getting
out of it h what what do you get out of
eating this The Taste and joy like what
what do you get out of eating anything
else no it's just it feels like more
work than fun sorry it doesn't meet your
fun standards but these are two for
me I'm turning 10 so that it averages
I'm 10 out of 10 I'm like a six okay
six eight average is 6 out of 10 6 out
of 10
[Music]
I'm on my backyard huh like I'm on my
back porch eating the seed you don't
have a back porch you know what I mean
use your imagination sexy for later
thank you okay Matt felt like for some
reason we needed the Autumn mix and the
pumpkins of candy corn the word Autumn
sold me I'm not going to lie oh this
this we didn't have to get this we
didn't have to get but Chris I'm going
to kill you you of my favorite fall on
packs I take this ship very serious
I do if you stack candy corn in a circle
and continue to stack it up it looks
like corn do it all right snack number
four is technically three snacks in one
so we each have our own here which one
do we do first pumpkin pumpkin the big
ass
Tonka so good oh great M it's just like
a little like too much in your
mouth being honest I'm saying six to the
pumpkin no we can't do this crazy
averaging let's all come to a common
agreement after all three yes a regular
fie of candy corn is amazing they tastes
like the pumpkin just not in pumpkin
shape but the pumpkin's like girthier
I'm going to be honest the older I get
the less I enjoy candy
corn yeah like when I was like 8 years
old I would have a rifle thre a bag of
candy corn I don't even really want this
oh all right the gross little chocolatey
orange I love these ones
can we get to the point of like
all
yummy all right where are we at for
average four before four before I had
that last one I was at like an eight now
I'm at like a [ __ ] zero four zero yep
zero that sh I I literally would rather
die than eat that again I'm going seven
that's a
lot I'm going seven seven four zero I'm
going zero 6.5 is the average all right
it averages out to 3.6 on the candy corn
autum mix that [ __ ] was
dog next
[Music]
next I'm actually really excited about
this yeah of course you are Harvest
caramels oo don't you just feel the
tickle in your
t a Chris what grab one sorry you have
one all right you ready hold
on hold on Nick what I'm still
unwrapping mine no you're not you're
yelling you [ __ ] look at him mine's
got the tip on it look at it like how
that's gross dude like how do I get that
off like is this supposed to be like
this is more Ginger Brady than the other
I like
it m I like
it we're F so far what it's kind of an
overwhelming mouth sensation it's a lot
of mouth you got to like chew and it's a
hassle six mm-
five I feel like I'm grabbing the center
of a pumpkin pie no crust and just
eating it it does feel like that A
little I don't like just major mush
Vines straight to mushtown yeah straight
too much okay what did you say a six
five am I eating wrapper two is that a
three like this like what is this
number I couldn't tell what you were
doing is that what was that I think I'm
eating the rapper sexy to
someone all
right caramel pumpkin spice candies
average out to a
six
[Music]
next you're insane all right no can I
introduce one no next one is the pumpkin
do it no you just speak I hav done you
give me just say it say it Nick give me
it Chris every single time the person
holding it has not said it just say what
it is all right next up we have Oreo
pumpkin spice I don't know that is I
don't either why is it like a micro box
because it's it's a it's a special
limited edition I don't give a [ __ ] give
me the full give me the full thing oh
looks nasty
a golden
cracker pumpkin inside get M I took mine
I'm like we're trying to try
it
Oreo Oreo why did you do that why did
you do that Oro he said they are
good they're really good this is
the Nick it settle in for me Nick feels
a little warm inside I do I think I'd
rather a regular Oreo it smells like the
Christmas Tree Shop these are like the
only like the
Christmas these are the only cookies
that I'd probably reach for one and be
done I do not eat more than three of
these should we try with milk I think we
have to no we don't need a cup let's go
swiggy all right bet no yeah I'm not
swigging milk I'm not I'm not you are
dude what we don't have guests here ever
and we'll just tell them not to drink
the milk I don't want to do this do it
oh is it good yeah
go ahead yeah it made it way worse worse
five five solid okay five on the Oreos
five out of
[Music]
10 my
goodness what were you saying oh my God
let see let me see let me see let me see
let me see it just show me I will it
just show me it just show me oh never
mind oh my
God I thought it had black licorice but
it's wild berry watch your
head next up is Nick's very excited
Jelly Belly Monster Mash and similar to
the Candy Corn that had three different
F similar to the Candy Corn that had
three different flavors I'm going to
test five we have to try them all and
then rate whole thing overall experience
out of w to green
apple green apple quicker
quicker go go go green apple caramel
corn wild Blackberry Jewel orange and
Jewel grape soda Jewel jeel ghou
[ __ ] no that's Jewel this is
like a movie give me the jelly be just
touch my [ __ ]
them for
later thank you Chris yeah first one
Let's Go caramel corn it's caramel corn
here we go is that this one obviously
[ __ ]
you wait I really like
it I really like that one okay green
apple mhm oh delish Green City really
good wild
Blackberry not bad M tier the worst one
so far mhm this is grape soda something
like that love oh I feel it going down
my throat okay all right last but not
least Jewel
orange nice
job I love an orange oh that one's the
best eight out of 10 really good mix of
jelly beans I'll match you me three
eight it
is oh that was a new
[Music]
collab Nick please edit Crick oh guys
want to see a Halloween trick no I
really don't I can make your swag
disappear all
right you gra your I didn't know if
you're G to hit me all right everyone we
are now on to the chocolate division of
things all
right we have Kit Kats but they're
different this one is Ghost toast we
each got to borrow that and we get
witch's brew we each got to borrow this
and what flavor is that I don't know
let's go cinnamon toast let's go witch's
brew first okay or witch's brew wait
it's sniff it
smells like
soap
disgusting literally gross right yeah
it's awful yeah I'm right with you at
one Nick really one for the it tastes
like I'm eating a bar of soap I'm going
to make it a little difficult and I'm
going to say that that's a three oh so
it's we average a two no oh that [ __ ] is
nasty is actually like so gross
[Music]
next one Kit Kat ghost toast this one's
cinnamon flavor
[Laughter]
oh that could be fun what what wow let's
take time to appreciate this bar huh I
didn't take a photo of it ooh that looks
so good it looks like a creamsicle are
you getting that smell no I can't smell
it wo woo cinnamon no no no you're going
to take the side that you just pushed up
against your lip no I'm not okay
here act like we haven't Kissed before
we're
brothers when do you think like when we
like six and we go to each other and
like give each other a kiss that' be so
fun cute like when we were little let's
keep when we little right we don't do
that anymore yeah yeah this is way
better than the other six out of 10 I'd
say three I don't really like that at
all to be honest I would give that a two
it's just the wrong experience that was
a bevy or like
a okay 11 out of 30 I'm I'm I'm out of
I'm I'm done with I can't have another
pumpkin flavor thing I might become a
pumpkin like dead ass that averages out
to 3.6 out of 10 what what the 3.6
[Music]
is be R me of this pumpkin
flavor this is a lot
oh my God I thought our fridge was
Fallen Nick
really in the mouth I just you should
took our fridge Off the Wall no I
didn't thought it was going to fall over
Nick goes oh I thought our fridge was
falling ow just hit me ow
ow a neighbors guys
ready Chris get off the table all right
next up on the list is caramel and Marsh
mow pumpkins oh it's like a just it's
like a
peep we don't even need both of these
yeah wait I'm like kind of I feel like
I'm going to throw up no I feel sick
like all this pumpkin's like hitting my
gut oh I'm going to oh can I opt out can
I bite I'll take a little bite I'll take
a little bite Chris you have to can't
take a bite take a bite come on take a
bite get a
bite I hate
marshmallow I like it you are a gross
kid zero
oh got the caramel in the mar I don't
like it zero zero dead ass is zero for
me okay like zero mhm like below ground
level I'd rather lick the ground before
I eat that again that's dramatic lick
the ground no no no he thought about it
scar all right zero out of 10 for the
Russell stoven yeah what Russell
[Music]
I'm having a chocolate overload no I I
really am last of the chocolate
Wolverine tracks how cute so it's just
vanilla and milk chocolate flavored
Reese's this is I can do that this is
going to be good oh can I split with
Chris smells good yeah you can split
with chisp yeah I don't need
one
wow
okay this is good mhm pretty
straightforward tastes just like aes's
I'm going to hit it with a solid nine I
agree
[Music]
nine oh my God what is happening and
what do you think you're doing damn it I
thought I was going to be a loan but the
Tickle Monster paid me of is it all
right next up we got non sweet little
cookies non's Bakery pumpkin
spice I love a little biscotti pumpkin
away from me our hair our hairdresser
used to have literally these and coffee
when we' go there
o all right wait there's two oh no it's
just double they look good we can split
one we can split one oh it smells good
this might be it let's go let's go let's
go big Crimson
teeth oh gross
bite delish
snack if I had a coffee or a tea
nine seven seven seven five let not be
crazy five six it is six out of 10 I can
lock that in six thanks
non six for the
non all right nice KN you nice knowing
[Music]
you boy is not that com brownie brittle
all right I don't know what these are
brownie brittle obviously clearly all
right uh this one's pumpkin spice this
one's caramel apple let's do it it's
caramel shut up I don't care which one
are you doing first hello we'll go
pumpkin spice biteen bite and pass no no
no just pick one it's
small kind of good I like this
experience it's
like w I don't like it at all W oh I
hate being the only one that doesn't
like it like a six no it's not that good
I'll give it a four it's not it tastes
like chalk oh
no the finale just ruined it the finale
the fireworks are setting it down yeah
like a two
two I'd say three the flavor that's
sitting in my mouth is like a is like
not good 3.6 again 3.6 yeah don't throw
it how did I do that math I don't know I
think it's 3.6 I don't know we're you'll
count it though
[Music]
caramel apple same I'm EXC I'm excited
for this one I'm
excited fighting pass much
really I think it's better than that one
I tap out he thinks it's better than
that one not even [ __ ] close this is
like an eight for me one I'd eat this
whole thing you are a sicko I would
you're so sick eight
no no
eight one one
four 10 divided by 30 Nick 3.3 group
consensus of a
3.3 all right now it's ice cream
[Music]
time all right guys we have our final
item this pumpkin ice cream and then
we're going to do this Mochi for Tik Tok
what's in there got to let those thaw
out wow [ __ ] dude it sounds like I threw
a f medicine this is sweet potato and
marshmallow that's how they do it on
Thanksgiving flavor is everything well I
hope so how do you guys want to do this
with a spoon or just yeah that's what I
was going to do go you're up that was
criminal you guys can just bite an ice
cream like that see
yeah oh it's
gross oh he wants to spin it back oh
there's Crunchies in there zero that was
the worst thing I actually kind of
gnarly like how is that for sale type of
questioning zero zero out of 10 oh I
feel bad for that company we just like
ridiculed it to our millions of
followers it's it's the well it's there
there there's there's it's the way the
cookie Crum there's something there's
something for everybody we are not the
audience for those yeah thank you guys
for watching this week's Friday video we
hope you really really enjoyed it go
follow us on Instagram as a group go
follow us on Instagram individually go
follow us on Tik Tok as a group go
follow us on Tik Tok individually and
make sure you subscribe to us here on
the sty trip channel so that you never
miss a video and sometimes we live
stream on Twitch so make sure you follow
us on Twitch so that fortnite Battle
Royale if you want to come hang out with
us play fortnite sometimes we sit there
and talk the link to everything I just
told you is in the description down
below so you can click all of those
buttons but if you want to head over to
our Tik Tok first we're going to be
trying this and posting this the minute
the video comes out so if you want to
see us try this pumpkin spice Mochi
we're going to do that over on Tik Tok
we see you guys next week on Friday with
more fall content hopefully what I was
going to join in on this outro
experience but my brothers did it there
you go I don't know what to do there
fist bump that's all it is okay
[Music]