I bought 100 one two three
[Applause]
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
[Music]
yeah
Okay so
as you all know we're here because we're
YouTubers yes
good we're on the same page so
um as YouTubers we answer questions in
our car a lot but we're not in a car
we're on a stage of New York but we
still have questions
okay so if that sounds good to you guys
I'm gonna answer questions great if you
could switch lives with anyone who would
it be and why
if I could switch
[Music]
I
I would say exercise with Matt because
it's my life but a little bit easier
I didn't do the same thing but he
doesn't I think I would switch lives
with dick because I wanted to figure out
what he has to complain about so
what what do you feel like I would say
the same thing as Matt but I also have
the answer of our big brother Justin to
watch us when we grow up together
all right I need all you guys to see if
she blanks and then he'll judge me okay
I'll be the job all right hold on dude
start with your eyes shut someone report
her all right I'll count you in both you
guys better have your eyes shut I'm
looking at both of you three I said okay
okay three oh we'll sit over here on the
floor three two one
oh yeah
[Applause]
it's blinked off red
you lost you know it's a lot harder with
these lights
somewhere near me right now I'm creating
a nice breeze
congratulence questions good job
congrats you win guys since we're on
tour we have so many amazing fans coming
and visiting us and bringing us goodies
and gifts and here's a collection of
like little foreign snackies we've
gotten and so we're gonna invite our
friends to our hotel room and try them
for the video
[Music]
ah
then Matt close to the fight oh my God
such a strong shriek oh my God he scared
me
tomorrow we have our Boston show oh see
why they're so violent he doesn't mean
the stomach
he said I'm gonna sell a spooky story
someone is at the door
oh
[Music]
my God
get these from
awesome fans bro
and he's got like a like a jelly-ish
like oh
I think it's not like jelly though I'm
not explaining
it's okay so um you love this not bad I
love them
you just said yeah he's a good branding
it looks nice
you didn't even get to the middle yet oh
oh yeah
the first time I bit into it I judged it
in the beginning on the bus
it was ass
it is still ass but yeah it's a little
better than us because I'm giving it
more of a try because the middle is
actually not it's like we're gonna go
we're gonna go from right I wouldn't
hold on just willingly but if I had it
I don't understand what are you on a
phone with what are they calling
are you calling the company
I'm just doing my thing okay I want this
what's it called the caramel
Cara milk
it was fine what it's pretty good
it tastes like what it tastes like yeah
yeah
I agree
like it's like I've had this before you
know what I mean wait I want to try it
it was like whatever we see what it
looks like it tastes like that it's a
foreign
oh that's just good yeah yeah it's very
sugary all right so I'm replacing it my
favorite sugar
better or worse
I was just haters bro
okay it's French these are friends
like a fan come on girl
this is very nice you know British it is
right on the head yeah it could be a
taste tester you're good at it great
detail it is
no it's a better Eminem it's way better
and you know why it's thinner because no
because in Europe they don't have excess
of like they don't have XL things they
don't have like you can't get a fat ass
bag of cereal in Europe they don't do
that [ __ ] because they have portions
it's crazy you know in Canada they have
bags of milk that's why no one's right
like they put their milk it's like swear
to God like this is really good
everything is in bags they don't have
cartons jugs
[Laughter]
yo Trail your teeth look so white right
now
Colgate you know I kind of liked it I
just I just got the dust in my face no
it is very hard Nick loves it
that was good all right
oh yeah yeah you just clicked the group
rank okay Arrow I love that I hate it I
agree with this yeah this is weird Okay
Nestle coffee crisps
that looks nice all right I'll try this
one and then I'll try this bro that
looks like one of those like little
damages
really good number one number one number
one number one
this is really good number one all right
hold on okay I need to try this number
one I'm gonna try this here
number one let's go coffee Chris what's
blowing that is good sure
Matt approved number one number one not
so much like it tastes like coffee
that's the point give me a Java cake let
me I'll tell you what a job oh wow
you're kind of the rest of these
it's not bad is it
go ahead and finish it finish it then
tell me how you tastes
[Laughter]
it's a lot better
nobody else visits that [ __ ] so it's a
lot better than I thought
questionable unquestionable Let's uh
that's not bad but it's not better than
this
it's not better than this look at this
table brought some maps
I don't think I'll be eating this it
looks so sweet sweet oh [ __ ] oh what's
in the middle wow
yeah that smells so good oh my God
[Laughter]
amazing pack it up we're on the bus
these are great these are wonderful
number one
oh I love maple syrup
[Laughter]
this is our final rank
s wait let's see if you're out of
nowhere
I'm not laughing so studious
this is wait wait wait wait this is the
final right yeah this one's really here
yeah no no that's just awesome this is
way better oh this was better than this
in my opinion yeah that country was dog
[ __ ] I hate crunches man that's a final
order in my opinion okay well oh yes
whoa and then what you're saying how you
miss me yeah you miss me and all the
things