after what's it called I want you to
feel it
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
[Music]
oh my God I just thought that I was
gonna throw up
oh my God
okay all right not to help with the
throw bite unless you threw up but we're
gonna try that's good Segway we're gonna
try weird food combinations that I found
on the internet this is gonna be an
interesting video because I'm the kid
that's like only eating chicken fingers
and cheeseburgers every day first food
whatever first food is gonna be white
bread toasted so toast with sprinkles
okay toast toast
okay yeah toast
I don't know if that's gonna work that's
okay we'll see okay butter butter I
can't believe that's not fun stop stop
like transition ruin done what's mine
really yeah that's enough weird light on
the sprinkles aren't you you know it's
supposed to go you're not supposed to
like I feel like a decent amount and
then flip the toast you know what I mean
so it ever doesn't stick to the bread
Nick you know what I mean it's such a
smart little palette and it's just like
a
oh see then now you're like no I just
got what I got the pink toasted bread
blue toasted
oh my god wow okay ready everyone go
no it's actually delicious
well you have to also include the fact
that the only weird part about this is
sprinkles I just realized these badass
just ate toast oh yeah with wrinkles use
a toast
okay I'm confused
whoa this is delicious I'm upping it to
a five right out of the ten yeah I give
this like a seven bro it's just like
toast Matt
I'm not doing this hold on hold the
Knife Down
thank you move over
the next one we're doing is watermelon
and salt
can I open you can cut it in half you
can cut it into triangles okay
salt ready do you want to pick your
slice first why don't you just salt the
[ __ ] watermelon salt them off
I'm not trying to [ __ ] have a heart
attack please
I love salt yeah no sugar okay I'm
eating this one this one looks good
okay cheers Chris I want to rub them
together
it just tastes like watermelon but far
less enjoyable it like takes the juicy
out of it
I hate it
oh my God it's really bad it just takes
the juicy out of the water oh my God
it's awful I'm like shocked at how bad
it is I'm like eating I'm like eating
the side without the salt
it's really bad it almost like it's like
a weird chemical reaction
it's so it doesn't taste like sauce I
think I might have put too much salt
that one's a series maybe a heart attack
no that one's a zero
oh that one's a zero oh my God that was
bad next next all right next is popcorn
and hot sauce I'm not a fan of hot sauce
at all so don't know where this is gonna
go for me
popcorn's on hot sauce am I so boring
let's go sauce it up oh my God I just
figured we could dip it into this you
know
that's probably the most Tabasco sauce
that's ever been in one bowl at a time
that's not sure I know people who go
crazy for Tabasco let's move I'm really
scared give it a snip
in it I feel like I'd want my popcorn oh
my God oh my God oh my God I feel like I
dip it I feel like I'm at now after the
reactions yes you will I feel like I
want my popcorn
okay
that's probably one of the worst things
I ever remember
probably one of the worst I just don't
like it because it's wet like it gets
soft it's almost like putting popcorn in
water before I didn't bro if y'all hear
snoring Malcolm's on our couch by the
way
I'm giving this a zero like a legitimate
zero
no this [ __ ] was ass bro hold on five
dollars for wedding anyone
get away from me no no
this next one I'm actually really
excited for because it's not really a
weird food combo it's kind of just like
a food combo in Mexican culture oh guess
what it is what you know mango and the
chili flakes yes mango and chili powder
[Applause]
all right I'll chili them out first let
me do it actually I'm gonna scrape this
one like okay can you not put a lot yeah
I got you
that's a lot that's not a lot that's
like you gotta think man if you don't
eat it here all right give me light like
like that's perfect seti all right mango
this might be my first time eating a
mango too ready mango and chili flakes
Russia's low-key gas
it's a sweet in the hot experience it's
good like I'd just rather eat a mango
alone
not bad not my favorite we'll do it
again probably yeah same
yeah I agree I'm still going higher on
the scale it was definitely better than
the [ __ ] watermelon salt and the can
I try mango look right those are my
favorite fruit
yeah my name is good I'm definitely not
gonna join that like that bro all right
no let's do seven let's have an average
all right seven out of ten I'm going to
chili flakes next one next one I'm not
really excited for oh God guesses
um pickles no not yet I don't know
avocado and chocolate
who does that [ __ ] bro I don't know
let's see what was the first one like
who's doing this
this ain't no Curry oh wow what I'm kind
of creaming
[Laughter]
wow these are pretty fresh avocado that
wow that's like magazine avocado thank
you that's like the meme it's the
kitchen
here's my other half and it's like the
album no this is definitely like the
avocado meme where it's like me and you
I didn't know there was an avocado me on
what
I know exactly you guys are both like
that's like the meme I'm like no are you
not like the good old I don't matter if
you wanted me to account you'll find
yourself match my chocolate yeah okay I
got you okay I like mine thin as well
yeah okay this is on there boom it's
okay looks like a sushi type I don't
know can someone sign me up no I love
avocado a small small I have a feeling
I'm gonna enjoy this because I genuinely
really like both
they're kind of plain like they're in
the water avocado chocolate
wow fantastic
I just like my chocolate alone
uh I'd absolutely do that again I would
that's like 10 out of 10. this is like a
texture thing like with me it's squishy
not chocolate cheese
I was actually good at spot Chris bring
more oh not good is good but I won't do
it again okay but it's not bad next one
all right next one
next one I'm not excited for at all okay
any guesses pickles we're just gonna
keep saying pickles pickles no I don't
like pickles pickles pickles you saw
what I bought I hate pickles you saw
what I bought today we use cloud like no
one's listening listen Okay it goes you
saw what I bought today pickles and what
do you think it is
probably like the honey or some [ __ ]
orange juice
it's supposed to dip it in
bro that has to be like someone was
eating a pickle and they slipped and
like dropped it in there
Ready Set Go
I can't even taste the orange
you didn't dip enough them that's just
ass
oh no
it's like such a it's so interesting
maybe it's not that bad because the
Pickle's so I think we need a big dip
like I'm going Tonka dip on this
I don't mind it
I'd say it's like a solid five but never
am I doing anything honestly dude like
it dulls down the pickle for me and I'm
not a huge pickle I made it better
really wait because I'm not I I don't
like how aggressive pickles are like
people are in your face like oh you know
and this like just like it's like a nice
little oh no I'm here it's like hey all
right next one next one I have a really
good idea for this one it's apple juice
and goldfish
okay
I I love apple juice but I just
currently turned into more of an orange
juice Enthusiast yeah we're gonna go
cereal mode yeah
it's like with the milk and cereal but
it's apple juice and gold I feel like
anything you need to cleanse my pickle
palette God don't don't ever repeat that
or no man
this is such a way can I take a photo of
this okay all right
set go I can't like where am I supposed
kind of good I don't like it it's kind
of good no that's just ass
getting the whole school of fish right
now and I got a really good taste like
oh my God like oh well I don't like that
much he's enjoying it
freaking me out Loki could be bro like
three scoops is insane he wants it he
only wants more and this Loki could be
something I eat oh my God you're so
weird
like it's not bad enough for me to be
freaking out
yeah but it's not good enough yeah we're
doing it for six plus you haven't even
chewed the first Spoonful yeah eight out
of ten you're disgusting it wasn't like
amazing I won't do it again but it
wasn't awful all right next one all
right next one is probably arguably my
biggest [ __ ] fear
oh no what is it green apples
[Applause]
whoa this is a brand new album y'all for
real picked the best Granny Smith I've
seen in my life
that's granny right yeah yeah what about
me
bro chill I just spilled that on myself
someone puts in the fridge I don't want
to hear me ever again oh ready let's go
okay
I feel really defeated
just like let's move on
most foul thing that I think I've ever
put in my mouth in my whole 16 19 years
16. that's where are you that was a zero
this [ __ ] just blew my [ __ ] time
frame off yeah
honey in the bowl
oh my honey that comes out slow
oh my God honey such a luscious looking
thing bro luscious yes that doesn't look
like like okay okay you don't need a lot
I could lick that right now okay ready
set no legit hold on
before we dip Chris
okay can we go yeah
oh it's like slow
it's like molasses bro I'm gonna really
guys bro
all right french fries Ready Set Go
what's the noise for
it wasn't that bad
I give you like a six out of ten
never doing it again but six out of ten
see this is my weird [ __ ] bro I'm really
[ __ ] with this
very very mixture of Music across the
board I really [ __ ] with this we have
whimpering and pain tolerable
he really [ __ ] with it
what a crazy olive oil and vanilla ice
cream
the oil's not hitting for me the oil hit
for me and it's not
I hope it never hits again oh it's kind
of good I'm here oh you're weird you're
good that one's oily it's kind of good
bro get the ice cream off your lip
before you say it again stop sure
I can't do this I can't do a bite of
this anymore it's kind of great oh my
god oh that one's really oily yeah
I think that's what I got the first time
maybe I just didn't get oil yet
we have so many plans and I know that
it's been a constant state of the
sternula triplets telling you guys oh
what they're gonna do what they're gonna
do whoa
leave me alone April I think is going to
be one of the best sternula triplet
content months since OG starting to
electronics that's a big promise I
seriously agree I think group account
tick tocks every day every single one of
us Tick Tock every single day I think
great Vlogs I think amazing podcasts
what else by the end of April at least
I think like I seriously think that
April is going to be the best during the
triplet month since January of 2021.
with that being said
I love you all and I'm excited podcast
soon and then what you're saying how you
miss me yeah you miss me and all the
things