first snack we're
trying yay
press okay me and Matt bought a bunch of
snacks noce the audience inod the whole
thing today what we're doing it's the
holiday season we're with Madison
Beer
EXC and me and Matt me and mat went to
Target today and got
yes and we got a bunch of holiday themed
snacks some of them are just snacks that
are year round but the Holiday version
so let's get after we're going to try
them all and rank them all from best to
worst I want to be like the the the
revealer okay that's a good title the
revealer okay this is an everyday snack
with this red and green tortilla chips
I'm kind of like really scared of how
vibrant these are that's that's a bright
green ooh
ready it looks like a
mistake okay it's a tortilla chip
nothing special good yeah exactly what I
could have predicted it does taste weird
guacamole it tastes weird plain but I'd
be terrified I love it it tastes weird
guacamole it's all
right it yeah we love guacamole Squad
I'm very midlevel on guacamole I don't
like the way it said guacamole I love it
yeah that's number one for now right
okay well there's nothing to compare
yeah that's good yeah I like next we'll
do peppermint oh no no what no pepper
I'm not a pepper person oh my God I can
already smell how bad it is it's not bad
they're good I like these don't let
Presley have it dogs can't have
chocolate pres take
wow I like it more than the tetilla
chip tetilla chip you don't like these
no it's fine right you're going to eat
that whole thing do you like it more I
took a nible noral you like it more or
less than the tortilla more me too more
I agree with that I can get up I can get
down with that okay
water we got like nothing in there we
have only soda we have Pepsi this is why
Chris doesn't drink water though it's
cuz you don't have
any yeah I don't even drink bottle water
and he added the hassle of getting a cup
first what are you doing I'm making a
surely Temple what I just want to get a
cup in the bottle oh my God you guys are
sick you guys I see one person
participating in the freak activity o
this is disturbing all right we're
moving on temples love but not like that
what about a joy Roger what's that one
is that Roy rer Roy
Roger all right peppermint farts maple
syrup goldfish maple syrup themed off
the elf movie well we'll try them that's
exactly what we're going to do Matt you
get one one awes I you already are you
gone already sorry no you're good too
excited oh my gosh they're the worst
thing we've eaten without a doubt it's
in front of it's number one for me
guaranteed I like them yeah I don't know
where you're at better than or sick it's
definitely better than this yeah
definitely better than that yeah if you
guys all agree then I can just I can
I'll be okay with it Matt Krabby Patty's
holiday M y'all just really said [ __ ] it
we're just going to get anything that's
red and green and call it a holiday
snack everything on this has said Thank
literally where's this it's Elf movie
does it say holiday limited edition with
snowflakes and an elf on it you're
telling me it's not for Christmas he
said everything on this quote unquote
literally play it back everything on
this table says holiday did he just say
that dude
leave there's an elf on said what I said
sure is wrong but it's holiday theme it
is holiday theme it's holiday them
question in the world crabby patties oh
my God there's three different colors
going to go bun yeah me too just bun
Pepto
bismal all right everyone take a bite I
took this part out cuz I don't like
lettuce it's
thatd why is it really good I'm not a
fan it tast at
allit guys why is it fire put that the
zero what is happening I just with
everybody you say shut up all right
we're going to keep going too much
talking
Fruity Fruity Pebbles and cocoa eating
the cocoa po one I refuse as of now try
it all right two of us got to go Coco
two of us can go Fruity Pebbles Nick
what do you want we should both be
fruity I'll try the fruity one too kid
what is going on I'm trying Matt it's
[ __ ] in a condom I don't know what's
going on it's crazy like you're insane
it's
w rapper I know all ready cheater well I
thought ready you
go guys I don't taste
anything oh
my it is true for
me it's bad no they executed the pr fa
flavor no I got the FR peels eventually
I just feel like I have to suck on it
for a good while the flavor out y had it
before Oh my God that eat it it's so
awful it's really bad you have no NOP
NOP Noe
you'll get it in a second really bad it
tastes like a Tootsie Roll you left out
for 10
years okay those are saf we in last
place all right which one's in last I
like these better than the craby patties
I agree no I like the fruity one more I
go Coco to the right you guys are sick
they're both worse than the Krabby
Patties they're worse than the crabby
patty yeah go on oh it was like a hand
of agreement oh I got agree good all
right moving on
what I don't like that agement agement
okay I don't like
the I don't know Snowball Citrus holiday
exclusive right there still look on this
B I feel like you're you're a little too
confused on something that's really easy
to comprehend there's holiday edition
snacks guys take a guess about what I'm
going to do he's going to call me
tough what's I thought holidays was like
good fun it doesn't smell good guys so
wored take a bite ready like no cookie
should smell like a lemon oh now great
great go took a deep breath and [ __ ]
bre okay oh great have to eat this with
a bib on like a candy canes it tastes
good but the hassle is not worth it put
it at the back I'm putting it here the
hassle what's the hassle oh I got to get
all messy I got
that I agree no no no no no I can get
behind that I agree the cookies were
good pressing want the another one here
you go oh see sorry for the snow it's a
[ __ ] assley I'm sorry sorry for the
snow okay I just don't like it like it's
like dude first of all anything that
comes in a package like that's
ridiculous I'm not going to eat all five
what if I wanted one so you put one you
get one and then you go like
this my baby bottle pop candy these are
going to be fabulous you got to like get
oh my God I'm so excited are you guys
like more like Cherry people or Blue Rag
I'm definitely a cherry person Cherry
blue all day Cherry Slurpees you don't
get a blue one you get a red one
honestly actually I get blue no I was
going to say I get blue too yeah guys
it's actually kind of lit I really like
this are think number
one let me let me get my hands on this
I'm thinking yeah definitely better than
those goldfish I'm 100% this well cuz
also it's like what a fun and Innovative
way to redo the candy can I love you
know what I mean all right we're going
in the one slot hand of agreement Chris
you just took a baby bottle pop and made
it fabulously holiday theme but also
with a baby bottle pop you kind of got
to like get the lid and then flip it and
then shake it get so is a dropper like
the sour drop
off Royal this is not a sewing kit you
guys know the the whole thing with that
the lore you guys know the L these boxes
SE I have no
idea Danish butter cookies oh butter
yummy I hate butter guys I can't yeah
give it to me I got it oh don't break
your
to if I was Nick I'd be swinging right
now like I wouldn't even why what don't
I if try this next one while M get that
Terry's snowball this is supposed to go
in hot chocolate no it's not it's an
orange flavored snowball it's like this
chocolate is sliced like an orange
like you've had this before I've seen
this before I've seen it too and never
tried it so I'm excited I don't think
I've tried it I think it tastes like
it's orange flavor orange chocolate yeah
it's like orange e CH I'm sensing but
look how cool
it's guys that is nice of agreement I
would say more of an apple um what try
indul I I use said
indul we have to really do it oh what's
inside it's like crunchy yeah last lot
this is better than the cocoa pops candy
oh you didn't eat it like an orange you
ate the edge I ate it like a
that's
weird everyone else with the edge I
thought you were supposed to eat it like
an orange I put it here no I'm eatting a
million crabby patties before I sniff
this again what you're crazy yeah this
was in the wrong spot do you like the
crab and patties more no that is absurd
I'll buy it whatever [ __ ] I don't care I
agree with that do you agree uhhuh hand
of
agreement
no I forgot you don't agree I thought
you were just not paying
attention I thought that you were just
for I invented the end of agreement
three people put their hands up it stays
that's the rule oh are we all going
pretzel it just like sug they all taste
the same
sugariest mhm let's do it prusty ready
for my
crumbs he really is
dud he knows I'm the sloppy one that's
going
I mean it's just like literally
bread that's good though dude that's
like me too like that with like a nice
cup of coffee or hot chocolate I agree I
eat more of these than I would I even
say I even push it past the goldfish in
my popular opinion I kind of agree pain
of agreement two nice that was delicious
actually candy cane Hershey Kisses hat
it already but you P them just like
peppermint oh yeah white chocolate oh my
God this is your biggest nightmare White
Chocolate and Peppermint my nightmare
you don't white chocolate I love
these oh it's I can't do it it like
smell like gone yeah no just it's
delicious what do you think don't like
it where first but you can rank it I
would put it right there okay I can do
that I can do that too like the the
chocolate ones are better like right
there I AG yeah okay this one's really
terrifying that me and Matt are going to
do I'm really scared yeah you guys
probably won't like it Nick and Matt
went shopping today by by the way for
this I didn't go inside the store so I'm
also on the same page as you where I
like just don't know anything guys
eggnog I feel like you love it probably
I've G my whole life without trying it
same we've never had oh my God we're all
about to [ __ ] eat egg warm me and I
don't know should we warm it up I don't
we have to eat this we have to eat it in
the most like the way it's intended all
right I'll go yeah I was going to say
somebody well also me and Matt wereat up
eggnog me and Matt were surprised Google
that me and Matt were shocked cuz it
says non alcoholic it's like do they
sell alcoholic no a lot of people put
like brandy in it make makeig fancy
holiday I didn't know that you knew this
I think we could just take a sip of this
out of the fridge I think you can I
think you really can the deep breath
trust I really think you can eggnog is
usually served cold but you may choose
to heat it up wa so what is eggnog
what's an EG okay egg is of the
ingredients I feel like it's got to be
just milk um just fancy milk cream high
fructose corn syrup oh that's in
everything thank you what is that not
everything's got high fructose corn
syrup I call the blue cup or not be
afraid that sounded good though from
everything you just said it B don't what
shake well supposed to shake
it why not shake it the color oh it's oh
it's yellow and thick
hey yellow and thick what are you saying
a
to what what requires that it smells
good I called the blue cup thank you
it's did you say thankk you thank you
he's said not finishing cheers I'm about
to
drink Christmas happy
holidays oh I don't I hate it at all
it's really good actually guys you
wanted to I wanted to like really not
enjoy this experience why tastes like
every holiday snack I've ever had in my
life in one drink it tastes like
Christmas this morning oh [ __ ] it we're
going all the way guys this is oh wow
wow I actually really just enjoyed that
what are your guys thoughts completely
agree I think it's like near here wow I
did not
expect pass the cookies is pushing it a
little bit no I I'd agree it's really
yummy Okay Hand of Agreement N okay I
just know if I had a nice tall glass
that my stomach would hurt no yeah I
can't believe we're like 20 all in our
20s and have never had eggnog before
I've avoided it no me too cuz it sounds
gross eggnog like I to make such an
unflattering name I told Nick when we
came up with this video idea like we
have to have carrots for the rain dude
this is a cartoon ass
carrot that's what bugs Mone no look I
see just sticking out the ground like
the big green
thing [ __ ] carrots
yeah oh it's tastes like
dirt it's good though no it tastes like
it came out of the ground an hour ago um
is very fresh it's just like a different
category for me you know I personally
like glazed
carrots not and we're not doing that
they're just carrots like it's hard to r
at the bottom bottom these are the last
are they're better than the Cocoa
Pebbles Italian dry salami oh you're
just steing anything holiday that's what
we're doing this is in the holiday
section you guys can try that one oh
yeah you don't have meat oh
yes am I supposed to just bite that
what's going on you can try
it B bite out of you want me to cut it
for you do you want me to cut it for you
oh wow you're sick just oh I already
smell like the deli I like pepperoni
it's salami oh what so they're cousins I
think yeah big fans bacon ham take a big
bite salami take a big oh that's
terrifying take a big bite right there
like a big Giant's
finger pork salt and less than 2% of the
following deck
row I'm there you go yes I'm okay fast I
was showing you the bite good bite thank
you no s stuck my teeth it was way
better than these Citrus [ __ ] messes
yeah right there dark chocolate caramel
cookie caramel corn flusters wow say
that really
good love that [ __ ] I'm not a fan best
no I put it in best number one no hands
thank you all right I'm not the biggest
fan that's oh it's just coffee we can
just take a sip oh no a Sip Coffee a
small sip it's peppermint coffee oh no
oh yeah yeah I tried to make it better
wor peppermint mocha seems like some
annoying person to order this in front
of me I got to wait for this dummy to
get her peppernut
pepper really bad you're going to hate
it it smells like mint chocolate chip
ice cream it's probably good I hate itz
I hate coffee too if I think about it
like that I don't hate it it's actually
not bad yeah this shit's [ __ ]
disgusting absolutely it's not bad never
having it again though I love mint
chocolate chip but I don't like to have
I I love mint chocolate chip
yeah that's good yeah that's perfect
perfect all cherry CH it's bad so bad I
remember Christmas morning my
grandmother gave these to Chris and he
thought it was just chocolate and he
like threw up I just don't understand
how things can be even sold like how is
this in stores like how are there enough
people buying this garbage to put in
retailing stores come on time for
medication I'm actually not eating this
guy I like can I take like my one
pass Madison tried multiple things she
didn't want you didn't have salami
though you don't eat meat I don't eat
cherry Cher you Cherry Frosty let's go 1
two
three my mouth is like filled with
liquid all in one moment did you eat it
yeah I hate the whole
thing not eating
this I refuseed to eat this you can spit
it right back on his I literally refuse
to eat this chocolate Mas put at the end
delicious there you go you all over your
face you MK Chris where do you want to
put
these regular old candy can that
certified classic righte of eggnog I put
it ahead of eggnog too I put it right
here actually guys I haven't even tried
it yet no BL Pop's better the really I'm
still eating mine white CH chocy
dipp what white chocy dipp pretzels hold
up
okay
go I really enjoy I would literally put
this number one I would do we each get a
gingerbread cookie yay they're little
cue a thank you yes here Chris oh CHR
all right guys oh my God mine has the
most festive pants on ever I feel like
you would rock those that's been this
Christmas video stay tuned for more
Christmas videos about about hope you're
enjoying the Christmas content so far
shout out Madison for joining us today y
thank you and Shout Out Presley as well
he's also here
a know what you saying how you miss me
yeah you miss me and all the things that
we did we said we going to travel from
the island to Madrid we had a lot of
plans but they
all why because of some but it's okay
cuz I'm moving different don't be saying
when I P with other [ __ ] my brothers