good morning everybody
we're all going to the airport to just
fill out agricultural forms and that's
it anyway we're going to Hawaii for a
Mad Dog's birthday so happy birthday Mad
Dog
also speaking of getting there traveling
is like
universally our favorite [ __ ] our least
favorite [ __ ] thing so we're not
gonna Vlog at all until we're through
airport security and on the plane
because I really don't want to I hate
going through the airport well not only
that but it's also it's not worth
vlogging if I feel like I'm gonna miss
the [ __ ] plane to Vlog so we'll see
you when we know that we will actually
make it to where we're trying to go oh
that family's taking a big selfie with
just a blue ocean background they're
gonna not even gonna remember where they
took that
wow this [ __ ] looks cool
no we're at like a little downtown
hangout spot right now or something I
don't [ __ ] know but we're about to go
we're about to go shopping a little
we're gonna Adventure we're in Hawaii
we're at like some fun we're at a fun
Street I like that music oh chicken
chicken has to be a reason Mark hours
dude I never got outdoor things having
hours what are they gonna rope it off or
something yeah wait hours here yeah
no swing
oh is this live oh he's singing right
now Hi friend should I take the mic
no it looks so nice
Amen to that that's that's what it is
that was beautiful just like this one
big tree it is a beautiful one big tree
doesn't it just look like he's gonna
punch me in the face he's a strong boy
you really gotta go watch out
I literally saw that
and I obviously just did the coolest
move ever no the ocean oh my God is that
boat sinking oh wow oh my God sideways
it does look like you're going sideways
boat it's like Rave Cameron to be like
that it looks like Rafe Cameron just
jumped out of that hoe no Outer Banks
references that shows bad I got Nick
look at that oh my God there's millions
of them Chris there's hundreds of them
I'm not as scared of big birds like this
this is why look how cool that birds
are the tiny ones
am I yes
I thought you were I don't know
oh my God you guys have churross
that's okay you have so many other
options food flavor where do you see
watermelon on that one oh I'm looking at
the wrong thing
for the shaved ice
oh
Tiger's blood what is that
strawberry coconut
and we'll be right back Matt we'll be
right back with our shaved ice and give
them ratings
shave dice eight
point nine word Chris
okay Maddie
Chris
okay
10. Chris
okay okay
why why are you so difficult I know you
put a number into the world
well like pick one watermelon or lemon
not gonna rate them both well you got
both you're rating it overall so
together six rate them individually in
your head
[Music]
that's low guys we're in a CVS right now
and I bought uh I bought a film camera
and I brought it here with me to Hawaii
but I forgot film and I've been
Scavenging the entire Island for 35
millimeter film and they don't have any
anywhere we got a baseball bat and we
got a bright yellow kickball and I saw
the lady I was still talking I saw the
lady give these out on the plane and I
missed out and I was praying for the day
I find them again and I'm buying them
right now wait this is legit like the
airplane wait they have Orchard bars
here hey guys welcome back we're back to
our hotel room but we're all starving
and there was food trucks like outside
earlier so we're gonna go Venture and
see if they're still there because we're
some Starving Children right now
I feel like Suite Life in the deck
come on come on gorilla guess what
pulled pork sandwich pulled pork
sandwich pulled pork sandwich sandwich
we're waiting on mine I'm order number
79. oh that was a bar rate that pulled
pork sandwich
10 out of 10. oh honestly I said this is
so [ __ ] good like 465 times yeah
straight up 10 out of 10. this show is
amazing
my phone just dead ass almost fell out
of my pocket that would have been a
funny Vlog moment
okay vlog
I'm writing a song right now called
beachy beachy no it's called beachy I'm
so sweet yes that's my song we're at the
beach for the sunset Matt what do you
want to do the sun is set so it's like
Pitch Black it's not Pitch Black I can
still see you
tell them what we're doing after this
we're about to go eat we just got
noticed by some girls and it goes Aloha
as we walked away they were really nice
I had to keep the Hawaiian spunk update
we're in the hotel lobby right now we're
gonna go to a farmer's market which is
down the street that me and Maddie went
to yesterday so it's already certified
good and I got some really good food
there yesterday me and Nate miss it me
and Nate were snorkeling yeah everybody
snorkeling so right now we're gonna walk
to this farmer's market it's Maddie's
birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you
um
Hawaiian water it can't be just Hawaii
water that's what I'm saying
speaking time ever in my life so excited
or now I can't even explain it why is it
doing that bro don't prop the camera
down this isn't a [ __ ] eat with me
yeah it is no it's not Nick okay okay
it succeeded my expectations that's nice
man who's saying is fixated
succeeded yeah it did that too okay it
was so good it succeeded and exceeded my
expectation how was that how was that
cinnamon roll you just got it was
gasoline bro I hate the whole thing
let's go look Nate stop bouncing the
ball
look
Bounce It Up look it's like almost gone
I'll have this piece
um hello Vlog my hair's a mess but I'm
playing baseball we found a field we
found a big long field so we're playing
baseball in an empty field
oh there it is
oh my god that actually scared the [ __ ]
Street rack
oh my God I thought I was gonna die
all right I'll record a couple balls
they call me David Ortiz David okay
he didn't even pitch he's a designated
hitter no
no what a character honestly dude I'm
good
honestly like I can play for that
oh
that's a good one
[Music]
Nick said that he wants to get some of
his hits on camera so I have to beat
four out of ten sorry I've got it
wow God damn that's fun so far
they out there bro he caught it
foreign
got a nice angle of your ass Matt
oh
oh right to Matt
six out of nine
oh Nick is going dummy out there
oh
foul tip
it's up it's up where is it
and he caught it
oh my God that's what I thought I was
looking boy
backwards hat horse necklace black polo
jeans and white shoes Nate go
I got Hawaiian [ __ ] off
black shirt and jeans yeah why is there
a desk in the corner where
that's so scary
pose for a photo
okay ready
[Laughter]
Nick
hey Nick Nick hey Nick you're in Maui
Hawaii how does it feel
how's your Hawaii experience so far next
turn yellow next turn YOLO Nick we want
to hear the news we want to hear what's
wonderful I'm an open book what's going
we're on a Hawaii all day tour this is
the first hour of 10 but we didn't Vlog
like the beginning because it was just
boring getting on a bus and stuff like
that yeah it was 620 but this is the
first stop and there's Turtles at the at
the bottom are we going down there we
can you can't go all the way they look
like grass but those are turtles
did you guys know I planted all the
grass on this island shut the [ __ ] up
all right this is so wonderful
hey
I just got spotted by a group of teen
girls that know who we are coming out of
the water Chris we're making friends
okay
Matt Chris come on let's just make life
easier
should we just walk that way yeah
where's she at I don't know they were
over there running around frolicking all
right guys fire goes up to date just
look at there's a turtle on top of
another turtle over there and then or on
top of a rock and Nathan goes that's
another turtle they're making babies
Laura
bamboo forest that's not true this is
the rainbow trees oh should I fall yeah
in fact she said in the cars they can
guess how many gallons of water it can
consume in one day if it rains a tree
oh my God and look they're bark when it
falls off it's fun and colorful it looks
like when they do fake trees and like
Escape rooms
it does look fake you know what I mean
yeah these are all fake and just like
not real and we're on a set
hello Indian you probably won't be able
to hear this but stop number three was a
bathroom break but that has an entire
[ __ ] clip for you this [ __ ] beautiful
dog this [ __ ] is nuts
why does it close
oh my God hey it's Mr Moonstar Mr
Moonstone Moon Sandstorm here with
Channel 7 News Maui today we're looking
at sleeping grass
by its name if you flick it they close
shut
how wonderful I'll thank you Dan
dude stop pretending to be the weather
reporters welcome back to channel 7.
Jesus hairline oh my God look at the
hairline this is sand Moon storms
this is reporting live this is a black
sand beach as you can look down
black sand and rocks that is why it's
called
and Matt and Chris have kept throwing
rocks and consistently I'll update you
sorry
are they bat caves bruh it's not a there
says no bath we're just in like the
biggest cave in Hawaii I guess we're in
lava tubes oh lava tubes look at how
cool it looks like up there that's
insane
they can find your power in your desk oh
my God you're completely correct Maddie
if I'm ever gonna become a Power Ranger
it's right now and today can you see me
can barely see anything
Mr Moon's handstorm here shut the [ __ ]
up we are in the lava cave for once
where lavas were and now where lavas
were
just [ __ ] us all up what dude this is
insane Matt take the Vlog camera I
really wish I could get superpowers
right now it'd be like my life oh it
looks like a dinosaur
and the history of the darkness if I
were to ever get super powers you know
where it would be Matt where in this
[ __ ] all right guys we just got back
from a legit 12 hour long tour which was
really fun but I'm exhausted and
starving so we're going to get a pulled
pork sandwich this is going to be my
third one this whole trip which I'm
really excited for because it's [ __ ]
amazing I don't think you guys
understand the beauty I feel while
eating these pulled pork sandwich but
I'm going to show you this masterpiece
momentarily there's no way you're
recording this Nick I talked to the Vlog
about it so um gonna show them the
pulled pork I'm not gonna be like hey
I'm gonna get the best pulled pork
sandwich from the face of the [ __ ]
planet and then not show them I wouldn't
add up
anyways
without further Ado here we are
crazy it is
I'd say
for lack of a better term life-changing
Matt how are some ways you would explain
you'd Describe You're a pulled pork
sandwich good that's all I got there you
go that's all I got that's [ __ ]
boring I'm not gonna be dramatic about
it I'm not gonna I'm not being dramatic
I'm being realistic I'm not gonna say
it's life-changing I'm not gonna do any
of the theatrics that you're gonna do
it's pretty good that's right
you guys are
huh
it's just funny it's funny watching your
reaction like I bet your pause after I
said that is gonna make people laugh
I'm from here for
Vlog they gave me an extra cake because
it was broken
hey so it's our last game while we were
walking around that's pretty much it
I just wanted to say like because we
haven't vlogged once today so it's like
the sun's already setting and it's our
last day and then we're gonna randomly
soaking today in like a big spot
oh music incoming what
oh
hey people
okay I'll give him like
my hair
oh
do you guys just want to say that we're
leaving
yeah we're leaving okay
back to L.A
back to LA BRB real fun in Hawaii
super warm super nice super cool uh-huh
you know it felt good felt good to be
with all my friends my pals soaking that
let's do an outro in our living room
okay
[Music]