really dude scared the [ __ ] out of me
you know you always get mad like I
scared you but you never like physically
look afraid like this is you getting
afraid record me you go make a noise
oh scary
[Laughter]
boo it's not real let's react let's go
say and react but no this is literally
you Chris goes you say boo boo well that
scares the [ __ ] me bro every time I'm
like you don't look afraid I just boom
boom boom boom hit the rolly store with
the rolly can you sit up can you get off
my [ __ ] back let's do this get this
yeah get this
dumbass okay oh well now he's missing a
[ __ ] limb cuz Chris's fat ass is
still on it that was completely not my
fault on it get up completely not my
fault that Matt decided to try to pull
him away while I was sitting on that was
completely not my fault liess [ __ ]
how how is it that backto back Friday
videos were destroying stuffed animals
you know that was Matt's fault again I
literally hate you get off come on Matt
stand me up bro come on is there a hot
FR under the couch right there Nick Nick
come on hello everyone and welcome back
to another stolo triplets Friday video
by the way I'm fully convinced with 100%
certainty that this like isn't a
voiceover or it's a voiceover but Matt
said that it's like a voice over it's
not real he was reading comments and
he's like oh I I can't believe I thought
this was real at some point I'm telling
you right now off of my opinion watch
baby
lasagna oh you found your
moo good job
we yeah that's obviously not it's really
[ __ ] funny yeah it's it's funny why
is there a song in there good morning
oh you found your
moo good job where' that come
from oh wow that's the
original what
Nick
what what oh you found your mve why is
he so that was behind the scenes content
I never wanted to see you just wanted to
see that's like getting all the way to
Oz and realizing the wizard are you
ready dude the cap being I can't stop
laughing at this gay ass cow is crazy a
couple twitch streams ago I pulled out a
period simulator and Nick and Chris said
that they refused to do it on live and
obious I do genuinely still refuse to do
this so we're going to see how this goes
cuz it's like yeah we're pulling it out
but we're not necessarily guaranteed
that we're doing it I don't know if I'm
doing
that that's a crazy crazy crazy out of
context yeah we're pulling it out but I
can't guarantee that we're doing that
that was a crazy caution what does that
say nothing read it nothing important
caution yeah definitely read that so not
nothing important you're also definitely
going first by the way Matt oh there's
levels to it we'll be fine he bought
like a black fitted hat and he literally
asked me my permission cuz of how iconic
I made a black fitted hat
no oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God oh my God oh my God God I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry that was worse than the M
no I know it was doomed like we need to
get rid of this couch cuz it's just all
bad vibes over here and it's ugly I hate
this ugly couch hold on it's it's
attached to Matt
stomach okay 50 gigahertz that's not a
gigz it wasn't even a funny joke that's
really good do you feel it no I don't
feel a thing
are you just so strong maybe you've been
empath empathetically feeling women's
period cramps for shut your mouth
oh I felt it oh
wow felt it so what's happening okay it
just like stings this it supposed to
sting sting ow can you sit down yeah I
can sit down wait so hold on can I be in
control of that [ __ ] no absolutely not o
yeah level three hurts wait do does it
say does it say on the book what level
three is supposed to feel like it like
stings give me this why does it sting oh
there's different Sensations Matt do you
want burst normal modulation I want a
burst I want a burst I want normal two
stupid kids right here just
ow [ __ ] it's not like it's I know it's
not period cramps cuz it's not camic it
just feels like I'm electrocuting
myself it's just shock yes like I just
slowly feel like I'm electrocuting
myself all at
three
ow are you
good it just hurts can you can I do this
to you no let me do it three let me do
no I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine yeah this
is fine walk in the
park and then he's like okay go yeah
this is fine ow the right one is lower
than the left one [ __ ] do you them
placed on you in the correct place I
think yeah look at you have a [ __ ]
where's the uus dick Matt did you pee
your pants no what is that that was
there from laundry I swear to God okay
I'm just letting everyone know that Matt
has a laundry stand on his wiener and
it's not come on stop I want them to see
like oh it's piss come on it's not piss
ow [ __ ] hurts dude the our neighbors
are okay I'm done I'm done I'm done what
what level quickly fix your hair no give
me this before no give me this oh I hate
this Matt
shot it feels cold and empty you can
trust me no give I can't yes you I
already feel it I already feel it off I
know but I feel like it's coming okay
look ready I'm I'm just going to one to
turn it off I Chris Chris on my soul on
my life I'm not on my soul and on my
life I'm not going to make you
uncomfortable I promise you ready it
feels like minty on my chest a little
okay don't turn it fast cuz it hits you
like all at once I swear to God you feel
it yeah does it feel nice no do we have
any other takeaways yeah yeah I feel
like my belly button's like P pulling it
like it's like popping out kind of your
belly button is popping out yeah where
you at what level three get to
four now you really feel yeah it's a
little tle yeah go to four no I feel
like you know you get a cramp when you
run that's how it feels well is he
realizing what we're doing here I think
so how do
women what did you get to four and it
hurt right that's what I'm saying it
like felt like an
eels in my stomach an eel in your
stomach wao now SL did I swear to God no
I'm not going to do it any no it's like
feels so bad don't touch your
dick it feels so bad bad ow owie don't
hit me five you didn't even get to four
yes I did I swear to God I did I went
back I went back I went back I swear to
God are you just going to like Edge it
the whole time no I don't want to do
this anymore okay then
stop what are you at four let me see get
off I don't believe you get to five get
to five no you're not at four you're not
at four stop clicking your heels too you
psycho ow give it to me ow what are you
at four no you're not get to five baby
ow ow ow ow ow ow I just put it up to
six by accident oh [ __ ] did it hurt no
it felt great survive through the pain I
get this off of me you know women don't
have a choice of what level no I'm not
going to touch anything I love how
ital the keys to my life I love how it
has like a metal belt clip like
someone's going to like carry this
around like to the and just constantly I
don't know if I bought the right thing I
don't know what this does get this off
of me
literally could be like a [ __ ]
stomach resetter or
something stomach resetter yeah okay do
I have to do this ow where'd you put it
right
there your finger alone was too
much I'm going to [ __ ] it's like seeing
it coming it feels bad my God it already
feels like cold and I hate it that's
what I'm saying it feels like jelly on
your
belly dude
okay I'll I'll oh my God oh my God okay
let me have it I'm afraid that I'm like
too unhealthy like I feel like I'm going
to I already feel like I'm like in a
panic I'm what do it feel like like can
I like will it like will it hurt bad no
no no it just feels like weird like it
feels like your stomach's moving on its
own
no that's the worst way you could ever
describe it are you dead serious that's
what a cramp
is I already feel like sharp pain they
this is actually like your Dr
this is so dramatic I do let me do it
Matt there is no way on Earth I'm like
feel my face yeah you're hot you need
water you look like you need water
e don't make me laugh I feel like it's
going to make me
explode what are you at it's like
attacking me what are you at two get to
three oh it's like such a it feels like
I'm being stabbed in the heart are you
that's not where your heart isud where
are you at three [ __ ]
ow yes it hurts right now get to five no
cuz this is uncomforting yes of course
it is Nick we know
this relax relax
need get to five you're not even at four
liar that now you're at
four where are you at oh my god it feels
like there's like like lightning in my
heart like Zeus is in me
zo in
you okay now that I've had a comforting
feeling with it I'm going to see what I
can actually do here and then we're done
sit up straight I felt like I was
feeling things I've never felt before
one of the Tor surprises you should just
do this at level 10 for likees I
couldn't even my brain couldn't even
process that it literally oh I feel the
lightning I can feel the Lightning
Lightning
McQueen it literally feels like you're
like in control of like your imp ending
ow [ __ ] this hurts what are you on I'm
at three yeah tingles
ooh
ooh ow what is it that ow it's literally
like making my tummy Rumble like you
know the rumbling feeling in your
stomach that's what it's doing in my
chest right now feel it no feel it feel
it feel your belly I always feel M belly
do you feel the Jiggles oh my God I do
I'm getting abs right now it's worse
when you sit straight up like I feel I'm
a whole new man right now I can go like
100 new levels 100 new levels ow it's
like moving the [ __ ] into my
ass that's what I'm saying my biggest
wor was [ __ ] myself oh [ __ ] moving
the [ __ ] to my ass o look at it look at
it look look look
look oh sick animal five no way it goes
to eight what do you think would happen
if you put it on like one of your butt
cheeks like both butt cheeks like a
sticker like on your balls Nick really
like I don't want to think of my
pulsating balls oh you want ice cream
yeah I know when the hotline bling cuz I
know when the hotline bling bling bling
bling bling that can only me one thing I
hate Drake I don't know why I'm singing
Drake okay so basically me man and Chris
are in an in out drivethru cuz we didn't
eat dinner tonight and we wanted to eat
dinner tonight at a restaurant but we
just did so much other fun stuff that we
never went out to eat so now we're going
to get in and out and then and then we
are really missing do you I don't know
if you guys know friendlies but Matt
what is tell them what friendlies is and
I think we've talked about it a million
times friendlies is the best ice cream
and food place
ever that's a really bold and aggressive
statement they have waffle fries that is
true they have chicken tenders uh-huh
they have the big they put me on the
honey mustard they put Chris on the
honey mustard it's just a phenomenal
eating dining experience but it's like
little kid-like and they have like fun
sodas but they're also it's like an ice
and food comes in fun baskets and and
and the ice cream comes in nice silver
tins so we're going to eat our In-N-Out
and then we're going to go to the
grocery store and get stuff to make like
little ice cream yeah cuz they don't
have friendlies anymore we're recreating
the friendlies they have no more
friendlies we want the friendlies exp is
there are friendlies anywhere in the
world right now I have no idea I'll fly
there I would fly there that was going
to be one of my tour surprises I was
going to fly to a friendlies and eat and
eat dinner I would strangled you I would
have been so filled with
jealousy beat you black and
blue do it just for
that do you do you have a problem guys
I'm not going to lie to no listen
speaking of Tor because simulator is
pushing [ __ ] out of my ass dude it's
making me feel sick making me feel a
little sick I feel like I literally got
torched in the stomach like I torched
Nick what do you prefer Ino or Five Guys
oh wo wo I always prefer Five
Guys speaking of tour surprises cuz
brought up tour surprises we're going to
go on tour late March and all of April
pretty much yep and we can't tell you
guys where we can't get like the
specific dates yet but by the time next
Friday video comes out the dates will be
announced late March all of April see
you I'm so excited to see you guys on
the road there's so many secrets that
I'm actively keeping from you guys the
it's hard for us to play guys I have to
tell you one of my tour surprises I
can't wait you have to I'm pregnant okay
dude you're really weird the burger I
don't know what to do get back in the
car get back
CH but put a [ __ ] in
rotation do your burger dance do your
burger dance CH CHR he do your burger
dance do your burger dance sing my song
do your burger dance do your burger
dance yeah oh wow oh wow oh wow oh
wow we're about to get the magic mint
ice cream magic mint I made that up I
could tell the monster mint and we're
going to monster make it and we're going
to monster meet Monster meet your
maker oh
no I'm joking I'm joking I'm joking by
way we're in I'm getting a Cream Egg ew
there's there together stuck together
they look like testicles oh don't point
the camera in my face when you got
that do stupid little
kidsor I wasn't dud I have hiccups
behind the camera I sound
ridiculous I think it's the mix of how
fast I ate that cheese burger and the
period things on my stomach it's like
giving me the hiccups like the mix of
both the hiccups right now I swear swear
to God it is I feel like I'm G throw up
oh my God duct tape I love duct tape me
too no it is one of those things that
you're just like of
course now what how have you
been me that I ser
ever do that stupid [ __ ] I
agree we're going to make the the B
chocolate chip ice cream thing the
monster but I'm going to make Nick put
it on the screen and then show you guys
what we get and what ours looks like at
the
end give me the freaking thing okay are
you guys both going to want a monster of
your own no I don't like this stupid
idea why are we here why are we doing
this cuz you want it what am I like dud
you must follow orders of triplet kind
like you're
good oh my
Gody do they have Hershey's with
almonds Grandpa yeah they do you want
this one no that's huge yeah you act
like this isn't a two nighter for you
what dude I have the hiccups get it out
of me
yes sometimes Chris is this what you
want a collection of of
oh my God you're going to like
throw
sweet I'll
get there's someone behind you there's
other Mama girl my Nick where where the
cherries at um on the ice cream aisle I
think oh my God
you're a [ __ ]
freak he's a [ __ ]
weirdo ice cream ice creck call them
pancakes I'm going to do this off of
memory and I don't want to see a photo
of the monster so no one show me the
monster okay do you want me to cut your
reesei cup in half or no wait why are
you cutting yours in half okay well if
you were to do yours off of memory I'll
tell you right now you would fa you're
going to fail I'm going to make like an
Avant guard deconstructor version of him
what the [ __ ] are you saying weird what
that just meant so can I have the the
red M&M's please two of them here can I
get two blue ones no you have to do red
I want it to have red eye and blue eyes
nope red I think it had blue eyes no it
had blue eyes and I'm proving everyone
wrong give me the [ __ ] blue ones give
me two blue M&M's right now I'm not
playing where are all the M&M don't
[ __ ] touch my penis give me blue M&M
give me them Chris my [ __ ] is getting
[ __ ] up it was red I want blue ones I
disagree give me the [ __ ] blue M&M is
that your cadberry egg ow ow ow are you
pinching me seriously no I didn't pinch
you I was going to give it now my
Monster's ears falling is this your
cadburry egg Matt is this his yeah I'm
at 2 seconds from crushing this do it
give me the [ __ ] M&M's dare you to do
it Chris give I don't care about those
I give me two blue M&M's now it it
shouldn't be this big of a deal give the
two blue M&M's my [ __ ] monsters ears
are already falling off this about to be
crazy but I don't care Chris
please oh my God Matt I'm dead serious
oh my God you are a psycho crush it
Chris give me the crush it destroy the
cadburry egg destroy
it crush
it now here you going have it give me
the two B Ms no
Nick take a picture please
ready
a amazing Matt definitely it definitely
had blue eyes M&M thanks
freak you look stupid fudge can you um
heat that
Up's going to take a coal plune because
he said he he wanted too I just like
it's good for your heart and your
circulation and your your body and your
bones all right
you did watch one too many Alpha mail no
it's a joke but I genuinely want to just
do it I think it's
funny I hate doing this like with
clothes on too because
like it like you stay cold you know what
I mean so take your care off I'm not
doing it let those nipples Out Boy
freezing my hand off it that's ice
can you stop please stop you're
free I do have nice feet though to be
honest all the way in this is an awful
idea this is an awful idea can I sweeten
the pot what if you get if you can fit
your head fully under I'll give you 500
bucks 500 I literally like I would take
your offer but I can't do that like the
tub's not big enough like cuz when I sit
in here just in general you have to like
lean I want you to lean all the way back
your feet go up to like here and just
get fully Smur your head 500 bucks no
that's scary I'm not doing that scary
baby there's no way I sit down I wish
this was a pool because it just like I
just jump in the thing is is like no
matter how uncomfortable this is I Will
Survive it you know what I mean and
that's a
good die right here unless you turn into
a big ice cube but actually the ice
already melted in there so obviously the
freezing point is below wow the [ __ ] are
you
saying dude dip your nuts stop talking
like a teabag you just got to keep
getting them in there not you don't need
to squat up and
[Applause]
down come on it's a mental battle Nick
yeah Nick yeah Nick you're winning
you're good you're goodal battle my God
you're battle and I've never been more
proud of you now legs in and then lock
in all the way Y in there this is awful
just no worse feeling than this think of
a fire pit think of a of walking on hot
coals my hands are
shaking don't don't touch anything I
want gra Ice Cube turn the shower on
okay that was enough that was enough
what was this dude's name again La
swagler Benson definitely definitely
wasn't horn swagler Chris that's a good
one for maybe the next St animal we buy
right we'll keep that one on the list
next time you guys has by stuffed animal
suggest the name horn swagler don't
forget it um thank you guys so much for
watching this week's Friday video we
hope you enjoyed it um keep your eye out
for tour dates announcing soon we're not
going to say a specific day but it's
going to be before the next time we post
a YouTube video we are going on tour for
pretty much all of April but super late
March we're sorry that we can't give you
guys the dates just yet cuz I know a lot
of you guys are trying to plan where
you're going to go and how you're going
to figure it all out but stern. triplets
on Instagram is going to be the first
place you're going able to find out and
it is going to happen this week yes and
we're going to hit the road for the
third time which is terrifying and so
exciting and me Matt and Chris have put
so much time and effort into this show
we literally have been focusing more on
planning and getting ready for this tour
than our actual YouTube content recently
like we have hours of unedited footage
and unreleased footage that you guys
don't even know about or you guys don't
even know about that's what he just said
no he said you guys and I said you guys
I'm really excited it's all happening
it's happening quick and we'll see you
you guys next Friday look at horn
swaggers [ __ ]
moha he's so lit
[Music]