there are three core principles that are
really important elements of what Jack
Todd he was regarded as the West Coast
War buffit so the first thing is around
the power law in any asset class there
are only a small number of companies
that drive all of the returns the second
one is around compounding the
compounding of value of these special
assets happened in years 10 15 and 20
not in years 1 2 and 3 and then the last
idea is around this notion of a hedgeh
talk my name is Tay I'm a partner at
Altus Ventures so Altus is a venture
capital firm that was started here in
Silicon Valley in 1996 as a firm we are
Global generalist Tech investor so it's
a very wide and flexible mandate we
really focus more on the orientation and
alignment with the founders who we work
with I actually think we are more like
life cycle investors you can think of us
as early stage investors typically
leading series A's and after that
initial investment we take a very
long-term approach to company building
and investing literally thinking in
decades rather than years we love
partnering with Founders who also have a
similar mindset of building these
durable businesses over a long period of
time and we have a lot of flexibility
and capacity to further support those
businesses through additional
Investments as time goes on there are
many cases in our history where we would
start very small and early with the
particular company and then end up
investing hundreds of millions of
dollars in addition to the initial check
along the entire journey of the
companies I do spend a lot of time
meeting and investing in software
companies software happens to be a
business model that is very Capital
efficient it actually is also a very
durable business because the world
continues to get digitized and software
is playing a very large part in helping
with that digitization it actually meets
our general criteria of long-term
company building Capital efficiency
pragmatic company building and software
companies exhibit a lot of those
characteristics that maybe makes it a
really good fit with what we are doing
uh at the broader
level so in 1996 when the firm was
started we had One Singular LP and the
idea was to invest in SE stage very
early stage startups and then feed them
to the very well-known Silicon Valley
BCS to come in and mark them up and lead
the series a so ho and Han were
classmates from Stanford GSB they
started Altos back in 1996 I think in
the early days when we thought we were
good we were fairly smart enough to lots
of interesting business ideas and we
realized that as long as we got the
founders of these companies to make a
bit of progress on management hiring and
potentially offer themselves up to a to
be very open to getting a CEO into their
companies as long as we got them
prepared and we put that package
together we took it to a the larger
Venture funds they would mark up the
price and invest in a high valuation
they put the new CEO in then the bankers
start showing up and the companies were
ready to go public and it was literally
like that during the bubble days of
internet and so we obviously thought
that was the formula for being a very
good venture capitalist that worked
until it didn't in 99 2000 many of these
companies go public crazy high
valuations everyone looks really smart
and then literally all of our companies
went to zero and I think that gave the
team and the founders Insight that wow
like the way we were doing it was just
wrong there is no real value creation
who cares about markups when the
eventual number is zero so I think they
went back to the drawing board and we're
trying to get back to the fundamentals
like why do we invest and who should we
invest behind and how do you ultimately
create value and build these durable
businesses and I think that's when the
Warren Buffett Charlie Munger thesis
comes into play with the help of
Professor Jack
McDonald I actually met ho and Han back
in 2015 when I was at Capital G Google's
growth Equity Fund one of the partners
who I worked closely with Jean France he
and ho and Han were all classmates from
Stanford GSB so through that
relationship we looked at a few of Al's
companies including toss and roadblocks
ultimately couldn't get there on either
of them uh which was a big mistake and
then I just always felt like they were
really good people and so we always
stayed in touch and then when I went to
Stanford for my own business school
experience I took a class called the
Investments class I was taught for 50
years by this famous Professor Jack
McDonald he was regarded as the West
Coast Warren Buffett I was sitting in
the classroom and ho and Anthony just
walked in and I was like wow what are
they doing here and it turned out that
Jack was a very important figure and
adviser to alter when alus got started
there are three core principles that are
really important elements of what
taught so the first thing is around the
power law so in any asset class there
are only a small number of companies or
assets that drive all of the returns if
you look at the public markets you would
look at companies like apple Google meta
and so forth that have driven almost all
the returns of the S&P 500 over the last
several years this is even more
Amplified and more true in the world of
venture capital where only a small
number of companies in every Vintage
Drive all of the returns the second one
is around compounding there's this
really simple and classic example of
should you take $1 million of cash up
front or should you take a penny that
doubles every single day until the end
of the month and of course the answer is
you should take the penny because it
turns out that even in February when you
have 28 days that Penny ends up becoming
more than a million dollar at the end of
the month if you're lucky enough and you
are in a leap year and you have 29 days
in that February that becomes 2.5
million plus and then if you're super
lucky and you're in a month like January
with 31 days it's over $10 million at
the end of the month and so we believe
that a lot of the value that gets
created for a startup and a company
happens in those latter years when the
base gets much bigger and the value
keeps acur in a durable way so that's
why we try to be extremely patient I
think uh Roblox is probably the most
well-known example of a company where we
first partner with Dave and the team 16
years ago when we LED around with a 1.5
million doll investment and up to the
pre-ipo Round We invested another
hundreds of millions of dollars into the
company and so we were of course a
larger shareholder when the company went
public and in some sense we view this
still as an early stage company there is
so much that the companies building and
a lot of potential to further grow the
business from here on in some sense We
Believe in this notion of the infinite
game and that's the game that we want to
play which has no time bound because the
compounding of value of these special
assets happen in years 10 15 and 20 not
in years 1 2 and 3 selfishly we want to
generate wonderful returns and we should
be super
[Applause]
patient and then the last idea is around
this notion of a hedgehog there's this
Jim Collins analogy from the book good
to great about Hedgehog Founders versus
Fox Founders we have a blog post on our
website as well and Hedgehog Founders
are people who are maniacally focused on
trying to solve one problem and trying
to do that really really really well
foxes are extremely smart very cunning
but they often have a lot of things
going on they have a lot of projects
they're quite distracted and for us we
gravitate towards the Hedgehog Founders
people who feel like this is their
life's work and something that they want
to endure through the ups and downs and
we've experienced
that those types of Founders are the
ones who can endure the difficulties of
a startup Journey no startup journey is
linear and up to the right all the time
there are a lot of challenges that come
and being that Hedgehog founder we feel
like is an important ingredient to
building something great over a long
period of time I think even within our
team we have slightly different views on
what a hedgehog founder means and how do
you identify someone as a hedgehog
versus a fox in some sense it's a
spectrum so it's very difficult to say
well you're a fox and you're a hedgehog
it's a spectrum of how Hedgehog e are
you versus how foxy are you I find some
of the best Founders and often times
they are these hedgehogs to have very
strong opinions but loosely held so the
strong opinions come from either an
inherent connection to the industry or
the problem that they're trying to solve
and that was the Genesis of why they
started the company to solve their own
problems so there's one bucket of
Founders who come in that category but
then there are are other Founders who
also become extremely entrenched into an
industry or a problem through a lot of
studying and a lot of conversations and
more of a top- down approach to trying
to figure out how do you solve this
problem that I want to solve and in
either case the best Founders seem to
have at least a strong point of view on
what the world should look like and I
think that's very important because you
have to be a Visionary to change the
world or bring to the market a service
that did not exist before at the same
time what's really interesting about a
lot of the Founders is that these
opinions are loosely held so they're
strong but they're willing to change
their views if they see something new or
if they learn something new and that
part is also really important in our
view because you have to have the mental
plasticity to figure out whether you're
right or wrong about something and have
the humbleness to admit when you're
wrong that you have to course correct
and so this is where the continuous
learning mindset comes into play and the
best Founders and the best Learners tend
to have that characteristic I've been
working with and partnering with a
number of vertical Market software
companies one company is called push
press which is a gym management software
company we first led the series a two
and a half years ago what they're trying
to do is to provide the best software to
Independent gym owners across the US and
across the world the founders were
former CrossFit gym owners they had a
paino of finding a software tool that
work for their own gym so the founder
who had a technical background just
built a software tool for his own gym
that ended up becoming push press now
they have about 100 people at the
company of which the majority were
former gym owners or former Fitness uh
professionals they live and breathe the
category the industry that they serve
and it shows in the way they approach
customer support and the way they talk
to their customers that's been a really
fun Journey so far a lot of Founders
would come and say we are looking for
the next 10-year type of partner we're
very serious about finding the right
partner it's not about valuation oh and
by the way we need a term sheet by
tomorrow that's very hard for us because
how do you get married after the first
date and we view the partnership as a
marriage and so we really appreciate
having the time to get to know Founders
and get to know each other and I think
that is actually really important to
building a very long-term and fruitful
relationship because let's say you enter
a relationship without having that
alignment well in the first board
meeting or that second date it's going
to be very apparent that this is not a
good fit and what's the point of that if
the goal was to build a generational
company for 10 plus
years I have one definition or one
analogy that I personally really like I
was at my son's preschool and there was
a teacher parent conference where the
head of the school was giving a speech
to the parents and she made this analogy
of you parents know your child the best
we teachers know children so if we
partner well together it can be an
extremely fruitful partnership and a
symbiotic relationship and I was
listening to that and I was like hm
that's kind of like my job as an
investor there is no way that we as
investors and Venture capitalists would
know a singular company more than a
founder or the team that's working hard
at it but we do see a lot of companies
and we end up working with a lot of
companies over the years and that
pattern recognition or the sheer amount
of data that you can aggregate of seeing
the good ones the okay ones the bad ones
the full gamut of company building
allows us to hopefully provide guidance
when it's needed for these businesses to
avoid mistakes or accelerate their path
to Greatness and so in some sense maybe
I was thinking to myself a venture
capitalist is like a preschool teacher
where you're trying to be a helpful
Steward but you should also be humble
enough to know that there is so much
more to that singular child or company
than what you probably see so you have
to respect that and work with the parent
or the founder to understand it as much
as you can and then with that context
and the partnership you can provide the
insights and the support to hopefully
accelerate that path what we are trying
to do is of course to not be average and
hopefully add value and maybe the way to
add value to a company's trajectory is
increasing their odds of success again
the success is still unclear whether you
can succeed or not as a company as a
founder or even as investors there's a
lot of inputs that go into that eventual
outcome which hopefully is great but
there's luck and there's a lot of other
circumstances that have to go your way
for that to happen so then what is it
that we can do well we can definitely
control the inputs to getting there and
hopefully the partnership with a venture
capitalist or an investor is a strong
partnership that allows the thinking to
keep expanding and for the VC to help
Steward and guide the company in a
direction that increases the odd of
success so I really like that framing of
the role as
well belus is a totalitarian state I
wanted to be free the guy worked in it
advised me if you get that job you will
be free free you can get out of barus
you won't be dependent on rules of the
country where your parents are where
your relatives are and and you looking
to get free so that works that totally
works