that's really been exciting about
building this company, especially over
the past year as code generation has
gotten so good. As agents get better and
better at generating code, the the way
that you're interacting with them
probably isn't going to look like how we
we write code today. it's v 0ero bolt
new replet agent like something like
that where you know where you're
interacting with these agents and
prompting them and and iterating on
their experiences and it's almost more
analogous to code review than it is to
how we would write code previously and
that's why we think like owning code
review as as the starting point is what
matters you know far more so than the
fist fight that's happening over like in
loop code generation right
Hi, I'm Mel Lutzky, co-founder and CEO
of Graphite. Graphite is the code review
platform for the age of AI. We take
best-in-class workflows and tooling from
companies like Google and Meta and
combine them with our agentic AI code
review companion to help engineers uh
create, review, and merge code changes
faster than ever. We work closely with
the team at Enthropic um to power our AI
code review agent um called Diamond. The
series B that we just announced was $52
million. Um, and Graphite has grown 20x
in the past
[Music]
year. Graphite started on a completely
different idea. We actually we actually
had sort of two one small pivot in the
beginning in the first three months and
then then the iOS tool. We'd hired in
the process then a few engineers uh a
few of Tomas's ex-coorkers from Meta and
this we'd had this really peculiar thing
that happened when when they onboarded.
So they'd start on their first day we'd
get them set up on GitHub. We'd show
them how we do code review at the
company and all of them had this kind of
allergic reaction to it immediately and
they all said you know this feels like
so much slower than the tooling that I'd
had at Meta. I I feel like a caveman
using this. Google and Meta have both
built amazing internal tools to help
their their teams of thousands or tens
of thousands of engineers um all working
on on one monor repo at once even across
across time zones and across you know
spanning these massive code bases. And
um if you go outside of those walls
though u it's very hard to to get that
same level of of productivity and uh
have that same that same tool chain. And
that was a lot of why, you know, why we
started Graphite was we saw kind of the
the gap between what we'd had at at the
large companies that that all us and the
founding team had worked on and what was
available to every company when they're
just getting started. And um that was
really what inspired us to to build
graphite. I think it's so important to
like deeply understand and care about
the user that you're building for.
You're going to spend if your company is
successful, you know, 10 plus years
talking to these people every single
day. And if you don't genuinely care
about making their lives better, about
solving their problems and about
building uh product experience they
really enjoy using and get a ton of
value from, it's going to be really hard
to just sustain your your level of
enthusiasm about that. And one of the
the things that's so fun about graphite
and one of the best parts about getting
to work on this is that it is something
that we all on the team use every day. A
lot of like great companies use every
day. our friends at at these companies
are are using and are constantly texting
me with feedback. It's just fun to be
able to to build something that that's
for um a user that we're so you know
that we're so deeply familiar with and
um that we genuinely care about and and
want to like make their lives better. So
in the beginning we started with tool
for creating stacked pull requests. The
idea of stack pull requests um is that
instead you you break and having that
all be one pull request um instead you
break that up into a series of small
dependent changes um that all sort of
chain together and build upon each
other. And the advantage of this is that
you know first of all nobody likes to
review like a thousand line pull
request. that's like, you know, there's
that meme that's like, you know,
thousand lines like looks good to me.
And I think that that really is is what
you see play play out in the data. Like
nobody wants to to like give a detailed
review to a change that big. Um that's
really why, you know, why stacking is is
so powerful is it just it gives you so
much time back um that you would have
spent kind of sitting on your hands or
trying to find something else to build.
And we've seen like really meaningful
improvements in in development speed at
many of our top customers. ASA was the
one where where we save 7 hours per
developer per week. At RAMP, we
increased their development speed by 3x.
One of our adviserss kind of famously
said like once you stack, you don't go
back. And I think that that's really
true in terms of the both like the user
excitement and then also just the the
retention numbers and and you know the
engagement that we see with graphite
pretty much every
day as every engineer has tools like you
know cursor and windsurf and copilot and
even some of these more agentic code
generation tools now uh they're able to
like write code faster than ever uh they
can they can do or they're creating more
code changes than than they ever have
before. That's only really the first
part of the story. I think even what
we're seeing with with vibe coding right
now is a lot of those products are kind
of MVP like there. You still need to
take that change and get it through code
review. You still need to test it. You
still need to deploy it and measure the
impact. and that whole kind of outer
loop process um where you're
collaborating with your teammates that's
like a huge part of of your life you
know almost as much in many cases as the
inner loop of of how I'm like writing
code testing locally and getting it
ready to uh to like push up to to a pull
request. So I think that as you know as
you have like this this idea of like
vibe coding and AI code generation it's
almost not enough to be just you know
engineer anymore like the best engineers
are also great product thinkers and
great business thinkers great designers
in some cases it's really it used to be
the case I think that the limiting
factor on creating anything was was you
know asking like how do I actually build
this and how do I implement it now you
have these great tools that can help you
answer that question and kind of get to
an early version like a working
prototype of of something like quite
quickly. So then the question shifts
from being like how do I build this to a
little bit further upstream of like what
should I build in the first place that's
actually going to be of value? you know
how do I actually interact with this and
what is the optimal experience here and
then how do I differentiate that and how
do I in a world where like anybody can
you know go on replet agent and prompt
you with a few prompts make you make
make like a working prototype of
something how is that different from
anybody else's like vibecoded version of
this and I think that that software
engineering looks a lot more like you
know reviewing or even designing or or
like you pming in the future versus like
writing code as we know it today.
the transformation of software
engineering uh with AI code generation
is has just been the sort of seismic
shift that's happened in you know as
we've been building the company and you
know we were fortunate in that we were
working on solving a problem that was
now made 10 times worse by AI code
generation code review has always been
and this outer loop of review and
testing and deployments has always been
a bottleneck at large companies it's
always been an area that that needs
better tools And that was true before
AI, but now with with all these great AI
code generation tools, that need is is
all the more acute. And I think that's
that's one of the things that's been I
think we were lucky that we were
building kind of the the right thing at
the right time. U because we built uh we
built tooling for accelerating the outer
loop and we got that into a lot of great
enterprise customers. We also built the
trust with those organizations to be
able to now deploy AI to help them
review code faster. Uh I think it's
really hard if you're just starting an
AI code review company to convince an
enterprise or convince a company like
Shopify to give you access to their
entire GitHub repo from day one. It's
taken us a long time to build up that
level of trust. And I I think there are
a few factors there. One is just like
building just adding value progressively
over time, shipping features constantly,
like showing the customers that we work
with early on that we are consistently
able to like deliver on our promises and
you know continue to just add more and
more great features to the graphite
platform. Um we spend a lot of time
making sure that that everything we do
is like you know best practices for
security. We're pentested very
regularly. Like we really want to invest
in in making sure that that that piece
is is central to what we're doing you
know. And then and then part of it is
just climbing the ladder. I think you
have to you have to start with like
smaller companies first like you're
always going to have kind of more you
know smaller companies that are willing
to adopt tools tools in the beginning
and then like building up trust over
time and I think now that snowball has
really like started to roll and um we
have you know some of some of the
largest technology companies out there
that are are trusting graphite every day
and u you know we're we're really
privileged to be able to serve