I don't have 2020 Vision so you have to
check 2020 Vision c
b guys it's Thanksgiving which um it's
turkey day it's Thanksgiving and I guess
we're thankful no Nick stop it the first
thing ni I ha you ungrateful the first
thing Nick said to me today when I saw
him I said hey Nick good morning you I
was joking you should probably wake up
it's 2:00 he goes I'm not thankful for
anything I thought it'd be funny that's
the first thing he said to me
yeah are you you are so weird for you
Chris no I'm not eating a carnival pop
big lollipop I got it for Chris to suck
on while he while we film so he doesn't
interrupt us as much Nick you're the
only thing that's sucking on
anything okay this is a lot give it to
Chris you it' be a good how many licks
do you think it would take to get to the
center not many Tootsie Pops are thicker
really yep what do you prefer girth or
length don't ask me that ever again can
we all stop Happy Thanksgiving today
we're going to be talking about things
we're thankful for the other day was on
my phone and I I was like oh my God I'm
a triplet things of three like you know
things like that H happen often in my
life I feel like only people that aren't
triplets think like like that is that a
Chinese finger trap yeah it is can I do
it yeah it's working it's not a Chinese
finger trap this used to have a marble
in it it's a fidget toy oh I know the
difference that's why it's not working
it's not a Chinese finger trap my bad
Matt who thinks Matt looks Matt looks
good okay Nick stop I saw a photo of us
three and I was like oh my God like such
an underrated Duo an under underrated
Trio I mean and then you think the three
of us are an underrated Trio yes but I
was like want to know what the most
underrated Trio is they're sick a Pepsi
quench Doritos in a Jersey Mike sub yep
underrated that's the big three right
there you're sick that's my big three
you're sick if Jersey Mike came up to
you and said no nick no nope you
wouldn't let him dominate you no what
you guys know as me Matt and Chris like
every single time we're filming a car
video we're like oh I wrote this down we
usually just like if I have a crazy
thought or Matt or Chris have a crazy
thought we'll usually go on our phone
and write the crazy thought down to
share when we're filming a YouTube video
and I went to share write down a crazy
thought the other day and I was opening
my notes and guess what I already had
written down what I'm gay the sky is
blue what
else what what was your point there I
have no idea I'm gay the sky is blue
what else it sounds like I wrote that
down I'm like what was I planning it
sounds like a start of a poem my God so
as you know we're in Boston right now
and we just came from LA and while I was
on the plane I was like playing mobile
games cuz I was bored OB baby in a
toddler yeah no that's just what I do
it's people that aren't babies in
toddlers play mobile gam you are the
funniest guy I've ever met in my life
and I hope you know that like if I had
an award show I would give you so many I
was talking to someone new the other day
and they were like who's the funniest
brother I was like honestly I think it's
me and they're like oh like you're just
saying that I'm like no ask Chris ask
Chris to ask Chris to
is the funniest person on like this well
here's the thing I would never say I
would never say myself I would never say
myself I would never say myself and he's
not funny at all I am funnier than you
are cuz you're just angry I must be
sleeping right now cuz I must be [ __ ]
dreaming I'm serious I'm ready to wake
up I'm ready to wake up you're not funny
you're funny when like you're mad okay
okay okay funny guy what's good you are
so funny thank
screenshot you just showed me no Matt
just showed me a note on his phone car
video with nothing underneath nothing
stop leaning forward I'm laughing at you
don't do it again yeah laugh back here
cuz you [ __ ] make you go out of focus
every time your big head look like Mars
Rover is getting closer to the camera
lens every time that red hat glares on
that light it literally looks like a
solar beam is shining into the camera
you are so funny
we just went from LA to Boston I was on
the plane I was playing a mobile game
and I was on level 666 and I was like
literally in my head I was like I have
to beat another level before we land cuz
it was
like are we dead serious I don't know
dude give me the
phone
hello I want to kill you all
right hey shut up I love you so much I
love you so much I do I love I love you
so much but when when you burp I do want
to just strangle you like I I and when
you do [ __ ] like
that is when you guys think in your head
do you hear someone talking like is it
your voice thinking it's just my
thoughts it's not a voice do you know
some people don't hear a voice at all
they just do things is that not weird
serial killers I'm sure no no Ser
there's people that don't like that no
people have to have like an inner
conscious no they don't some people
seriously are just like I'm getting up
and I'm walking over here and I'm what
fascinates me they don't have anything
in their like nothing in their head
that's saying like words that's insane
seriously like dead serious I don't know
where the [ __ ] I am or who's driving the
[ __ ] car speeding down the highway
sipping me and Nick were in the store
and these two girls [ __ ] risen up the
dude that we know about yeah you know
the guy that's the old guy yeah him up
they're like do you have family here and
he's like no and they're
like did you have a good Thanksgiving we
can make it a good Thanksgiving like it
was crazy they were getting down they're
and he's an old man they weren't like
nice looking young
ladies speaking up you want to know what
I hate no me and I were talking about
are we going to address the butter balls
turkey or no I don't know it has nothing
to do with us but that it's kind of
wicked it's an old video though I just
can't believe that old like 20 years old
20 years old yeah it's fake they they
brought it back up this year to try to
like shut them down or something like it
was a Peta stunt again or something I
don't know oh wow I don't know hopefully
you know what I hate what things that
are individually wrapped cuz I'm not
going to have just one of these and
you're telling me I got to like do the
whole thing to slow fat asses like you
down that thought process needs to be
halted you know you got to you think
about it more you're like damn I've
unwrapped 10 of these I should probably
slow down that's true I think the worst
type of person ever and this is my major
my most major Red Flag Ever I hate a
[ __ ] that just hands you a
Christmas gift rrap that [ __ ] please
yeah wrap that gift if you if you hand
me a Christmas gift and it's not like I
don't get to like Veil it it's like
what's going on the whole point put a
little tissue paper yeah like an I'm
thankful yeah you could wrap a clog and
give it a me you could wrap clog you
could wrap a rock and give it to me and
I'd [ __ ] Shout at the Treetops you
wouldn't yes I would Shout at the
Treetops I've never heard you do that in
your life yeah you haven't gotten me a
rock just said what I do to do it all
right I'm going to get you a rock give
me a rock I'll shout from the tree
record a video you open I need a minute
to get to Treetops but I'll do it the
moment I'm at the access of Treet tops I
will [ __ ] scream at the top of them
yeah okay are you dead ass questioning
me
mhm
[Laughter]
uhhuh [ __ ] didn't even say m he
goes look at me pick your head up my God
you're like a bobblehead what's your
favorite food to eat on Thanksgiving
anything dunked in gravy H some gravy
on what I myself in
gravy the Matt girls would lose their
mind all right [ __ ] we should
all get naked and cover ourselves in
gravy and then pose with a big turkey I
think people who don't like I don't like
gravy yeah and I think that people who
don't like gravy are just babies that
need to grow up I don't a baby that
needs to grow because also turkey turkey
without gravy on it is like gross a
little like it's like dry and like not
good I love dry turkey oh God Matt loves
feeling the dry turkey go down his
throat turkey makes me so sleepy oh I
almost took a nap today I was this close
I almost took a nap today did you look
like a dad you're taking naps like I
don't know what next what's next for you
yeah and you look like an idiot and
you're talking about how much you love
gravy see where that gets you an idiot
that likes gravy or a [ __ ] 21 that
lik naps I'd rather be an idiot that
likes gravy all right then you are so
I'm going to put that on a shirt what's
something that's normal but weird normal
but weird you are you serious dead I
knew you were going to say that well
something normal but weird feel you just
shoed like a [ __ ] gazelle what does
that have to do with anything we're
talking about that's also chewing like a
[ __ ] giraffe or something at least I
don't sit with an under bite literally
neither do I sip with an under bite sit
sit like sit normal with an underbite
your your resting face underbite under
bite it's fully over I'm not doing that
under bite Aug oh true I don't have an
underbite neck and even if I did you
underbite Vibes no can you stop like the
way you act and behave I wouldn't be
shocked if I was like oh my God Chris's
an under well yeah cuz when gets all
Angry he goes like that's what he does
underbite I used to have an underbite
when I was a kid underg Chris
stop immediately covering his heart say
I hate when he does that fighten my
trickl oh I ought to knock your tricks
out you ought to [ __ ] relax what are
you thankful for Chris I'm thankful for
what am I thankful for that's a great
question Matt yeah should we hold hands
no why why did we all agree that that
turkey is the Thanksgiving birth cuz it
was pass it's passed down from
generations and generations and that's
what like cuz of pilgrims that's like
what we killed first like we were like I
want that big but like we eat I feel
like like I want that big I don't know
they're probably eating chicken and they
were like that bird seems somewhat
larger that would feed more people let's
Feast upon him I feel and then they took
him down shut your [ __ ] mouth you
asked a question I asked a question and
I didn't it was rhetorical I didn't
expect you to know the history of why we
eat turkey and and I don't and I'm
taking an educated guess you ID
like dude what I'm saying you expect me
that my Factbook of turkey knowledge no
I expected you to sh he expected silence
and unfortunately he was gret with gret
GRE describe
it
okay I'm going to bleed my hand you're
going to [ __ ] hit my my hand my hand
my butt crack's not out I saw it you're
not going to smack he just threw like
this like that why oh yeah you want now
you look like under bite under bite
no get out of here I don't have my butt
crack up yeah you do I then what's that
what I'm trying to say is tur
Thanksgiving turkey I only it's okay I
only ever eat turkey on Thanksgiving
right tea to
Turkey you did it wrong
idiot why are you see honestly good
decision yeah put that back on once you
embarrass yourself once you just go on a
train of doing more can you [ __ ] shut
up on yourself again my God you [ __ ]
shut up I'm going to start doing it to
call Poli I'm saying is called who the
police what I have two lunatics who've
gone Rogue and they're beating up their
little brother yeah it's you and the
thought I need help I need help they
both smack me upon the right side
Gustavo that's what I'll call call the
boss all right go ahead the only day of
the year I eat turkey is on Thanksgiving
and like
wrong when did I eat turkey sandwiches
I've seen you have them you're wrong
you're dead wrong you've had turkey cut
wrong you don't only have turkey on the
on the day of feast that's it no you
don't yep seriously you don't these are
you don't only have turkey on the day of
Jesus Christ stop you like your digital
footprint is actually the the worst
thing I've ever seen in my life
stop are you stop serious cuz I'm not
going to let you do that I was enjoying
it now I have to throw it away I hope
you do GG said that she's thankful for
Matt's Tik toks I was thankful for so
many things this year
really I'm still going don't don't
interrupt me or I'll [ __ ] smack wow
I'm serious I said really like what like
share really you were thankful and
you're about to share what you were
thankful for really that's how you said
really I was saying I was saying really
cuz you said I'm thankful for a lot of
things this year and I was going to
continue but you interrupted me yeah but
the lot like surprised me I was like wow
he was thankful for a lot really were
you not miserable Matt I was thankful
for I was thankful for video games
Sports parls and and and my ankle being
hurt why would I be thankful for my
ankle being hurt because it made me
complain more and be more miserable and
I love being angry and mad I'm thankful
for my underbite and my hats that I for
my and my hats that I can like this and
show my seaing hairline all the time SE
hairline I'm thankful for my pants that
I don't even know how to wear and I'm
thankful for my belt mean I always wear
my I'm thankful for my boots my big
boots like okay dude I'm thankful for
laundry cuz I get to clean it and I'm
thankful for for more Sports I'm
thankful for uh what else do I do drive
I'm thankful that I drive uh what else
that's he is oh I'm thankful that I'm
thankful for Chris I'm
thankful I'm thankful for Chris cuz
he'll order my food for me you're
thankful for Jersey Mike
BLTs yep Al what else Chris I'm thankful
for I'm thankful for a lot of
things I'm thankful for I'm thankful for
my sweatshirt cuz Matt bought me this
sweatshirt I bought you this sweatshirt
Chris I did right Chris Chris's eyes are
like I'm thankful for my under bite I'm
thankful that I got this
it's funny do have under I have a
perfect I'm thankful that I get to
scream and yell at car videos all the
time and I'm thankful that I get to go
whatever
thanks and I hate it I hate
it I hate it cuz I end up making I end
up making fun of you in the clips that I
see of myself of the things that you do
all the time I'm thankful for sports I'm
thankful for soup I'm thankful
for the [ __ ] you eat you always eat soup
you've eaten just as much soup as I have
I'm thankful for stuffy I'm thankful
foru my stuffed animal pug I'm thankful
for Derek white I'm thankful for I'm
thankful for
soda I to drink 100 sodas a day I'm
thankful for restaurants going I get
french fries and soda you're thankful
for you're thankful you're thankful for
I'm thankful for my Baga boots and my
Crow Parts earrings I am seriously
though I'm thankful for the past four
years of my life from becoming an adult
and and just changing and being with you
guys and learning so much about myself
in my future I'm thankful
that yeah I am really I'm thankful I'm
not going to get mad I'm going to
continue what I'm thankful for that a
joke soad I'm thankful for my brother
Nick I'm thankful for my brother Matt
I'm thankful for my brother Justin I'm
thankful for my Jes Christ really every
[ __ ] night there's cops here yeah I
know La Poli I am thankful that me Matt
and Nick have been blessed and put in a
position where we can live our life
every single day with no schedule and
get to make our own plans and do what we
want and do what we love and make a
living off of it I'm thankful for all
the opportunities that I've gotten in
the past few years and where I've gotten
to travel because of my job where I've
people I've gotten to meet because of my
job and just things I've always wanted
to do and see I've got to do and I could
have be more blessed than thankful I
fully agree and I'm sorry for making a
joke when you were saying yours I am one
of the best joke takers ever amazing you
take jokes well yeah what else you take
well you don't take constructive
criticism well because you're such a
Negative neilly I agree with everything
that you're thankful for as well
basically
man I'm thankful for a
lot I'm thankful for a lot I'm thankful
for cheeseburgers I'm thankful for I'm
thankful for ice cream I'm thankful for
dessert I'm thankful for chocolate I'm
thankful for all the little cookies I
can have all the cookies I'm thankful
for fortnite I'm thankful for the item
shop I'm thankful for the golden scar
I'm thankful for sh forite more than I'm
thankful for my computer grenades
I'm thankful for my button up I'm
thankful for my fuzzy hat I'm thankful
for my fancy pants I'm thankful for my
loers I'm thankful for my horse necklace
I'm thankful for all the so many
beautiful fans I'm thankful for
everything I'm than that's your man you
know I'm thankful for lemon I'm thankful
for juice I'm thankful for Blended
lemonade iced tea juice I'm thankful for
any sweet juice that is in soda so I can
I can say I'm not having soda and have
juice sweet juice like orange apple
juice I'm thankful for Easy
Mac I love Easy Mac I am thankful for
Easy
Mac what's his name thankful for Carl
Jun I'm thankful for Walter White I'm
thankful for math because we can make a
whole TV
show J Carl junor
your oh my
God oh my God for car you I'll kill you
oh Carl
J
God my [ __ ]
God I'm thankful for Carl J you're not
that serious I
me I me wal funer is that he said Walter
right after the funniest thing is I said
I'm thankful for meth because they can
make a whole TV show about it I heard
that okay what I've noticed in the past
year is I'm I'm thankful for every
single super difficult scenario I've
experienced in the last four years and
every single thing that has challenged
me and upset me because I've never felt
more confident in my decisions in myself
because I feel like I've dealt with so
many different situations that have led
to me having the best ability with
confrontation and with
Triumph amen and I feel like I I want to
say what I'm thank I feel like I've had
I feel like the past four years have
been major in terms of self-discovery
for the three of us and who we each
individually are and I feel like I'm
just thankful to be at a point with you
guys where I truly truly feel like I can
say or do or explain anything to you you
guys without judgment and we never had
that and people think that we've had
that our whole life because we're so
close and they see us together every
week but I feel like we're finally at a
point where the three of us the three of
ours relationship is the best position
it's ever been Yeah in our
life I need water I don't know I'm just
I'm very thankful for having uh a
platform that we have that helps me
build the confidence and who I am
because I feel like there's a lot of
myself that like when we first started
doing this the opinions that we were
saying in these car videos were for us
to look back at what our opinions were
um 20 something years ago when we're
with our kids it wasn't for the internet
to understand and know our opinions and
and know our comedy and know who we are
as a person it just kind of happened and
it picked up in a crazy way so I think
the fact that us just doing and talking
about what we want to talk about for our
future being an outlet for people to
watch in their present day is just like
really crazy to me and like that it
blows my mind and I think the what I'm
most thankful for is just every single
project we take on whether it's podcast
whether it's tours we've done whether
it's car videos whether it's merch
whether it's your brand whether it's
your brand um just the overwhelming
amount of support and um Dedication that
people put towards us is just insane cuz
at the end of the day nobody celebrities
influencers whatever artist nobody's in
that higher up position we're all human
beings and the people that make people
feel like they're in these crazy higher
up positions are the fans so it's like
it really is just like a a moment of
reflection that us three and everybody
else you see on the internet are just
normal human beings and we're nothing
without you guys making it like a bigger
deal yeah um so yeah I don't know I'm
thankful for being a human just like
they are but being able to experience
the craziest things in life and support
from all different
directions especially with big group
plans on the way and a personal project
after the big group plan oh wow no
spoilers but boom in that thankfulness
gets five big booms boom boom boom boom
boom someone said they're thankful for
Matt sack on our Instagram Story by the
way so I just thought I my sack yeah
Matt's sack I'm thankful for bear I'm
thankful for my tractor all right for
the last part of this video we're going
to talk about things that we are
thankful for but we're going to get as
niche as we possibly can a good bowl of
peanuts at a Thanksgiving dinner but
you've never had peanuts at a
Thanksgiving dinner how about tonight
cashew cashews it's [ __ ] it's cousin
bro like not not it's [ __ ] it's
cousin man no boiling my hands are
freezing yeah you want to
fight what the [ __ ] are you doing giving
them a good like intro to an edit what
you want to tussle
hustle bot bot ball bot just B how do
you spell that I don't know Bachi I'm
thankful for growing up with Poland
Springs being my local water source
that's a good one that's a really good
one actually cuz [ __ ] you Arrowhead
drinkers people who drink Arrowhead
you're sick Poland Springs is the goat
water best water of all time Arrowhead
is disgusting I'm thankful
for
like trifold signs in front of local
shops I'm thankful for that girl in line
to get onto the Disney tram that we were
waiting for like 14 years ago with a
really big forehead yeah she was so nice
she changed my perspective on like
seeing a stranger you know I I agree she
was so sweet and she was like I just
felt so bad for her how old were you
like 8 years old yeah someone was making
fun of her yeah someone made fun of this
girl cuz she had a massive she had a big
forehead I'm not stuck with me I was
like it's I when I saw her I didn't I
saw beyond that big forehead you know
what mean like I saw I was like that
girl is so pretty and so sweet and I
felt so bad that she was like actively
being made fun of like I felt horrible
give us a second okay I'm going to need
more than a
second I felt so bad for her this was
like literally we were like six years
old eight yeah it changed my life I'm
thankful for Bowser
because
Bowser why thankful for Bowser because
he's a bad guy on smio C that's what
your answer why are you thankful for him
why are you thankful for Bowser Quest I
am thankful for Bowser because when I
was a young kid he he made me face fear
for the first time cuz I had to get
through once you defeated Bowser you
could do anything I had to face Bowser's
Castle if I was Princess thankful for
that you would have stayed with Bowser
we get i' settled with Bowser yeah yeah
you wear it I'd be happy about it
yeah I'm thankful for pepy good I'm
thankful for really big office spaces
like it just allows so many people to
get their work done that need to get
worked done I'm thankful for having a
sense of
reality my favorite thing ever is
recognizing that I'm a normal human
functioning like a normal person like
doing something simple that brings me
back to reality like burning my finger
or spending time with an old friend
stubbing my toe taking a shower the last
thing we're thankful for is you right
before this video ends we just want to
tell you guys that if you do want our
merch just went live so click the link
in the description if you want to shop
our new merch line it should be right
down there and it should be on the
screen as well if Nick's not lazy in the
editing process I also dropped for my
brand today yes and Chris dropped and
Nick has a sale so all of all of the
stern yolow triplet related websites
welcome to Black Friday have dropped on
Black Friday so if you want think
there's also
I think there's some old available old
merch available on the stern trip disced
for a discounted price so take a sneaky
peek over there and we will see you guys
next Friday oh my God
[Music]