does that look good to you guys unfazed
unbothered unfuckwitable [ __ ] why
bother does that look good I'm watching
this turn triplet right now a
second ah my ankle
itches dude there's not a [ __ ]
venomous snake biting it I have an
asthma attack right now and I don't have
an a Halo you said that said that you
said that in past I had an as I have an
asthma attack right now like it's like a
thing I know I'm having an asthma attack
and I don't have said that like all
right guys top three cheeses
oh shoot me with a gun around 3 years
ago it makes me really sad and it was
one of our most viral moments and most
clipped moments and the audio went
absolutely crazy dumb of us talking MLB
used it let's talk MLB the NFL the NHL
Bunch Tik Tock
influencers it was Nick and his top
three cheeses well actually shout out
fan accounts because genuinely you guys
are the reason we have the career we
have if you didn't Supply The Intern
with short form content of us we would
be nothing of who we are because the
colby jack audio in the original video
is different than the colby jack viral
moment major thanks to the fan who made
that I wish I knew you us so shout out
all of you fan pages that were on Tik
Tok and Tik Tok is getting B I'm going
to buy it you don't have to worry about
it me and Chris got it covered thank you
so much amazing if that app goes down
liar if that app goes down pants are on
fire I if that app shut up I wish
caught on fire cuz you know what I think
some of you [ __ ] would be blazing for
a fact cuz half of y'all are lying I'm
not going to yell I'm not going to start
yelling today I got to keep it chill cuz
I can be funny without raising my
[ __ ] tone but genely people be like
liar liar pants on fire where the [ __ ]
are the burning pants cuz I know half of
you [ __ ] are not telling the truth
Pinocchio ass [ __ ] if people started
lying and their pants caught on fire and
their nose started to grow I'd see a lot
of ugly [ __ ] with a burnt bottom for
sure and I know and I know that yeah and
I know that if Tik Tok actually gets
erased I haven't talked to Nick and Matt
about this but I want to film and film
and film and post YouTube video every
day of the week for one okay yes yeah I
hear you we'll post some YouTube content
but you're was saying if you guys are
making consistent Tik Tok fan edits I
love to see them I I'm not going to be
sad about Tik Tok being gone but I'm
going to be sad about the community that
we built over there but M and Chris are
on Instagram probably more than Tik Tok
so if Tik Tok does get banned come on
over to Instagram I'm sure that we will
find you back no matter what happens I'm
very very happy with the community we
have here on YouTube me m and Chris have
said to since the beginning of our
career that YouTube is our favorite
platform to post on because we feel that
you guys actually get to know us and who
we are and we feel like it's the best
platform for us to be able to
communicate to you guys talk directly to
you and build a sense of community so as
as much as I'll be sad that Tik Tok is
gone I'm very very happy with what we
have here just don't touch my
YouTube I was thinking at some point I
don't know if you want to do it this
video we should share things that feel
illegal that isn't like for example I
just full sprinted down the street at
3:00 a.m. and I felt like I was going to
get tackled and arrested by who the
boogeyman yeah you thought the boogeyman
that or like like I don't know police
what do you think the boogeyman's made
out
of what do you want me to say boogies
like out of here dude s dog B Dog Z dog
K Dog yeah I don't like that idea I
don't either so should I kill
myself you just Chris are you dead
serious I wasn't are you dead serious my
car is going to be all sticky now so
Nick what was your big idea that was it
just changing initials and names yeah
what would you do if I put jumper cables
on your nipples and put the other end to
a Ferrari and
I feel like Matt would be able to take
it that's the craziest thing who do you
think has the most sensitive niil out of
the three of us I'm not getting into
that yeah like what that's absolutely
not happening on our YouTube channel
definitely Nick guys we found out
honestly Earth crushing news today what
I don't nothing crushed my Earth today
nothing M and Chris were hanging out
with old friends we hadn't seen in
Forever here in Boston Massachusetts I
had a
girlfriend in middle school that I
completely forgot about
yeah and I really think that changes
everything in my life I no cuz nothing
happened with a girlfriend of course
well we were like 10 and best friends of
course Nick but that doesn't mean
anything what the [ __ ]
okay it's just like really crazy cuz
like I've so confidently been like oh no
I've always been gay like I've never had
a girlfriend I had a girlfriend at some
point in like fourth grade for probably
2 weeks I think that that's actually
like a bigger deal than we're making it
right now that's insane yeah that is
crazy I was it fully like it like we
were best friends and like we didn't
kiss or touch her fourth graders yeah
but did you ask her to be your
girlfriend I guess I I didn't remember
this I was reminded maybe you trauma
blocked it I remember I know but I love
I remembered it and then you would
always just say no so I was like I
wasn't saying trauma blonded bonded
because of who it was I was saying
I date her today I am gay yes that's
what I said what I'm saying I'm so happy
for you I love being a gay person that's
good I want to move to a house that has
a nice picket fence in the front okay I
agree I I always I you guys clocked me
once I talk about my bushels that I want
what Nick want nice shubber I want nice
shubber in front of my house I've said
this before time to time again I'll say
till that dad die you should get a bush
with berries that would very your F good
I don't want berry bushes I want
Shrubbery that's fire no but little
bunny rabbits can come eat them no all
right guys like we were saying before
Nick went on a little Rampage we're
going to do top threes today and we
haven't watched either one of those
videos so we might ask the same topic
and our answers have might have changed
so who knows but let's top three ways to
kidnap somebody Chris come on dude top
three ways you'd want to be kidnapped
tranquilizer dart I was like out in
public and a [ __ ] person Tran darted
me and I was just like feeling loo
and I just fell to the ground and I woke
up like in the back of that would be
crazy I feel like a Tran Dart is just
something I want to own not for any
personal gain but just to have on me
that's good yeah I always say and this
is I'm dead serious I don't know if I've
said this on the Internet or not before
I am so afraid of getting my blood drawn
I I say this and I mean this
wholeheartedly if I had the option I
just have to say before you say this
Nick has said this to 25 plus different
people after meeting them no like it's a
real thing that I fully believe it if I
had the option at the top of the month
at some point this month you need to get
your blood drawn you can either schedule
a normal
normal you can either schedule a normal
doctor's
appointment or this tribal Huntsman is
going to follow you for the entire month
with a blow dart and at some point at
any given moment he's going to [ __ ]
shoot shoot you with the blow dartom and
hit me in the neck and I'm going to wake
up getting my blood drawn and I would
choose the Huntsman okay anytime because
it's like the problem is about getting
my blood draon is like the ease up to it
did I eat enough today am I feeling
[ __ ] mentally prepared can I do this
can I handle that and I the answer is I
cannot if do you think that if you
actually get sprayed by a skunk you have
to lather yourself in tomato juice or no
I hope I never find out I hope I never
live to tell the tale I feel like on an
unpopular opinion skunks don't smell
badad let's stop with this nonsense it's
like it's like a crazy stench yeah it's
like a it's definitely got a spunk to it
like it's like a crazy stench but I
wouldn't say it's
like like I've smelled people who smell
worse
than and that's me being that's me being
Boy Scouts Honor I swear to God I've
smelled some people who naturally stink
more than worse than skunks I'm serious
flamingos at the zoo flamingos smell
worse than skunks correct I would there
are some people I'm thinking of I'd
rather smell skunk's ass stop so mean
it's mean but it's honest you know what
I mean I'd rather go I'd rather have my
kids or my nieces my nephews my brother
remember me as an honest man than a and
that's the truth that's my truth stand
on it some some stinky can un smell get
the [ __ ] my face so I have a question to
you guys doing I have a question to you
guys I know that we were going to do top
threes are we doing that at all is this
a top three [ __ ] the big three it's just
big me oh my God Nick I wish I'm going
to start blurring my face when you do
[ __ ] like that cuz I don't want people
to see me I agree like near you please
blur mine I'll pay yeah yeah yeah top
three sharks number one
Hammerhead and the Hammerhead lowkey
fell off cuz the Hammerhead when I was
in school everyone was talking about the
hammerhead shark I feel like that's a
tattoo you oh my god top three equatic
animals I know my number one someone say
it with me in Sy octop no my number one
I I got it I got it I'm the count you
have to know my number I know it you
think about me think of who I am as a
person think of the fun I bring I know
it three if if one of you got this I'm
going to [ __ ] punch someone in the
face don't how about you don't say it
and me and Matt try to just see who can
get it starfish puffer fish oh my God
clown fish I swordfish yes I knew it
thank you m thank you I do have a puffer
fish tattoo in my body so I'm a
hypocrite [ __ ] swordfish are you dead
serious dude you should get a swordfish
tatted so top three aquatic animals go
swordfish number one okay cool number
one sick name to puffer fish number two
yep number three slot Nick jellyfish wow
crazy pull one slot octopus I think I
think I think I have
to Nick you know how cool an octopus is
yeah they're pretty cool not cooler than
a [ __ ] sword fish and this is like a
really unpopular opinion minnows I have
so many memories with a minnow okay yes
there's cooler things that I could say
like the hermit crab or like the whale
you know what I mean I don't think those
are
cooler what is the black what is the
brown and white spotted whale called
someone help me number one is a stingray
I no Stingray is in my three number two
is a dolphin can I finish go ahead
stingray's in my three cuz they killed
my boy Steve irn and I can't put them
higher than up up than the other ones go
ahead Stingray yeah dolphin yeah number
three slot CHR the [ __ ] whale shark
these [ __ ] are tough yeah he is
cool I also a stingray used to be my
favorite animal I like aquatic animals
more than I thought because I have a
stingray stuffed animal I have a
stingray keychain I'm a fantasting race
I love a classic Lobster I think a
lobster oh my God you guys are boring me
to death is there ties in here yeah
give top three fruits number one slot
has to be grapes pineapple no grape
grapes chis grapes well a pineapple
becomes such a [ __ ] mission when I'm
the person who has to cut it I'm great
Chris yelled at me the other day because
I we were at a party and I was eating
party party not party where was that
chery board I was eating the grapes and
no nobody else was touching the grapes
so I ate them all and I was getting made
fun of I thought I know what your number
your number one fruit is and you're a
liar oh and and a lot of people haven't
experienced this picking a green grape
off it sounds like you're just swall
like a rag like that was gross I am
going to throw off right
now can't breathe I'm we I'm like having
an asthma attack take a better drill are
you a benad let me [ __ ] one outan you
can no one's Peg granate pineapple
number one I'm pomegranate oranges
orange like a little Clementine two
slots raspberry two slots of raspberry
yes say blueberries two slot blueberry
my two slot is Apple
kiwis one of my favorite things ever and
this is like me being a Portuguese
person cuz I feel like in my culture no
taking a grape a green grape from the
[ __ ] Vineyard from the vine over a
garage and eating it and spitting the
pit out if you haven't done that find
some fire experience mhm me Matt and
Chris I feel like we've never told the
internet we're Portuguese dude I feel
like that's oh my God what me and my
brothers this is heartbreaking
information we're 50% Portuguese 25%
Italian and 25% Irish yeah so I [ __ ]
thought yep same my dad comes in the
house and tells me hey there's a good
chance you guys are also well he didn't
just come in the house to us it was a
conversation I and he's like yeah
there's a good chance you guys are
probably 2 or 3%
Scottish not good do you know me I know
you when I [ __ ] like something and
I'm happy and content with it yeah I'm
good yeah I'm a very Happy portugee
Irish Italian Y and to hear that I could
be 2% Scottish throws my [ __ ] Vibes
off I'll be honest I'll be so honest
like I think about the possibility of
Scottish ancestry
and it really [ __ ] pisses me off not
that I don't like Scottish people but if
I knew this I'd be I would have have 21
years to deal with it but today I get
not today a while ago I get betrayed
with Scottish descent are you [ __ ]
kidding me and then Dad got you and then
Dad and then I obviously no no you made
a big deal the thing is the reason why
it's such a big deal to Nick isn't that
he's actually Scottish it's the fact
that he was betrayed by this I'm a liar
I'm not what I think I am Y and then and
then Dad got you Scottish cookies top
three satisfying
things oh yeah real funny stupid [ __ ]
ugly ugly you want know just like you
know what's funny I said my answer I
said my answer and you said it was funny
and I wasn't joking top three spaghetti
shapes
rigatony rigoton is my two slot rigaton
is my number one I love shells fetuccini
number one fet Ron is good cuz you can
get like I think I imagine a fork like
this and a rigatoni is like you can go
there's so many strats you could go
pinky down eat it I'm doing it I'm doing
all the fingers so prepare I don't care
you could go pinky catch the end of it
eat it off that you could go Splitsville
and go bottom two on two this one's
about to get crazy you could go middle
Raton catch right or or all four if you
get in there you could get the Roni with
any aspect of the this conversation I
don't care I don't care to be sexualized
I'm talking about Ron no I know but you
you didn't say
anything of that is care I don't care
cuz it's my truth I'm talking about
pasta if you want to take my words and
scramble them go ahead Riddler uh I'd
put rigatoni and my two I'm going shells
at one no no I'm not going shells at one
what is your I'm not going shells in one
once again this ties back to the minnows
I'm going bow TI you're eight you're 8
years old no because I Nostalgia will be
the death of me Chris no I'm not kid
anymore I need I [ __ ] need every
[ __ ] place that has the capability to
do it to start selling tokens and coins
again and make everything in life a fun
experience imagine if you were buying a
car right hey shut your mouth and
instead of buying the car or the car
keys you paid for a big token you enter
it and you spin the wheel and then your
car like like now we're talking now
that's stupid we got kids swiping little
plastic cards you don't even know the
value of the coin you're putting in the
machine when you're a kid and you have a
bucket full of [ __ ] coins going to
the arcade and you see each one go and
invest into every game you play you know
you're working hard you're swiping your
card swiping your card you don't know
how much value that has and then you run
out and then you think it's like life
dad put more money on my mom put more
money on and then you go to and then and
then you go to the store and you start
swiping swiping swiping like it's
nothing cuz then when you go get a prize
and you get that Chinese finger trap
even though it was only 75 tickets you
put that work in you know like I earned
this I feeling like a oh my God I just
had a nostalgic item flood my body with
joy wow yes
okay a kazoo oh my God top three us
States Maine Maine is up there Maine's
in my Maine might be in my I feel like I
got to go Boston California that's not a
state idiot Massachusetts Sorry God
forbid I got to say Massachusetts no I
think I'm Massachusetts Vermont Maine I
think those are my three New England or
to the day it's so hard I feel like I
have to pick Massachusetts and
California cuz those are where we
reside but it's tough between like
Hawaii Maine Vermont I completely agree
those are my those are are all my third
St I feel like you can find a little bit
of Vermont New Hampshire if you go to
the right place in Massachusetts you can
find a little bit of it all in Maine
plus Beach life you're so true and the
reason I don't want to say Hawaii is
because as much as Hawaii is beautiful
and gorgeous and amazing it just feels
so Co it's so tropical that I feel like
I could find that in other places even
though I've never really been yeah I
think I got to give Maine my third slot
top three most annoying things to hear
as a triplet where's Nick where's Chris
if I punched you could Chris feel it or
could Nick feel it those are my top
three dud you sound like Guitar Hero
intros I've never thought of it like
that for sure those are my top three my
least favorite question ever this isn't
really trip related is what are you
doing here it's like what the slow your
horses I I hate I go I know me MERS
aren't party people but I'll walk into a
party someone come up to be drunk what
are you doing here
what are you doing approaching me here
yeah top three compliments you could
receive top three compliments I could
receive I enjoy being around you oh my
god I'd cry I'd cry oh my God number one
actually oh my God that's number one I
don't take I don't take any kind words
well but they mean so much to me like 4
hours later no it's unbelievable someone
told us the other day I can see why you
guys do what you do you got guys have
like great
vocabulary I was like I never struck us
for vocab guys but I'm totally down for
this I think my vocabulary if I'm see my
vocab comes out best when I'm provoked
if you provoke a [ __ ] good word I'd
be I'd be like oh this is a posterous
but I'm never going to say that but if
you provoke me to get to a point of like
what is that video and it's that viral
video that kid and he goes his mom's
like I'm pregnant I'm going to have
another kid and he goes this is exactly
erating that's me like if I'm provoked I
say the craziest word ever and I'm like
I didn't know I knew that word but in
that moment I see dictionary Pages blood
in front of my eyes see I literally was
about to say I see your head as like
you're saying something and like 90w
options come in literally whenever I was
a kid and people would be like oh you
have to think before you speak I'm like
what do you mean I can't add words and
syllables and crazy little statements
mixed into my sentence as it's floting
out of my Dome you know what I mean this
is like I can't control the river dude
it's like put a dam in front of it my
God so was like think before you speak
I'm like you want me to build a goddamn
Hoover wall in front of my [ __ ]
tongue I cannot do that the words the
thoughts are moving too quick I can't do
it you've lost it even in that moment
when I started that thought I didn't
think I was going to end up at the
Hoover Dam but here we are my God can I
say my third I wish to be as funny as
Nick one dead dead off ow ow are you
[ __ ] stupid Beyond hey guys guys
that's a slippery slope three
compliments let me think of the
third if you make me want to be a better
person that's ative
B that only happens in a negative
scenario not true yeah no yeah that's
not true I've heard I've heard um you
and your you and your brothers made me
forget what I was sad about who said
that to you I know I could cry right now
I think a simple you guys make me smile
oh that's a good one oh my God I feel
like us three and growing up with each
other we've explained a lot of our
emotions to each other our entire life
so I feel like us three are best don't
look at me like a scar I just feel like
us three are best at like talking to
each other or just every like expressing
emotions especially like how I do on my
own Channel with anxiety stuff when I
was at that wedding that we went to the
the other day it took everything in me
not to be crying in in every moment of
it and I have no and I have no idea why
because I'm I'm the type to be like
they've all seen the podcast clips of
like I don't want a wedding which is all
everything I said is still true don't
want a big wedding none of that stuff
you know what I mean but like being
there and seeing all like the people
happy about their thing I think I just
feel for what other people are feeling
and I was almost a wreck just sitting
there like cuz I was looking at what he
was a wreck just sitting there a a wreck
not a wck my God I had a boner sitting
at the table no cuz genuinely and I feel
you is like I find so much happiness in
other people having a good time or a
good day I know like if I look at
someone and they're smiling and they
look happy because something is
happening it fills my soul with I
remember ultimate bonus okay hold on top
three sleeping positions not in a sexual
way we've did this we did this one last
time and you went like this oh L FL oh I
did lay flat on my back top three best
business moves ever 24 hours open is
like the best I have no idea what you
just said like top Aura moves by
business establishments I'm happy you
can add staying open for 24 hours yes
that's like ice cold like if you can
stay if you're operating all day long
like you are boss what are your guys top
three times to wake up I love a
10:30 9 11 is good 9:45 sick 11 is good
cuz then I like starting my day at noon
cuz it's like what him what 9:45 up at
up out of bed at 10:00 and then you're
fully functional by best time to wake up
ever like ideal if considering you had
never had to go to school or never had
to work a job 10:00 noon 10:00 10 is
really good 10:00 thank you guys so much
for watching this week's Friday video we
hope you really really enjoyed I enjoyed
even though we didn't really get into
the actual meat and potatoes of the
video um I hope that we can film this
video type of topic again let us know
what you guys want to see it's the new
year there's new content rolling out
what do you want to see us do again what
do you want to see us do for the first
time what do you never want to see us do
again bye thank you guys so much and
carry on those socials on other apps
other than Tik Tok if Tik Tok gets
banned and we appreciate each and every
single one of you guys and we will see
you guys every Friday at 530 on theet
YouTube channel shy had them Apple
Bottom Jeans
boots with the dick
[Music]
[Applause]