nowhere that's focused no way you're
focused Nick I'm actually full arm was a
shut up
and all the things
you guys wanna do top threes what the
[ __ ] dude almost punched me the pillow
shut up [ __ ]
do you want to do top threes yeah I'm
down top threes colby jack Colby yeah
top three cheeses
oh I just spilled that all over you
is it Oliver yep Christopher
it's fine
nothing new nothing new shut the [ __ ] up
it's not acting like I've ever
just like always
give me that no that what is that oh
speak [ __ ] is that what do you
want I said that a tissue no it's a
[ __ ] Dunkin Donuts wrapper if you
would put that there too
is it oh it's my burger
gross
and bro's going stupid on the suckage
back there
like can we be real that's like the
craziest [ __ ] ever
because you got plans tonight
[Music]
not singing go ahead Matt I'm not
singing here
the fans want it that's too bad okay
we're gonna film top threes again so
we're gonna pick random subjects and
then State our top threes from them
um if you're not familiar we've done
this before
um we had a really viral Tick Tock audio
that's kind of corny now because of how
calm it is but it was a cool moment I
just think it's kind of like it's
outshined it's been done and we've seen
it and I've heard enough in my own voice
and
I think it's time for us to really pump
some new love into that and we're gonna
wow we're doing a top three new and it's
time to make a news it's time to make a
new like video for that topic okay Nick
start reading them Matt [ __ ] you you'll
do it
I don't see you doing [ __ ] okay please
what is it don't worry about it what is
it
yeah
that one almost stayed trapped inside
oh I love when this happens three
crackers left and three cheeses left can
I have one count top three meats
all right what are your top three meats
I think top meat for me and I think that
this can be spoken for for a long
chicken wrong top meat and it's in the
name it's the meat man
meatball number one in my opinion we got
meatball coming in on top then chicken
two reliable good constant consistent we
love them chicken meatball number one
chicken number two number three
I'm not a steak fan so hear me out I'm
going cheers
on it so hamburgers made of ground beef
you want an ultimate ground beef tacos
ground beef is three
I'm not gonna say it because I can't
speak Spanish but there's some Spanish
meat that I love that I refuse to say
because I'm white as [ __ ] but we got
honestly I
might like that ground beef really
no I ain't more than chicken for sure
I'm switching it up for me it's going
meatball
ground beef
Mexican meat I'm not gonna say because I
don't know how to say it and I don't
want to sound stupid
um I think
but that's my top three meats what are
yours chicken meatball
and praise the Lamb and what braised
lamb or just lamb I love lamb
don't sorry don't yuck my yum sorry if
you're vegan
that's something you gotta deal with
the top three they say it's in the name
man
three so social media apps
number one come in YouTube YouTube
we got that YouTube
yeah then we got coming in strong at
second place a personal safe place for
me love talking to people on it Snapchat
incorrect Instagram oh I love Instagram
action Instagram two Snapchat three tick
tock four absolutely YouTube Instagram
Instagram Snapchat my top three yeah
gotta say that
next
yes Nick that was smooth
[Music]
you stop it's so annoying I will take my
face every time
no you look at this every time three
Hangouts boxes it's all stupid top three
hangout spots none of your business I
see your strategy with asking us that oh
you know yeah where do they hang out one
of their top three so I can maybe the
park
I like hanging out sketchy alleys at 4am
go find me
um don't hurt yourself friends houses
friends house is number one boom number
two the park
two Park three vehicle all the car the
car what the [ __ ] are you sure for that
one whatever the car's there all right
we're gonna no cars won for me honestly
car friend's houses Parks yeah
top three shot
top three
restaurant good old restaurant to hang
out Oh I thought you like you just said
restaurant after the conversation hey
shut the [ __ ] up
where are the wild things at Nick top
three pastas
I think we just covered this in the last
one
are we on sauce included or just pasta
shape that's really important
really really dude I don't know really
let's figure it out let's do both okay
top three pastas no sauce no sauce I
gotta go fetish hair feta cheese wow
Penny penny
did I say it wrong gotta go rare pick
for number one coming for me rigatoni
yeah incorrect rigatoni
fire fettuccine on top it's going
rigatoni for me classical spaghetti love
it ziti
boom
okay real quick top three pasta
pasta
Alfredo number one for me Alfredo two
for me garlic sauce little garlic
three
move forward
three clothing articles
number one for me what no no no no no
number one for me gotta be a scarf
me too your next cold heated up
somewhere else
none of your none of my business go rub
your hands on it yourself do something
different I [ __ ] hate scarves me too
I gotta go number one clothing item for
me it's good pants love pants pants can
make or break a fit I agree
another one and you're diverse with a
jeans cargos second for me has got to be
shoes shoes the Wings shoes not even
like shoes like oh I love shoes but like
shoes like the shoes you put on can
totally change them for me the vibe of a
fit and make you feel so much first
number two for me I'm gonna go with a
nice Jack
love that [ __ ] answer let's go and
and number three for me probably not for
most a hat I love a good hat for me can
I throw in an underrated pick bro the
socks
the socks what's so important about them
can't have the shoes without the socks
well he does make a good point I'd wear
shoes without socks you're weird if I
only had to pick three yes if I could
only pick three articles of clothing I'm
going shoes
pants pants shirt okay this is top three
not only three [ __ ] yeah
so then you can do shoes without socks
debunked whatever yeah socks really
aren't that important I just love them
they make them feel comfortable that's
good it's for your person it makes me
feel comfortable because I eat too much
sugar so my feet go numb
so I have to wear tight socks top I'm
being for real I know yeah
we'll figure it out three
top three colors
purple purple what's your favorite color
purple black and green is your favorite
color green
not funny you're not funny my top bones
are purple green and black what are your
purple black and blue copycat what are
yours
mine are orange black
baby blue good three solid three solid
solid three nice but like I'm looking
for more
not like a pastel yellow top three sodas
Dr Pepper root beer Pepsi root beer
before Pepsi for you no that was just
like my top three okay in order stupid
root beer Pepsi Dr Pepper Pepsi root
beer okay honestly Dr Pepper Pepsi
Shirley temples
Bingo
beer and [ __ ] you too I'm gonna go with
Dr Pepper all right
Pepsi first third I'm gonna go with a
can I throw a sweet tea in there
it is Chris no oh they're doing drinks
no we're not we might be I don't know I
can't remember then I'll do root beer
top three merch drops that leaves them
yeah the next one the next one after
that and then the next one after that
my favorite one is our tour merch that
was like different state to state number
one for me I agree got number two for me
is the holiday one the little icy one I
love the globe Casey and really those
are two for me as well I just like them
because they were our first I like my
babies yeah and then number three for me
is
I liked okay the the brown shirt with us
Rihanna in the car now it's in the
dinosaur shirt the dinosaur shirt's good
um next no
last thing I want to say too is I liked
our four million shirt yeah me too
a lot of people didn't like our four
million shirt you know what I have to
say
don't buy it
correct and keep your [ __ ] mouth shut
I'm keeping that in too no you're not
yes I am Nick cut it off I [ __ ] am
that's how I feel
three best
I gotta go oh wait is it like just
American Business
can you even name three biscuits yeah I
could you [ __ ] idiot okay
crazy yeah that's all right all right
Lucille's biscuits
three so go [ __ ] yourself because you're
you're gonna smile and be all happy once
I mention a good biscuit oh I'm gonna
say is
an idiot I don't care I actually don't
like Popeye's biscuits I hate them
they're drying can't see ones are good A
Biscuit is supposed to be soft and your
teeth are supposed to feel like they're
just like kind of sinking into a pillow
exactly if you're feeling if you're
chewing a biscuit you're doing it wrong
Lucille's biscuits number one no KFC's
over no no no
nope Lucille's can't see Popeyes
Lucille's KFC and then [ __ ] Lucille's
on a rainy day [ __ ] I hate
Popeye's [ __ ] I hate pots I love that
chicken from Popeyes the biscuits made
as [ __ ]
[Laughter]
love chicken Papa good good spicy
Popeyes chicken sandwich brings me back
to sitting with my friend Michaela in a
car and just breathing in the fresh air
I've been nice I love lukewarm I love
[ __ ] underneath I love going to
Popeyes with creamy sauce and a nice
chicken
love that chicken from pop pop okay
all three ways you want to die oh my God
probably blunt force trauma
who the [ __ ] just laughed about three
sounded like a president three sleeping
positions on your stomach like that on
my back no
I didn't do this last time
slap back like this that's so creepy can
I stand by that no flat out like this
that's perfect that's all I can do is
the no
it looks like he's praying no not back
like imagine there's a mattress right
here okay you can't see me because
there's a mattress we're gonna turn your
head a little you want to use it
really
sometimes I go this way
oh my God this kid's insane okay then
I'd say good like
just like this like a ball
foreign top three pieces of Jewelry
earrings love a good ring no I hate
Rings [ __ ] you I don't actually care
that much but I just thought it would be
funny
three fruits pineapple on [ __ ] top
every day every week I'm really getting
into mangoes
I must say I don't
pineapple
like I love pineapples don't get me
wrong but I needed a pineapple prepared
for me as much as I love pineapples I
don't love it enough to cut the [ __ ]
top off cut the sides off cut the
[ __ ] middle out the core cut it into
little pieces like I'm really honestly
love pineapple but I'm good so buy it
pre-cut
in the little plastic tins not nearly as
good those people don't have passion you
know people who works people who work at
a grocery store that cut up fruits and
put them in the little plastic bins like
the little to go containers they don't
have the [ __ ] passion I would have if
I was cutting it and I don't think it
does what do you even mean by look I
mean you have to adjust I don't like I
don't
I don't produce is in an intimate thing
for me
there's a bruised Apple I might pick
another one I might see an apple and
like be like oh like I definitely want
that one or like a pack of raspberries
I might see a pack of raspberries and
there's a couple mushy ones I'm like you
need a different home that's not mine
and then I'll find a pack of raspberries
that I want so I think that on all
circumstances they cut up fruit and
stuff I don't think those people are
taking as much time and care and care to
take out the gross pieces they're just
throwing it in the container they don't
they it's by batch and then they put it
out
so anything cuts at the [ __ ] fruit
Master no I'm talking about like The
Raspberries like they're not picking
them yeah no not those I'm talking about
the pre-cut ones oh well
because I just I look like if I if I
needed 10 things from the produce
section like the berries from the
Batgirl and the [ __ ] hair
there's 10 people at this if there's
someone at the store and I have like 10
things from the produce section that I
want and someone's like oh I'll go get
it for you I'll be like oh honestly I
think it's better if I do it okay and
I'll do it with love and knowing that I
want the fruit honestly raspberries and
grapes are really top two for me
I love clementines oh like that's a
[ __ ] lie the Halos what the Halos the
Halos [ __ ] you the Halos that's a lot
all your pants on fire like the Halos
[ __ ] Halos [ __ ] you and your intimacy
process you idiot you're in no [ __ ]
position to say that's me yeah I am I
intimately pick up my fruit often when
you eat a clementine never so I'm much
more Justified to say that you're a
[ __ ] liar you're a phony you're not
even a real fruit lover you just buy to
be healthy then you let it go to waste
in our fridge and you don't clean it up
after yourself I end up cleaning it up
or Matt oh that's the funniest thing no
you're funny not true that's true double
not true
oh man thank you guys so much for
watching this week's video as always
keep dabbing on the haters come back
next week we'll see you next Wednesday
and then we'll see you next Friday peace
and love hope everything's good and if
you're watching hello I'm not subscribed
to our [ __ ] YouTube channel you have
a button to click so get the [ __ ] out of
my face and go click that button Nick
don't be rude it's not it's just like
persuasive a little bit
I'm passionate we were gonna split that
let me feel it empty yeah [ __ ] you
I hate you
yeah yeah