All right, y'all. Welcome to the car
video section of this video. We're going
to pop in and out and just talk about
what's what we're experiencing. The meat
and potatoes. The meat and potatoes. But
the you might see us just jump in every
now and again. But that's Is it now and
then? Every now and then. You always say
now and again. And it like infuriates
you like I just want to beat you up cuz
like now and then is like giving It's
like every now and then. Now or later.
You now and again. Right now. And it's
going to happen as well. Well, it could
happen again is my thought process.
Yeah, I think you're like making up a
new term that just looks a lot like
something that's a thing. I works. No,
it's just way too chunky. Like every now
and again. I'll see you now and now now
and then. Every now and again. No, now
and again is not the same. I'll see you
every time you say that. I actually
fight the urge to like hit you. Like
it's annoying. But anyway, you guys you
guys That's insane. You guys get the
understanding. We'll be um popping up
every now and again. Yeah, every now and
again. Now, let's jump right into the
video. Hey guys, we're about to be at
the San Diego Safari Park.
Fruit Beer. Fruit Beer. Any ketchup
today? No, thank you. Matt, no ketchup.
No ketchup for the stereo loop. What are
you doing though? This camera is so
[ __ ] heavy. Hold on. You have big
hands, right? You're strong. You're a
big boy, not a baby playing around with
blocks. It's time to grow up. Hold some
real [ __ ] All right.
Where's five? Chop. Chop. Nick. I'm
going to have your burger. Okay, no
problem. Should I scream into the
interview? No. Nick, give me my [ __ ]
burgers.
All right. Here you Thank you. Have a
good one.
Boom. All right, guys. Welcome back to
the Stern Triplet YouTube channel.
Today, we are doing something that we
have never done before. Something a
little different. Something a little
extra with a little pizzazz and flare.
Yeah, exactly. Basically, this video,
me, Matt, and Nick splurged and spent a
good amount of money. Hold on. And we
bought out the entire Roar Safari Park
at the San Diego Zoo today. No
sponsorship with San Diego Zoo. No
partnership or anything. We're just
doing this all for fun. I wish there was
a sponsorship. We put a [ __ ] bag down
to do this. But we hit 6 million
subscribers and you're going to come
along with us today at our day at the
safari park. Oh my god. You can already
hear
you can already hear animals in the
distance. But we're celebrating 6
million subscribers with you guys today
at the safari park. There was I just saw
a shadow of like a big bird. Was there a
bird going by? All right. Well, we have
a whole day and night and the day again
of safariing ahead of us. So yeah, we're
spending the night at the zoo. That's
what like we're experiencing the roar
and snore. It's a legit zoo overnight.
We're going to roar today, snort
tonight, and roar tomorrow. Let's do it.
Matt, do you have anything to say to the
vlog before we get into the safari? I'm
just happy to have the time in my life.
Wow, that's good. Oh my god. Nick, how
do you feel? I just hope it lives up to
Matt's standards. I really do. I see
children walking over there. Let's go
say hi and see if they like the zoo. No,
let's not do that. Yeah, probably not
the best. Yeah, probably not. Good
joining us tonight. I guess since
there's three of you that look similar.
Yeah. Yep. We're the triplets. That's
us. Nice. Welcome. How was the drive in?
Not bad at all. It was really fun,
honestly. Yeah, we were singing music
and killing time.
[Music]
Yeah, I heard you guys are celebrating
your birthday. No, our 6 million
subscribers.
Okay. Well, so the game of telephone
really worked on me. Yeah, it's okay
though. Um, well, congratulations. Thank
you. Thank you. A milestone. Yeah. What
brings you guys to Roar tonight? Um,
he's a big animal guy. Loves love
animals. Oh, I'm You know what? I got
there. Nick always making me answer
questions that I didn't want to. We go
up to the lady at the front desk and I
go, she goes, "Oh, what brings you to
the zoo? Like, why are you and Nick just
goes like this right to me?" I think if
I I think if that happened to me, oh my
god, put on the spot. Putting Chris on
the spot is my favorite thing when I
don't know what to say cuz like he'll
think of something. Well, I did it twice
in this video. You did it numerous
times. It just blows my mind. Well, you
did think of something. Yeah, I always
do. I'm the You love animals. was real
creative and unique. I think I said
that. Yeah. Either way, it was a [ __ ]
stupid response. Better than this. I'm
sorry. I just hate chitter chatter. Like
I hate
I don't It's not that I hate I just hate
like the Let's get to the [ __ ] stack
of this conversation.
I hate like the initial like about to
get to know somebody. Yeah. You like it
like an hour later. Yeah.
And then just over by the elephants,
just don't use any um lights into the
habitat since they have really sensitive
eyes. Absolutely. Um ju just all around
is totally fine. Me too. Restroom.
Right. Restrooms right here. And then I
think they're bringing the cart to us.
Oh, they're bringing the cart to us.
Never mind. I have hidden cheeits in
here. So I hope they don't find it. I
have to bring And I have Fruity Pebbles.
Well, it's like dude, dinner's at like
10. Yeah, they have dinner at 5. Like
we're not we're not 80 years old. Come
We also aren't gonna feed the animals.
Like, what are we gonna do? We're not
gonna feed the animal. They're gonna You
catch me at 4:00 a.m. in the elephant
habitat with with a flashlight on. With
a flashlight on and Fruity Pebble. No,
it actually broke my heart. She said,
"Don't use your flashlight near the
elephant. They have sensitive eyes."
Well, isn't it crazy that like elephants
really like in the wild? They don't know
what like a flashlight is. Yeah, good
point. Let's go. Yeah. If you shine a
flashlight at it, it's probably like,
"What the heck?" Like, I think that that
with all animals, Chris, how do you
feel, Nick? Like a kid in a car seat.
Nice.
Looks like you have like a shitty
diaper. That's what people compare these
things to all the time.
I'm like, pull your hoop. Chris, stop
it. Okay, wonderful. Matt was just
referring to um back when we were in
high school, there was this guy name
and it and it wasn't tight enough and it
Oh my god. Yeah, really bad. Why did you
say that? I don't know. I exploded his
whole side cuz we don't ever say that.
So make sure your thing is tight. It is.
It will be
[Music]
I'm so afraid actually. This is
insanity. Not the type of guy to say,
"Don't look down." No, I'm not, bro.
Look it. You can see right through it.
Look at me. He's going. I just We never
formally introduced Memo. He's just like
filming for us. Okay. Look at him. Oh my
god. He's a champ. He's This He loves
this [ __ ] I know. You love this [ __ ]
Stop. No. It's filming sharks if you
could. No. If this is if this was
haunted, you'd like it more. Piece of
cake. Piece of cake. What have to break?
No, it's all automatic. It'll break for
you. It'll break for you. That's great
news. I didn't want to like have to like
pull a lever and twist around.
Imagine you just like you're getting to
the end. You're just increasing speed
faster and faster. Hold on to the black
straps while you land. And don't cross
your legs. She's tell I'm going to cross
my legs and hold on to the black straps.
Okay, got it. No, you're supposed to
hold the straps. You go like this and
Yeah. go like this across my face.
Something about Nick like listening to
instructions and like not being able to
scream and yell at someone is so funny
to me. Look at him. You can take a seat.
It's the swaying back and forth after
you take the seat. That's the scariest
for me. Yeah. The loss of control. Mhm.
All right. Who wants to go first? Matt.
I'll go first. Sounds good. Two.
Wow.
Sorry for the hairline cam, y'all.
Ready? Yep. Three, two, later. Wow, you
guys. I have to be quiet cuz of the
rhinos. This is crazy being this high
up. Oh my god.
Oh my god.
Wow.
This is a lot less scary than I thought
it would be. Dang.
Dude.
Oh my god. They look back at me. That
was the cutest thing I've ever seen in
my entire life. Dude, I'm freezing cold.
I look like I'm I'm like crying my eyes
out cuz of all the wind. This is like
insane,
guys. I'm not crying. It's just really
windy.
Oh my gosh. Oh, what's up?
Hi, sheep.
I'm flying.
Wow. This is going so fast. Imagine just
the top.
Listen to the landing c. Okay.
Wow.
My eyes are watering like so bad.
Oh, wow. That was nice. I don't think
I've ever needed a tissue more. That was
crazy. That was a beautiful ride. I
know. Very beautiful. You're in tears. I
know. I'm not in tears cuz of like how
emotional it was. It was just really
windy. Dude, the second my hood went I
was like, "Yeah, I can't do selfie
mode." This is a rough scene. No, it
looked like when I had my head out of
the [ __ ] sunroof of the
It's so cold. I think the left. This is
the left. That's the This is the right.
This is the left. Nick, why did that
fence to the right? This is to the left.
Are you serious? Now it's to the left,
but it's to the right over there. Is it
to the left? Am I losing my mind? To the
right.
We went this way. We went to the right.
They would stop us if we were going the
wrong way. We went to the left. We took
a lefthand turn. Look at where that
thing is and tell me what side of it
we're on. If you're facing this way, the
left
and snore. Wait. Yo, where's the
bathroom? Ask Joe. Joseph, is that is
that the bathroom? Ask. I don't know.
Like, why would we know? Why would we
know where the bathroom is? Oh,
restrooms. There we go. Good. All right.
There's a sign. Just that whole that
whole experience is like a reverse
catfish. like the internet. Am I seeing
an an elephant? That that zipline
experience was like reverse catfish.
Like it has Can you [ __ ] off? I started
this sentence six times and I've yet to
finish it. I'm just concerned cuz we
don't have like a zoo person with us.
We're at the camp that we paid to get.
We're going to be here all day. Yeah,
but don't we have like a safari to be
attending right now? I don't know. Let's
go to our find our stuff in one of these
camps. I have no idea. Oh my god. Space
camp. Oh, I get it. It's like I know
you're just super excited about that.
They're really annoying.
Is that a [ __ ] dinosaur? What is
this? I think it's a lion. It's just
someone in the bathroom taking a [ __ ]
Imagine. I don't think we were supposed
to walk away from that. I think we like
fully just broke the rules by leaving
the the front over there. Well, we were
supposed to go to the [ __ ] left. And
we went We took a left. It was Listen,
when we left, there was one of these.
See this fence? There was something just
like this. Like, no. Like we took the
only true path to glory. Like this was
the only way we could have gone. Yes.
But look what I'm saying is like see
that path right there. Yes. That's to
the right right now. Right. But if I was
here, it would be to the left. That's
what you're not getting. You took a left
and then went right.
Was I supposed to just stand there like
this and wait for Joseph to the left?
Wait. We have time. What time is it? I
don't know. That little tour we took was
so so many facts. I feel I always feel
devastated hearing about how many
animals are extinct. But I also found
out that's the thing about the San Diego
Zoo. They're working hard to bring them
back. Nonprofit organization.
They they make all their money and they
send it back to the animals. Yeah. Like
the in the large amount of money we
spent to do this whole thing on our own.
We just Let's think we just donated it
to them. We essentially just fed the
animals, which is such a nice
heartwarming feeling for me. You want to
know it's the the Are you serious now?
What is going on? He's hitting me with
this. You want to know what's the the
craziest thing that I learned while in
that step for safari? Tell us, Matt.
Endangered doesn't actually mean like
there's like none none left. No. Yes, it
it does. So endangered, listen,
endangered is like under 100. Extinct
means that you're out of here. No,
extinct doesn't necessarily mean you're
out of here. What I heard him say that
you're going to say is you can be
functionally extinct, which means
there's like all just like like two or
three female ones that can't like
they're extinct cuz when those ones that
are alive die, they're out of here.
Don't say die. That's a strong word. Say
like pass away. Yeah, there we go, dude.
And there's another animal which the
horse that was cloned. Yeah, that was
the first clone. They cloned a horse or
something. One thing that I blew my mind
was crazy that blew my I want Dude,
cloned a horse. Hold on. Wait, we're
going past that way too fast. They
claimed the horse. They clowned a horse.
He said that he said that it was the
same horse was alive in 2003.
It was me. I did it. I hope they're
working on the woolly mammoth, I think.
Okay. Undisclosed information. They're
working on the woolly mammoth. It's
unreleased. No, I think they're
unreleasing it. Okay. So, the bathroom,
it's in cryosleep right now or
something. This tent, this tent,
according to my map, is Oh, brother. is
tent number Oh, Joseph. I see him.
That's our guy. Get down there. That
one's 1038, by the way. Any questions
before we uh continue on?
[Music]
No questions. No questions. That was a
lot of fun. Excitement. When was the
last time you did the zipline? You know
what? I'm going to leave it to the
professionals
line.
It's kind of fun getting to go on the
zipline, see a little bit of that first.
This is the longest continuous zip line
in the continental US. Yeah. Over 2/3 of
a mile. And this is just like what three
habitats you're going over. Yeah. So,
uh, it just gives you a bit of scope on
on where exactly you are. I didn't even
realize I was on the zipline till I was
at the third habitat. It was so much at
first. Oh, here I am.
Great word. Habitat. I love that. Okay,
buddy. It's just a spell and define it.
I'm not going to spell it. I thought you
were have to pay for this. Yeah, take a
look. I thought for sure I was like
going to need a quarter, but we caugh up
money. Wait, there's another one.
Oh my god. Are you serious? You just let
go and hurt my hand. Up at the top of
the hill, we have a facility. You might
see the fences uh kind of put near the
trees. That's where the condor breeding
program beame uh began for the
California condors. Um in the 1980s,
there were 22 on the planet of the
California condors. Very Yeah, they are
they are scary, right? Very very cool.
So we call that the condor miniums
basically. Ah,
that's really been the main driver of
their
plan.
They what they talk about on the um on
the spotlight tour. We learned a lot
about your plant research and all that
type of stuff. Yes. How the plants are
worth more than Well, not not um
emotionally worth more, but like we love
the plants. We love the plants. We love
the animals equally. We don't have a
favorite child, but like if we're
talking money, the plants are making us
more. Yeah, exactly. So, if you think
about predators like lions, they're
mainly going to be able to see in a
grayscale from black to white, whereas
the colors red and green are opposite on
the color wheel. So, these mala, if they
can find a green grassy habitat, they're
not going to be seen. That's crazy. I
see them. Yeah. Right. And then if you
also look at their vertical stripe
pattern, that's going to break up their
body. Instead of looking like an
antelope, it's going to look like tall
grasses or bushes. Wow. Shout out
Evolution and Charles Darwin group.
That's our young female born in July.
Her name is Eminem. M&M. She's got two
younger uh brothers that are somewhere
in the habitat. Their names are Junior
Mints and Big Red. Junior candy. Who the
name? You guys have a generator or you
guys name it? Yeah. What is the process?
Camouflage is such a crazy thing. Like
camouflage just blending in. Well, it's
also like just it's the fact that it's
camouflage because of how the lions see.
You know what I mean? Like we can see
those things clear as day. Lions cannot.
I think us being triplets. Oh my god. Hi
giraffes. Oh my god. Giraffes right
here. Mac goes rhino. You need to see
these guys. What's up y'all? Pewdiepie.
Oh my. It looks a lot like the serial
six mil merch shirt is right here
actually. Hold on. Wait, this is great.
The camouflage is working cuz I only saw
that rhino. On the left there is a
rather special giraffe. Her name is
Satuni. This past week was her second
birthday. Let's go. Happy birthday.
Right. Happy birthday. And when she was
born, her ankles were too weak to stand.
Literally me kind of. So So what would
happen to a giraffe that couldn't stand
in the wild? It would die.
Unfortunately, it would be a hyena happy
meal, right? Unfortunately, they're not
going to be able to survive. Yeah.
Luckily, here at the Safari Park, we
have something called the Harter
Veterinary Medical Center. We were able
to create custom leg braces for this
giraffe. I think we can agree she's very
fashionable. All right. They were
literally giraffe print, the braces.
Wow. I love that. And uh yeah, after 5
weeks of physical therapy, she was
deemed strong enough and and was sent
back to her family here. They are pretty
special. These birds are monogous. They
will mate for life every day. They will
sing to their partner to show that
they're still in love. How beautiful. We
need that nowadays. Yeah, we're lacking
that in the human species. Come on now.
Key to a long relationship is karaoke.
Amen. That's a big [ __ ] pond. Holy
[ __ ] Is that a male? This is a male.
Way to go. And uh he's what we call a
Nile Lechwe. Uh leche is an African word
meaning antelope. So he's a Nile
antelope. He lives in Sudon along the
Nile. But you may have noticed he had
kind of like a tuxedo on. He's got that
little white bow tie on his neck. That's
how he gets matches on Zoo Harmony. Yes.
So the females are camouflaged.
Whereas the male stands out. So in the
female's mind, she's going to say, "Wait
a minute. A lion can see you when you're
still alive. That's really handsome."
So big and strong, Miss
Waffle.
are striped because they don't want to
be spotted, right?
That was a great joke. So, when there's
a big group of them together, a predator
might not be able to determine one from
another. It's so crazy that that's like
just their natural pattern. I feel like
I'm getting vertigo. I know, right? The
fence, too. I'm like, what should happen
if you're a lion? Your eyes are going to
hurt after looking at these. Yeah. Oh my
god. They're definitely white with black
stripes. Like I don't know who started
that debate. Yeah, that one reminded me
of the um zebra print let's trip banner.
I was getting that I was getting that
vibe too. In terms of wildlife uh in
Africa, they are considered to be a very
protective animal.
They can even kill lions if they have
to. Damn. To keep their family safe. So
what they'll do is they'll form a
defensive front line. Bye zebras. Say
bye. Bye. Oh sorry. It's like our baby
Elliot here. He's not going to get the
dark coat until he's just waved at him.
Going into like giraffe puberty. How
tall is a baby giraffe? Like how tall is
Elliot? We stood next to Elliot. So at
birth, how how uh tall would you guess
that? 4 foot three. 43. You see that the
confidence there? Really? I don't know.
I took a guess, but I was like, I need
5T. I was I was going to say 4 foot. 4
foot. About 6 feet on average. Very
close. I'm 6'6. My height is a one-month
old giraffe. It's very humbling. Yes.
Right. True. That's important because
they've got to be the tallest animal in
the world one day, right? Uh the adults
stand 14 to 19 ft. Wow. And for every
foot of height, they have approximately
an inch of tongue. Damn. Wow. Inch per
tongue per height or whatever. Crazy.
What crazy ratio. Yeah.
hour.
I yawned. Nick, when you're editing,
when I yawn, it's probably like a
Okay,
quick brief announcement. Um, our tour
guide, Joseph, was shining red lights
like right in the animal's eyes. And it
probably looks like kind of like
annoying to the animals, but fun fact,
Joseph told us that the red light
doesn't bother the animals because it's
the way the animals see. Like all the
animals he was shining the light right
in their eye, they don't see the red
light, so it doesn't bother them at all.
The only animals that you can't shine
red lights at are birds and elephants
because elephants eyes are sensitive to
light and birds can see ultraviolet.
That's what it was.
Birds can see ultraviolet light. I don't
even know what that means. It's UV.
You've heard of UV before? I think we
can see that, too. We saw the red light.
I don't know. Something about those
animals don't see. They can see
ultraviolet. We saw the red. We saw we
saw the red light. I know that. Like, do
we have not the same vision? Sorry. The
red light isn't ultraviolet light. Okay,
whatever. Everything has ultraviolet
light. The sun is producing ultraviolet
light. So, shock that the birds are can
able to see it. Whatever. It doesn't
matter. Anyway, this is just a
disclaimer that Joseph wasn't being rude
and blinding the animals. They just
couldn't see the red light. True. We
have a ran antelope male. We actually
have several of them. Hello. I I'll I'll
pause here if you do want to stand um on
the cart. But you can see they've got
this interesting facial pattern, right?
They knew we had special guests today.
They put their makeup on. Yes. Glam and
the uh the black line that covers their
eye extends the appearance of their
horns so they look scarier, more
formidable to predators. Wow. So makeup
is their protection. These are all boys.
So these are the drag queens of Africa.
Yes. And uh very very useful. In fact,
the nickname is the lion king. If you
can see the exposed rock face in the
distance, that is our habitat for our
male big horn sheep. So, you can see our
big horn literally have the entire side
of a mountain up. Yeah, that's crazy.
And they love it because they're great
rock climbers, right? So, if you put
your hands together and squeeze really
tightly, there's almost like a suction
that occurs. Yes, I do it for fun
sometimes. Right. And that's because
they have a hard outer bony shell and a
squishy soft inside. Um, and that that
really does act like a suction cup to uh
stay on the rocks, right? Help them away
from predators.
That's crazy. We can hear lions. Lions
are dying. Not that they happen, but
what's the protocol if a lion escapes?
You pray really hard.
No, there's a lot of security measures
in place here. Oh, it's cuddling
together.
That is so crazy. See, right in front of
my eyes. I thought it was a statue.
Laying on her back. Gigantic. So
gigantic. These are one of the most
powerful animals in the world. And they
kind of just looked like our house cat
scaled up. Yeah. Wow. This dude is this
lady, sorry, is looking right into my
soul. I know. She definitely is. She
definitely knows you're here. Uh, as I
mentioned, there are three sisters about
10 years old. Their names are Zuri,
Malikica, and Amira. Shout out this
piece of glass. For real. I know. Shout
out to the glass. Shout out to the
glass. Doing everything I needed to do.
I would be Zur's lunch.
How you doing? Welcome.
How are you? We got you guys in ready.
I'll take really great care of you and
I'll come back to get you in one.
Awesome. Thank you. Can I run to the
bathroom quickly? Here's the reconc
Hello. Hi. Ooh. Wow. This looks really
good. There's ribs, wings, mac and
cheese, baked beans, klelaw, salad, and
roll. Awesome. Thank you so much. This
entire Roar and Snore experience, this
is the craziest part for me so far. We
have this full restaurant to oursel,
which is insane. I'm about to eat some
ribs. I'm about to get some What did she
say? This was mac and cheese. Mac and
cheese sandwich. Oh,
Nick and Matt need to get out of the
bathroom, bro. They're missing out. I'm
about to steal all our food. Nick just
told me that there was a lion in the
bathroom and I had like a mini jumped
back and then he turned the lights on.
He was like looking with his flashlight.
Matt, he was looking for a minute and 30
seconds. I go, Matt, there's no lion.
Like I jokingly told him and he started.
I know. How crazy is it that we just
have this whole restaurant? Like I know,
dude. Usually there's like probably 40
people, 30 people. This is our first
time using our big boy YouTube money to
like do something about that. This is
the first time we've like balled out in
our YouTube curb. This and buying dad a
truck. Yeah. So, make sure you guys
watch this [ __ ] video, please. I feel
bad looking at animals all day and then
eating them. You're not eating them.
You're eating like I don't care. I'm
starving. I'm hungry. I'm hungry. I got
to eat. She said there's hot chocolate,
coffee, like tea, and then if we want
soda, we can just ask one of them and
they'll get us a soda. Wow. What a
[ __ ] fruitful experience.
Fruitful experience. It's so unfortunate
that there's nobody else here cuz these
salad going I love [ __ ] like this cuz
it's like just private and us three and
memo get to experience all this but I
feel like such a douchebag. You know
what I mean? But it's for like us. I
feel great. This is like they should
have made all this. I know. It's just
It's okay. We'll be fine. I'll eat as
much as I possibly can. What is this?
This is so fun. Oh my god. Hey, we're at
the [ __ ] zoo at night in the middle
of the night. That's That's always been
my biggest fear. I walk around the zoo
during the day and like imagine being
here at night and now it's in front of
right here. Well, it is cool just to be
private and like Guys, this is We have
to just be super thankful. Do we have
cash we can like give like some people?
I got nothing. Yeah, I know. I got a
hungry belly. That's all I got. Dude, I
love that memo. Oh, the fire crackling.
Snap crack snapple pop. I thought B was
coming to get me.
You definitely see the camera full
shake. I was so nervous. Yeah. No, I
thought you How are you enjoying? Give
me a second place. Dude, I asked you a
question. You didn't answer. Chris,
favorite animal you saw so far. Did I
see a deer? Yeah.
What? What was that called? I know it's
like annoying to say cuz it just
happened, but I think that those lions
were like a top tier experience. That
was crazy. They were right there.
I hate eating ribs on camera. I'm just
like sloppy right now. I love this font.
Oh my god. Matt, where do you recognize
this coffee font from? Um cuz it kind of
looks familiar to me. I can't really
tell like where it's from. It looks like
um What the [ __ ] Guys, if you know what
this is from, please let me know. Oh
yeah, that's right. It's the Still
Triplet 6 Million shirt. Nick, doesn't
that font look familiar? It looks so
familiar. It looks exactly the 6 million
Stella Triplet shirt. I feel like the
www.sernalclo.com
that's available right now on the triple
website. Every single one of these
tables and every single one of the tents
that you saw earlier is supposed to have
somebody in it. But we bought
everything. So look at all the empty
tables.
Just us and Memo so he can vlog and the
zookeepers. Yeah, the keepers of the
zoo. No, I can't believe like I'm super
respectful that the Lions are over
there, but I can picture like other
teams.
Yeah. Like shining the flashlight. Also,
we're so we're fully unsupervised and
there's an African elephant right there.
Right there. Like we could do just about
anything, dude. That's unbelievable.
I've never had this much easy access to
an African elephant ever before in my
life. I know. I could go outside and
ride the Fortnite emote on a for on an
elephant. They're right there. I could
probably hit him with this cup.
Literally, I'm not going to, but I
definitely could. It's just crazy that
we're here and this is what we're doing.
But also, we've done so much today
already. We still have a night vision
safari tonight, which I don't know how I
don't know how we're going to vlog. A
night vision safari. And then we have
tomorrow morning where we're going to
meet an animal. So, yep. Guys, where
we're going right now is our little
night trip. And we entered this room and
we were told we were going to see bats.
So, I decided to pretend that the bats
were going to attack us the moment we
walked into this room. our camera like
really really sucks in the dark cuz we
didn't have a light and we're also not
allowed to shine the light at the
animals like we just said previously. So
when we walked in it was like those like
double doors that like they have at like
um what's it called? Petting zoos.
That's it. It's like those double doors
that they have at petting zoos but for
like the bat for the birds to stay
the bats. Listen to these goddamn bats.
Listen to these goddamn bats. That's all
I have to say.
Oh wow, it's hot. I'll open up the next
door once this one can close.
So nice to get warm for a second.
Release the bats.
Nick, this is totally up your alley.
Bats are like my favorite animal. We did
we did a tour and we like competed
against each other and each picked an
animal and Nick the bats
on specific animal. Did you see him
spread his wings? No, I was blinking. He
looked like [ __ ] Robert Patson in
there. Okay, let me go. Oscar. Yes,
Oscar from Fortnite. You have to get his
frenzy auto brother. Oh, hello. Here is
big brother. This is I believe our male
rail. Yeah, he looks like a statue. And
if we kept walking, we wouldn't even
know me. He's just like the Fortnite
skin. He does. Fortnite.
It's crazy how like tigers are like the
most intimidating looking animal in my
opinion. Really? Oh, yeah. Yeah. Like
this dude looks like he's just going to
attack. Yeah. Especially because look at
his face. His head looks so much bigger
because of that. It's kind of like a
beard. It's a facial rough. He has all
around his head in a big circle. He
looks a lot more formidable. So he if he
encounters another tiger, he's gonna
look more powerful. Earlier I was
mentioning their feet, right? They have
suction cup feet. That's going to enable
them to go up these incredible steep
rocky uh cliffs like literally nothing.
I can't even walk in a straight line. I
know.
That's insanity. These are all females
that we hope are pregnant right now. Uh
our male Diablo got to come out here and
um she looked it up. Diablo.
Hello. Diablo came out here and
never mind. He was a great
conservationist, one would say. Yes, he
helped a lot. He helped a lot to save
his species. He had a great time.
But here's actually what the male horns
look like through the years. That's
crazy. So, you can see as just a young
animal all the way up to a fully grown
ram at about 10 years old. It's a word.
Do you want to explain the rarity of a
platypusy?
You mean a platypus? I can explain the I
meant to say platypus. I didn't even
mean to be funny there. That just funny.
No, cuz you said it so casually. Do you
want to explain the meaning of a
platypusy? This is [ __ ] crazy. This
is the craziest fact I've ever learned
in my entire life. There's only two
platypus in this entire world that are
not in Australia. And they were both in
that [ __ ] enclosure at the San Diego
Safari Park. And we met them. No, we met
one of them. We met them. What was his
name? I don't know. Julius. No, that was
a snake. That was the snake. Julius.
Julius Squeezer.
That was the snake. Cuz he's a Cuz he
he's a constrictor snake. Squeezer. Get
it? Oh my god. What are you doing? I
think of Harry the Platypus from Every
Time, right? Me too. Frozen. Yeah.
Superb.
[Music]
I have grown. I think platypus might be
in my top three favorite animal. I'm not
so cute.
[Music]
opportunity
to walk inside. I love platypuses
so much.
S'more time. S'mor time. What was that?
Popcorn. Popcorn.
Something about me is I'm the best
s'more cooker around. Just saying. I
take pride in my s'mores. I used to grow
up in Cape Cod making s'mores.
Vermont, Maine.
Such a New England activity to roast a
s'more with your friends. I'm not even
close to the fire. Hands are nice and
cool. The most mids'more maker I've ever
seen in my [ __ ] life. Golden brown
delighteness.
[Music]
Nick, are you serious? Stop squeezing
it. When we were like 11 years old, Nick
hit Matt with a flaming marshmallow and
it stuck to his face and he had to go to
the doctor. That's crazy. Fun fact.
I'm feeling literally amazing. This is
like a dream to me. Mhm. Like actually,
I'm going to drop a bag on my honeymoon.
It just be me and my wife looking at the
zoo animals. Okay, so one of the things
that we did while we were at the safari
park, but we didn't vlog was the night
vision safari only because we don't have
a night vision camera. Yeah, obviously.
Which I do have. I just didn't bring.
It's in my room. Rats. Rats. Should have
brought it. Anyways, we're going to sing
you a little song while we insert photos
from our night vision. I'm not singing
anything. I'm not singing anything. All
right, we'll insert music. But here are
some photos from our night vision
experience.
Reveal yourself.
Guys, this is like the scariest bathroom
walk ever. Get down to it. Get down to
it. The lighting is kind of mid. I bet
you the tap water here kind of gross.
Like it's probably like mongoose
infested. You don't even know what a
mongoose is.
I'm going to stand here and watch guards
that we're not all [ __ ] at the same
time. Dude, brushing your teeth at the
zoo is a very difficult. It's not even
difficult. It's just like, how do I spin
this? Triple tap the right side.
Whoa.
I never I never thought I'd do this in
my life. Good morning, campers. This is
your wakeup call.
Breakfast is served at 7 a.m. Please
have your personal items packed up. You
can leave those items right inside your
tent door as to avoid them getting wet.
Good morning world. Good morning
friends. We're going to get ready for
today. Yeah, we just got wake up call at
the zoo. Literally, we woke up. She's
like, "Good morning." Me starting a
podcast. She said, "Good morning,
campers." And I instantly thought I was
on camera. No, legit. I was like,
"Hello, podcast."
Hi. Good morning, campers.
We unzipped this. We could see an
elephant. Don't unzip it. I need to
change my underwear. Okay, I'll zip it
back up. Dramatic [ __ ] Move out of my
way. Oh my goodness. Get out of the way,
man. The animals at the zoo are
experiencing aggression this morning. No
elephants. It was
no elephants. No elephants. I fell
asleep pretty early. No, it took me a
while. I lied. They gave us these
bracelets yesterday.
Oh my god. Found out today. I can't
sleep with them. It's like one of those
sensory things. I was like rubbing my
arm. I I ripped it off in the middle of
the night. I was like I was freeing
myself from shackles. I ripped it off my
body. I said, "Free me." I think the
first thing we do today is like get real
up close with an animal. Let's find out.
Well, Nick, how do you lose your
toothbrush the bathroom toothbrush?
Asking how do you lose [ __ ] If everyone
knew how they lost [ __ ] do you want to
know what happened in this world? No one
would lose [ __ ] Thank you, Matt. Well,
it's just like too frequently that
you're losing stuff. I think
this kid's using a [ __ ]
finger to brush his teeth. How gross.
People are going to blame me for that.
Sure not, Nick. You got to do what you
got to do. And you're glamping.
Yes.
I woke up like this. Wait, where'd you
get that cool shirt, Nick? Still.com.
No. Um,.com.
Whoa.
It makes you really look cool in your
outfit fully. I woke up like this.
Flawless. I woke up like this. Flawless.
Okay, dude. I woke up. All right. All
right. You're freaking everyone. You
keep making me think that there's
someone that I'm recording you. Well,
cuz you're saying, "All right. All
right." Like as if like there's a crowd.
Well, it's just like, "All right, settle
down. Let me take you out. Go." I can't
believe we woke up at the [ __ ] zoo. I
thought I was in the psych ward. Like I
woke up and I'm like, "No way. I'm
actually with animals in the zoo today."
I thought this was a dream. What are we
hoping that's on the breakfast menu
here? Um I'll just be happy to see bacon
and apple juice. Honestly, I could use a
cup of OJ right now. Big time. There's
not much sugar left. Chris had the whole
[ __ ] cane yesterday during breakfast.
During dinner,
drank every last bit of iced tea and
used every [ __ ] sugar pal. Nick, try
those.
I don't know. I don't know. But this
bacon looks good as [ __ ] Get that
bacon, buddy. All right.
How many days out of a week, Nick, do
you think you could survive out here? 10
million. I could live the rest of my
life here. I guarantee myself. This
isn't like crazy conditions. It's
breakfast. Cold. I'm just cold. No, I am
genuinely like
I I wish I could spend the rest of my
life here. Would you guys not even grab
breakfast? Breakfast with a with a view.
What do you mean? I got some potatoes. I
got this. I'm going to try that [ __ ]
little fritter. I'm going to I'm going
to go for everything. It's I'm going to
have to do a rewalk up for sure. I just
can't believe we are where we are. Look
it. Wow. Look out there.
It's just unbelievable. Is it crazy? And
here we are. This is perfect. Good
morning, world. I'm going to skate the
safari today. I think this will be the
best view I have eating breakfast for at
least the next 8 months. Yeah. Unless
Nick wakes up, gets all Nick wakes up
and gets all pretty in a couple
wedding and the elephant can be like the
officiator. No [ __ ] can't. No, he
can't. How is he going to say what he
needs to say? No, he can't. No, he
can't. has the No, he doesn't. No, he
doesn't. That's a good elephant
impression, that dude. Get He's in the
trunk, too. Uh-huh. How's your coffee?
Didn't try it yet. Sugarless cuz of this
idiot. Sugar, dude. He was dumping like
sugar packets in the thing. I was like,
"You need to go to bed tonight." Yeah, I
took a sweet tea to my room, but went
crazy. Go to bed, dude. It's like 2:00
a.m. We're all getting in bed and he's
like, "Dump. You're sugar wrestling in
the corner of the room." Like, what are
you doing over there? It's like a kid on
Christmas snooping in their kiss.
[Laughter]
Thank you.
Nice. You're not real. Breakfast. What
was that? Two Advil in a Yeah. I don't
even have a headache yet. I just know
that's coming. Yeah. I have a headache
every morning.
Elephant be your neck up there. Up here.
Oh, Chris always says that a fun fact
that he loves, but I don't even know if
he's right or not, but he likes that
what is it? Baby elephants like can't
control their trunk. That is true. It
takes them 5 years to figure it out. Oh
my god. So, our friends just figured it
out. Yeah, they just figured it out.
That's crazy. Yeah, Chris always like
he'll randomly tell me that. I'm like I
don't know how true that is, but that is
very true. Very true. Wow. So, wherever
he got your information, it's accurate.
Amazing. Good to know. Now I can say it
fully and yeah, proudly. I like tell
people that all the time. How big is a
baby elephant born? So, they're usually
born between 200 and 250 lbs. Wow. Uh,
their moms are pregnant for about 22
months. Wa. 20 to 22 months is the
average. So, they're pregnant for almost
2 years. That's crazy. I I just started
saying I'm two right when I'm born. If I
was like, I'm two. That's so long.
You're My god, Nick, you are two baby
elephants. Two of you is one baby
elephant. Isn't that crazy? What do you
mean? They're 300 lb or or 200 300. Was
that true? At birth. Yeah. Was an extra
big baby. She was born at 281 lb. The
largest calf ever born here at the
Safari Park. Wow. Damn.
That's crazy. She was born early, too.
Yeah. It's literally you twice is how
big shows. I'll say like two and a two
and a third. Two and a half. Maybe.
Yeah, I will. I'll give you some wiggle
room. Just maybe. Yeah. Never. I'd never
want to think about my weight being that
close to an elephant ever again. Baby,
baby, baby, baby.
They don't even know they're drunk yet.
Both around 4,000 lb. Oh my god. I'm not
there.
Hello.
She must be sick of us. I just saw us
all yesterday. Oh, there's the third.
Hello. Big yawn.
Big yawn. Good morning. Oh my goodness.
That's insane.
Just the sheer strength of a lion scares
me to think about. Like, oh my god.
Looking at the view. That was crazy. And
she was right here. I was like, "Hello.
I hope this glass is strong so you don't
eat and kill me." Did you see the marks
on the glass? Oh. Uh, yeah. Like the Oh
my god. Yeah,
I'm good. Wear and tear, baby. One day
that thing's going to bust open. Hello,
Nick. Nick, what are you pushing?
Pressure testing. Pressure. Hey, like,
let's not do this [ __ ] It's inch
thick acrylic. So, wow. See, Chris,
yeah, this isn't going to do anything.
They're [ __ ] Don't disturb them is
what I'm saying. You don't tap a fish
tank. You know what I mean? I didn't tap
it. I was like, "All right. All right.
Stop leaning on it." That was a lion.
The last thing I'd want is you banging
on my glass. Shh. I didn't bang on it.
Didn't bang on it. Hearing the smell of
the predators over Eurasian eagle owl.
Eurasian eagle owls are found in Europe,
Asia. Females are larger. It makes a lot
of sense. Think about they're the ones
that lay the eggs. They're the ones that
stay at the nest site. Things like that.
You all are very strong guys. Well, we
used to all work at a grocery store and
when you said I just think of like a
quarter pound of cheese and I like used
to like hold that and I'd be like,
"Wow." Like that. It's heavy. Like 12
times is how much the owl is crazy. Go
dig.
So, she's going to do what's called a
digging behavior. She's got to find
those meal worms. Exactly what we want
her to do. And that's a natural behavior
for baby foxes. They will dig dig dig
dig dig. And they're inseexctovores
somewhat. They're also carnivores as
well, too. But in comparison to other
canids, they actually have an extra set
of mers in their mouth, giving them the
ability to really break down those
exoskeletons
because when mama fox goes back to the
den and has to regurgitate all that
yummy food to those um kits, you know,
the the baby foxes, they need nutrients.
So, African porcupine. You guys ever
seen a North America?
Yeah, this is crazy.
Super huge, right? Uhhuh. Oh my god. So,
one of the things about Harley is that
you'll notice that she has very small
eyes. She's got There you go. There you
go. She has very small Oh, like um they
look like rodents. Rodents. Exactly. So
the rodents, this is the rodent family.
You ever taken any of those signs and
the quills are sharp and the black and
white is a signal is a myth. They cannot
physically shoot quills out of their
body. It would be like me shooting
eyebrows out of my head. You know what I
mean? It's just not physically possible
for them. But it'll come out like if you
get your sunglasses stuck in your hair
and you pull your sungl out of your head
in that capacity. Well, if my hand goes
here, the quil sticks in my hand and I
go out, then you've got an infection.
It's like a splinter. If you leave it in
there too long and it's a real dirty
splinter, you're going to get like Zuri
is this cat's name. Means beautiful in
Swahili. Um right now Zuri is going to
do some fishing right now incredibly
well. She's under great medical care
here at this Flashstone.
Um it's warm water at least. Um but we
actually do blood pressure with her now.
10 to 15 years, but you can tell she's
still moving around incredibly well.
Unlike a cheetah, cheetahs have spots
only. She has spots and stripes. So
those spots and stripes make them really
unique in that capacity.
He is huge. So Aaron came over to help
as well too. People think it's Oh, this
is a great pet. Yeah. They bring in
their home and then it gets this big and
they don't have the space for it. He
sticks it out, senses the environment,
brings it back into that Jacobson's
organ, which are those two pits in the
roof of his mouth, and it allows him to
decide, do I need to go left? Do I need
to go right? Um, and then he also I do
this with some people, and I their hands
go down like that, you know. So, I want
to make sure that you have a good
support.
So, we're going to put him up here. I
call tail end.
And put your hands out again. There you
go. You're going to be a little dirty
after that, though. No problem. And are
you good? Oh, he's going down. He's
going to I'm holding him as he's moving.
Okay, put your hands. Put your hands
flat. Come on. There we go. Put your
hands flat.
He moved that part of him right there.
He's sort of wiggling. There you go. Do
you want to check those roads first,
though? Yeah, we can check the roads.
All right, cool. You guys are kind of on
an adventure, but we're checking roads
for our leads for the rest of the day.
So, you get all the fun safaries rest.
I'll share my opinion on that. I'll let
you guys know. My very professional
opinion.
We've got my favorite girl in the town
who's standing up right here on the left
side of the truck. She's got the lobster
clash horns. Hi, pretty girl. Oh, she's
so cute. Isn't she adorable?
Have you guys been this close to its
before? I don't think so. No, definitely
not actually. Truly prehistoric. Hi,
pretty girl. You going to come say hi?
Hi, Andrew.
Um, get her glamour shot for me, please.
So cute. They're kind of like a baby
elephant. Like the face. Like just the
face. Uhhuh. They got kind of those Oh,
she's closing their eyes. I have never
seen her do this before. Oh my goodness.
This is crazy. Hi. They kind of look
like big anteaters. Like their their
face.
Now over here we have a sleepy
20-year-old boy.
Suck around. Get some tired. Did you
just say suck around, Nick? I stuttered.
I woke up two seconds ago. Okay. Nick
woke up. Say hi. Chris wanted to do the
prank where like we scream and I was
like, "No, I don't." Yeah. Where we like
record you and go, "Ah, you should have
done it." We're a person away from 6
mil. Go subscribe. I'm already Hold on.
Hold on. Cuz if it goes If it goes It
could go down. If it We got to get to
like 610 and then it's good. Cuz watch.
It's going to go down. What? Who Who
would do such a thing? That's
Hold on. We're too close for comfort.
603. Oh my god. Triplets. Okay. You made
that joke last time. Okay. I feel
comfortable now. Celebrate. Okay.
Celebrate. Kiss. Kiss. Kiss. Kiss. Kiss.
Get away from me. They felt le.
How crazy is that? Let's get your
reaction. Wait. Pretend like we just did
it when I turn the camera to you. Ready?
Six mill.
Okay. All right.
I got it. I got it. I got it. Hold on.
Let me take a photo of it.
Who would have thought? Who would have
dunk it? Who would have thought it? Who
would have thought it? This is why you
have like 900 stitches. And I like the
hand like that. That's really like
bleed. Like he's like calm. Very nice. I
like the hand.
That was a good cut, Matt. So like Do it
again. Do the hand again.
I loved it. I've never seen something
like it, right? It's like a like a
peaceful cut. That's like beautiful.
Watch this. That's art. Watch this. You
guys
No one's like you. However much cake is
here, I'll cut it. Okay. Speech from
Mary Lou. She had something to say. No,
I just What do you say? What do you say
boys? Jimmy, what do you say? Let's
shoot for seven. Here
we go. Here we go. Seven. I can't
believe we held that [ __ ] snake. Do
the Do your best bat impression. No, I
can't do that. I can't believe.
That's kind of what it sound like.
[Applause]
No. Accurate. No, that was good. That
was all right. Thank you. like a um
like like it like loud like I'm not
participating in this. You sound like
you sound like the owl at the end. Oh
no, the owl. That's that's what the owl
like. Remember the owl?
That's a chicken. That's a chicken.
Yeah, that's chicken. What you had
before?
What animal did you see that you just
wanted to become that moment? Oh god.
Like I wanted to just be a tiger. The
second I saw him lurking. I was like,
"Oh my god, I'd do anything." What about
you? Um, I was good. I didn't want to
be. Yeah, I was done. You didn't feel
that once? No, not once did I feel like
I wanted to be one of these animals.
What about like
how about the turtle named Flapjack? And
he's a pancake turtle. What? The
pancake. Oh, I forgot about that idiot.
Flapjack. He was so dumb.
Flapjack. It was so pancake turtle. He
was cute though. Like call me human
then. You know what? What are you
talking about? Like I don't know. It's
just a lame name. It's not creative.
Thank you guys so much for 6 million
subscribers. We wouldn't have gone to
zoo without you. So thank you so very
much. Thank you guys so much for
watching this video. Thank you so much
again for 6 million subscribers. We had
so much fun filming that video. If you
like videos like this, we want to start
doing more elaborate videos, but
obviously it made us miss the Wednesday.
So let us know what you think about
that. That little combo crossover video.
We might also just start doing car
videos on Fridays. Whatever. We'll
figure out a schedule. Who knows what
the but we're just having fun right now.
That's it. That's that's that's the goal
in it all, isn't it? Day and that's what
you guys should be doing as well. Go
have fun. And also, while you're having
fun, go also shop for Sternolo Clothing
merch at sternalo.com.
Subscribe down below. Now that we've hit
6 million subscribers, we're on the road
to 7 million people. All of our 6
million merch is now available right
now. Six mill merch is never coming back
again after it's sold out. Fair to say
it is gone forever once it's gone. Also,
we're going to put a signed postcard by
all three triplets in each order for
every single 6 mill purchase. My hand is
hurting. This is what Matt is signing
basically. Yeah, we've been signing a
ton of cards nontop. Everyone say
something really awkward to the camera.
Like, you're really going to go out
wearing that?
What? I think it was funny. I don't know
what to say. Something like that. Oh,
let's do oddly specific. Yeah. If you
watch this Safari video wearing merch
from our 2 mill drop, you're awesome.
Oh, I like that. Okay. If you watch this
video with two drinks to the right of
you on your nightstand while in bed,
give yourself a high five and grab a
third drink. If you watch this video on
your couch and it was on the TV and
you're with a loved one or two, give
them a hug. Ah, I love that. That was
awesome. Thank you guys again for 6
million subscribers. That's like 6
million people.
Release the bats.
[Music]