all right guys thank you so much first
and foremost for 7 million
subscribers I feel like that's the
perfect audible
reaction I
personally cannot believe it we need we
need to commit our sin we have to burn
something down 7 million 7 million
people watching our videos makes me want
to violently puke and scream and
diarrhea at the same time because it's
just like it's like an insane
unfathomable number of people wait a
second I think we finally have beaten
the population of Massachusetts don't
even [ __ ] say that my presence near
me or by my side yeah 6.9 million we
have more subscribers than the
population of the state we were RoR
in I'm like sick wait my stomach hurts
really bad I'm a little disg isn't that
a crazy statistic not no not a lot of
people can say that but no guys it's
like insane when I think about it
because me man and Chris have been
filming some sort of YouTube video or
Internet content since we were literally
infant babies and being triplets going
out and like getting recognized by
people just for being triplets our
entire life like people were always
amazed by that so the fact that kind of
like I know it sounds like ridiculous
cuz it's not like we're really like
bringing something to the table in terms
of like it being a thing but like our
triplet Hood allowing us to portray
ourselves on such a massive
platform is most mindblowing experience
ever cuz it's something we've always
kind of been chipping away at and it's
just it just continues to amaze me that
there's people that genuinely sit and
take time out of their day in the one
life they live to watch me speak yeah
it's not real me personally do that for
you you know it's crazy cuz our career
is built off of the fact that you do do
that you do sit and listen to me speak
and it's gained milon subscribers so
you're a [ __ ] idiot true that is true
um but yeah I I
feel
gratitude I feel in magnitude oh yeah
gratitude and magnitude that's vctor
completely oh yeah don't touch you you
let me make sure mine are these we're in
the car and we have a fun 7 million
subscriber celebration that we endured
and we're going to be popping in and out
to explain things that we experienced
and we're going to talk about it and
we're going to have
fun you're so
Weir like I hear I hear the beep that
you're recording and I look and you're
like like you're a [ __ ] weird where
are we going today horse back
riding Matt where are we going we're
going to go ride horses yay horsey um
yeah you know what time it is you know
what time it is I don't come to [ __ ]
around he don't come to [ __ ] around yeah
ride we're absolutely not doing that
abely not dude we have to get high ride
till I can no more that song is horeshit
no it's not
Matt oh oh that dog was so cute did you
see that dog look at him Vlog it Vlog it
look at how cute he
is cute
dog [ __ ] look like a weirdo oh my God
oh my God oh my God ah he was so kiddy
why are we going horseback riding cuz
I'm a
cowboy no oh look at him he's so cute
did you see him yeah we're going
horseback riding because we hit seven
resilon gabillion followers sub that's
like 7 million people
nerd you're a [ __ ] fat idiot you're a
[ __ ] all right guys basically when we
get there me man Nick are going to race
on the horses no we're not yes we are
I'm going to kick the [ __ ] out of my
horse with the Spurs I'm going to go
kacha kacha they're not going to give
you Spurs you're not riding in a derby I
literally never thought I'd be on a
horse ever in my life for some reason I
I knew it would happen I L I have zero
desire to do
this I don't really want to all I no
being honest I i' I've never had like
motivation to go on a horse oh no wait
they better not give us those helmets oh
guys we're going to have the helmets on
I'm not putting a helmet on I'm dead
serious I'm not doing you have to you
have to put not putting a helmet I'm not
putting a helmet on yes you are I'd
rather snap my neck you're going to have
to put you're going to have to put like
that goofy helmet on IEX sign as many
waivers as they want I'm not signing I'm
not I'm not putting a helmet on if I die
cuz I don't want to wear a helmet you
are not to blame sign on the dot Chris
stolo no we're going to have to wear
those goofy there's like horses here I
don't know say that again I don't know
there's like horses around like it's
crazy guys we literally like we got up a
little Street and there's like stables
and cacti and white fence so there was
literally a street called stable Bow
Street I'm so excited I'm like you have
done no like mentally oh mad what no you
swerved the car didn't my hands I think
I just turned in the curve in the road
like guys I can't believe I'm about to
like see a horse you're about to be on a
horse I don't I kind of don't want to do
it of course you're doing it I don't
know I feel like people that know how to
ride a horse like are really judgmental
about people who can't you know like I
feel like that's like good thing like if
it's like if I know how to ride a bike
and you don't like I'm going to make fun
of you I like can't believe my eyes
there's a horse right there turn the
camera what's going on there's horses
everywhere really freaked out by like
don't be freaked out freaked out is
crazy just try your best I want the
tallest horse right away put me on the
biggest one I was meant to do this one
of them just hit like the classic nay it
was pretty fire no one of guys you would
she was walking this one back to
whatever this is called and you could
hear really nervous dude I don't know
why don't be nervous Chris hello so I'm
Emily this is co we're going to be your
guides today thanks for coming thank you
for having us yeah he's a little nervous
yeah I I don't know why I was like he's
a
nous for you okay amazing amazing who's
the bossiest Nick yeah he's really the
boss perfect we have a bossy horse for
you great do you have a shy horse for
Matt yeah is there one like filled with
anxiety scared to do anything okay guys
so basically M man and Chris pulled up
to this place and we were going
horseback riding and we were filling out
the paperwork and Chris is looking me
dead in the eyes the entire time and
asking me what to fill out the questions
are like what's your phone number what's
your name how did you get here emergency
contact and I'm
like how are you the level of brain dead
that you are that you're asking me
personal questions what would you do no
when he asked you what should I put here
and it was what's your like House
address I was like I was like Chris our
address like okay listen to me the lady
went up to Nick and she said this is how
you fill out the waiver and then she
walked away and it was Nick's
responsibility to give me a waiver and
show me how to fill it out
self-explanatory no it's not he gave me
he gave me the packet of 90 wavers
packet of 90 waivers and I I I ended up
filling out like three waivers yeah he
writes his name three times that's a
little on three different papers he's
flipping papers and it's the exact same
thing every time and he keeps putting
it's like phone number name last name
Chris sternol signing a contracto phone
number over and over and over I've like
never thought I'd be on a horse in my
life so oh yeah now I'm
here exactly to flip this page and then
sign the backside too then you guys
don't want helmets or you do we don't if
we don't have to how are you signing
this it's the front I'm putting all my
information you know it's personal to
you like your name I hereby declare that
I am physically fit yep oh my weight I
declare that I am happens to you and I
get everything
you easy just yeah perfect your initials
here Nick
yep Nick what is this oh no I'm not
pregnant I don't have to Circle that
just doesn't
matter just write your name Chris I'm
Nick you're the you're Nick and you're
the one that said bossy yes I'm giving
you rusty rusty rusty Nick and Rusty
you're going to have cupcake cupcake I
love for
you middle name is Ben it's Bernard yeah
it's like it's like it's like a variant
of it BT and Matt Chris and cupcake Nick
and CH and cupcake that's like Chris and
cupcake is good yeah Chris you arear a
cupcake okay what do I do cup it are you
able to ride a horse
oh he keeps asking me questions like
Nick what's the answer it's like phone
number like that's yours your name hold
hold on C has the perfect name I was
going to say is that this got to be a
nickname the guy here his name
cult what's my medical insurance you
don't need to put that she just she said
you don't for that put your parent guard
and they put like put give me this Jesus
Christ wait I want something like horse
related I don't know yeah they like a
little merch shop yeah like I'm want a
cowboy you want to know who does wait I
think the St tripet are dropping like um
like Western team 7 milon mer that's
perfect for this occasion I agree yeah
that's what it is I was confused for a
second but make S let go oh guys okay
now you get to keep this that you messed
up in your pocket all
day not did you hear that that was I
heard that that was classic it's not a
horse named cupcake like I couldn't have
panned out better for you like Chris no
helmets are you happy about that thank
God you just have to sign away that
you're going to be fine guys I want to
have a broke Back Mountain moment today
what do that even mean they gay you your
back broke they were gay they were gay
people they were I was joking cuz I knew
you might get it yeah but they're not
going to get it watch the
movie I'm I call dims not going on a
horse first by the way hey guys hey wait
can you try to guess which one's which
first oh sure that's fun I'll decide who
okay wait who do you guys think this is
that's got to
be I have no guess Chris Rusty is it
Rusty nope that's that's cupcake it's
cupcake First cupcake Chris you didn't
identify wait I don't want to go first
can we not have cupcake yet no Chris you
you can go he can go first no I don't
want to go first I swear you can grow up
I agre yes that's us good idea Nick you
go first Nick I think you could totally
go first we'll grab Ben first wait so is
your name your real name or is that a
nickname for nickname I love it got to
be yeah I love it I was going to say
Colt's too perfect to be doing this Nick
you look like you're like going in
office right now like you don't look
like you're about to ride a horse yes I
do no you don't yeah I do no you
don't it looks like you're like going to
work look I'm going to work at riding
these horses Nick yes can you please
stop horsing around you're not funny bro
not funny at all did everybody just hold
their horses for
you everybody hold their horses another
joke do on Matt thanks Matt you got to
think of a horse joke
um HHO bless you that was a good
one that was terrible that was a really
good wait Matt you have to think of one
she's like I never heard that one yet
cuz it's terrible it was good it was
good
hey Rusty all right Nick be careful I'm
going to be as careful as can be got it
oh Rusty's really cute Rusty all right
like I'm getting in a car what
what open the door there you go that was
so that was the easiest thing ever
wait Rusty you're on a horse I'm on
Rusty this is insane this is the
craziest thing
horse they don't feel real till you're
on them then you're like whoa then it's
like yeah I'm on a living this a
creature it's alive wait he's so awesome
I love I can't wait for you to meet
cupcake nothing like getting in a car by
the way nothing like it I could imagine
nothing how fast are you going to go
you're going to hit that's not up to
me his left right is right back is stop
and just keep your hand down when he's
walking or standing this hand can hold
the saddle if you want okay and then
he's going to demonstrate all right so
squeeze your heels together into belly
bring him forward there you go want to
stop and you pull back belly button
perfect oh and he stopped so gracefully
once he stops you just relax your arm
down again got thank that was so good I
don't know if I should there you go
compliment you or Rusty I feel like
Rusty was Rusty it was all rusty he's
he's a great listener wow Matt you are
on a horse I know you're doing how's Ben
Ben is good you kind of look like Ben
like it adds up and Chris looks like
cupcake got it right yep Chris my turn
got it chis cupcake I'm excited come on
cupc Chris I was telling I was telling
him I feel bad for Rusty he's I'm
sitting on Rusty right now look at Rusty
and Ben they're going to kiss Rusty and
Ben Matt how's Ben Ben is great right
now they're so calm and TR the leader of
the pack yeah no way the leader actually
yep he likes being up front so he's not
fil hit by the tail I kind of rather be
in the back with cupcake to be Hest
cupcake is chilling just like want to
say Yeehaw like really bad it's like
eating me
alive what's your opinions on the Texas
Roadhouse I love it I love the Texas
Roadhouse that's where I feel like I am
I just like pet my yeah I feel like you
have to eat a cupcake in honor of
cupcake I will I most definitely I'm
literally eating Matt's
[Laughter]
dust Nick Nick that's awesome are you a
righty driver or a lefty driver I don't
know how I'm driving this thing it's
just happening I'm a lefty driver
decisions gotcha Matt Lefty driver right
holder yeah that's what I'm at right now
I like don't think I could imagine doing
this at like a faster Pace than like 5
miles hour I know imagine running on a
horse imagine doing this at like running
mes hour that the most unbelievable
thing wait what's the max that a horse
can
go 55 wow that was a solid guess for me
55 milph bring me to the Kentucky Derby
after this I need no more practice wait
what Matt what I need people betting on
me quick it's a very intimate experience
I feel like I've known Rusty my whole
life I know will say it's nothing like
those um horses with like the the stick
that you like hold between your legs
nothing like
that yeah this is the real thing how's
how are you
cupcake what a crazy
joke oh away
pull away Matt go to Left gotcha what's
his
name Ben it's not time to eat just like
me he's like it is time to eat Ben Ben
saw an opportunity and he took it Ben
said yeah and Ben are one in the same
you say you felt like the polo logo yeah
that's insane I just just call me Ral
Floren for the rest of the day man you
are Matt you got to tell Ben to go green
light Ben that I tell people huh when
you Ki what you want to hear for huh you
heard that got yes sir you can kick him
go there you go yeah man all right
awesome come on Ben come now there you
gooy mat pretend it's Chris shorten your
rains on cupcake
Chris this way cupcake Matt yeah tell
Ben to go come on Ben how's cupcake
Chris so good wow that butterfly flying
by just felt like a movie like I feel
like a character
Nick how insane would it be if there was
like a sternol a triplet fan that just
met us all on a horse like
imagine confus someone drive by like oh
I love your videos we're all just
arguably the most confusing experience
ever for yeah that'd be insane it's like
very out of character I feel oh Rusty's
beaten up past Ben this is bring me to
the derby Chris this feels illegal cuz
you don't have licenses I know Rusty if
we get pulled over you're showing
ID listen to
that yeah at Le at least there's no
grass for Ben to eating the
RO Ben's not it's a pretty straight shot
where Milkman and cars are on horses
question of the day definitely cars
imagine doing this at night really fast
with a lantern in
hand that's what I'm envisioning whoa
Ben cut me
off should I get Road Rage or what the
[ __ ] you look so good on a horse like I
never thought you'd look this great what
I knew it I foresaw
I don't know why I just looked back
expecting to see like 10 more horses
kick them dude I'm
like I've never practice my inward kicks
so they're so they're not good today
yeah thank you nice work Rusty Chris did
you know it's good did cupcake and Ben
just have a moment I think cupcake and
Ben just kissed each other cupcake and
Ben just fought a little bit
guys um if you noticed us while we were
riding horses thank you so much for not
leaking that we were filming this video
M and Chris were on the horses and as
you just saw or you're about to see we
were in the middle of the street on the
hor my horse was like blocking traffic
for it was insane and then these two
girls were in their car and they were
like smiling and waving and like taking
photos and I was like oh my God guys
like our our like we filmed we filmed
this early so that because we
anticipated hitting 7 million
subscribers we wanted to make make sure
we could film the video in time so we
were just so thankful that no one posted
that we did this because we were like oh
my God our entire plan for like
celebrating 7 mil ruin is like going to
be told to the internet and then while
we were on the horses we were going
through a park and some kid was like
asking us to take a photo with him and
we were like I was like a like I can't
really do anything about it so I'm just
happy that whoever we saw didn't post
about it but it was so wild I just think
of how funny would it be if we just
opened our phone and there was no
explanation at all and there was just a
photo of us on horses like in the street
unbelievable I think people would
actually think we've lost our mind I
don't think they'd believe it at all age
they'd be like what is actually
happening seriously guys I think that
Ben has made it very easy for me to
learn he's giving me a little obstacles
you know learning to kick learning to I
can't believe the first time I got on a
horse I was granted immediate Street
access right I also can't I've never
been the competitive type but being on a
horse near you guys I just want to like
I need to enter a race tomorrow that
show never been one to sports bet either
but tomorrow I'm putting all my money on
a on a horse that looks like cupcake hey
no cupcake no eating grass Nick's Rusty
cuz you were slowing down I didn't want
Rusty to pass come on you know yep it's
because I'm an elite horse rider now we
used to ride around on horses and now
cars have horsepower if you ever think
of
that wonder where they is that deep
that's like that's like now imagine
pulling a chariot as well oh my god with
the royal family in the back imagine
being a police officer we filmed car
videos and our car was moving by a horse
and we were like in the back like
talking you hear the Galloping that's
insane I can't believe you guys drove a
horse on the road before a car what' you
say you guys drove a horse on the road
before a car I know this is
extravagant
extravagant yes spell it no let try no
come on nope an attempt no extra gav try
extra Gavin no Chris come on no cupcake
extra bues Nick Chris come shut up it'll
be a fun little task while you're on the
horse oh I love those chips Chris
seriously Matt what are the odds that we
had our favorite Dorito in the bush
Chris are you unwilling to diey shut up
e me and
Ben oh my God this cupc do that do that
I love a nay that sounded the whoever
spelled out nay was dead on I feel
really cool I feel like it's my birthday
at the Texas Roadhouse right
now we're going good no come
on come on Ben is hungry man he's
starving dude never believe how much
grass I ate
today I thought that was low hanging
fruit for com you just say that I said I
thought that leaf was low hanging fruit
for cupcake dude what does that even
mean means it was low hanging fruit Matt
focus on getting Ben to move forward got
Ben we're good hey guys we're
interrupting this video for a quick
minute because we want to tell you that
our 7 million merch is available right
now with the link in the description or
the link on the screen so go shop 7
million merchandise before it is gone
forever and enjoy the rest of today's
video I'm going to tell this Amazon
deliverer to give me five packages give
me five of those I'll help you out yeah
I'll slow your load for the day I'll
help you out I'll bring five horse five
packages via horse whoa cupcake you're
picking up
speed Nick why did the horse go across
the road to get to the other
side what do you have a punch line or no
no I just I just felt like it needed to
be said wow this is downhill Ben
yeah keep
going wow cupcake good
job Chris you're impressed by cupcake
just such a good horse I love cupcake
I want an edit of me and cupcake like in
our relationship that's crazy cupc
you're such a good horse dude look at
all this horeshit Chris yeah Matt crazy
their path AR
M&M thank you
guys your guys horses look pretty crazy
too get it I get it the
bike they didn't get it Nick no they
didn't get it it's okay Ben's having a f
day with what we're walking through
right now he's he's like fighting the
herge inside of him it's like must eat
bushes come
on cute little flowers must eat dud he's
so mad I literally think cupcake just
looked both ways Nick you said what I
literally think cupcake just looked both
ways could what looked both
ways I'm de street I'm dead serious
Chris maybe we run through canes yeah
yeah I'm
done get a little canac combo yeah real
quick just eat it in the car imagine
going through a drive dve through with
this thing welcome to the joke Matt that
was that that just would be so funny
welcome to the joke no cuz I heard thing
I've ever heard I just heard bless you
rusty rusty good sneeze it's like that
that'll be that'll be 1297 at the next
window this whole time I've been trying
to mentally figure out the name of
Woody's horse or Jesse's horse in Toy
Story um what's his name [ __ ] who the
the horse and Toy Story um bullseye
bullseye bullseye uh I'll do three
chicken fingers Ben will do nine was the
in heaven you had any dandelion back
there take the 95 home I said welcome to
the freeway cupcake yeah
literally next time I'm going to fight
with someone I'm bringing Rusty I'm
riding into the fight with on a
horse come on Ben I that's I recorded it
come on Ben this is so oh he's pooping
yeah oh my bad Ben I he didn't he didn't
break a stride though he really didn't
he I know that's why we were slowing
down was imagine fully taking a [ __ ]
while you're just walking while walking
tough that that's hard I mean all that
fiber they're getting from the dandelion
it's not that hard me and my trusty
Steed take over the night all
right all right all right all right all
right all right wow I feel like me and
memo are like Paul Rivier and his allies
right now or what I don't know when
being side by side with someone else on
a horse is a surreal feeling it's like
where we ated yeah like I know what you
mean though yeah thank you like I fully
understand you know once your you have a
common enemy yes correct I don't know
being side by side on someone with
someone else on a horse it's like a
debrief before the final Sprint yes
exactly Chris I'm getting closer to you
like in my brain Chris what do you
associate horse with cuz I have a fruit
I'm thinking of like a raspberry no a
blueberry God pulls up like this what
you doing for
real Matt [ __ ] at the squad pull up like
this what you doing literally nothing
imagine this is how we entered tour like
this is where we went everywhere just
like on three horses I'm headed to Ralph
I'm getting on Rusty I want to play
baseball at this field Nick I think
Rusty and cupcake are friends I think so
too best friends yes are view from the
top of this godamn mountain
was
unbelievable
unbelievable it was a it was a peak
moment of my life I'd say I agree R just
riding that horse onto that hill in no
phone I felt like a cowboy I felt like I
was going up there to
kill oh my God I'm the rowdiest horse in
the town keep that to yourself but is
that not crazy it's like I felt like a
true pescatarian
that is someone who doesn't eat fish
esquarian I don't know what you're
trying to say what's the word I'm trying
to say esquarian a um esque esquis I
felt like a true pescatarian Nick what
are you saying what's the word what's
equestrian equestrian I feel like a real
equestrian that day it's someone who
rides horses I don't know I would know I
would know cuz I ride horses okay dude
but it was so crazy it was also like me
CH also the we asked we were telling a
friend about our experience Saran I
forget who it was I literally zero idea
so don't ask who who was it I literally
I don't know are youying who the [ __ ]
was it I don't know it's okay and I
forget who which one of you I was with I
was was it and we go oh yeah we went
horseback riding whatever and they go
did you saddle up or ride bear back and
hold the hair who asked who was that
that imagine I don't know who asked that
but I remember this conv that I forget
who was it who get who's like who goes
on a horse for the first time and grabs
That [ __ ] by the M me and you are
trotting today I'm like I felt really
good I felt good my hand I someone asked
me that and I was like is that was that
an option I like Believers
wow like it's just crazy that that's
like a thing like you just get up on
that but you got to think about it
horses and cowboys were a thing before
there was Saddles I it don't this is
what I don't get I feel like I I rode
someone else's horse and what I mean by
that is like watch for your ear deep
water I know I know what I mean by that
is like if I had a horse I would have
such a connection with it it would only
it would only let me ride it I felt I
felt pause felt the
connection horse did I ride I'm happy I
was with Ben you know what I mean I felt
such a connection with my horse you guys
will see at the end of the video I was
oh it was so deep what this is I can't
believe looking to the left and the
right and seeing what I'm seeing in I
feel like I'm becoming a pro horse back
right wow this shows how much I trust
you look where I am I know cupcake look
at
this you know just swinging by on a
horse inside of a hill it is crazy up
here I love it this is insane holy
[ __ ]
oh I am uhoh uhoh oh my
god oh wait they're like babies oh
my oh wow God oh my God at the end we
were we were nearing the end and our
horses pulled up on some skunks it was a
cute little skunk fan it it felt like it
was literally Disney characters it was
there was a tribe of nine skunks running
through the I forget I forget that there
was like six yeah like six no there's
like six I forget that like wild skunks
can actually spray spray me I don't give
a [ __ ] no I was like ready to defend I
don't know how I was going to like I'm
serious I was I your hands are going to
be in my head I was thinking I'm going
to need tomato juice to bathe in after
this and I was serious as we were
passing them I was I'll be fine I was
good I was fully thinking like I'm going
have to B tomato I was ready to have
Rusty stump on the skunks if they were
to come near Pummel their backs into the
ground oh my God no but they were so
cute they were really Ben coming through
oh Ben's taking a piss Victory
P Ben's such a good Ben's so polite he
waited till the
end Ben waited till
later very good I can't believe it Ben
needs some dandelion some leaves he
deserves
it I'm proud of Ben I am too get over
here how uncool was that I just fumbled
the bag could have looked way cooler but
I got my foot
stuck I got my shirt stuck Rusty I Rusty
and I are one and the same my brother
from another mother if you seriously I
feel deeply ected to Rusty I feel like
closer to him than Matt and Chris that's
insane that's insane
twins right all right let's see how this
happens yes I think he did that the best
smooth that was smooth oh no recording
me from behind I'm
sweating bye Rusty bye Rusty I love you
so much that was very fun I love
Rusty I have treats if you guys want yes
more than anything
more than
anything oh wow what oh my God yeah he's
scratching his back so cute here I'm
going to give you the um invention I
forgot it's called the saddle bag saddle
bag right I Googled and I said what are
the best horse
names funny best funny horse names oh I
was going to say I feel like that's very
um opinion based I agree it's not I
Googled I Googled give me a I said give
me a list of some funny horse names if I
were to name a horse just because my
horse sugar cube no that was one of them
listen to how ridiculous these Google
God responses are oh God hoof hearted
hoof hearted yes hoed who parted that's
ridiculous that's dehumanizing to the
horse wind is the second one I don't
like that I don't like that's mean to
the horse they live imagine living one
life and you're a horse and they name
you who's farted no that that wasn't it
who
farted
farted HED harded ho harded yes or
passing wind yes oh I'd Burn the City
down Harry
Trotter I was debating whether I laugh
or if I'm
disgusted it sounds like a bra person
talk about like if like you act two in
the pink is like a real funny Forest
jump I love it that's a good one cuz he
runs I'm just thinking of like which one
of those as like a first name is the
best Forest passing is like you're
naming a horse passing passing that's a
little weird Forest is a good horse name
Forest Matthew Ser G Spot spelled GE e e
s p o g spot yeah terrible main m a n e
attraction I love
it I love that's like if a horse was a
drag get
ready May the horse be with
you that's a real you want who gets a
lot of [ __ ] who Disney adults do you
want to know who needs more [ __ ] people
who say Star Wars adults yeah now they
get weird this back half they get weird
now yes they're not weird already no are
you ready
we the Fox Hat w a r like where where
the Fox Hat where the Fox Hat okay can
you stop reading these cuz I'm in next
next big
tits I like it 50 bales of hay like 50
Cent Maple oh my God I'm a [ __ ] idiot
I'm a [ __ ] idiot it's so obvious the
joke you saying CT oh I like it I like
it a lot that one's good now like like
what okay in all seriousness if you had
a horse what would you name
him um I would name mine Sparky that's a
terrible name okay I'm sorry I don't
name it [ __ ] Bodacious Tata I was
going to go big tit okay no I'm kidding
I would name my horse I'd name my horse
Shaggy that's a good one man I like that
thank yeah based off one of my favorite
cartoon characters I would name mine
windy like he runs through the wind
that's kind of ass yeah like he just
said mine was bad yeah yours was kind of
[ __ ] I don't know how scary like how
dangerous it gets I was just signing I I
was so happy she let us do it without
helmets me too oh my God I literally
said that while we were there I was like
I'm praying to God I don't I I would
wear a helmet now that I've rode a horse
if I wanted to [ __ ] around and try to
pick up some speed sure or like jump
something like knowing we were going for
a mild Trot a helmet was not necessary I
also feel like I could get thrown off a
horse and be fine no dude that's a big
fall and oosha if you fell if you fell
from a 6ot ladder you could certified I
thought that was the name one of the
horses in oosha you know how much you
know how much ben kept eating the grass
yeah unbelievable he was Matt not tame
Ben no cupcake D eat grass
whoa yeah yeah it was fighting every
urge in me to not just [ __ ] ride that
horse into the distance and leave
everyone behind dude that was I would
say I can fully understand how like
there's Cowboy lingo like when you're up
there on hor completely like I get it
like you wanted you want to talk gidy up
was just like like burning up inside of
me like I just wanted to scream it and I
felt like I was just like you know what
I mean I was like ex oh it was so fun
but it's also like M and Chris don't go
out much as you guys know and it's like
we don't do enough and it was like being
able to go out and have such a peaceful
experience together and not be bothered
by anybody was such an amazing thing oh
it was beautiful I I putting my phone in
that saddle bag and just riding the
horse into the distance I felt like a
new person me too I felt like I had a
whole new respect for nature I felt like
I had a whole new respect for Animals
especially horses I I just built so much
character in that experience guys that
has been this week's video thank you so
much for 7 million subscribers again
it's just unbelievable that we're able
to do this and crazy we're never going
to stop it's going to be on a projected
climb the entire time 7 million
subscribers that's like 7 million people
also me Matt and Chris in honor of
hitting 7 million subscribers we have a
new western themed merch drop that ties
to this video that ties to this era of
subscribers so go shop now because it
will eventually sell out and it will
probably never be back again so shop and
it it unfortunately we didn't have the
merchant time to wear during that video
but the design process for this merch
and just bringing it to Life along with
the video I think it's my favorite merch
we've ever dropped ever so cute have you
seen the design of us on the horses um
yes so the big Hors so cute yes the baby
tea best baby tea we've ever really
loving the boots so cute also first link
in the description it's the link on the
screen right now it will sell out pretty
quickly I assume considering there's a
million more of you guys so click the
link in the description go to the
website on the screen get yourself some
St 7 merch before it is never ever ever
attainable again every other place to
get Stern triplet merch is a is a faker
and a liar just like your mother oh I'm
just kidding I had to say that uh what
was your guys's favorite takeaway of the
horse moment
peace peace and connection kept it so
simple and I'm happy peace and
connection
man I think that he likes when Ben
peed I just think like it it really
changed your perspective for reality
when you can just put your phone away
and go do something and touch grass you
know completely agree I but also this
has been my biggest piece of advice take
um no not yet with talking about
breaking out into the real world if
you're on your phone and you're feeling
upset and it's bothering you I've
noticed some of the best advice I've
gotten while being in the social media
space is if you put your phone
down wherever you are right now and you
look around at your
surroundings you are where you are and
your your phone is what's bringing you
these negative Vibes and thoughts so if
you're ever feeling negativity from
being on your phone put your phone away
and look at the reality around you
imagine if that's horrible I'm
sorry um imagine I said that and they're
like they're like in a car and they look
up there's like a car accident on the
side of the road or something Nick relax
I'm going to share my favorite moment
because neither of them asked so I'm
going to share it anyway what's your
favorite moment thank you mine not that
we give a [ __ ] or anything yeah we don't
care mine was seeing the Horseshoe IRL
just seeing it when we walked over it it
made me feel like I like the Trot sound
like the I love that oh a couple nay was
awesome oh a nay yeah really it classic
Shivers on my spine it was awesome but
yes and before we outro this video i'
just like to say at the end of the day a
Sour Patch Kid is just the sweetest fish
but with a little bit of sour on it so
thank you guys so much did you you you
like you reacted like you knew that was
no I was just like wow that was really
true that was [ __ ] Vibes thank you
guys so much for watching this video and
we'll see you guys in the next one road
to 8 million now for some reason Matt
didn't
scream so bye
[Music]