I'm just surprising you guys with this
cuz I think it's cool and because I
think we need to start decorating our
house we need to start decorating our
house so this is the perfect thing to
put on a
shelf I have a BL I want to do it let me
do it no no no no please don't fight
with the me over a knife I'll get my own
knife if you don't give me that Nick
give me the box you can cut here and
then I want to cut the other side
okay you try to take this knife from me
I'm stabbing you I'm not going to try
and take the knife from you
I'm not but you're going to give it to
me dumb
fool you got more oh I have to do the
other half of that it's already open no
nick nick put it in the middle it's
already open I'm going to I'm going to
I'm going to
ready oh so cute and
fun I'm so excited what the
[ __ ] it has Doc and Marty oh my God you
don't know how cool I think this is I'm
so excited but how cool you think it is
I Love Back to the Future is one of my
favorite movies ever one of my favorite
movies too and look at the license plate
out of time classic when she thinks his
name is Calvin cuz God I love this this
is a really good gift kind of a lot of
money it yeah I figured cuz it's like a
ob is this rare yeah how much is
actually 100 something are you serious
very wait Matt hold on wa can you is
this like the ones to collect or can you
build all three of these no that's all
one and then you build it and then this
this will sit like on a shelf the back
than you yeah that's how Legos work I
know that oh my God I just want to he
just said guys I can't I'm editing right
now and I can't stop laughing at why
does why does Chris go to grab a knife
when he disagrees with me why why does
he why is INS think to go pick up a
knife I'm putting that clip again look
it he he he yells at me and picks up a
knife
what look again and then you build and
then this this will sit like on a shelf
the back to thank you yeah that's how
Legos work I know that oh my God I just
want to he just oh my God his like he
picks up his eyes like like like oh my
God and you'll build it and then this
will sit on a shelf you're not allowed
to partake it's me and Matt only right
Matt is that cool yes I'm very excited
yay let's do the Lego dance the Lego
dance Lego what was what was going on
the other day where I almost started
singing Everything Is Awesome by
accident I don't remember hey guys
what's up me Matt Nick went out tonight
and we were somewhere where there were a
lot of bugs and one of our friends had
bug spray and I caught a full like
perfume colog spray of Spritz of bum
spray right into my eye go ahead Nick
and get a closeup literally ew ew ew
open your eye open your eye
horrifying is it a good like is it a
good captured Vlog moment terrible I
know this incident with the spray
happened probably
like 3 hours ago and I just got home and
my eye had has been like consistently
getting more and more red and more and
more irritated and itchy and burning and
so I Googled it and it says to flush out
your eye with warm water within 15 to 20
minutes after it happening and it
happened 3 hours ago so I'm going to
help him flush his eye out now that
we're home Nick's going to help me flush
out my eyes had these cooling Comfort
eye drops and they expired literally 2
years ago which is crazy I haven't even
lived here that long I don't even know
how I have eye drops that expired longer
than my stay in this home guys are like
actually okay you need to stop talking
and we need to do it can you come here
I can't I can't keep my eye open once it
like I can hold it open I just can't
Vlog okay hold on what do you feel
flushed oh I feel [ __ ]
flushed I have no altitude this is like
2 to 3 Ines
away all right no altitude on that level
oh is that in my my eye yes it's going
in your eye of course guess what Nick I
can't see
it of course I'm getting it in your eye
that's the whole point of this I know
but I can't
tell are you done yeah it still hurts a
little but I think that's just cuz I'm
getting like immense amount of water in
my eye so I think I need to just chill
let it dry for a second and then go to
bed and wake up and hopefully I'll be
better but I cannot believe that [ __ ]
dude oh baby and they know what today is
today is
July 11th 711 they have [ __ ] balloons
up in the 7-Eleven for this I it's
literally it's birthday I think I'm so
excited it is their happy birthday
balloons Matt they're happy birthday
balloons oh this is the deal what it's
not even free Slurpees it's buy six cups
get we have to do it out of order
$1 slurp no
free what a [ __ ] RP
off oh I take back all my 7 support I'm
out of
here [ __ ] 7-Eleven
birthday I don't even care anymore World
moving I wouldn't have even came yeah
why are we here
that free slurp [ __ ] this
place [ __ ] the [ __ ] this
7eleven well that was majorly upsetting
that was like kind of our whole purpose
of like I'm like literally devastated
right now going to 7eleven for some
reason I like knew in my soul that they
were going to pull some [ __ ] [ __ ] Bro
all right guys we are here in the
completely empty Mall
shut this is the intro to the video but
we just completed our day at the
American Ninja Warrior Adventure Park in
inside what mall are we at I don't know
just put it on the screen at this mall
come do it it was so fun they gave us
Slurpees everyone who works here was so
nice we just finished inside but welcome
to the video of us doing what we just
did it's weird I'm filming the intro in
like past tense yeah but that was the
craziest thing guys American Ninja
Warrior is hosting me Matt and Nick
tonight for a little private experience
where are they they're hiding in the car
who you what get in the Vlog there's
people leaving still what are we doing
tonight tonight we're doing American
Ninja Warrior all right and this means a
lot because sometime every once in a
while you do something for the little
you and you and this is one of those
things you know he put his [ __ ] fancy
new running shoes on to get ready for
today right now yeah brand new white
shoes is crazy crazy work you must wear
athletic shoes on truss obstacle course
you must wear tow grip socks or hello
are for
the what I'm just talking oh hey thanks
guys for coming in of course first we
got for you guys we have our ninja grip
socks these will be used for and are
inflatable your normal shoes will be on
the big horse I love it we've got a
quick safety brief and you guys can
watch and then we'll get out there and
crush the course sound good do let's do
awesome ninja warrior obstacles overview
this is where you can take on the
obstacles and test yourself just like we
do on
TV and if you want a little extra
protection for your hands you can
purchase ninja club at registration I
don't need next be sure to warm up and
stretch to loosen up your muscles this
I am ninja one you're
IDI to always ninja within your ability
yeah we go to like the little kid Zone
first no I want to like [ __ ] around in
the bouncy house and stuff my back I
already kind of got like a pain Matt's
been bitching all day he's been like
sneezing and stuff and Nick's been
complaining about his back I think I
slept weird whatever he could he
literally took a deep breath earlier and
like oh my back my back hurt I feel like
an 80-year-old respectful to 8-year-old
be respectful of the other ones around
youe go first down the and one at a time
so you don't C I'm not going Fe first on
American Ninja Warrior Adventure Park
promotes long is this video failure to
adhere to the rules that American Ninja
Warrior Adventure c will result in the
loss of your ninja time no whoever
breaks the most rules wins by the end of
day I'm kidding follow rules that was
the you did the smallest one
bro my socks are coming off
bro
yes out here I need to go for the small
one you did the smallest one though I
know that's some baby [ __ ] I can
probably I could probably do the smaller
one that matches it with no hands God no
you could promise I could all right get
down oh I just got a wedgie bath ready
memo oh my God Nick just he pushed
me [ __ ] B on no hands go ahead [ __ ]
at
me that was impressive okay no hands go
no mat no hands I can't do it get down
go down that way you don't deserve the
slide put your hand get down you can't
come up here until you do it with no
hand
come I can't do it either all right I'm
going again I can't do it
either I feel like Road
Rash ow I got a I got a wedgie break my
leg
okay I won by default oh my
God that looks evil can I get Nick
again we're at the start of the off rid
so right now we're at the start that
over there is the end are you going to
the Finish Line yeah I'll meet you guys
at the Finish Line Matt first the winner
bring my sure no you're not ready no no
no let me let me let me you guys don't
know what I
got
USA
let's let's go I'm doing it for my
country oh my god there no way brother
oh my God it look so funny come here
give me my shirt
B he Nick busted out the USA shirt for
the American Ninja Warrior obstal course
just
no that's what I got on under here and
I'm ready to win that's the craziest
that's the funniest thing you've ever
done in our whole
career Ready set
go
hey
uh I got like 50 bucks on
Nick oh no wait they
switched no
way oh my God oh my God get out of the
ball
pit I haven't done that much physical
activity since I was 12 that's not
that's not an oxal
course no it's not electrical the nerves
of chasing me through that thing like it
felt like a grizzly bear was on my tail
like I'm being serious for our birthdays
growing up as a kid in New England there
was this place called Jump On In I don't
know if anybody remembers Jump On In but
this is what Jump On In looks like I'm
going to have Nick put photos on the
screen but Jump On In is where we spent
a lot of our birthday parties as a kid
and then we also went to the Cape Cod
inflatable park when we would visit our
grandmother in the summer which is
photographed like this so this is very
much a version of like I feel it's good
memories it's good memories I feel like
a little kid again doing this for our
birthday and it's so fun and awesome do
you feel like a loser or no no not I
feel good that I'm 20 and I can still do
this this is not usually in my physical
just telling them about repertoire
repertoire that's a good word how
awesome is our Jump On In birthday
parties dude every how old are we
turning seven eight and nine and six and
five w
wow you fell
hard idiot you fell behind
brother I want to see you go twice oh
[ __ ] no dude how they hurt
Matt ready
you oh he's struggling that's kind of
hurt I know it's like rug burn
a I got like an outfit just for this
like it's like a long sleeve dry fit
uniform I I say a silk outfit I slide
through these things Sue pair of like
all where's the balance mat dude my knee
almost just went the other way your knee
almost I swear to God I is the most
dramatic person ever I like land on the
ground and be like both my ankles almost
Nick stop leaning back what are you what
are you
doing I was already standing
there he's so dramatic he's like both my
ankles almost turned to
dust oh wow this guy's taking
forever I'm not doing that yeah you are
on the side of the Rope no I just like
oh we're doing this come on thigh
stretch come on three four 5 6 7 four 5
6 7even really feel it Nick we're not on
we're not on 11 the 1 14 really dude
don't ever don't ever push somebody's
crouching like that ever I'm not going
first we should like draw straws or
something no Matt you're good at this
type of Stu that's just a little monkey
you're good odd one out goes firstkey
odd one out goes
first my attention has been drawn away
from
here okay after after after ready go you
go the odd one out okay ready ready set
go
no no no that means you guys go first I
go second you have to go
that's oh my God easy oh my God you got
a lot of momentum got it
Nick is the easiest
one oh my God this is so good Bal be are
EAS wait check if it twist first I don't
want you to fall this one doesn't
roll thank you
perfect okay wait we should have timed
him and then when we went oh my God okay
Nick yeah the wall huh beat the Wall
[ __ ] no beat that wall the Nick do it
we'll do the walls out
okay oh my gosh are you serious I
thought my foot was there should have
thought that one out a little sooner kid
bad I don't know what he did my
technique was don't fall and be back
better than you and mat I
won big swing W you have to use your
momentum dude yeah easy Twi
cheese oh that was called twist cheese
no I made it up cheese doors cheese
doors cheese doors they smart
Oh no you're sick you're sick your
foot's going
to L the
[Music]
oh where does it get
you so wait Chris I should have got the
gloves
double you don't need the gloves I you
look like an animal yeah no [ __ ]
Nick nice these got to move what they
don't they te her and they CAU her it's
a teer wait I can't wait to see how you
do this what the [ __ ] is this the cheese
doors wow crazy
foot oh skipping a cheese
can't believe I just lost on the cheese
door it's okay I used to tell myself
when I was 10 years old I could do this
with ease you suck you you're the worst
you're
awful yes Matt oh my God you're going oh
my
God oh my God I'm falling this no no get
your hand out are you serious I just
want someone to do it the Todd almost
got me the cheese
doors have killed your family what are
you talking about the cheese doors are
your your enemies they're your failures
all built into this one old covered
design you want to beat
it just beat it through the door look at
this
technique oh my
God
a I'm trying to
swing come on ninja Nick oh I like it
that was my
technique oh oh oh skip skip
there come on let's go come on you got
it so
close oh my God you're I'm very
impressed with myself good luck to you
guys the first one oh God it's just
going to fall from the
ceiling oh he
skipped I'm so impressed about this that
was so hard let's go bacon back
opposing hand
grip come
on
oh tied up look like a ballerina tied up
oh wow oh his foot dude I like it looked
like I had to pee really bad I was like
clch oh you're a beast
Matt it's the studio lights that make it
feel real
yeah you're not beating this not to be
like the bear of bad news there's no way
no way he does this if you do this like
if you do this you deserve the American
Oh I thought you were to jump to the
third oh no way he does this Matt
Matt watch out how do I get out of this
be careful this is
ridiculous so I won
good oh he's slipping already you're on
the ground and it's over like that okay
someone else
go all right all of us got the same
place on on the on the third one no the
third one fourth fourth one it's still
two Z I have a point bro how I be I went
the furthest on the step thing we're
going furthest now I guess so 2 one I
should get the point for this one no me
and M me Chris made both further than
you let's even it out we're God I can't
speak I have an impediment two 1 Z okay
this is mine oh you're
kidding it was fun it was fun while it
lasted I got to do this thing now come
on no there's no way try
it see what I mean you're better than
me so Matt suspicious I want to try this
actually I'm going to look like a bug
flying at the camera try those memes
like you're watching the video and the
spider like jump it's about to be me
oh my God I didn't see the trampoline I
thought he was jump you want try holy
[ __ ] that scared the [ __ ] out of me you
want
try you're going to die you're going to
die Chris I'm
going
Chris kids are stop it come on I swear
I'm done get him away no I swear I'm
done I swear I'm done get him away I
swear I'm done get him out of here Nick
stop I swear here I swear I'm done I
swear I swear I'm I don't want either
one of I want you both on the finish I
swear to God I'm
done I swear to
God go he's not getting by
me wait I need to get way more air
okay ow
your ass I won this one yeah did I win
no 211 but Matt is the official American
ninja war oh wait we have to do the war
tall that's we forg that's worth three
points out
here oh yeah let me get
money if I do that with less clothes
it's worth a million
bucks Nick reminds me so much of like a
Harry Potter villain what
oh my
God y ow I don't like that I wouldn't be
a good stripper all right go ahead try
the first one you try the first one Nick
you try the first one
yeah is that how you're supposed to do
it whoa broke the rules that doesn't
hurt no it feels good is that like
totally I don't think that was loud but
it felt most com in my
heart I don't even want to do it try it
I got it don't be a baby do you have my
phone now I don't want to try that one
cuz I don't know how to get down you
don't have my phone I think I do yeah go
Chris how do I get down like I just you
just come
down I figured it out
what baby I didn't get a good enough Run
start always slide back down on
facing wall like
this that seems ridiculous we're really
stupid so like we can't follow simple
rules if you fail to make the climb look
at it Chris always slide back down on
hands and
feet facing wall is it supposed to be
like a backward climb type of thing or I
feel like if I do that my hamstring is
going to snap okay let's try to slide on
your stomach I don't know I think my
teeth fall out wow I feel like that
would
hurt slide down on your stomach yese I
see Nick
it see that's better better that you got
to kind of go on the side like the
flipping sexy fortnite emote that's how
I feel tell you that was insane
comfortable it's way better to be like a
get what are you doing
no nobody helps somebody out like
that dud the other day I asked Nick to
help me up and he grabbed my finger he
doesn't know how to do it like
what oh
yeah that's EAS we got to be the that
was I do it one more time I can get the
medium
one all
day yeah I'm not even
[Music]
that's insane on the side or something
ask if we can still get SL you you you
do it you do it you do it you do it I'm
not doing it I'm not 7-Eleven was
yesterday Matt ask him if you can still
get slurp is there a cash register open
for us to still get Slurpees or is that
like off
limits let's do it we can get it yeah
come on it works out perfectly cuz
7-Eleven day was yesterday and we didn't
get our free Slurpees from 7-Eleven yeah
so today we're getting our Slurpees
exactly # beat the Wall # crush the cor
that was so hard that was unbelievable
that was really difficult they used to
have this at AMC and Target and this is
my ideal slurp white Cherry gross that's
disgusting it just
exploded he squee it bro so much wait I
don't know what I want wait guys come
say hi to the Vlog are you
um I'm like not going to come over I'll
just get hey guys these are our friends
who work here what's your name Abby Abby
what's your name Jazelle and what's your
name Elli Elli here we are we're getting
ices we had a blast you're missing out
on white Cherry you know what's going on
yes you are I promise you I want to try
it E I want to try
ni take your straw and try it Oh I
thought the aggression is crazy oh I
just got oh my God I got it every rest
[Music]