so for the next 24 hours you can call us
Daddy
what to clarify for the next 24 hours me
Matt and chis to become the fathers of
little Eggies little baby little baby
eggs so
delicate M they could
crack starting now for the next 24 hours
M Matt and Chris are going to have to be
parents to these little egg babies they
don't have they don't have faces or
identities yet so we're going to spend
the next few minutes stop stop you know
like the parents are like oh come
on like that they have no identities
right now they're just blank eggs so
we're going to customize our children
while we customize them and give them
their little personalities we're going
to go over a couple of ground rules
ground rules of and requirements of what
has to happen we're going to have to
wake up several times throughout the
night to calm our baby down in the they
cry no I'm not waking up another ground
rule if your egg cracks it dies so you
cannot kill your kid in the next 24
hours or you lose the video everyone
liked this video cuz Nick's gay another
thing to note is there is no sabotage so
you can't go around trying to kill other
brother's babies your nieces and nephews
right yes I can feel his yoke Mr yi yi
yi I wonder if you could pre-s scramble
eggs is that a thing
my egg kind of looks like Jeremy
fragrance no no
way oh my God that's the scariest thing
I've ever seen in my life he's kind of
ugly I kind of want to kill him and try
again no you can't that's your kid I'd
let it happen if your kid was ugly would
you kill it and try
again I'm going to kill you I'm going to
kill
you him let's try again wait so
Nick lost no
St that's just really like that that one
pissed me off why did you throw Matt's
egg cuz I wasn't going to like do
another one I
won Nick
oh look look at look at the Yoke on oh I
didn't think it would explode like that
I just had to get revenge Nick all right
so it looks like we're going to try
again wait look at look at my at the
camer camera get the camera Matt get the
camera and it's like D look it's
dripping off the table I if I I can't
stand up it's going to drip egg
everywhere all right we're back three
new eggs one two we've cleaned up the
crime scene that was just in front of us
we have three new eggs so we're going to
create egg identity I to fully change
outfits and then after we cre yeah and
the now you can hear the washing machine
cuz the egg is being washed off of their
clothes okay a couple more rules I'm
going to go over while Matt and Chris I
identify their eggs like real children
you don't leave them alone cuz they
could kill themselves by accident they
could get killed they get kidnapped so
you're not allowed to leave your egg
completely alone for more than 10
minutes you have to have your egg in
your hand on your bed next to you with
you if you go out no matter where we go
The Only Exception is we're going to
have crib safe zones in the middle of
the night we're going to create a little
safe Zone we just have to keep our kid
happy healthy and alive and that's it
yay all right here's our eggs this is my
egg on the screen right here this is
Chris's egg he has a red hat on yep and
this is Matt's
egg yeah I just saw you break it did you
just see that is your egg your eggs wet
what he's like cracked a he's damaged
ooh you need to be careful let me see it
Matt for the Vlog show the Vlog I'm
showing the Vlog this is this is unfair
cuz I have to drive give me your baby
I'll take good care hold him don't worry
because me Matt and Chris are amazing
parents we are going to go bring our
kids outside for some Adventure Time
it's crazy we're only going outside
right now bring our kids to bring eggs
they're not bring eggs not eggs they're
not eggs I should maybe roll the egg all
the way down the street a break if you
roll my my egg will kill you you're
chaperoning right now cuz I have the
camera I'm so happy that our eggs are
going to be able to experience a nice
little stroll on the bite of the Hershey
with
almond that's the scariest thing I've
ever seen what what look at that little
kid
statue oh my God that's like in my I'm
like really scared garage looks like a
big flat screen TV record
it guys Photoshop something on that TV
yeah Sports turn tripet video PA drag
race yeah I find it kind of
scary how about we drop a slight 20 mil
and buy one of these beach houses no we
can't afford it tell me it doesn't look
like I'm like an a mermaid and I'm going
to just like run into the ocean and be
with my mermaid
friends you if you do your egg will be
in danger shut the up Mr Egg on the
beach can you stop act like this is
weird like I'm making jokes but you're
like being weird so much confidence in
the sand being soft that I would throw
my egg on would swear to God no you
wouldn't no you wouldn't I'm going to
risk dropping my egg on this sand course
that's a r are you serious yeah I am but
your kid's going to die if I get out
right now but why what's the reward the
reward is knowing that he has some life
experience you know if I when I fell and
got injuries as a kid I grew up to learn
from
it there he is yes how was it clean as a
whistle how was it how was it Mr Egg we
the weirdest people I love it I love the
beach can you believe we're at the beach
and we're just like carrying and holding
everything like if a cop saw us or
something they think we're like egging
someone's house um yeah until they see
these beautiful little illustrations on
the egg let's go let's go bring them on
the we should bring them on the swings I
already did mine's Mr Egg oh
um mine's Dorothy ew bro Dorothy the boy
ugly ass name I drew his face to look
like a scarecrow and I don't know the
scarecrow's name in the Raz is he's just
a scarecrow right correct life
experience like we talked about we need
to enrich that mine's life experience
was almost cracking in the car yeah that
was crazy that was his let's give him a
shot give him a little push a little
push oh my God I'm so nervous Toto
you'll be
fine I thought it was dark give him a
bigger push Nick come on life Matt Matt
Matt wow give him a bigger push no I'm
nervous no I is still in that in the
thing we fell is he okay he's not going
to fall he's completely fine how fun was
that my egg is beating your guys's egg
in life experience I say if we were on a
point system I'd be at 10 Chris would be
at like seven like the throw was risky
and Matt you'd be at like a five or four
Le now he's going to go for a trip ready
over that Nick no
way oh my God dropped dropped dropped
it's safe though right safe Andy and I
almost caught him that was like a really
Dad and kid bonding moment and he's safe
no Matt no go
long did it break Mi come here come here
oh my it did not break but he is bruised
like like mat bruis bad like
Matt wait let me see he's not broken you
just need to be so careful you need to
be so I'm going to break your eggs
and E them for breakfast kidding you're
Absol all right guys we'll see you with
our eggs when we get back home my God
what is that is that a
Pome why did it almost bite my ankle
where'd it go
dude did you get him on camera um I
don't know I the second you guys
flinched I whipped the camera on like I
don't know if I missed it or not ho
I'm so hot dude I left my egg at the
beach no you didn't not didn't it's in
my pocket oh my
God rat R where where where
another where record it Matt record it
record it record he's gone another oh no
he's not record it record it oh my God
no it's it's not a rat it's a baby posum
oh my nick nick nick oh my God I just
put my thumb in Matt's egg cuz the pum
scared me actually like almost did you
see him climb the tree I thought he's
going to jump in the car I don't know if
that's on camera but that what well you
breaking the egg and scrolling up the
windows on camera but I don't know did
you break the egg he put He put his
thumb like halfway in your egg no he's
good he's good it's no no no he's still
not leaking he's just bruised bad like
he's like not my God man I thought that
that posum was dead serious going to
jump in the car Chris was like record it
so I pul my window down I reach to grab
the camera I looked to the left and it
was in the tree did you see it I really
hope it's on camera it was staring at me
the like
gelatinous what the like gelatin kind of
Sensation that egg gives I think is like
pushing the embryo
sack because Matt's egg is like
reforming like tell me there wasn't a
bigger dent in the car I think like the
the like the egg is like pushing back
the shell all right so one of the
challenges with your egg is you have to
wake up and change his diaper at what
time like 4:30 in the morning in the
middle of the night 4:30 to 4:00 in the
morning whenever they cry when we hear
them crying like we're going to set an
alarm come down yeah I don't know why
we're torturing oursel and stop no it's
part of Parenthood we're stopping in
middle of the night we're stopping sleep
to come change their diaper at 4:30 in
the morning so we're going to leave our
camera on a tripod right there our eggs
are going to all be asleep in this very
little box for the night good night guys
oh no he needs a corner okay eggs are
going to be in here in the middle of the
night and then we're going to put the
camera on the tripod right now right
here and then at 4:30 in the morning
we're going to come down here and the
first person down here is going to hit
record and then we're going to have to
cradle our egg back to sleep for 10
minutes before going 10 10 minutes
before going back to bed I need to get
my Nick I don't want to like wake up
like I don't want to be like so I want
to like I want to like continue to keep
my tired to like make sure I can go back
sleep we have to wake up in cradle a for
3 minutes yes there that's okay much
better someone set a timer
please I don't have my phone do anyone
have their
phone does anyone have their phone
set a timer for three
minutes go to
sleep twinkle twinkle
[Music]
little I just dreaming to me and you
Chris do you have to be weird like the
weirdest person live even me and Matt
were on a pogo stick how have you been
sleeping good bad and been to fall
asleep restart by fan noise that's not a
peaceful rock it do has to be peaceful
good night now it is time to go eat food
for the second time today we ordered
first time so we stayed home with the
eggs so we're going to bring the eggs
for dinner because they starving little
kids tonight we're taking over then
don't mess around this place about to
BL okay
goodbye thank you thank you have a good
one go Mr
Egg yum can we talk about the world
record egg for a second the stupidest
thing ever really overrated yep like
what are we doing I want to be the world
record like V post W English English
language produced eggs normally take 72
hours before reaching your Supermarket
that's a good amount of time
wait so we're talking fresh out the
rooster but that's kind of that's kind
of insane Nick I like the Hat you wore
today was that on purpose
no bro it's got the hat it's
honestly kind of insane to think of the
fact that three days after being egged
what if like like how high are the odds
of like like if like Nick like a chick
mhm like what if you go to the grocery
store and then you go to like the egg
aisle and there's like 20 chicks running
around that's what I was going to say is
like what is the difference between
there is no difference we're eating baby
chickens M yep okay yeah so they're just
non-fertilized eggs thank you if an egg
has been fertilized the embryo begins to
develop within it it's worth noting that
the eggs we typically consume are not
fertilized but what is the difference
between can a sore bought egg become a
chick it's unlikely but not
impossible oh my God so wait how can you
visually tell the difference in between
a fertilized egg and an is there like a
tell or do you just have to know that
your chickens like haven't
you know what I
mean Nick you're taking it too far I'm
asking the same question as you are I'm
just not afraid to use massive vocab
wait was Humpty Dumpty just a big egg it
takes 24 was he really mhm I thought he
was just like a fragile boy
M wait is Humpty Dumpty an egg actually
why did all along I thought Humpty
Dumpty like had some ties to being an
egg like in his name no but Humpty and
Dumpty don't both mean
egg in order to protect their children
from the horrifying aspects of the story
parents made the main character an egg
not a human I hate people make things
easier for kids it's like no yeah just
tell the kid he's going to die
if he falls off the wall correct he goes
up the hill right that's C in
jail yeah what's that smash or pass
Humpty Dumpty pass pass majorly that'd
be a fun video smash or pass like fairy
tal done that that's insane no we
haven't oh not fables but
like like the big bad wolf you
him no
definitely definitely a chicken will lay
bigger and stronger eggs if you change
the lighting in a way to make her think
a day is 28 hours long that's kind of
sad why are we manipulating them
chickens can dream research has shown
that chickens experience RM rapid eye
movement while sleeping meaning they can
dream just like us what if a chicken has
sleep paralysis and his eyes open and
he's like asleep and he can't move and
in his like sleep paralysis demon is
just like a big chicken like running at
him like a big monstrous chicken
can you believe that like a chicken
could potentially have nightmares sleep
paralysis mhm mhm every pop like
what chickens are very intelligent
animals Studies have shown that chickens
are self-aware and can distinguish
themselves from the others they learn
from one another and they such as a
chick learning from her mother which
foods are good to eat chicken can also
demonstrate complex problem solving
skills a so they do definitely think
like in their head like oh my God
there's a rope right here I have to get
over this rope or like this fence like I
wish this fence wasn't here like they're
just thinking wait is it vegan to eat
egg no no no eggs it comes from chickens
no CH but that's like a healthy way you
can't eat milk or cheese but that's not
like animal being chopped up that's like
just like it came from the animal still
not that doesn't matter you can't even
wear certain coats I'm thinking a
vegetarian right vegetarian that a
vegetarian with vengeance to get you
back it's an angry vegetarian Nick shut
the up ventari in to finalize our
baby's experience on this planet we are
going to put them to the drop test to
see if they can survive hard life's hard
impacts yes L child
tribulation okay
so he's good he's okay he's okay let's
see he's okay
yeah uhoh uhoh uhoh uhoh we heard
noise Mr a it's good no it's
not wow a little crack they're ready for
the real world Chris my turn my turn my
turn God please please please wait
please no it's open it's open it's open
wait we have the first
loss well I'll say me and Chris won that
challenge and Matt lost was that it yeah
you're your egg is dead your egg is dead
clear off the table why cuz let all
clear off the table and shut the camera
off
yeah let's just like all right
everyone it's been real it's been fun
it's been real fun it's been real fun
what are you doing I can see it in your
eyes he was looking to my egg broke so
technically I lost
broke broke yeah okay I
just have one question before we wrap up
this video uhhuh if we were to all crack
our eggs technically
me listen listen is it technically you
lost of who's cracked first I don't know
please I'm going to need you guys to
both Focus up on this 4minute video what
what is going on hello Nick hello Chris
and hello everybody watching this video
I know that you might be confused on why
I am playing you this video in the
middle of an egg dad video but there is
very good reason and it's going to start
with the second I knew we were filming
this video you look like a like a like a
villain during the first drawing attempt
I knew I was not going to play fair I
was going to win this Challenge and I
was going to be the best dad of my egg
and I was going to let see my eggs a
phony be the bad dads that they are so
the second that they cracked the eggs I
went to the carton and I grabbed new
eggs but before that I also made sure
that there were two eggs that looked
extremely similar to theirs what I put
them at the bottom of the carton so I
knew which two to grab when I went into
my plan later in the day then when we
were taking the videos of the eggs to
put on the screen when Nick told you
whose egg was who I calculated that I
would be the one to record the eggs so
that I had an exact image of what their
eggs looked like at all
times shut up I so be quiet and watch I
am like be quiet and watch wait a second
wait a second I am like I am bamboo this
is the most Rogue mat thing I've ever
why is the most effort he's ever put
into anything in his life I calculated
that I would be the one to record the
eggs that I had an exact image of what
their eggs like at all times the next
thing I did was I am always BL to clean
up a mess so when I picked up the
Sharpies and put them back no quiet no
quiet I made sure to take the three that
I was going to need at the colors that
they used I brought them to my room and
I put them in my box lucky me I did not
do this on purpose but Chris got caught
by a pretty easy distraction of his
wallet being in the washing machine roll
the clip i a my shorts your wallet is in
your shorts I have a fear that it is no
I'll just leave it wow
wow
cooked with this now new knowledge I
knew that Chris would be way too focused
on his wallet and not on his egg while
me and Nick already had our eggs in our
pocket ready to go for the rest of the
challenge Chris was too busy seeing if
the tracker in his wallet got ruined by
the washing machine or not so he was on
his phone with him being on his phone it
struck the perfect opportunity right in
my nudely
drawn comp it to hiset Simply see that
they were a carbon copy and switch them
out and put the real egg in my pocket
Chris's egg was very easy to draw I just
had to make sure that the lines did not
pass the red line of his head and make
sure that his eyes
[Applause]
had watch
it you watch shut up
Nick was a good egg dad he sat there and
held his egg while watching TV and doing
everything that he was doing I knew that
he was going to be the problem and he
was going to be my biggest competition
Not only was Nick a very attentive
father to his egg but he did a good
drawing but the only thing that he was
missing was the fact that he was
smudging it all day long in the pocket
out of the pocket so what did I do I
drew his egg perfectly carbon Cy then I
went to my bathroom and grabbed a face
cloth and I simulated the motion of
taking the egg out of the pocket over
and over and over again until I realized
that the smudges will match and mine is
honestly a little more bold than his
then as we were eating dinner and
cleaning the table we decided to put all
of our eggs on the same plate Nick went
upstairs before dinner and that was the
perfect opportunity to go back into the
room compare the eggs make sure they
were close close enough and take his and
put it in my pocket and walk back to my
room now the hard part was done the
false eggs were put out into the world
and the real ones were in my possession
there were only two more things that I
had to do one of them it was gruesome it
was
evil but your eggs were my
breakfast no way you watching after
eating them they were very delicious but
the hardest part after that was just
making sure that you didn't fall for the
Trap and realize that your egg was a
phony and you guys were too caught shut
up most important part and you guys were
too caught up to even think about the
fact that I was smart enough to do this
but thank you you have lost this
challenge you have lost this
challeng case in point don't with
me that is like am I feel like I don't
know who you are I was about to say I
don't think I could ever trust that to
say that was
insane that was like that you must be
like living like a villain or it's like
it's like how do you guys feel taking
care of these here's the thing here's
the thing here's the here's the thing
here's the thing I don't even care that
he like swapped out the eggs it's the
fact that he goes and what did I do I
ate their eggs for breakfast no that is
the most mindblowing the other day I go
Matt are you hungry he goes no I had two
eggs eggs for breakfast little do we
know the I was for chatting the whole
time when we were at the beach I said
I'm going to crack your eggs and eat
them for breakfast I told you guys what
I was doing and you had already done it
Don that was actually like like
genuinely that's the most I thought the
video was done four minutes ago no I'm
in pure disbelief and I am actually this
is literally the carbon copy of my egg I
am in shock and I genuinely think that
this will alter my relationship with for
the rest of my life this is the most
shocking thing I don't even I can't even
look him in the eyes like I don't TR
like a fully edited video like when did
you have that don't trust Matt one bit
oh my God it was difficult but I got it
done that was unbelievable Matt I've
been putting in overtime for the last
two days that was unbelievable the word
like the words he was using the the
expertis of like the sness I had this
IDE once you when you guys were talking
about doing this video months ago I had
this idea like on lock ready to go for
so long I just can't believe that like
in front of our own eyes he ate our eggs
for breakfast like actually that's the
least shocking part to me I'm like I'm
just shocked at who are these guys
phonies we have one egg
left I like can't believe this your eggs
your eggs have been gone for
days I I saw you eat the eggs for
breakfast like I had had no idea my own
kid was being cannibalized in front of
me fakes are right there the whole
time
wow well I hope you guys enjoyed this
insane Friday video the plot twist of a
centry genuinely like I am shocked to
the core now these guys mean nothing to
you these are just regular old eggs
um I hope you guys have a good
day happy Friday and we'll see you next
week
[Music]