it looks like we're all like like kind
of like on a hotel bed with like a bunch
of candles around us I was going to say
maybe by the fire yeah I love a goodbye
the fire Vibe mhm that's really what
this V is this this
um you got that you're right there right
that's what this video's energy is going
to feel that's amazing all right guys
welcome back to the car video we know
you love them we know you missed them oh
it feels like it's been ages we love
filming them so I actually like have to
say ever since we stopped posting every
Friday being a car video every Wednesday
being like a vlog or something else I
feel like I haven't filmed a car video
in like in like 30 years it kind of
freak that's a sad feeling I like miss
them so ever so much all right how do we
want to start this off cuz I could start
this off with a little story let's get
immature I'll re ask since there wasn't
an answer I'm scared oh hold on let me
tell you guys real quick what's going on
we are I don't know what he's nervous
about what are you scared he's like oh
oh and he reass cuz there wasn't an
answer I'm like I didn't even hear a
question the question was how are we
starting this off or should I say a
story hold on let me say something
really quick sure I just want to let all
the viewers know we're trying a new
lighting method so if you like the
lighting of this video more than the
other ones it I love it a lot smash that
Thumbs Up Button yes Nick what you're
freaking me out fre I don't know what he
thinks going to say freaking out you
know you know how like when you go to a
restaurant or something go to a
restaurant oh wait I was going to a
restaurant right and you know how
there's like the that moment where it's
like you say Coke or Pepsi and then
they're like we actually got the other
like it's kind of flip-flops it's
whenever that moment endures it's almost
like they're telling you a substitute to
what you can't have so it kind of feels
a little negative I had that experience
the other day for the first time oh my
God and for the first time it was a
positive experience really I said hey
can I get a lemonade and they're like
sorry it's only pink lemonade and I said
better don't be sorry about that fat and
ey bring two cups over bring me that
little pinky drink over
here double down on that what was this
that's a good story I just made it up
cuz I thought like we need I was like we
need a little something so you're a liar
I am a liar I'm sipping on pink lemonade
right now actually oh that's whatp
that's what inspired this little fake
wow Matt I like that you but I thought
we had to get the ball rolling a little
so I was like let let me come up with a
little on camera I said let me I do I
said I said let me come up with a little
Fable okay mat just brought me to Jersey
miks for dinner and then I'm in I'm
sitting there and I look in line and I'm
like wow that looks like the guy the guy
in front of me I'm like that looks and I
was like weirded out by I literally trip
took like a triple take like is that I
was like who is that and then mat goes
Matt goes oh I bet
you he goes to see if wow cuz I was like
is that that' be my last phone yeah we
also went there and there was this car
and it looked like a
giant there was a giant like tin foiled
cylinder and it's like it looks like an
old vintage Volkswagen but it was like
made out of like tin and it was like a
perfect it looked like r
car I think there's going to be minions
in Jersey yeah it was really wild it
literally looked like a tin foil tin
foil Burrito on Wheels literally you
ordered food to the house and you opened
you opened it at the dinner table do you
recall what you said
is very intimate about your pasta no I
don't okay no I don't I might just slap
my dick on this food said I have you in
quotes that's crazy was probably
starving
dude I'm like sitting on the couch like
watching TV and I hear like the
preparing of food like it's a rustling
plastic bag opening the tin and he just
goes I might just slap my dick on this
food out of nowhere that's crazy and I
didn't even react I just like took out
my phone and wrote it down I never done
that I've never done that or deny I've
never done that last thing I written
down is when I predicted the future oh
yeah you're talking about now that was
[ __ ] I was taking a rightand turn on
this street that we go down all the time
cuz we're going in that direction a lot
and Chris goes yeah we go down that
street every here and there every once
in a while he looks at the lady like
coming the other way down the street
that I'm taking a ride on and he goes
goes I've this has happened before and
he
starts we were talking about like work
stuff and just like merch or something
and I was like oh yes and and as we were
taking the right like the conversation
that was happening in the car and then
like the right hand turned and seeing
the lady the craziest thing is you you
said before then we were having a
conversation about merch and like work
and as we were driving Chris was like
Chris was like dude I'm having crazy
Dayja Vu right now and then we turn the
corner immed I made eye cont he makes
eye contact with this lady in another
car he go oh my God he goes I've seen
her before like this is part of the deja
vu like this is crazy and he goes if we
drive like 10 more feet and there's a
guy walking his dog this is going to be
the craziest thing ever it wasn't 10
feet it was like two right turns I was
like if we take a right then a left and
there's a guy down there walking his dog
I'm going to freak out and then we did
it and the guy was walking his dog dog
and it was terrifying yeah we all I
literally like full body chills head to
toe I thought we were struck by
lightning or something I thought I had
to like win the lottery or something I
hate when a [ __ ] loves going on
a boat cuz it's like just stay on the
[ __ ] grass you idiots cuz it's like
it's the the [ __ ] who love
boats are just like always boating and
they're talking about like can't wait
till they go back on the boat and it's
like they like post Instagram photos
like oh me on the boat I missed the boat
and it's like shut the [ __ ] up do you
are you a mermaid what's good what's
this love when was the last time you
were on a boat Australia just asking
okay thought you were questioning me as
if I'm one of these V voters like these
voes no it's not me I just don't love it
like the energy of like severely just
don't love it severely enjoying a boat
I'm like chill the [ __ ] out bro take a
walk go on the Block I like I like a
good boat yes but I'm telling like
you're not like constantly talking about
like like it's like guys that like love
boating and they like talk to their
friends like they're at a bar and
they're like bro like you got to com on
the family boat like they talking about
oh my God oh my God shut chill out dude
it's like the
um like the WF Camerons of the world no
no no no no the murder murders the kid
who like killed his all his friends on
the oh my God I don't think it's like
that no I don't either I hate when
someone says you heard me when I go what
did you say and they're like you like me
and I will be fighting and they'll say
something stupid to me and I'll go what
and I he'll be mumbling like he'll be
like talking like too fast and too quiet
and I like what did you just say and
he's like you heard
me like no I didn't no the [ __ ] I did
not I wish I did so I didn't have to
[ __ ] ask and Matt will die on that
hill I'll ask him what he said he like
you [ __ ] heard me and I'll be like no
I didn't and he'll be like you heard me
and walk away and I'm like I don't even
know what we're arguing about cuz I have
no [ __ ] clue what you said and you
think I had I mumble or your ears Clogg
that's what I want to know you mumbled
you heard another thing I noticed the
other day and I was dead serious is like
I still to this day brush my teeth to
the length of a song song and I can't
brush until I hit start on a song like
I'll get my toothbrush ready and I'll
like my I'll get my toothbrush my
toothpaste ready and I'll kind of like
simultaneously like Play the song and
put it in my mouth at the same
time and I'll brush s I've witnessed you
maybe a hundred times this year brush no
song correct I no but in recent like
this been my new dental practice not
allow to get better you said I still do
so I got normally normally when people
say I still do
and I still do I got I spoiled myself
and I got a new electric toothbrush Oh I
thought you meant you shake your pants I
was like what to go take care of that he
got a vibrator
what I um I have a toothbrush that
automatically shuts off when you're done
really yeah it's like I'm brushing I
have that too you might you maybe just
don't brush long enough no cuz it always
stops and I'm like dude I'm not done and
I keep going no you don't that's the
thing about me is I don't think a a
vibrating Dental brush is doing as much
as I can you know I me like I want to do
it like I feel like I have more control
over like I can get it all I got a water
flosser I'm like feeling like the man I
feel like I put on a new smile every day
look at you yep okay just like that
goofy ass the other day y'all don't this
is the thing too is y'all don't know
[ __ ] about Target
time oh my God you guys don't know [ __ ]
about oh my God me and Chris were little
little kids that just rung bells in my
head when we were little little kids we
wanted jobs so at at Target that just
shows we were about the money like we
would literally be
like we were young like 9 years old we'd
all throw on like a red shirt like no
one of us no we were like N9 or 10 right
and we were like we were all putting on
red shirts and like tacki pants and we
were like getting ready for work and I'm
like I'm going to Target we we l Target
so much we like pretended to work there
from like 9 to like 13 cuz we wanted to
like really embody like our future and
we dude you remember we we would red
shirts and khaki pants we had the
dresser we had the dresser and we had
the the bin on the bottom had all the
red shirts and and I remember like we
makes me sick is most kids like will
like sing or something at we were like
we like yeah let's not
[ __ ] we like we you how geek you were
when we were actually in a Target too
remember the day of the year whenever I
see someone at Target wearing red that
doesn't work there I'm just like you ID
you betray are you [ __ ] [ __ ] you're
just trying you are the wor like it just
like it's just like I want to I want to
ask for help but you need the help you
know you can't help me exactly and you
think you can you're dressed around like
theu I'm going to just like if
especially they have jeans and like a
red it's khaki
khakis okay whatever whatever somebody
missed a couple of if I saw someone in
red and blue jeans I'd be like oh they
don't work here you would I guess my
God a Target shirt with blue jeans i' be
like oh they don't work here
but it's I completely agree complet the
uniform it's like in like it literally
when you like The Incredibles and they
like don't have the mask on that's the
vibe Nick you're actually stupid the
khaki pants are like that's you're
[ __ ] stupid I couldn't agree more
it's like when Perry the plat puts on
his Fedora that's how I feel seeing a
Target employee in khakis oh my God bro
the most emotional moment I've
experienced was the other day I put
music on my TV I I usually wear like
like shoes that I can just slip right
off
right I love how like that like has
nothing to do with this story oh wait
just wait till you hear the [ __ ] end
of it because it's gonna have something
to do with you think I'm just sharing
information for fun like I'm telling I'm
giving you details has nothing to do
with the store what the [ __ ] I'm going
to say time tees it up a little I feel
like that should have came first it
should have been like oh it was first I
haven't hit the yet it wasn't no it
wasn't so it Abol well no he started the
story and then he was like hold on I'm
missing a a detail here and then he went
to throw that in and
I was average Nick
Defender she talking I don't know I
usually wear shoes I I'm speaking you
want to know what I'm oh no I can't say
it go ahead the other day I was wearing
average Chris Interruption the other day
I was wearing shoes that were laced all
the way up and they were like they took
me like a good 3 minutes to get off dead
ass and Converse it doesn't matter boots
oh just asking and I was sitting on the
edge of my bed untying my shoes and I
had already put music on and I looked up
and I was in front of like my mirror my
closet which is a mirror and I was just
like wow like it was like the end of the
day like I'm taking off my shoes bro yep
and I'm ending my day uhhuh that was
really it and it was just like it was
crazy to me cuz I was like it's like I
don't think about it cuz I I just I just
usually I just usually kick my shoes off
you saying it like usually I usually
just kick my shoes off but tonight I was
like I'm taking my shoes off and ending
my [ __ ] day wow Nick what a blue col
it was just like it was like it was that
oomph I needed are you ever around
someone you're just like wow I'd rather
chew glass and turn it into sand then
spend another 5 minutes with you I'd
rather wait till I have a [ __ ] piece
of glass go to full erosion and become
sand in my
mouth then hear one more sentence from
your voice who I can't say go like this
so many people really it's just crazy
the other day oh my God wait the other
day I was talking to someone about like
our escape plan from the internet and I
was like I'm just goinging to buzz my
head and live in a cabin and no one will
ever see me again I was sitting in my
bed laying down so dizzy and I'm like
why do I need like a [ __ ] Dramamine
or the Dramamine what's the what's the
Dizzy medication Dramamine I know I was
like why am I laying in bed feeling like
I need to like how how am I dizzy laying
in bed how am I dizzy laying in bed
you're completely still oh I'm literally
looking at the I'm looking at the
ceiling I'm seeing Stars through the
roof oh my God the roof cough and you're
just like in another world no the day I
have mulp moment I take one wrong step
and all I see is white little dots
everywhere SP I coughed so hard and like
intense I was like like one big cough
and I opened my eyes and I just see like
white like Speckles oh my God dead ass
that's not good it was terrible
and
Reign like what has been on your mind
recently she got a little Deja Vu right
there really
yeah know do you know why why said said
what he said a minute before no you
didn't out loud no you didn't it's on
camera run the tap back um I literally
look the second you said that I looked
at the camera I
went what's going on here you didn't say
that I playing a little game of pretend
can't wait for you guys to watch that
one back tonight yeah I need my Alex ear
ring
light I'm about to make a Tik Tok I feel
like I think that us being triplets also
becoming adults right now we are
realizing so much about each other in
such a good way nothing you have to
share yeah what I'm just a psychopath
what
why I can't stop I'm The Little Engine
That Could okay you know that book out
the little train that could oh I know
just so much about him I'm [ __ ] him
hold on a second I'm [ __ ] him that be
a sick Nick edit like I'm [ __ ]
him oh my
God God buy it buy it buy it I need any
of these buy them right now oh my God
follow through with the order follow
through with the order my God Matt give
me 10 of
those what do you guys even know about
that bye it buy it right now is that my
debit card buy it right now doesn't
matter buy those are my last four digits
is it yes are my last four why would it
be um I don't know it's your Amazon I
don't think it is dude what the
[ __ ] that's mine dude why did those are
my last four digits check your card what
the [ __ ] are you cracked out your mind I
got the email look it those are my last
four digits [ __ ] let me see what the
[ __ ] you're an idiot oh my God thank
God thought you were stealing from me
tell me why I thought it was a tiger the
gingerbread the Gingerbread Baby yeah no
never mind next tattoo Gingerbread Baby
yeah that'd be my rap
name Gingerbread Baby I don't know why
that wait what you talking about that
made me pull that I was getting
emotional engine that I was literally
about to get like truly emotional why
are you the little engine you could
cuz I [ __ ] can the other day me and
Chris were out of the house we were
being bombarded oh my God like it was
like unbelievable and like people ask
why I don't leave the house we went to a
function a party if you will cuz we're
party animals I hate speaking about
going to La parties cuz I just want to
be struck by lightning I hate it I hate
talking about things that like are so
unaligned with My Soul that like it just
freaks it just freaks me the [ __ ] out
cuz I hate partying I hate everybody so
I hate I hate when I say like oh I was
at like I hate even starting with a
story a starting a story that I was at a
party the other day me and Chris left
the house we were at a house party show
me and while we were there these girls
would not leave me alone they wouldn't
leave me alone and I'm like I I was
trying everything I was like I was
trying to like I was trying to I was
trying to bring up oh oh my God I at
some point like turn my back cuz I
couldn't witness it anymore they
wouldn't stop talking to me my skin was
crawling out like I was crawling out of
my skin it's it blows my mind how
airheaded some people are cuz I'm like
I'm like I'm in pain listening to you
speak yeah like do you think in depth
about anything you do ever and they were
like they were coming up to me like I'm
like I also hate when a [ __ ]
touches me I was talking to someone that
I know my friend friend and some girl
comes up to me and she starts talking to
me and she was like she grabed I was
like
yet holy
[ __ ] like oh my God yeah like I hate I
hate I hate being touched unprovokingly
and yes that's a normal thing I feel
like everyone should feel that way but
it's like if if I don't know who you are
and you're inserting yourself into an
environment that I'm at and you're
touching
me you're lucky I don't have a [ __ ]
like you're lucky I don't have a taser
or you're lucky I don't punch you in the
[ __ ] face like I don't get when how
touching has become so normalized cuz
I'm like if you touch me I'm going to
rip all of your fingers off like oh my
God these girls are talking to Nick and
he's holding a broom and I saw him going
like this I was trying to get him away I
was talking to someone else and she
starts talking me mumbling and talking
like an idiot so I'm like I can't even
hear you and you're touching me like oh
man you're not engaging me in
conversation I can't hear you and you're
touching me the other day I was like
sitting leaning against the palm tree
cuz I was waiting for an Uber to arrive
and I was on my phone like for 3 minutes
leaning against this tree and I had the
Urgent thought to get out of the way cuz
of like a coconut like I realized I was
under I realized I was under a palm tree
and I was like oh [ __ ] and I like got
out of the way I wish I I wish I had I
wish I had anything to say back to you
there's no coconuts here you know how
those things and it's like oh like all
of our child childhood was spent here
and then it's like the nostalgic slides
and like one of them is always the green
box yes I don't think I've had that many
moments at the green box it's like the
tag the green box in the
woods are you guys making this up no
it's like it's like you have a Instagram
photo here when we were in Ohio Ohio
Ohio on the green box and it's usually
like the Bas they like electric man holy
[ __ ] you guys are killing me I'm like
the green box I'm thinking of like a
little like you I just thought of
actually an anal crate from fortnite no
shut animal crate ano Oh I thought of
like the little like the put a book
leave a book
libraries that's what I love
those going on the record saying this I
hate when I see a Tik Tok account fully
like saying like Chris stolo with like
my profile photo and here on out you're
getting blocked if I see it I agree I
love peanut butter crackers [ __ ] that's
that's something that I figured out the
other day cuz I was like I was like
sometimes I'm not like want to snack and
I don't I'm not hungry I just like got
to put something in my stomach you know
oh my God something in my stomach so I
can have like an Adil or an algra for SE
and it's like for and it's like I
haven't heard that and it's like I don't
want a full I don't want a full meal and
I'm not trying to like have like snacks
but like a peanut butter cracker will
kind of I think we should when already
ate I think we should get into Game of
Thrones and not cuz it's a good show but
genuinely so we can get into the lingo
cuz I feel like that'd be sick if we
could like just understand like like get
into the words like the terminology and
like just talk to each other like that
cuz that's like kind of our like no like
it would just I'm all right too yeah I
hopped off the plane at
LAX with a dream in my C again that was
so us actually we had a lot of plan I
know bro y'all heard ofo y'all heard of
wh y'all heard of wh who's wh Nemo
secret
cousin the self-driving
cars what white ones with the Big C my
friend I was in between them I was a
sandwich a we
sandwich my friend was telling me the
other day that they were in a
whmo I'm never getting in one of those
by the way it picks you up it picks
you're by yourself right and they were
in the car and it was driving down the
street and it was at a turn with a red
light green light red light green light
you know you go and it kept turning
green the car would not go and they're
like what the [ __ ] do I do and they
press the button that was like hit the
oh no it's good it's good it's good it's
good I have to go quick it's where the
camera's about to die the um um um um
um the car didn't move so we hit press
for assistance and instantly someone
comes over the speakers of the car like
what's going on like what's the issue
and he's in real life
like no I thought no and he goes oh the
car won't go and he's like okay we
should be it should be going now and
they like hit they like redirected it
from their thing and the car just went
and they're like We'll add that to like
our routing issues or something but like
what dude me and Chris me and Chris were
driving to dinner the other day we're
driving on the way home from dinner the
other day one on my right one on my left
I was in a weimo sandwich and then we
got like a [ __ ] little and then we
got and then we got Wall-E delivering
pizza
what I'm waiting for like and like laser
beans to break through the window all
right thank you guys so much for
watching this week's Friday video we'll
talk to you guys whenever the [ __ ]
Friday yeah next Friday yeah uh bye you
bring the oh my
God she this my perect ha want to take
him a look wait can I do one
yeah oh w we no I do it better
[Music]