and all the things
[Music]
welcome back to the studio triplet
spelling me part two stop chewing so
[ __ ] loud
all right well if you haven't watched
the first spelling bee video go and
watch that one now I feel like you're
complain about something real soon or go
and watch that one after but
yeah you think you do it stop rolling
your eyes at me stop hitting people use
your [ __ ] War are you [ __ ] stupid
I'm gonna hit somebody next you're an
idiot I'm gonna go idiot
go ahead dumbass stop using hateful
words
oh yeah touch me again give me an excuse
okay buddy
let go
all right one person lays another hand I
mean you're getting the full graph
because you're trying to touch me nope
not true yes it is anyways
yeah you're an idiot come on we're
filming shut up
breaking the bed
go ahead Nick explain
hey guys today we're gonna do a spelling
bee part two forever get your head
straight I just want to like get shot I
know
oh
no no shut up
you're gonna actually break something
it's not funny go back where you are
first word
Pharaoh oh my God
like the bird no
Arrow Arrow a ruler in ancient Egypt oh
my God like King Tut
Crusher pharaoh
I know they want me to say f uck
I'm not gonna do it
okay H yeah
pharaoh Pharaoh
Tick Tock are no what'd you even sound
like I forgot was PHR no
I'm so stupid dude correct what level
word is that I don't know
okay rotate what how do you actually do
it get away
rotate as we update you on the score
[Music]
I got the word I hate my life
handkerchief
h-a-n-ck no
laughs
[Music]
yeah that's what it's called that's not
real yeah it is
come on bring the spice are you excited
I actually wish that you would take all
your spice and throw it away can I have
a sip of that drink absolutely I need
something you don't need anything I'm so
thirsty just ask him a [ __ ] word move
on in heckable
is that what that word is he doesn't
even know if that's the one yeah that's
what your word is yeah I am yeah P
uh-huh get out of here it's my full list
of words
yeah see
I am p e c you know I T nope [ __ ] all
right
whatever rotate as we update you on the
score
[Music]
all right your word is baloney no I
don't want to spell it it's balag
balognia
baloney bologna
get there please I see it is it a no
it's O yes
okay with my gut rotate as we update you
on the score
[Music]
I'll do it okay lucrative
lucrative
lucrative l u
C
there's a silent D in there
[Music]
no or we just saying wrong
hand to Kirk shift I don't think we're
saying it wrong handkerchief okay I got
it yeah shut up please
you can't I'm literally not giving you
an energy drink
go get water
okay
Matt it was broccoli b-r-o
bro
C
this [ __ ] makes me embarrassed me too I
don't know we update you on the score
[Music]
can I give Chris the next word
sure I'll just give no words today it's
a pretty it's a pretty simple word it's
the number 20.
I don't think I'd get this one to be
honest very easy word
okay
let me start spelling it
you never said the word 20.
the number 20 is about out spell out 20.
you have fours f-o-u-r yes I don't want
like 20. there's no way it took that
long
I thought you said number 20 like yeah
yeah
I correct twenty TW uh-huh
t-w-e hello
and
t-w-e-n so correct give me a nod of
approval just keep going spell faster
t-w-e-n
-t
e y no e
t w e n t y 20. birthday is the update
you on the score
[Music]
chauffeur
oh my God I would never get this CH yep
a yep
you yup no
that is okay you're right I don't know
what he's talking about
c-h-a-u Burr is it like f
yeah f c h a u f e
r
c h a u f f e u r f f e u r never dude
you're so smart what school did you go
to stop
[Music]
do you want to give him one of your
words
sure we can compare so last time no I
gotta go there actually no I don't care
he just [ __ ] sent me I'm already
going last time we gave you a pretty
simple word that you got wrong because
you thought I had a second you thought
you had a silent P yeah this time your
word is crouton
see
I forget how to spell futonium It's A
Small Piece you know how to spell futon
even I know how to do that a small piece
of fried or toasted bread VR
salad
oh c-r-e no crook crew yeah but you just
got it wrong like like the like the um
Crouton is c-ro rotate as we update you
on the screen
[Music]
okay
get out of my face
[ __ ] minuscule
can I abbreviate it to Minnie minuscule
why didn't you guys give me easy work
you can ask it here here I'll give you
uh we literally gave you I'll give you
I'll give you I'll give you a little
cheat right now you ready you can ask
for a shuffle and I'll pick one of
another two words that I have except one
of them is more difficult and one of
them is easier but I'll rock paper
scissors Nick for harder or easier work
I don't know what you should have said
okay it's like a shuffle like do you
want to think
minuscule
sounds like mini stool okay perfect can
you say it in a sentence
the amount of water they had was
minuscule
I don't know bad example bad example
whatever Nick can you get any amounts
I want a next example this should be
taking a minuscule amount of time but it
is taking you far longer for no [ __ ]
reason
am I
yep
and yep I know
rotators
[Music]
you ready Nick yeah hello blue
[Laughter]
hullabaloo
can I hear it in a sentence
[Laughter]
h-u-l-l yep a yep
l
o
u l o o l o o I should have noticed
okay I was close
rotans we update you on the score
[Music]
sacrifice s-a-c
yeah r i
yeah
Vice
f-i-c-e yes
rotate as we update you on the school
that was awesome thanks
[Music]
all right your word is malarkey
Malarkey that's a whole lot of malarkey
is that even how you use it yeah Nick
doesn't matter go no it doesn't matter
just spell it say it in a sentence
that's a crock of malarkey I want
it used in a sentence don't believe that
that's a whole lot of malarkey what
about a definition
get the definition
meaningless talk or nonsense that's what
Nick that was all Lucky don't give me
that Malarkey isn't it
I'm gonna start using this it's
literally spelled exactly how it said
yeah that's a whole lot of malarkey it's
for real ma Larkey m-a L M A yeah R yep
malarkey
Amazon
he's on the last three letters here
malarkey k-e-y
rotate as we update you on the school
[Music]
I love these spelling bee videos
inconvenience i n
c o n v i nope
e v i e v e n i
[ __ ] rotate is the update on the score
[Music]
I think that one oh sorry oh you're fine
I have one word left so which one do you
want to use let's see
that's mine but he's seen mine I didn't
see yours
um this one's simpler but it'll trick
him anyway that's good
considerable
c-o-n yep
s i oh you just burped
shut up shut up
I didn't even hear you said
c-o-n-s-i-d-e-r
able
oh my God you got it and here is a final
look at today's score
[Music]
you guys get this stuff
I don't know who won me either
definitely wasn't me that's for sure
well I feel like [ __ ] Kiki Palmer
right now I feel like akilia and the bee
aquilia the tequila kill on the B you
added like an extra little uhlia is it
not it's not anchilia you're adding an
extra like I don't care why don't we
ended with this video yeah
[Laughter]
well that was a part two of our spelling
base series and I'm super excited to do
it again hopefully get away in fact if
you guys want a part three of course I
don't want to do it
okay I'm out of here see ya Nick you're
full of malarkey
I know what you're saying how you miss
me yeah
[Music]