[Music]
we're on tour obviously and we're in a
bus and still moving so it's probably
it's probably really loud but ignore
that we're gonna just do a couple like
these sit down moments throughout the
video where we're like explaining what's
going on because sometimes you need
context throughout this video I'll
probably put this in the beginning yeah
disclaimer that we're gonna pop up like
this explaining what's going on
oh I'm washing my face
the seventh story all the way to the
13th and the 14th are supposedly all the
ones there's reports of I don't see a
lady with white dress phone's ringing
all kinds of bumps and
foreign
this is absolutely happening
built in 1924 on the original location
of the element Barracks the building was
originally constructed as a Medical Arts
Building with family doctors offices
dentists surgical floors emergency rooms
and a psych unit the building also had a
Morgan crematorium a facility employer
with 100 medical professionals ranging
from dentists to surgeons in 1976 the
hospital closed and it was turned into
an office building until it was
eventually sold or transformed into a
hotel why would they make it a hotel
station
was purchased by the Hilton family and
turned into a DoubleTree while keeping
them
oh
most haunted hotel in the world
the seventh floor which was the former
psych ward the ninth floor which was the
surgical floor and the 14th floor which
was a waiting area the basement is also
said to be haunted which was formerly
the morgue in 1984 when the building was
first purchased and turned into a hotel
the construction crew entered the
basement and began Renovations what they
found was hundreds of boxes of human
ashes from unclaimed Bots
spreading the ashes
he said they took the ashes that they
found from the unclaimed bodies they
just spread them along and then built
this [ __ ] on time
they spread the ashes around the hotel
grounds yeah
one local Legend claims that the pool is
constructed from melted down steel from
hospital guards oh my God that's crazy
you still hear the girl who's being
wheeled down the hallways accompanied by
strange bones and labored breathing only
to reveal that nobody is Walking The
Halls
requesting to change we're checking out
at odd hours many with days to own the
reservations
we were told that on the 12th and 14th
floor of the Emily Morgan Hotel it still
smells like a hospital Andrew who's a
firefighter and a paramedic was unaware
of these claims as we explored these
floors the second we got off the
elevator to the 12th floor the smell hit
us Andrew's exact words before any of us
said anything was
formaldehyde that's the smell of
formaldehyde all right let's all stick
together team
together okay here we go I'm the first
one to step foot there you go
all right I was gonna do that
um
[Music]
I know
all right first thing is first we can
walk into the hotel we went into the
elevator I hit four number seven because
that's where like the spooky floor was
but then this random ball dude ran into
our elevator last minute and started
asking a bunch of questions as you'll
see in the video about like what floor
are you staying on this and that also
our like part of our other members of
our tour team were staying in the same
hotel as us and with before even telling
them about that experience we had they
told us the exact same thing that
someone rushed into the elevator last
minute same like description of guy and
asked them the same man and both of and
both the people like on our tour that
were also staying at the hotel they said
that the person that rushed into the
hotel were holding like clean T-shirts
from like a dry cleaning place and the
guy that was in the elevator we didn't
get them on camera but he also was
holding like we didn't care but we have
our filmer here Guillermo
but he filmed the dude and as he got in
the elevator as we were walking off memo
filmed him as he was walking off and
there's literally frame by frame this
dude has black black eyes and like a
black mouth and that's a 4K footage
camera like yeah there's other clips
that you guys will see eventually from
the footage that he's taking but it is a
high quality camera
he's literally shooting in 4k like it's
impossible to not see someone's eyes in
the camera and make elevator clip and
then after the elevator clip I'm gonna
put the photo that we got from Memo's
camera after we looked way later yes I
don't believe in it should we go to the
seventh first everyone get in here
where's Laura oh sure
we have the security guard Nick we're
good we're safe right Nick
let me get my little
puzzle
to prove 605 wow this thing is hauling
up there yeah how's your day glissa not
bad not bad no it's yours not so far so
good so far so good good what's up what
are we at six we are at six you guys
have a long trip oh yeah
all right let's go have a good night
okay thank you sir
thank you
thirsty love this
where's the spooky dookie gonna go down
no I I asked him I said what floor are
you going on sir no response that was
already a really scary
Stadium
this is really
really sorry no Batman was really
terrible
that was hopeless oh that was really
scary why is the light so dim
oh nah this is so scary I didn't know oh
that robe is terrifying so who's gonna
hold my hand
dude this is oh my god look outside look
at where we are
look in there what the [ __ ]
that's scary
why is the light turned on it is cold
wow it looks really pretty though it is
pretty did Nick shut the light off
what if Emily starts wiping my ass
[Music]
hand sanitizing wait so there's legit no
bathroom unless we come all the way to
the room
yeah is that the plan I think this is
really scary no he was a weirdo
he goes what are you guys doing here
it's like we're in a hotel bro there's
not many things we could do well it's
probably there's probably mad people
yeah he was there and he was like
dressed all funky like carrying clothes
around like I don't know that came out
of nowhere
I gotta [ __ ]
yo this is like the perfect time to play
with me if you do it I'm good on friends
like you got this here turn like a fan
on my [ __ ] yeah
all right y'all better not play around
we're just gonna be right here Chris I
would never leave you so for real y'all
Chris I'll stay with you till I die why
does it look like someone's standing
right now stop kick it no one's there
we're safe kick this thing over
really scary
I don't know bro that guy was like the
weirdest part of this yeah that freaked
me out a lot yeah and like he like ran
into the elevator you heard when I when
he first came in I was vlogging like
myself I was like oh cause like he
almost got caught in the door like I was
just so startled that he was trying to
even make it in our elevator because we
were what floor did he hit he didn't hit
one button he never went to a place he
just like came in I don't know seriously
would be if one of us thinks something
happened and everyone else was like what
the [ __ ] are you talking about that's
weird people knocked the [ __ ] with me or
am I legit feeling [ __ ] someone
something nice
I'm so dumbass
yes
wait which wall that one the red one the
red one's outside the room something
knocked on it I'm not even lying I'm
sorry I put it on my life really I put
it all my life three knocks yeah no [ __ ]
bro
that's crazy
that was so stupid
so then as you can tell I went into the
restroom to take a [ __ ] in Emily Morgan
Hotel yeah and that red wall that's
behind the toilet oh my God that scared
the [ __ ] out of me because we're in a
moving bus but that was terrible yeah
but anyway I was sitting on the toilet
and I wasn't flushing or anything wrong
big movements were going on like I was
in the beginning process but the red
door the red wall that's behind me
murdered like three knocks that were
like loud but like quick but it was
literally like
like that yeah three solid knocks but it
was also really terrifying because
everyone could kind of sense Chris's
like fear no And Me me saying like like
when I went in saying oh no one [ __ ]
with me whatever blah blah like I
genuinely thought leaving the bathroom
like it was one of them like joking
around but once I asked everyone and
they all said we're not faking anything
like you can genuinely see my fear the
whole rest yeah like I was ready to get
the [ __ ] out of there you know I was
actually dead ass terrified he was just
scary because no and also it didn't look
like he worked tier one he like he got
in our elevator while it was closing
that was the weirdest part the door was
closed then he like stuck his arm and
jumped in it was full
and then see if he actually came out
like once he like tried to edit your
stuff maybe he wouldn't oh my God no I
said I was scared I was already like so
close to myself that's why I didn't
think anyone else was gonna try and win
oh uh that's a bucket list experience
took a [ __ ] in the third most haunted
hotel ever y'all can't say that spooky
he was just so confused he didn't really
need to get the [ __ ] out of here because
I'm scared wait where are we going we're
going we're on our hotel room is on six
but the scary floor seven so we're going
up one I do not like this
yeah no no what are these hallways
up or down
we can't come all the way here and not
go to The Descent I already handled my
experience oh
shuffling
. we're going to see the hospital
because like it's not gonna let us watch
we're gonna see the
Mountain okay
so what
oh it's not closing someone's sitting
here earlier
see that was terrifying I get stuck in
this [ __ ] that was scary if I get
stuck in this elevator we're gonna see
things that we we wish we didn't see
they call us the [ __ ] Ghostbusters I
think scary yeah it is this hallway's
terrifying down
at this point where we hit the elevator
down buttons we're ready to go back to
the lobby but we want to stay in an
elevator where it's just our crew so
we're keep denying people that are
showing up like in one in the elevator
alone but so then this lady comes up the
elevator she's fully alone right and
she's holding her purse like at her
waist like
angle this camera at me this lady has
her purse and she's that ass holding it
like she's holding it like this
in the back of the elevator and then so
it opens and then me and Matt didn't
even see her in it so we started walking
on and then in the clip you can hear I
think Nick was like oh no we'll wait but
if this lady was literally standing like
this holding the purse and she was like
I'm going down you guys would you guys
like to join me terrifying like this and
this and as she said that memo who was
recording literally this exact moment
she was awesome seconds before she gone
kind of dirt kind of yeah like while her
elevators coming to our floor and while
the elevators opening she's talking to
Matt and Chris you can hear while I'm
taking a photo you have to pay super
close attention while I'm taking a photo
of Chris and Maddie and Matt you here
beeping from Memo's camera and he's been
filming since we started tour and then
after this Vlog he's been filming ever
since we were at that hotel so it's been
like a week and a half that he's been
filming and he's not filmed for stuff
like on the news like he's yeah he's a
professional he does not miss not messed
up filming anything so it's really scary
because that's like his camera's cutting
and you can literally see his fear of
like yeah he knows he didn't touch him
and there's a clip where I turn the Vlog
camera fast enough and it literally
shows him not clicking
yeah
take one take one photo of us
foreign
okay down
come on no do you see they're cut look
oh look like okay
the camera keeps like stopping and
starting recording by itself
there's a lot of us
we're good
show yourself what happened
make yourself really the name of the
world
okay we're good where are we going Lobby
or is it ground is it g
yeah do not put LL that's lower level
list
come on in let's go let's go thank you
holy Lord no that was scary the camera
I heard like I wasn't expecting to have
this much activity the first moment yeah
what if we like it then we're
Lobby because we're done but once we got
to the lobby we realized there's a
staircase down to the lower level and we
weren't gonna go to the lower level
because it was the crematorium before
and that was terrifying but once we
found out that the lobby like led to it
with stairs we were way less scared so
that's all I wanted to say because that
segues into wild yeah so we went all the
way down and that's when I was looking
at the muskets and [ __ ] I feel like who
those guys like the YouTuber guys Colby
and what
yeah
oh my God
that's how he said it yeah what are they
meeting there for let's meet here
because you do like Chris Chris
aim steady
wow Chris look you and Maddie can have a
fresh love second choice meeting in
there oh yes Halloween drop Queen
okay and I was talking
that's the [ __ ] who owned the
musket I bet you a million dollars he's
the one going steady clean your buckets
bar
that's so scary Matt come here
we're gonna show him this like Shrine
for that man Matt
bro it's like hard to breathe I know it
is like I felt like I was dying it
smells like Hospital everywhere sweating
like crazy yeah look at that
oh those sideburns are horrifying
we left the hotel now this is pretty
much it yeah but you can see like once
we're out of the hotel it was like
feeling the breath of the outside air
was so it felt way better it was cold it
was like must dry it was like so hard to
smell just like hospital it smelled like
hot like funeral home the whole yeah
really scary and what I'd like to say is
thank you for watching this video and it
was it was a great experience I was
terrified they were not faking anything
we actually didn't sleep in the hotel we
were all scared so we slept on the tour
bus yeah
right thank you for watching this
Wednesday video we hope to see you guys
next Wednesday and Friday and if you're
coming to any of our shows we're excited
to see you there thank you for following
our tour thank you for subscribing to
our YouTube channel we'll see you next
Wednesday and Friday love you all
and then what you're saying how you miss
me