another truck get out of here cuz we
going to make you lose your mind what
that car is on but there's no one in it
where where where right next to us where
there's no in the front right there it's
on there might be someone in the back
hey they
getting all right Chris asked me for tea
and I didn't know which one to get him
so we have between sweet
tea peach tea are you serious Nick
raspberry tea which one do you want why'
you three of them and if you want more I
have double of each are you serious Nick
what are you doing I have another
raspberry I also have a bubbly
grapefruit which I was going to drink
but if you want to drink you can have
what's your choice that's everything
nothing else is my bag of tricks okay
I'll take that just the regular sweet
tea yeah okay I'll take a RZ take a
RZ uh these remind me of work at Star
Market take a look oh you squirt it on
him Nick what are you going to do wipe
it off you
grownup I hate when adults bitching
complain I wish I was a pirate and I
could just like casually add every
sentence
with do you think they did that he I
don't [ __ ] with you
[ __ ] ah you need to walk the plank you
stupid
[ __ ] to [ __ ] I'm not going to
have them glow up but they do woo party
[ __ ] I'll leave them off I also
realized I was wearing a Pez shirt with
Easter bunny ears on it's not Easter yet
but [ __ ] what are you doing it's so
close so I thought to myself in CVS
let's just really capitalize on this
Easter
feeling I Got a Friend for today's car
video you said there was nothing else in
your bag of tricks shut the [ __ ]
up a little chick and he he has hold on
does he walk is he
broken he better [ __ ]
walk oh my
god
dude hey get
it this is [ __ ] stupid dude we filmed
her so many times and that sto like just
now sto that sto yeah you did say it
hell like boss like a little baby not a
Boston what did I
say I didn't mean store oh what do you
mean that house it just right now hit me
it looks like gr lives there this glass
where are you getting [ __ ] next it has
dirt in it but I want to use it cuz it's
fancy let me see it's been here for so
long what would you do if dinosaurs
still
[Music]
existed I don't I know what i' do I'd
probably hop on like a camel and try to
rang in some more rang in rang in we
[ __ ] they rang in there it's another
complaint about steing the produce
section they ranged it in it's like a
country grocery store they rang in they
said that Jean in the back is not doing
their job we need to do something about
it they rang in I you're insane I I
think I would I'd have to have one as
like a p like a little like a if I went
outside and a [ __ ] pterodactyl sword
at me do you know what I do run away I'd
pretend to be it little baby I'm I even
car
I'm a little pterodactyl get on the back
and me and the pterodactyl fly across
the the land dude pterodactyl are huge
huge Nick I just want to be a baby like
pterodactyl in a nest no that's crazy
Nick that's actually absurd I I wish
tell me if you were if there was
dinosaur still existing you wouldn't
pretend to be a baby dinosaur no I'm
joining them I'm joining them I want go
pretend to see be a baby rhino and see
where that get you no I'd have to like
get you stomped out of the tribe they'd
[ __ ] literally mow your head into the
ground if I dressed up like a rhino
though big I can't even picture you as a
baby rhino right now it's freaking me
out like not even if I got like a little
outfit and I crawled around no with like
a pretend horn Nick stop freaking out so
much grass dude you know something about
what is firewood is that not just wood
it is wood grow up firewood I think it's
ready to be burned yeah it's like drier
your mother I'm done I'm done it like
infiltrates my brain I can't stop it the
words are just on my the tip of my
tongue I can't let them sit there oh I
just wish Pokémon were real that would
be insane imagine what would you pick
what starter I don't know what's it
called a p i don't know Pichu no Pichu
Pichu what Pichu Pichu I can't even talk
to you BL you [ __ ] what the [ __ ] are
you saying literally a p you're not
what's a Pichu it's like the Panda one
no pan champ pin p someone says if you
were to commit a murder how would you go
about it
What the fu do you want to answer what
Pokemon you want what the [ __ ] are you
saying to me delay that answer no I'm
just I was just wondering Nick what
would you be as a Pokemon I would be
what's that Rhino one Chris ryhorn what
Nick I'm not a rhino you just said you I
said pterodactyl you brought up rhinos
Mr mime Mr mime I do anything to be a
mime you should do it for a car video
Nick has talked about how he loves Mr
mime so much that was terrible
what if there was a wall right here and
I had to get in be like Nick Nick stop
Nick stop Nick stop Nick Nick Nick Nick
stop doing
that you can't yell no I opened the door
so you can finally hear me you can't
yell you're you're
right I'm not making noise it's the door
squeaking Nick
stop I just want to walk Barefoot on
grass and really like soak in the
universe no no no you said you had that
written down somewhere I do let's see it
no I'm not pulling my notes up dude I
was going to say I think flipflops are
perfectly named you've said this before
did I really yeah I think about it often
because I'm thinking about it if I'm
Barefoot I want to walk through
someone's freshly cemented uh garage
with no car in it and they're like I'm
like hey they come in the room ready
picture this close your eyes think about
it close your eyes I'm at my friend say
like come from room that I have no idea
where it was and they have a freeze pop
and I say oh my God can I have one of
those they're like yeah it's in the
garage go get one and I'm Barefoot my
feet flop over like I'm a dirty little
penguin all the way over to the garage
door I whip it open I see that beautiful
white refrigerator is their second
fridge in their house all the way across
the garage and there's nothing in there
all the cars are moved out except the
sides has like kickballs and baseballs
and Whiffle balls all the fun summer
supplies and I waddle over my big feet
just flapping on the ground like it
sounds like gunshots it's like boom boom
boom each my feet hitting the ground I'm
slapping my feet on the ground like deli
meats hit in the back it's
like like I'm this big beastly animal
all the way over to the fridge I grab my
freeze pop and walk back inside with the
same beastly
stride W tell me that's not like just
joy that was beautiful with my beastly
stride in my stop saying that what
beastly stri I know whose house you're
thinking of so do I on three y hold on
sh sh on three hold on sh Wait I'm
trying to think of their names 1 2 3
that what you said yeah
yes that's exactly what I was thinking
yes ni got you have a good Storyteller
that was good actually now that I get it
can we normalize being a [ __ ]
psychopath I want to go outside and see
someone dressed up as like a [ __ ]
Dragon getting ice cream from the
grocery store store like I have so many
little like weird aspirations see these
bunny ears on I'm wearing them For Your
Entertainment digitally from a car I'd
love to wear these [ __ ] to the
grocery store where are the people that
I want to see I want ComicCon everywhere
all the [ __ ] time if you feel like
you want to dress up as a little
creature and crawl around Target who
should stop
you if you want to but it's like I'm
obviously limiting it I don't want to
see people like pretending they're a
dragon in public let's keep that let's
limit that for sure for sure like no
psycho level craziness but I'd love for
people to just get outside and be more
creative all these [ __ ] wearing the
same jeans with the same cup you mean
like if I wear like a big furry coat and
furry shoes and call myself a Yeti it's
fine but well like also like that's a
lot right these are a lot too I don't
even like these like that like that
wasn't even my point you what I'm saying
is no I was kind of like I I was making
too much point I don't want to see FES
out at CVS yeah you know I'm thinking
more of like why is it I hate Trends
becoming a thing and everybody's like oh
I have to hop on the norm I need the
like think of 2019 I need the shell
necklace and the the shoes and I need
the the cups and the metal straws like
even now like the Stanley Cups lead your
own step take your own stride I want to
see people just being more openly
themselves what like I hate Trends
Trends should all die everyone's doing
it it's like un fun try and be creative
beautiful Nick that was deep that was
beautiful it's not that deep I just want
to see people like if you're like if you
want to go outside if you want to get
like there you know how many people
think oh I want to dye my hair this
color I want to do this I want to do
that and they don't do it out of fear of
peer pressure [ __ ] your peers they're
ugly it's that's the thing if I want to
dye my hair and I say it as an idea and
someone goes oh that wouldn't look good
you shouldn't do that you're [ __ ]
ugly
if you're going to say something about
the way I look it's like dude stop it
stop stop projecting your insecurity cuz
you know you have a [ __ ] ass haircut
right now you're projecting what could
possibly happen to me at least I'm
willing to take that chance I don't know
that's how I feel though
yeah good good idea incoming
uh-oh I think we rent a retro pickup
truck for the whole summer W love that
idea like a vintage yeah of course you
can and we just ride around in our truck
as three Bros all in M can you stop
saying
[ __ ] Nick why threw up that's gross what
did I use for dinner pizza Buffalo lucky
it's not on Buffalo a it's not oh my God
how is it every single time we're in the
car I just ate Buffalo that's happened
the last like four car videos I'm a big
buffalo wing guy just recently found
this out when I was a kid I didn't love
buffalo wings but I grew up and I love
them dude I don't know that's a [ __ ]
very frequent experience right last time
I burped you were like oh did you eat
buffalo wings I was like yeah I atat
buffalo wings that's crazy yeah that is
pretty wild the odds are with you
Buffalo Wild somebody got
shot someone recently just got shot at
our local buffalo wings crazy pray up oh
is he coming to take a photo of our
license plate no dude he's going home he
just ended a shift [ __ ] out of here
don't do that
put your middle finger up toward people
he was looking yeah but it's still
[ __ ] up get the [ __ ] away from me I
was saying something oh yeah I know I
think we should definitely get a pickup
truck or something what's he doing I'm
sort some sort of like nice truck and
drive around his Bros I'm so oh this is
what I was going to yell at you about no
I enough with the as Bros what ni we are
triplet siblings if you pitch an idea to
us you don't have to tell me as Bros
it's never anything but correct we could
go home and take a [ __ ] as Bros we can
go home play a board game as Bros go to
bed as Bros rock climb rock climb rock
climb rock climb anything we do is as
Bros so [ __ ] off you're making it you're
making it seem like it's like a romantic
level and it's weird I want to dance
with Matt as Bros no do you want to kiss
him as Bros to ni just tell me
everything if you're going to be mat
tell us something that's on your mind I
want to hear from you no I feel like you
often keep things in your head you
should just throw it out there tonight
there's High odds I piss myself tonight
what you I when I scroll on my for you
page I'm seeing edits not just of me of
actresses movies all that type of stuff
right watched a romcom when I had Co no
yep on my for you page and edit for that
movie which is crazy cuz that's like the
first time ever that like an edit you
know you know you watched a romcom what
type of movie correct right it's getting
weird liked it liked it you like the
movie or the Tik Tok the the the the Tik
Tok the romantic comedy Tik Tok well
both yeah liked them both liked the Tik
Tok turns out that that fan page that
makes edits for movies is also a fan of
us cool right saw that I liked it
screenshotted it posted it and everybody
was making fun of me what movie who's
making fun of you no one's making fun of
me I just I just thought it was so funny
who's doing like what are the odds
say what I would do if someone made fun
of you in okay you know how we were
watching the Batman movie I Am the
Shadows correct yeah how what wait what
is it not not the Batman The Dark Knight
and then we start I'm not wearing hockey
pads yeah what's the with the quot I'm
not anyway we were watching that started
talking about Heath Ledger the boss told
me to get him can you [ __ ] off and he's
like no he told talking about Heath
Ledger
yeah oh yeah cuz cuz we had the Heath
Ledger conversation cuz we only knew him
from Batman correct so so I watched the
romcom that he in that was free on
Disney Plus what's it called 10 Things I
Hate About You great movie really really
good movie and and it's like yeah and
he's completely this is why it's also
crazy this is why I can't Matt no but
it's also crazy cuz like watching that
movie and then the Dark Knight it it
really does show how crazy talented he
was cuz the dark the dark like playing
The Joker and then playing like a high
school kid the [ __ ] dance and going
to high school class and [ __ ] his acting
switch was insane how often do you watch
movies alone not often at all Nick how
about you actually frequently actually
very often yeah I you I'm so mad that
someone said something about you
watching this movie no but I watch m i
watch movies like that that I wouldn't
think you guys would like you know what
I mean God I hate never watch it's also
like I'm not going to be like hey guys
let's go watch a romcom together as Bros
you know as Bros as Bros I this what
drives me [ __ ] crazy Ro people show
interest in anything R that's the issue
in this world that's the issue we have
do you guys think that they when they
were inventing the wheel dude I can't
talk about the
wheel [ __ ] yourself a circle idiot what
came first the circle with the wheel CC
Circle 100% well Nick you're I don't
like that I don't like that take I don't
like that take what your little take of
what came first the circle of wheel I
don't like that the circle obious
what what came first what came first the
triangle of the tortilla chip obviously
the [ __ ] triangle yeah something's
invented like it's not it's obviously
the shap well think about it how long
ago the [ __ ] wheel was wa Nick what
came first the rectangle or the
door exactly tricky you're just like you
can't you can't be like oh what came
first well no it's like there's no way
something they made oh my God I'm
getting cramps cuz of how bad I have to
piss is do you think when they invented
the wheel it like took them a while to
put four on a car or like do you think
they tried to make like a a two a twofer
a two-seater a two- wheeled mobile or
like three dude there was a two- whe
mobile it was called a chariot no it was
called a bik that was forck Yan two Yan
two two big wheels oh you're right
yanked via horse I need a chariot and a
horse and quick if you had a horse why
would you name
it lucky good horse name good horse name
hor shoes good horse name I'd name him
Sunshine oh my God how trash
horsey how did I see that coming how I
see Mr horsey creeping his way about
maybe unicorn unicorn okay unicorn the
horse jeez you're isane I just want to
chry it so bad because the how historic
of a city Boston is like I want to go to
where Paul Riv found the Lantern and I
want he didn't have a chariot he was
just on a horse yes but I want to take
it in the horse so you want to be lazy
you
want I want to go into Boston via
Chariot and horse and
say okay and then the horse
like I love a horse pitter patter
sound like think about it when a horse
like I want to ride a horse oh my God I
have to peal
peees out
actually that was so embarrassing that
was actually too embarrassing to keep in
I can't keep that in to stop laughing
all right all right if I were to name a
horse what would I name it oh no one
asked you Matt did [ __ ]
face I was just ow thank you God I have
to pee Nick you're not don't I probably
bus bu oh my God cuz it's like the the
modern bus is the old horse yeah an old
horse is just the bus if you think about
it a horse is
no cuz they're more than that they have
a heart and
feelings I love I love hey I love hay
favorite videos on Tik Tok are when they
cut off like the they trim the horse's
toenails it was either that or Hooves
when they trim when they shut up they're
just gling this horse's hoov it was
either that or stone foot Stone foot dud
or Iron Iron Horse Iron Claw where is he
bringing you to battle no I love an idea
a ho a hoov all right right guys thank
you so much for 6 mil I think we hit it
that's like 6 million people classic
that's like think about it though think
of think of 6 million people in wait we
should do what we used to do and Google
what 6 million people look like I'm
about to say something crazy I saw what
you Googled the population of
Massachusetts is 7 million so so we are
one less million of the entire
population of the state of Massachusetts
all subscribing to our Channel I need to
go home and close my eyes the state we
grew up in we're a million million shy
of of every single
population well thank you guys so much
for 6 million people it shocks us each
every single day and we are so thankful
that there's a single person out there
that wants to create and be I mean not
create but look and just at what we
spend time with us it's all about I just
think of it as like we are spending time
with 6 million people people who love us
enjoy our presence we help a lot of
people and it just blows my mind and it
feels good it blows my mind that there's
anybody out there that looks at me and
be like oh that kid's funny cuz
personally I'd say that kid's psychotic
and terrifies me but people don't say
that yeah they're really nice so it's
just wild you guys are amazing and it
just it shocks me every single day it's
been a wild rides from I'd be happy with
one subscriber amen Nick and there's 6
million of them yep and a lot of them
tune in to see what we're going to do
and care about what we do every day and
that's something to constantly remind
myself when I'm feeling down Nick you're
so 6 million people there's 6 million
people who care about you and want to
know what's up in your life it's crazy
cuz it's also like just being in this
parking
lot I'm feeling good tonight trip of
that as crazy as that is it is crazy
well we hit 6 million subscribers as
brothers as Bros as Bros we did do as
Bros we hit 6 million subscribers bye
love you all thank you so much for 6
million
[Music]
sub