hey everyone last video we posted we
were in the car and Chris said everybody
pray for Nick he's got a stuffy
[Music]
nose everyone pray for Nick he has a
stuffy nose pray for to a stuffy nose I
think I'll make it the pray for
neck what I'm totally fine turns out I
had Corona
virus anyways here has been our life
Adventure while we've endured the Corona
virus Nick tested positive for covid
like the second we finished that car
video last week um and then Matt tested
yesterday which is like 3 days later and
he's also positive so we're currently
getting attacked by covid and I am the
last one of us to get it um I'm negative
as of this morning I tested negative
dude I it's so uncomforting to Vlog in
bed but um I tested negative this
morning for covid I'll probably get it
tomorrow literally I called Nick this
morning I go hey I know you have Co
match just tested positive doesn't say
anything else he goes you're
next movies fortnite sleep movies
fortnite sleep movies fortnite sleep I
guess we're vlogging on our own I was
told to do this I got a pounding
headache I don't know what to talk about
I'm
bored um I was just eating this Heath
bar right here and I can't I swear to
God I didn't finish it but I don't know
where the rest went I have a feeling
it's hiding somewhere on my bed for it
oh my God it's right right there it's on
the teddy
bear hey guys I was going to update
you about my night but
it's oh my
God oh my
God I still have my headphones
on little room
status Nick and C's rooms are
dirty and disgusting right now cuz
obviously I've seen pictures and stuff
this is the only thing dirty about my
room is my unmade
bed everything else is clean
right I can do clothes dirty and I can
do bed dirty and the bed's not made cuz
that's the only other than this chair
that's all I've been for the past what 3
days
now and I can do that I can do that type
of dirty the second it's food dirty in
here
food dirty like I'm talking food dirty
like there's a million spoons
everywhere you got leftover burgers and
french fries sitting on your PC like you
got Coke cans and this and that count me
the out I can't be with with a food
mess like that I have all my clothes
everywhere right here um space camp lip
balm go shop I just ate these BJ Brew
House
sliders they're right there I didn't
finish them I got some shoes Panera
Panera mac and cheese peanut &m
Coca-Cola Cherry this I would have Pepsi
guys don't flame me but this is Nick's
doing I was going to update you guys
forever ago but then I played fortnite
and it's like 7:30 in the morning I am
positive for covid it's day three of me
having
Co good night I'm going to bed I'll see
you in the morning good night we just
got off fortnite I'm about to go to bed
I'm really scared to wake up tomorrow
with Co I still don't have it and I
still feel great like I feel fine right
now but both times Nick and Matt have
like both of them tested positive right
after a night's sleep I'm about to go to
bed I'll upload y tomorrow good
night hello just woke up it's almost
3:30
p.m. and everybody has texted me and
asked me how I'm feeling and the best
way that I can describe my feeling right
now or the way I've texted everybody
back has been that it feels like I ate a
40 lb dumbbell and I just have the
entire weight of a 40 lb dumbbell in my
entire
head but other than that I feel great
now I'm going to go take a
shower chill out and then probably play
fortnite watch a movie or go back to bed
so
good morning everybody I just woke
up I feel fine I feel
great but I have to go test I'm going to
turn my light on get dressed and then
test ooh that was a little rhyme but I
feel like I'm about to test negative
which is good I don't feel sick at all
right
now
let me go get up and
test hey guys I know I'm in a very
similar position to when you just last
saw me but it's been an entire night and
the sun's already set again and I just
woke up well that's my pile of
[Music]
Reese's dude why is it so bright
on this camera feel like I'm seeing the
rise of Jesus all right guys let's say a
little prayer
please dear God keep this
infectious covid-19 away from me I don't
want it I don't want anything to do with
it I'd like to leave my house in the
next few days so please just give me a
negative test I feel good I feel fine
I've been washing my hands with soap and
water soap and warm water may may I
add Nick's trying to fix this camera
right Nick what's your
solution bashing it on the
counter I don't want no false
negative the fact that we're still like
vlogging with Co makes me laugh so hard
like why normal people would be like
yeah I'm not posting a video this week
yeah I know going to be us soon so yeah
no Yeah we actually can't post on um the
20 the 29th for a podcast oh oh
yeah no Co for me no Co for
me I pretty much tested negative there's
a very very faint line so the t hold on
let me spin my
camera oh my God don't mind how dirty my
countertop is but there's like the
slightest line ever at the tea so I'm
going to wait till tomorrow to leave my
room one because I might still be
contagious with Co two because I don't
want to leave my room
and also Chris is still testing negative
so I don't want to go near him until I
can like clean my room and like assure
that I am no longer going to give him Co
but tomorrow I should be good I like we
had all this like trash and recycle
right here so I just went through it and
just put it there so it's ready to get
thrown
away but I didn't actually go bring it
down to the trash because I don't want
to pass Chris's room just in case so
I've been staying here my bathroom in
the
kitchen and I recently added these to my
bathroom I don't know if it's like cool
or if it's
like
stupid but there's Bears he's in the
bathtub you know this is where I dry off
so like sometimes that's just like me
you know I stand right there and do the
same thing probably going to go clean
the kitchen and stuff too and just tell
Chris to stay in his room cuz our
house is a mess cuz Nick and
Chris love to just leave
everywhere so there's that and I'll keep
you all yall updated on some more anyway
I finally put all my clothes in the
laundry that were dirty and I cleaned up
all that clothes
um yeah cleaning my room made me realize
how little I actually have in this room
like furnished it's kind of sad like
look at that whole side of the room is
like empty and then I have like my my
desk with that I bought at Home Depot
for like 20 bucks and then my PC and my
chair my bed TV and like literally just
this poster but my room's so empty but
like honestly I've been thinking about
it like me Matt Nick suck at Furnishing
our house because I feel like we just
like for me personally I just feel like
my vibe changes so much like I bought
this bed thinking it was going to be
awesome and that I was going to like
love it so much whatever and like it has
like drawers on the side and the
front and I'm like dude I'm not 10 years
old anymore like I just need like a real
bed with like no drawers like that's
such like a little kid thing to have is
like a bed with like shelves for
my little clothes like all right all
right all right room tour first my
closet there's so many clothes like
everywhere so just like you know keep
that in mind like my closet's amazing
and
[Music]
wonderful I feel like I could sing a
song in
here it's like a little Echo chamber as
I was cleaning my room I was
just um texting Nick and Matt and I
decided to dance like really really fast
and send them like a funny video of me
dancing and
um I literally got a headache because of
it like really bad cuz I was like moving
around and I was like I texted them I
said one of two things just happened I
either danced too hard or just got
Co yeah yeah yeah you
[Music]
make oh my God I just like two lights in
here there's not just one there's two
light bulbs don't you battle with my
lary
tonight all right that was my closet
that was an experience I just I figured
I'd show you guys that it's still empty
so you may be asking I just almost said
my name before I said asking you may be
asking Nick where are all your
clothes well there's some right
here this lovely rack in the middle of
my
room you may have just asked yourself a
minute ago Nick what is this thing that
you have there I'll go back in my closet
to show you so I saw this on Shark Tank
forever
ago I'm actually kind of scared to do
this I saw it on Shark Tank forever ago
and this is called a chirp wheel and
it's supposed to like crack and stretch
your back and I always have consistent
back pain so I thought I'd get it but
I'll I'll use it to show you guys what
it does this is a very vulnerable
position so I'm putting this shirt over
my
crotch I cannot believe this video of me
is going to be on the internet hold
on
it's not working it's not working it's
not
[Music]
working yesterday I literally got a
notification for my health app that was
like hey we um we sense a little bit of
laziness I'm sorry that that's just like
an insane call out but they it literally
called me out cuz it took less than 100
yesterday which in theory is not good
but like I'm sick and I don't really
have anywhere to step to but like less
than 100 steps is sickening
actually so I'm I think at some point
today I'm just going to paste my
room like that sounds like absolutely
insane but I think like I'll just like
go from like door to shelf over there
back like 40 times but I just woke up I
feel phenomenal so I hope I test
negative again last night I took another
covid test because I sent Nick and I
think I already vlogged this but I sent
Nick and matad a video like dancing
really really fast Nick's probably going
to like put it in this video while he
edits or something I hope he doesn't cuz
it was a really terrible disturbing
video of me trying to dance but um well
not trying I wasn't trying to like be
good at it went to bed woke up I feel
great I'm going to covid test
again hopefully I'm still negative
that's my goal it's Tuesday this video
comes out tomorrow
sorry for the indoor Vlog this week but
like obviously we couldn't do anything
cuz of Co good morning it's day 4 I just
woke
up um I realized I forgot that I had a
meeting so I have to take a meeting in
like 10 minutes on a zoom but I just
took my covid test before so we'll find
out today if I'm positive or negative
moving
forward 10 11 12 13 14 15 16
17 18 19 20 21
also while I'm here I'm going to
Vlog while I'm waiting for my test to
come
back 24 25 26 27 28 29 I just want to
say a big thank you to Prime my people
over at uh Prime hydration by Logan Paul
I love their green flavor the lemon lime
and so I begged Logan Paul himself I
went knock out his front door and I said
Logan please get me the green Prime
please I need it bad
30 31 32 33 34 and then was at my door
he pulled some strings he figured it out
and um I got a case of the green ones
upstairs and I got the little Prime
sticks shout outs to you Logan
Paul 35 36 37 38 39
40 41
42 I'm kidding by the way I don't know
Logan Paul at all personally I just dm'
Prime and said yo Prime hook your boy up
I hope you guys got that joke like I
hope none of you thought I actually went
to Logan Paul's house that'd be
crazy 48 49 50 51
52 don't actually don't do that that's a
lesson let's learn from that guys let's
not show up to random people's homes why
is it so bright I feel like
every time I record myself I don't do it
right so I also haven't seen sunlight in
a couple of days so I'm going to go to
my window over here which I never I
never in my entire life
open this window cuz I never just like I
never have like a need to open the
window I don't know for one of in my
room but we're going to open it and see
the
sunlight oh the Sun is
setting I got like 20 minutes
probably
can't say I didn't
try all right guys look at
this where's the thing Co free negative
y'all this thing of cheeseburgers and
french fries has been on my floor for
like 4 days in a row not lying all right
y'all saltburn is being continued right
now first note I want to take if I ever
got called
a a boot
licker it's going down it's going down
immediately I got me and my boy Nathan
right here
guys Monumental moment right here it's
my best friend ride or die love this kid
more than I love anybody else in this
world besides Nick and Matt and Justin
and my
family so yeah I keep it up there to
remind myself that There's real in this
world Nathan do liveing proof I just got
nothing but nice things to say about my
friend I don't know why I'm just
rambling about your my friend right now
but like this is a lesson guys in life
if you have a good friend make it known
that they're a good friend that's a
lesson that I've learned cholo 101 if
you have a friend and you appreciate
them make it known that you appreciate
them because a lot of times in this
world sometimes you forget to thank the
people you got to thank most
damn I'm getting I'm spitting bars right
now be like a beverage count of how many
cans or cups I throw away Coke Vanilla
Coke Cherry can Coke Cherry Coke Cherry
lemon lime Gatorade SEL and
Gro I think there was mac and cheese in
this but I'm not sure Poland Springs
Water Poland Springs Water Poland
Springs Water Coke vanilla
Coke vanilla raspberry bubbly SEL and
Gro lemon lime Gatorade lemon sherbet
bubbly this one got a sip left in
[Music]
it good
movie Crazy
concept good movie Crazy concept
concept very
strange pretty good though very strange
but pretty good but for real sometimes
it's the people you appreciate most that
you tell the least and you just got to I
I make it awkward bro I'm never a man to
fear awkwardness I'll go straight up to
somebody and be like you know what I
really value our friendship and I think
you're amazing and a lot of people are
uncomfortable by it cuz they hate
overwhelmingly positive stuff like Nick
like if I went up to Nick and I was like
Nick I'm so happy you're my brother he'd
be like oh thanks like I appreciate it
thank you thumbs up but I know deep down
he appreciates that and so does everyone
if anyone got a super positive message
they'd appreciate it just some people
don't know how to react
1,000 oh god I didn't even see you guys
there I was just uh you know making sure
I got enough physical activity today cuz
I didn't get enough steps yesterday I
will say I'm feeling the best I felt
right now than I have this entire video
right in this moment so I think tomorrow
I might be waking up to a negative test
or a very almost negative test and I
think in about a day and a half your boy
out of here what is up guys it's
Wednesday night
um wow my hair looks really bad um so
I'm done vlogging here I hope you
enjoyed our Co Adventures I'm sorry that
this video wasn't like the rest of them
yeah thank you guys for watching today's
video and also probably no podcast or
definitely no podcast next Monday
unfortunately just because of like the
timing we can't film one because of um
Co and everything but love you guys
thank you so much for watching peace out
see you well thank you guys for watching
this week's video I am now finally
negative with
Co so I can now live my life
[Music]
freely
oh