Yeah, pump that gas, sexy boy. Yeah, I
need you to get the [ __ ] out my face.
It's like broken. I've been It's broken.
No.
Look at me.
Look at this. You're in LA. Trusting
you. I know. Hold this.
I'm Guys, I want to shave my face so
bad, but I'm taking photos in a couple
days and I I need to like time it
perfectly. So that's why I have like all
this on my face and I hate it. Let's get
a closeup. No, get the [ __ ] away, dude.
Well, yeah, you look horrible. Situation
going on. You look horrible, too.
Hi. How are you?
Oh my god. How are you? How are you?
Nice to meet you. Oh my god.
[Applause]
Great trip. Let's address the rumors.
What rumors?
The rumors, Nick. I hear the rumors
talking. Address the rumors, Nick. What?
That mat looks bad in pink and red
stripes. There are no rumors. I just
wanted to see if you'd say something
like off the top of your head and I did.
You're [ __ ] gross. And you only ever
burp when there's a camera on and that
true. It's cuz I just drank this drink.
It doesn't matter, Chris. It just makes
I just drank this drink, you idiot. My
diet Dr. Kel. Wonderful. Hey guys,
welcome back to this week's Friday
video. It's Nick, Matt, and Chris. Here
we are sat at our Oh god, you hand this
kid a microphone, he starts talking like
a robot, literally. Hello. Good
greetings, Earthlings. It is Nick. I
actually just I am filming on a
microphone. Hey guys, what is up, guys?
Welcome back to our [ __ ] channel. Me,
Matt, and Nick found our old old podcast
equipment from like 2 years ago and we
were going to start a podcast in my
bedroom in Boston and we decided, oh my
god, let's see if that works. And by
doing so, we bought a picnic basket and
some picnic [ __ ] Picnic We're not start
We're not starting a podcast. We just
thought it was funny and we saw the
equipment and we were like, "Fuck it.
We're just We have a [ __ ] picnic
podcast." Yeah. This is what we wanted
to do like 2 years ago and we were like,
"What the hell?" We found this [ __ ] all
in our garage and we were like, "Why the
[ __ ] not?" So, now we just have a picnic
basket and some food and some questions
and we're going to do that today and
it's honestly going to be really fun.
So, basically, Matt went and bought a
bunch of mystery items and filled up
this picnic basket. Oh my god. Hold on.
Oh my god. And then Nick filled up this
little ceramic cup thing with like
random questions. It's a vase that me
and Matt don't vase. That looks like a
ginormous mug. Yeah, this is just
missing a handle. Yeah, that looks like
a huge mug. I really like it. Matt, tell
Nick what you just told me in the
parking lot. No.
Okay, I'm fine with What are we doing?
Question boy and picnic basket. Also, I
bought this picnic basket for this
video, but it's like really cute. Oh, I
love it. It looks I like that it has
like little underwear on it. I just
can't believe we're not sitting. I feel
like if I open it, I'm kind of like
taking its panties off type [ __ ] Don't
say [ __ ] That's a really freaky and
weird thing to say. That's like really
weird. It's like a little lacy set for
the picnic basket. Dude, you're you need
to stop. Yo, check out my new Sternolo
Triplets merch. What a crazy little ad.
Sternolo Triplets surprise party tour.
Yeah, if you are if you are wanting tour
merch, we have tour merch
available. Check out my hood from the
link in description. And this is our
tour merch that is going to be sold
during our tour on our merch website.
Let's get into this. Come on. Some Whoa.
What is the first thing here? See, I'm
very uninterested in having apple cider
right now. That's not apple cider, you
[ __ ] It's sparkling cider.
What's your favorite type of cider?
Um, I don't know. Apple. What about
dickens cider?
Dude. Dude, what was the fake name that
dude? Dude, what was the fake name Matt
used this morning that was in Morehead?
Craig Raven Morehead.
It sounds like a really good like
It sounds like a really good That's a
fake laugh. No, it's not a really good
horror movie character. Craven Morehead.
No, we got a squirter. Nick. Yeah, Nick.
Hurry up. Hurry up, Nick. Hurry up.
Hurry up. Run. Stop. Matt, you're going
to get your hand all sticky. No, I'm
not. Open it, Chris. Guys, I have only
had water for all of 2024. Should I
break that sweet? Yes, 100%. Stop being
a baby and drink something other than
water. No, Matt, don't do this.
Oh, I can't watch it. I can't watch it.
I can't watch it. I can't watch it. I
can't watch it. I can't watch it. I
can't watch it. I just think of his
tooth flying out of his mouth. I can't
watch it. Kid almost cut my finger off
when he went to grab that. Oh my god. He
almost cut my finger off. Woo! Turn me
into a
dog. Let me do this, please. Can Can I
do it, Nick? I'm chipping away. I'll
stab you in the I'll stab you in the
neck. Give it to me, Matt. In the neck.
There's nothing I hate more than
something that just happened to me. And
when Matt took the lid off of this, he
threw it at my head and it lightly
grazed the back of my head and flew
behind me. And I've said this countless
times before. My least favorite thing on
the face of the earth
stop is being lightly grazed. I [ __ ]
hate it more than anything. If something
were to like slightly touch my hand,
slightly touch my arm, I want to
destroy. What about your ball sack? Like
when it rubs up against my back, like a
slight touch to the sack. In what
context? Like if No, you just said you
don't like being slightly grazed. You
started listing body parts and I want to
know about your sack. If something
slightly grazed my ball sack. Is this
what you're asking? Is I don't know if I
like this podcast.
Jokes that we normally make. Seems so
serious. Well, Chris just asked me if
being slightly grazed in my ball sack
area would bother me. And I think the
answer is yes. I do. For me, it's never
like bothersome because it's almost a
sense of how often is this happening?
because it's almost a sense of relief
that it wasn't full-fledged contact. All
right, can we get into something in this
basket or little naughty question? You
want to know what I do often? What? I
click on depot instead of Door Dash.
Never happened to me ever. And then I'm
like, why is Door Dash selling $20
current day issues?
Let's throw that one on the screen. Make
it a viral thing. Huh? Yeah, let's do
it. #curren What was it? Current day
issues. Yeah. Yeah. Like millennial
problems.
Gen Gen Z issues. Do you do you know
what you are? Nah, I think I'm Gen Z.
What are we at? Who? What's being alpha
or gen beta? I think it's Craven.
Is it Craven Morehead? I think this
generation Craven Morehead. I think it's
Craven Morehead. Is this new generation
generation Craven Morehead? Has to be
one of the funniest things I've ever
heard. All right, let me open one of
these questions, please. What the What
else is in here? It's Matt's mystery B.
No, there's so many things in Why would
the [ __ ] would you do that? Cuz I'm
curious. No, no idea what's happening.
It's Matt's thing. Shuffle them around
first. No way. I just pulled this one.
What does it say? What does it say? What
do you mean? Oh, thank you. For the
picnic. A shakuderie snack board. Have
you ever met someone for the picnic? Are
you ready? Have you ever met someone
named Craven
Morgan? What's one family rule we had
that in hindsight was completely
unnecessary? Um, I would say no
swearing.
I mean, it that rule ended up backfiring
because now it's my favorite swear all
the time every day. Yeah, I'll tell you
right now. I love salami. Chill. I don't
want you to eat it. You like pepperoni?
I do. I love pepperoni. Why does your
salami look different than mine? Cuz
this is pepperoni and that's salami. Oh,
so it is different. I got salami. What
are you asking? What's the question at
hand? I'm asking why his salami looked
different but on The untold secret was
it was pepperoni. The secret was told.
There was no secret. Do you want to know
the keeper of untold secrets? Yes. His
name is Craven
Moore. I go hot and I make it look easy.
They're the coolest. Okay. I know. I got
Nick one of these. All right. Just got
this. Are you Sorry. Are you guys
enjoying these things? Yeah, they're a
little hard, but when I don't like them
when you mix it with cheese, it's fire.
Vanilla cupcake goldfish. I know how
much you love them. [ __ ] I know. Matt
just bought the grossest thing in the
store. Holy [ __ ] I know how much those
mean to you.
I wish you gave these to me first cuz
now I got salami in my face and I want
this instead.
No, seriously. Thank you, Matt. Wait, is
there someone behind the camera? It's
Craven. This Oh my god, it's Craven.
This joke isn't funny anymore. Just
kidding. It's the
I literally just heard your echo stop.
It took that full four seconds. I'm
taking another question. It took four
[ __ ] seconds to miss you. I'm taking
another question out of this. My energy
is on top level, Doug.
I kind of really want a soda. I wish I
didn't drink that. I love when Nick
moves around like I just don't want
anything I got. Well, no, Matt. It's
like I It's like you got me [ __ ] This
is the the the picnic essentials, dude.
Oh my god.
It kind of looks like Daffy Duck is
yelling at himself like in a in an
infinite glitch. You are the [ __ ]
weirdest person I know. You know what I
mean? Look, he's like, "Hey." And then
it goes to the next one and he's like,
"Whoa." And then he's like saying it
essentially. Do you think it's
exclusively hey and wo or do you think
he's just No, those are my
interpretations. If your brain was a
house, what weird room would you have in
it?
Okay. Um, I definitely would have a room
where like there's like a guy at the
door and he stands at the door and he's
like, "Is this going to be Hello, I'm
Craven Morhead." And he's like, "It's
the Craven Morehead layer." Okay, so
this is the room in my house. I'm going
to set this. I don't think that's the
question, but in my brain house, imagine
you walk into the room. Okay, close your
eyes. It's pitch black out of nowhere.
Craven. If you guys know, if there's one
more Craven Morhead joke, I'm walking
off. Then you walk up, you open the
room, you still can't see anything. It's
pitch black. You try to feel around
what's in there. So, you walk in one
step, another another. You find yourself
in a very dark room in the dead center
and you look back and the only light is
admitting through the doorway you just
came in. Boom. LeBron James. The doorway
shuts. No. The lights turn on and you
look down and the whole floor is covered
by treadmills and it goes zoom zoom zoom
and it starts speeding up and now you
have to move forward and you look back
and there's just no the wall that you
came in on is gone and there's just a
steep drop down afterward. What does
this represent for you mentally? And
then you just have to start running and
running and running and running. Never
know what happens until you stop
running. I'm taking a guess that you
would fall if you stopped running. Nope.
If I had a room in my brain, it would be
There we go.
What are you saying? Here we go. Like
you didn't just say the stupidest answer
to mankind. Are we going to like ignore
that or what? So, let me guess. Are you
in a really dark dark dark No, I'm
actually Then all of a sudden, Craven
Morehead in a LeBron James jersey walks
in. Go ahead, Matt. Go ahead. Sorry.
It's 5:57 on a spring evening and the
and the sun is about to set but it's not
fully set. So, it's kind of like that
cloudy gray that it gives. 557. Yeah. In
spring. Yes.
The the winter soul size didn't change
the time yet. So, it's like springy
weather and it's like it's I love the
adjective springy. It's it's it's on the
verge of like it's like hoodie at the
campfire weather, but also like you had
shorts and a t-shirt on the whole day.
That type of vibe. And it's a c it's a
it's a treehouse in the top of a 750T
tree. Oh, 750T. I'd be scared out of my
[ __ ] And that's it. 750T tall tree is
insanity. Yep. And it's a giant spiral
staircase all the way down. Or it's a
Or it's a monkey pulled elevator. Monkey
pulled.
No, hold on. Seems like a lot. No, it's
not. That's it. I feel like maybe like a
little tree excavator. And it's like an
excavator, but it's like an escalator.
What's an esavator? Is that a thing? An
esavator is like a construction site.
Like a big chewing in the mic, by the
way, too. An elevator, but it's made by
like woodbinding apes. What the [ __ ] is
going on? No, I think an actual room in
my head would be like a Nick. Do you
know who Josh Allen is? No. He's married
to I think there would be like a really
cool Here's a hint. He plays for the
Buffalo Bills. What position?
Quarterback. Whoa. That was good, Nick.
Nice. That was really good. Good work.
Thank you. Thank you. That moment when
Nick defies all odds. Yep. Okay.
Defhound.
I'm
defying gravity.
All right, we're going to rifle off
these questions. We're going to like get
really like we're going to we have to be
entertaining. Hold on. Let me take my
sweater off. Okay, are we ready?
Defying gravity. No wizard that there is
or what? Would any of you guys like a
slim gym before we start? [ __ ] No,
dude. Did you go into the grocery store
and say, "Let me get the nastiest things
that I can even [ __ ] buy." Fig. What?
Fig Newton. Who goes? Imagine checking
it. I'm just trying to imagine the
cashier vanilla covered yogurts. Oh my
god. What is wrong with you? I was
trying to be picnicy. I was trying to be
all picnic vibes. I think you failed
tremendously. But no, you didn't like
little like cracker [ __ ] gyms. I I
think that like in my personal hell
would be like it'd be like while I'm
waiting in purgatory while they decide
my fate, they're like they like feed me.
I was going to say a crazy thing. I was
going to say like a neverending slim
joke, but that's like insane. But like
like dream like what? Your biggest
dream. Okay, Nick. I actually your room
and your whipped cream and I'm like what
the [ __ ] are you? My biggest dream is a
never- ending meat stick. Shut your
mouth. I got you. Dude, you said it. I
didn't. No, I You literally said it. I
didn't. No, you implied. It hit your
brain first. You were the first one to
bring up a never- ending. You were the
first person to bring up Craven Warhead.
So, yeah. Newsp fire. Um, Nick, this one
you'll actually like. I got you dots,
dude. These Oh, no. They're all stuck
together. No, they're not. Open it. Mac,
can I see it? You probably bought the
most heinous possible things on the
planet at the grocery store. Like right
in my face. You wanted to see it and I
forgot that like you had to be conscious
that I was throwing it at you. Is it?
Anybody want uh Mr. Beast Bar? I really
don't. Is there an almond one? I already
said no. They didn't. I'm good. Okay.
Anybody want Pixar gummies?
What did you do?
Ow. That's what you get. You want Pixar
gummies? What happened to you? There's
like a sharp thing in there, Matt.
Nobody wants these. And you don't
either. This slim gym's kind of like
weirdly. I do want a Pixar gummy. I knew
you did. They're right there. Like cuz
these look really unique. How quickly
you guys know that game show and it's
like the things pop up on the screen.
How well do you think cheesecake apple
pie chocolate chip cookie first
name now that you're choosing this? I
was going to say first one to name
Nemo's dad, but I said his name by
accident. Try again. What was his name?
Mark.
Marlin. Marlin. Mark. Yeah, he was a
[ __ ] white
man. Yeah, Mark. Nemo's dad's flipping
some burgers on Fourth of July.
Okay, give me I feel like everybody has
an Uncle Mark. We don't have an Uncle
Mark. So, already done there, right? I
came up with some good questions. Let's
go through these. Okay. If you had to
fight a clone of yourselves, what would
be your strategy? Oh my god. Crispy
cream donuts at the top of the stairs
with a spike trap. I would really want
to strike panic into my own self. So,
what I would do is I would hide in my
room and wait for the lights to shut
off. Cuz this is a serious fear of mine.
I have a fear that the second my lights
go off in my room and I lay in bed at
night, someone's already in my bed. Oh
my god. With like a knife or something.
Like when I lift up my blanket, I just
slip it. Can I say my biggest fear when
I'm my most vulnerable is probably being
completely naked in the shower. Like
whenever I'm completely naked in the
shower, I completely always That's when
you have to get your clone. No, no, no.
Shower. Like I'd still be so
uncomfortable like immediately. What is
this thing for? It's me fixing my
posture cuz like this is what it is is
because like I'm fully naked and there's
no in the shower there's no fabric or
like cover anything covering my body.
When I'm in the shower I have this
immediate panic that like something's
just going to rip all the skin off my
body and I'm going to be like stuck.
This pepperoni is dog [ __ ] Dude, no one
gives a [ __ ] But do you know what I'm
saying? Whenever I whenever I like am
like whenever I look or focus too much
like I look at my hands I just imagine
like cutting off one of my fingers one
at a time with like hedge clippers or
something. What? That's not good, Nick.
No, like No, but like not in like a like
I want to do it. It's just like I I'd be
so afraid if that happened. I know
exactly how I'd get mad. Like the other
day I was cutting a pizza and I was
cutting like a with a pizza cutter and I
just imagine just like
right over your fingers. No, like my
whole body just skinning myself with the
[ __ ] pizza cutter.
Wow, that'd be so awful. Go ahead,
Chris. I would drive real slow in front
of Matt in the car in his clone and then
his clone behind would get real angry
and try to pass. And the second he
passes when he looks at me like, "Yo,
what the fuck?" I'd have a gun. Oh my
god. And then I'd just shoot him. Whoa.
Wait, what was the question?
I forget. I also was the question. How
would we get our clones? Was the
question a complete demise? If you had
to fight a clone of yourselves, what
would fight? to the death. I don't know.
I think my strategy would be go for like
the my knee pits first. Knee pits? Yeah.
I hate getting hit in my knee pit. You
know how when you like kick the back of
your knee pit and it folds your legs?
Oh, that's my biggest pet peeve. I think
I try to kidnap yourself. Me? Yeah. I
don't think you're trying to fight like
a fight to the death. You're trying to
fight yourself? Yes. You need to answer
this question for yourself. Is it Am I
trying to kill somebody? You're trying
to fight your clone. I don't know how.
It says fight your clone. Fight
yourself. So, you're not fighting me. If
you had to fight a clone of yourself,
what would be your Oh, okay. And it's
also like not to the death. It's like
fight. I already said mine, though. Hide
in the bed. Hide in your bed. I think
Chris, it would be so funny if you um I
just imagine Chris like going into his
room and like there's like a a snack on
the floor or something like he's a
carrot cake and it's on it's on like a
red visible target and he steps in it
and like a big mouse trap like a
humanized mouse. I would never, first of
all, ever grab carrot cake off my ground
and then just start eating it. Chris,
really, really dig deep and tell me
that's the truth. 100%. If there is a a
good That's obviously bait.
I'm never going to run into floor carrot
cake in my bedroom.
You would do it though for your your ass
would get caught in the buffalo chicken
one.
Slow down. Yeah, you heard me. Slow
down. Like a more realistic option is
like a Kit Kat. Like if I found a Kit
Kat, I'd be like, "Oh shit." Like it has
to be something that I could have just
told me that he leaves candy and money
in his pockets of his winter coats so
that when the winter comes around, candy
is not. When I was 10, I did candy.
You're an adult. Now I just do the
money. You just still do the money? Yes.
No. Do you think someone's head ever
exploded going into outer space?
Definitely. That's so scary.
Don't worry, Chris. No one's going to
make me go out. You want to know what I
would do if I was lost in space and I
and I came back? If I was lost in space,
I'd come back with the craziest lies
ever. I'd be like, "We landed on like a
planet very far out of our solar system
and there was other humans." What's that
big movie with the one with the planet
far away? Star Wars. Oh yeah, that's it.
Happy Gilmore 2. Okay. Need to rewatch
the first one and then I'll see what's
going on. Need to rewatch the first one.
The second. Was there a guy who died and
he saw a ghost? No. Yes. He got crushed
by the air conditioner or bit by the
crocodile. He got knocked out of the air
conditioner or bit by the crocodile.
That was that guy.
Was that the guy who died got bit by the
crocodile? Wait, I could also be
thinking of a totally different Adam
Sandler movie. No, because at the end
I'm pretty sure there's like three
people that seems like you know what I'm
talking about. I don't remember. I need
to rewatch this movie. Definitely an
Last time I saw Anthony the Crocodile
got one of them. Last time I saw that
movie, I was 12 years old. That movie is
so good to my remembrance. All right.
Freaking No. No. But also, he's a Bruins
fan. He is. He is. That's it.
Whoa. Go Bruins. Whoa. Can we talk about
how the Bruins traded Brad Maron?
Why would we trade Brad Marshon?
Thank you for that. Shopping up to
Boston.
Thank you for that. Freaky Friday. Yeah.
What the freakier Friday? Freaky Friday.
We should start calling Sternolo Friday.
Okay. Freaky Friday.
You're a dumbass. Just kidding. Freaky
Friday. The original. Yeah. Jamie Lee
Curtis. Lindsay Lohan coming back.
Freaky Friday. Freaky or Friday. Not
going to be as good. Definitely not
going to be as good. Not going to be as
good. My my
my um my expectations are low. Really? I
like how she was. My expectations are of
course low. The first movie was
unbelievable. First movie is really Is
that where she meets the guy at the
Chinese restaurant? Yes. The woman the
fortune cookie is is the reason
why sky high though. That's where um Oh
my god. No, not Blaze. What's his name?
Oh. Um, War in Peace. Yes. And um, he
like heats something up. And what's her
name? Ivy Girl. Ivy Girl. What's her
name? I don't know. Love her. Love her.
My favorite scene in that movie is when
she's with like the cheerleaders and the
cheerleaders are like and they're doing
their cheer and they're like they're
like turning into a bunch of different
girls and they're like and then they
like there's more of them and they're
doing like their whole routine and then
they like get mad at her because it was
like sidekick or hero and you're like a
hero if you have a good power and a
sidekick if you suck. And she like
didn't want to use her powers leave
anything for
she wanted to the girl start the grass
girl Ivy girl. No stop. The grass girl
believed she was like oh you could
she's like oh grass girl hit the
cheerleader and she was all like you can
only use your powers for good is what
she believed. So what she would do my
mic again and I'll [ __ ] slit your
throat. So what she would do is she
wouldn't use her powers if pro if told
to. She had to be provoked. So don't do
not pull another question. So what
happened was she was provoked by the
cheerleader girls to use her powers and
one of the hardest bars in the movie.
They're like, "Oh, we thought you were a
sidekick." And she's like, "I don't
know.
You forgot Nick." She's like, "I am a
sidekick or something." I don't know.
But it's cool. all that.
I literally don't remember what they
said. It was like
that was like all the girls. You're the
dumbest person I've ever met in my whole
life. I don't No, you remember I'm
talking about that. She's like Cuz the
the cheerleader girl cuz that's also
what was so [ __ ] sick is the
cheerleader girl. She's a twin. No. Is
she? Yeah. You're telling me cuz you
think that's what I'm going to say? I'm
telling you the truth. She Listen, she
listen. She was the whole [ __ ]
cheerleader squad cuz she could
teleport. No, she's a wife. No,
duplicate. Not teleport. What is that?
Duplicate. Yeah, cuz she was the whole
cheerleader squad cuz she was one
person. That was like nine people. There
was her superpower cuz she's a twin in
real life. What are you saying? It's
easier to clone somebody when there's
already two people to reference. Matt,
what I'm telling you is there was no
cheer squad for Sky High except her cuz
her superpower was cloning herself. So,
how [ __ ] sick is that? She's like,
she's What I'm telling you is that girl
in real life is a twin. I'm talking
about the fictional movie Sky. I don't
care. The person the I'm talking about a
superpower. The reason why she can
duplicate in the show is because instead
of making one girl duplicate eight
times, it's two girls and they made them
duplicate. Wrong. Because if you I I'm
not saying you're wrong that she's a
twin. I'm saying you're wrong that
that's the reason why she has the power.
Yes, of course it's easier. But Liv and
Maddie were both Dove Cameron. So, how
do you beat that one? Which I don't
believe. Like, they look totally
different. Chris, it literally glasses
and a [ __ ] side part was the only It
literally looks like two completely
different. And she's a good She was a
good like kid actor.
So, it was like I was like I was
convinced. Double the role.
If you had to describe your type using
only three fictional characters, who
would it be? Easy, easy, easy, easy,
easy. Candace from Phineas and FB, Sandy
Cheeks, and Nogops. Sandy Cheeks. Candy.
Candace from Phineas and Ferb. Yeah, cuz
she's kind of annoying. I'd probably say
Craven Morehead. Nick, stop. That's a
really good one. Um, I need What's that
dude that was always doing jumping jacks
for apples?
I have no clue. Who was doing the giving
tree? No, it was like a dude who was
doing jumping jacks for apples. Correct.
I have no clue who was doing jumping
jacks for apples. That's like Nick's
tight though. Who was doing jumping
jacks? Like some weird liveaction Sesame
Street or something. Liveaction Sesame
Street. I don't know. That's like the
We're talking about cartoon characters.
Chris, jumping jacks for apples. I don't
know, dude. What the [ __ ] are you
talking about? Come on. Can I go to the
next question? I probably Oh, Chris is
talking about um the dude that wears
blue in Oh my god.
Um Spicus.
Yeah, Sporicus, but he's not a cartoon.
But yeah, you're not wrong at all.
[ __ ] Thank you. Jumping Jacks for
apples. What a good little clue. Dafany
or Velma, to be honest. Both of them at
the same time. Both of them. Two bad
[ __ ] at the same damn time. Say no.
Not chancing along. At the same damn
time. Same damn time. Two bad [ __ ] at
the same damn time. Scooby Melman do.
You remember my favorite scene in the
Scooby-Doo live action movie is when
Scooby-Doo is at the end and he Well,
no, no. Early this is this whole thing
is just me explaining movies. Earlier on
in the movie, there's like a call and
it's for Scooby and they're trying to
like lure him out to the woods. They
call him on the phone. They're like,
"Oh, it's a call for Scooby." And then
or or it's a call for There's going to
be another You like to like, "Oh, we
have to figure out." I do remember this.
They're at like the bar at like Spooky
Island and there's a call and they're
like, "Oh, we need um we need
Scooby-Doo." And then the guy's like,
"Oh, uh is are you talking about me? I'm
Melman." And he's like, "No, like we
need Scooby." And then Scooby-Doo walks
over and answers the phone. And then at
the end, they're doing like the
possession, like Scooby-Doo is getting
possessed and they're like, "We need a
sacrifice." And Scrappy's like, "It's
going to be Scooby-Doo." And Scooby
goes, "Do you mean Melman do?" And he
points at the guy. That's really funny.
It's so [ __ ] funny. Okay, next. But I
want to just like sit and like allow a
Oh my god. You could trade one skill you
have for a completely random new one,
would you do it? I would want the
ability I don't know what skill I have
now that I'd trade actually fully know.
If I could trade the ability to edit
videos, if I I wish I could forget how
to edit videos that it was one of your
jobs. What I would do is what or what
ability I really want is to be able to
make a beautiful, gorgeous, perfect
house of cards with a full deck of 52.
Wow, that's really good. I would turn in
my ability of being a kind, thoughtful
guy into being the most evil person ever
and take over the city and get Craven
Morehead on your side. Next question. I
don't have an answer to that question.
And even if I did, Chris just ended my
opportunity. Money talks. Money talks.
Dirty cash. I want you. Dirty cash. I
need you.
I really love the genius design of the
feastable bar where it's unlike any
other chocolate. Do you know that I've
not given you any money cuz I'm not
being sponsored or paid for by Mr.
Beast. You get I want to be in a Beast
video. I want to do it. I see so many
other YouTubers being a Mr. Beast video.
I want to do it. Look, there's the
That's my cry for help. Beast, get me in
a video. I'm I'm ready. There's three
along the side and then it's a full bar.
Do you want to know the full bar? I'm
actually going to show you. I'm a true
Beast fan. Do you know why he did that?
Why? Because in the original version,
Mr. Beast, See how the long one, see the
long one? Do you see it? Look at it.
Take a look at the long one with no
brakes. The original chocolate bar was
all one big bar with no brakes at all.
But he said in the design process when
he put it in stores on shelves it would
tip over and shatter like glass because
those breaks are basically to like give
you a guide of where to break it to eat
it.
Last
what
what I just put two pieces of a
breakable bar in my mouth instead of
splitting it in half. I thought Craven
Morehead was about to be here. All
right, you ready? Last question. Matt.
Yep. He's gonna answer the other one
now. What's one thing you've been
meaning to do for a long time, but still
haven't?
Meet Graven Morehead. I like to get like
a little bit on the edge and talk about
these. Stop doing that.
Hey, help Marot. Nick, do you think you
could deep throat this whole mic? Please
don't ask. What's one thing you've been
meaning to do for a long time but still
haven't? Um, I have
like seven, eight,
six, seven.
Any do you? No idea. Do I? I have like
seven or eight books in my room that I
want to read, but I just feel like I've
been like so go doing this, prepping for
tour, doing for that, and I haven't read
them in a while. And I feel like some
reading. You should do what I did when I
was a kid and read a chapter a night.
You should do what I what I do when I
was a kid or what you did when I was a
kid. You should just let me finish a
sentence, right? Just saying. Oh, [ __ ]
What? I just My hand was like this. I
dropped the mic on my pinky. Drop the
mic. All right, guys. Thank you so much
for watching this week's this week's
Friday video. Um, we appreciate you guys
all so very much. And we are going on
tour literally. I'm sorry. I'm a
disgusting [ __ ] fat. Both of you are.
And we are going on tour in 4 days from
right now. From right now. Well, 5 days
from right now cuz we have to start
leaving early. Go shop our new merch.
And I He got that [ __ ] on. This hoodie
that is gray and green also comes in
like a nice pink. And then I have that
black shirt I was wearing earlier on.
And also this isn't merch that's going
to be live at the show. All the live
show merch is going to be different than
this. Just an FYI. Yep. I'd rather give
you guys that heads up now so that if
you're going to the show and you want to
like save money for in-person merch, you
can have that option. or if you want to
get the online exclusive merch. There
you go. Love that. Just want to share
before we absolutely conclude this video
here and go on tour next Friday that we
love you guys and we appreciate you guys
and we would not be able to do what we
love without you guys. So, thank you so
much and see you guys next Friday at
5:30
or not 2:30 in person.
Dude, we're going to have a show. Can I
also just
say you guys are not even remotely
prepared for what's coming in your
direction? What the [ __ ] does that even
Are you talking to me? I'm talking to
you. I'm talking to you. Wait, hold on.
Hold on. I'm talking to you. I just want
to share that I am a part of many really
amazing surprises that I put a lot of
effort into. And every single one that I
filmed individually, I put in tons of
effort alone to do it. And I can't
believe that I've been keeping secrets
from you guys for so long. And I just
can't wait to be able to talk freely
amongst you guys and the viewers about
my awesome surprises. That's all. I'm so
excited for you and I feel mutually the
same. I feel amazing.
Well, come see us on the surprise party
tour if you're coming. We're excited to
see you and we hope you have a beautiful
rest of your Friday and we'll see you
next week. Keep an eye out. Have a
wonderful warhead. Have a wonderful
weekend, my friends.
Something about Are you recording
Chris? Chris, my [ __ ] deal.
Something about using a credit card to
pay the meter just feels wrong. Like I
don't use a credit card to get a [ __ ]
gumball. We should get a roll of
quarters. I think that that'd be a good
fun thing. But you know what I mean?
Yeah. All right, guys. We are going to
our tour rehearsals today, but we're
going to eat right now before we go to
tour rehearsals. So, come along with us.
I'm wearing my purple I'm going to get
like little I'm wearing my purple I'm
wearing my purple shoes because we're
doing tour rehearsals and it's not the
versus tour, but I feel like this is
like emulating my tour energy that I
need so deep in my
bones. You're a [ __ ] freak. Let's go.
I really really love these cuz it's like
that's me and my food over here. Yeah,
Chris. Really? We We're vlogging out and
about eating breakfast today and our
hearts are racing. Our hearts are racing
and we're all nervous and I think that
we've all we all like inconveniencing or
bothering people around me. Yeah, we all
definitely have also a form of social
anxiety. You know what I mean? Majorly
like really bad. And I think what really
encouraged this this Where are you
going? What really encouraged this
action of vlogging breakfast is
yesterday we were walking on Rodeo Drive
and saw four people Instagram live. One
of them screaming and doing push-ups
shirtless. So it's like we are not we
are not a site for sore eyes during the
other [ __ ] that's going. If you live in
LA it's normal that people are creating
content. I have no idea what I ordered
by the way. I know. Dude, what were you
doing? What were you thinking? He's
getting like the panther and the [ __ ]
I just wanted to switch it up. And I was
also feeling like I didn't want I don't
like eggs and you guys got like egg
burritos. I'm like I don't want that.
It's breakfast, dude. I just wish I just
don't know what I got last time I was
here. What did you just say, Matt? I
said this is a rare thing. Eggs are like
a million dollars nowadays.
I should have got four of these. I'm
getting this and the brisket and the
[ __ ] Black Panther on the thing. This
one might kill me. How would they not
go? This is good as [ __ ] though. What
is that one? Trio. I ordered like a trio
and I thought the tea was an app and the
lady's like, "It's okay. It's the pond."
Like, "Thank you for making me feel less
[ __ ]
stupid." Petition to What am I doing?
What am I looking at? I don't know. I
love when does that. I'm just like, I'm
so confused. It's like the ceiling's
half open, half closed, and I like the
lights.
Yeah, this is really nice lighting.
Yeah. I don't like um lots like any
loads of cream. I don't like Oh my god.
I'm I'm with that. Like a big load of
sour cream or like a big load of
guacamole.
Not my like big load of um like mayo.
When you eat something and it's like
seeping out of your like mouth. Get get
Don't even That's the worst thing ever.
Raven's forehead. Dude, that would creep
me out.
[Music]
Never.