does anybody know why Matt was not at
Tara yummy party for one Nick Nick shut
the [ __ ] up only Nick buys himself a
full box of chocolates such a Nick
sterol little move I really like the
water bottles with the nipples on it
yeah feel like I'm sucking water
straight from Mother
Nature I thought this was going to go so
different all right guys this car video
is going to be things that we're going
to talk about things that we find either
really corny or really piss us off yep
so
it's a good video for Nick yeah I
actually am feeling really positive
recently and I have nothing negative
that's a lie taking the last of
something and leaving the
Box point at someone you know who does
that I'll break your goddamn ow dude are
you serious like why the [ __ ] would you
do that I just like felt my finger go
did you yeah you felt your finger making
noise that's crazy I never ever ever do
that so that was my first one why don't
you go to the dentist check if you have
a cavity I hate this kid I just like
really want to embrace this moment right
now what the [ __ ] what what's the to
embrace no guys you always freak out
when I say [ __ ] like that but it's like
come on we're back home yeah oh my God
we're in the van together mhm like
always as Rose okay okay I don't even
this doesn't even happen to me cuz I
don't eat it but like when people make
like the mac and cheese but they'll grab
like a second mac and cheese box and
open it so that theirs is extra cheesy
and then put like the mac and cheese
back in the thing or like if you have a
Ramen and then take two seasoning
packets for and you make it like extra
chickeny yeah and then you leave the
other Ramen packet so the next person
that goes to get it is only getting the
noodles and isn't getting the seasoning
well you should like you should just
throw away the second pack that's what I
would do what I'm saying like the next
person is going to be like oh like if
the last Nick a bonus
seasoner wrong correct Nick do I do that
Matt I don't know I know that Nick has
done that in the past would I make my
Mac and Cheese extra
cheesy yeah are you serious not extra
cheesy but you would make your Ramen
extra like flavorful I would do that
correct I've seen you do
it where the [ __ ] are my notes I think
tourniquets are like the craziest thing
ever Nick can you don't say [ __ ]
bleeding out and they just like tie the
limb off what why do you bring up tour I
had this charer and I was like wrapping
it around my leg and I think of like in
like those zombie movies when someone's
like arm gets bit I think it's just
corny if you have to squint I squint all
the time I know I think I just think
it's cringe like it's like walk closer
like if someone's like this like if
someone got up and walked closer or
something instead of squinting you'd say
the same thing now what like just what
you can't see from over there yeah well
no it's just like I just think it's like
dude if you're squinting no it's worse
when you're like in a seat that you
can't really get up from like if you're
like at a game oh what does that say
yeah if you're like a game or something
like a like an NBA game or like a
baseball game or something or like
somewhere where you're like having an a
SED seat like a theater okay and you're
just like this the whole time it's like
buy a closer ticket Chris squinty McGee
like you know what I mean come on I feel
like you squint often that's why yeah no
I squint when I
laugh a you're just so cute I think that
you're a chronic squinter and you don't
even know it yeah I AG see I might be
listing things that I do and that's a
thing that's like that's why it's like
this is all our videos are for fun and
for entertainment this one
self-reflecting Matt you're the king of
self-reflecting I actually mean that
you're like good at
it so what is that what what were you
getting at though I don't know I was
going to say like we always like I see
people I think I need a
soda I think I need a soda okay you want
me to you want me to go get you soda me
and Chris were out the other day and
someone literally told us that we should
go to a twin convention yeah like to our
face I was there no you wen't that dude
that's exactly what I said that happened
to me no cuz that's what Chris said to
the girl he said she goes has anyone
ever told you guys you should go to a
twin convention and I said no cuz I'd
never heard I go oh yeah said oh like
when literally me and Matt just had
someone T us it was at the car
dealership the lady was like you oh
y'all are twins asked if we were in town
for it I was like Weir it's going on
yeah that's what I would have said it's
going on right now yeah she was like oh
you're in town for the convention we
were like the convention what she goes y
all twins right and we were like yeah
she's like the twin convention like
everyone pulling up every twin ever is
pulling up she's like I got kids and
they go every year I was like no she she
tried to convince him to go her kids
were like no Mom that's [ __ ] stupid
and I they probably they probably ha a
if Mom tried getting us to a twin or
triplet convention I'd laugh in her face
yeah think about it no hate I'm going to
hold on hold on hold on hold on video is
just starting you need oh my God you
scared the dick you need spit that gum
out or learn how to chew you one or two
options there how tough are you not
tough oh my God oh my God no don't fight
oh you can't even stick to my face oh my
God spit it out or learn how to chew
thank you dude are you serious now I got
my own spit all over my face that was
had on your sleeve well instead of gum
since you can't eat gum I did get Chris
a gift are you serious I did yes I knew
it was going to be him me and Nick were
just in um CVS and I saw this little
Reese's Bunny and I was like that dude
looks stupid but he's like stupid in a
good way and he's so cute little Reese's
bunny oh my God Nick what a good gift
isn't he so cute we he needed to come
home he should sit right next to the
camera so now we just like he's watching
us film I just added a new thing to my
list a moment ago of things that annoy
me and it's when people say a big no no
like oh that'd be a big no no he added
it to his list cuz I said it correct I I
can see Matt like with little streamers
like like flipping around in the Park
yeah okay now I'm going to throw it this
way so you can't grab it again a
privilege taken away I have um I think
that they should make a wambulance like
if someone's just crying and they don't
need an ambulance and people are oh we
got to call the ambulance for the little
baby like what if a ambulance actually
came for the little crying
babies okay unpopular
opinion when people kick the back of
your foot or like someone's knee pit
like right here to like to like knock
them off it's so unfunny yeah it's so
unfunny it's just like dude like you're
you're like what take a trip to Home
Depot and I'll do it to you in front of
a [ __ ] power drill how about that
let's do
it no for me it's like you know what's
going to happen you know what I mean
it's not one of those stum it's not one
of those like 50/50 jokes you know what
I mean like that's hardcore you're
bending someone's knee if someone did
that to me like fully fell and
embarrassed myself I think I'd [ __ ] SLA
them to Mars I'd say get out of here
you're you're now in orbital spin
[ __ ] vamos you're out Vos is
vomos whatever there we go you're You're
gone see you in see you in Pluto oh yeah
it's like when you like Buckle someone's
knees that's what it is when you like
imagine like how unfunny it is kick the
back of their heel so they like I have
an unpopular opinion go ahead of when
people are like oh you're a tattletail
or like you're a rat like if you tell
like a teacher it's like you're [ __ ]
obnoxious I I never believed in like o
telling on someone cuz it's like I I
think it's corny to like if someone's
like doing something that they're like I
guess not supposed to but if like you
telling on someone you're telling on
someone who's actively infringing your
peace it's completely valid like don't
go telling on people if they're like
vaping or something like that's their
personal problem that's that's like
leave that out of it mean it's corny to
like snitch on somebody if it literally
doesn't impact you but if someone's just
being a total douchebag
to you and they're like oh you snitch or
you're tattletail it's like you're a
[ __ ] obnoxious loser so it's like I'd
rather be a tattletail than a
[ __ ] nobody wants to be
around yeah sums it up uh number four
I'm guilty on this very heavily I put
that all right got a sheep in the back
seat um I put
PR my ears it I'm going to read all mine
oh shut up I'm just going to hit you my
ears it you my [ __ ] ass it you shut
up I'm just going to read all mine cuz I
Nick you're just looking scre I'm going
to just start hitting stop chrisop God
that was insane I'm going to speak that
was a full array of
several the heck just like you need to
stop you need to stop no fighting if
that's the only you guys should do one
of those slap boxing things where you
just Bish slap each other as you you
shut up right you're just so fortunate
we're filming a video and I want it to
go good that's awesome say let's carry
on sounds good if I went up to you and
hit you as hard as I can in the back of
your head you'd have terminal [ __ ]
brain illness for like if I sucker punch
you in the back of the head in like the
kitchen one night you hitting the back
of my head stop you can hit me in the
face all you want the back of my I put
it in parenthesis I'm guilty of this
heavily so you guys are going to be
like go ahead you guys are be like oh
but you do that fully self-aware that's
good people that ask for your opinion
and then get mad when you
your opinion or disagree on that opinion
mhm see I don't really get mad when
people ask my opinion and they disagree
with my opinion because well it's like
that's when you realize it's the truth a
little well to me it's like I I give my
100% unprovoked opinion Almost 100% of
the time so if it's going to upset
somebody it like would like regardless
they don't have to ask for advice to be
upset by my opinion I'll do it anyway
unfortunately like I give my opinion in
every scenario yeah actually that's not
true I think you give your opinion in
every scenario I don't say it rudely
who's Matt if you show someone like a
shirt that you're like kind of on edge
of wearing who's Kinder about not liking
it me or Chris you thank you yeah but
that's you two to you guys I'll give my
full raw honest opinion if it's like an
outside person like a friend I'm going
be like well I mean like let's like I'd
word it nicer but you think that you're
10 times nicer to friends than me and
Matt 100% you guys can say the same to
me so I don't know what you're talking
about you are significantly Rudder to me
than any other person in your
life all oh you're gross you're
disgusting and everyone hates you we
should get Chris mat and I think you'd
get behind this like it's like a it's
like five mini Guillotines and we put
all his toes in it just chop his toes
off are you serious Nick what would you
even say that for that's like Chris
burps on you pinky out who am
I I don't know [ __ ] the prince of
England give me this I have no clue but
I I just think Matt is like so X Games
like you're the type of kid like what is
an X game it's like the BMX and like
snowboarding like I can just picture
Matt being like can you
stop yeah I'm like trying to listen you
[ __ ] stupid now sounds like you have
a
moraca me if I ever [ __ ] your
[ __ ] like
what what are you talking about I had to
say something to break the ice you guys
been [ __ ] yapping and yelling at each
other I had to say something out of
pocket so I could regain focus and
Consciousness to
the the last thing I said was I find it
corny when people actually use their car
horn but I don't think no cuz I I
understand using your car horn if like a
car is coming at you from the wrong side
of the road at hundreds of miles per
hour but it's like if you're like
Loosely at a red light and the person's
not paying attention a little toot toot
is good we don't need to hear it sound
like a [ __ ] 90 car pile up Inferno is
about to happen in front of my ass we're
chill with the Casual like beep beep
like oh hey you need to like there's a
difference between a casual alert with
your horn and then acting as if you're
about to be in a [ __ ] 90 car
Massacre I fully agree my biggest fear I
think would be once once I learn to
drive if the gods ever align for me to
do so and if someone if I laid on the
horn in front of someone and they got
out of their
car yeah that girl in like that um that
Meme and like the uh she's in like the
she takes her hair down she gets ready
to fight no no she's she's in the court
and she's like standing there like this
after finding out that like oh I know
you're not like what is her last last
sexual interaction with the guy she's
like suing and he was like this morning
and then they paned to her and she's
like Miss
Jackson she's like hella nervous I just
can't react to anything okay I uh people
that love social media a little too much
I agree this is a little morbid and a
little scary and gross and like whatever
I'm sorry tww trigger warning for those
who are triggered easily whatever this
girl I remember being in like sophomore
year or no it was 8th grade and I was
clicking through my Snapchat stories and
this girl texted me or something cuz she
was like in my English class she was
like my English partner and she was like
yeah I'm not coming to school today like
I have like my like my grandma passed
and I was like oh my God I'm so sorry
for your loss and then later in the day
I'm clicking through her Snapchat story
and she posted a photo of like her dead
grandmother in like her casket I was
like yeah get off your phone yeah Nick
that's insane don't even say I
was know who you're talking about
anybody that's just like to like like
they like know this the buttons to I
know you mean
the the Apple Geek Squad it's like you
go in like if you actually use a stylist
and open the settings app and you head
all the way down you can save a
percentage of battery life people that
can't understand human error like like
if a waitress like accidentally puts
like bacon on your mashed potato like oh
you [ __ ] [ __ ] I I clearly said no
bacon like but like like I I hate like
and it's it's it's crazy being in LA and
like living in La like going out to eat
there's some like obviously like super
rich people that go out to eat and it's
like it terrifies me seeing like these
rich people like the other day we went
out to eat and it was like 90° out
remember yes and this the coat family
the whole family there's a family you
remember Matt the family of coats oh my
God there's a family of five people
sitting down in the restaurant and it
was like a super nice restaurant sure so
it's like they wanted to like show that
they had money and they were prepared to
spend their money on steak and whatever
and they walk in and the mom the dad and
three kids I think it was a boy and two
little girls every single one of them
has matching like designer
jackets coats I was like yeah I'm in a
T-shirt and I'm dry heathing over my
meal like trying to catch a little
glimpse of [ __ ] cold I'm like give me
some ice I can fill my socks with and
cool my body down and this whole family
is in
gigantic I thought was I literally
looked quick I thought I was staying
next to five [ __ ] yetis these people
were like in five completely I'm like oh
my God who invited marshmallow fluff
himself the [ __ ] what's his name the
Sherman t guy is sitting behind me
family of five the daughters look like
they're hot like they look so
hot gripping
and like the mom looks like she's like
that was the funniest part for me is
like the kids are like kids are like so
hot she like put the jacket on you like
dude all this like I I'm down I'm down
for like feeling fle I'm down to feel a
little bit uncomfortable for fashion you
know I can always do like a sweater
might be uncomfortable but like you look
good like I'm down discomfort her
fashion but like dude [ __ ] your your
kids are sweating yeah your kids feel
like they're in a sauna you're burning
you're literally burning the calories
you're eating burning your kids I
thought you going to no you're burning
the calories you're eating right there
God but it was so funny Matt literally
said a timer kids were going to I said I
set a timer for how long it was going to
take for all of them to take their
jacket off it was like 35 minutes or
something the wife never took her jacket
off I think it was glued to her back dud
glued to her back no that thing was talk
to her it was crazy no and then she'd
like take it off one arm and then eat
and then put it on the other it was
actually like unal like we get it you
guys are
designer I just think it's so funny too
like when you go out to eat with friends
and [ __ ] and you see something like that
that occupies the whole dinner like the
whole dinner we ate our food and we're
just solely focused if these people were
going to take their [ __ ] sweaty
jackets off like it look like at one
point I saw the girl and I like felt
horrible like and I'm good at I wanted
to just get her a cuple I'm good at not
staring in public cuz it's rude at one
point I caught myself like
this I was looking at them in such
discomfort for myself like I you ever
look at somebody and you get hot yeah
for sure like that was going on too I
was I was and it's like dude I'm a huge
like I get nervous when I eat I like
this might be like a personal thing that
I'm just like oversharing right now what
no go ahead you feel I said speaking of
being nervous when you eat do you
remember when I pet that dog that was
eating at a party attacked me that must
have been terrified what was his name
Pedro oh when I eat like it's not like a
nervous like I'm scared e just like
You're vulnerable no it's not like it's
not that it's like when I do eat like
because I'm fueling my body and like my
heart's beating and like I'm like eating
food and like drinking Waters like I get
nervous that I'm going to like go into
like a [ __ ] heart attack when I eat
like [ __ ] like that like I just like I
overthink a lot and I'm like wow I'm
eating a lot of like like sugary food I
just get in my head and [ __ ] but what
the [ __ ] was like what was the point of
the family made you nervous because you
were like no so I have to whenever I eat
I can't be hot like that's a fun fact
about me like if it's like 90° out and
like someone's throwing a cookout or
like a picnic I cannot join in and eat I
have to like go inside and s in the air
conditioning and like even it goes for
like restaurants like I I have to take
my hoodie off to eat if I'm like in a
t-shirt you know what I mean seeing
these people in your the Jack seeing
these people like in like their Monclair
coats I was genuinely like really
nervous like I couldn't even eat dude it
was actually was so weird cuz I was like
I was sweating no I was sweating and I
was in a shirt I just felt bad cuz they
looked hot I'm all for like if you're
comfortable do your thing these people
looked like they wanted nothing more
than to take their jacket off they were
doing it for like the image of like
having their jacket on it was so funny
oh what about I put just the guy who
threw Nick's suitcase I added that to
the list so we could tell insane as you
guys can see we're in Boston right now
but in order to get here we obviously
took a plane correct and this guy I was
dropping my you know when you like I
don't know actually some of you might
not have ever been to an airport when
you go to an airport and you check your
suitcase they like put it on a conveyor
belt like you don't bring your suitcase
onto the plane someone else does it so
this guy he went to put my suitcase on
the conveyor belt and I had a 53 lb
suitcase so my suitcase was 3 lb
overweight and it literally looked like
WWE top ropes slammed down
suitcase SL slam it down I don't care
about the professional name WWE s sorry
I thought you did he took my
suitcase what
Smackdown smacked it down onto its back
left wheel and I saw the wheel concave
onto itself and give out and I was like
I literally just my whole face have you
seen the meme of the Chick-fil-A girl
just like no Chick-fil-A sauce goes that
was me he dropped my suitcase my head
went oh my God shock I'm like what are
you hucking [ __ ] across the room for
it's like it's just ridiculous it's like
whatever I understand he probably a
[ __ ] just tired guy works but it's
like dude now you have to buy a whole
new suitcase yeah now I need a new
suitcase he [ __ ] literally it looked
like my suitcase was his worst enemy and
he's been waiting 20 years for it to
show up to the airport it was insane I
wouldn't throw someone I hated that hard
on the ground it was unbelievable oh my
God it was so funny is when people like
threaten you with like you're lucky
they're like oh you're lucky like my dad
isn't here or something or like you're
lucky like my big brother didn't beat
you up like when people like say like
when people like threaten people with
like oh you're lucky that like something
isn't occurring you know what I mean
when is this happening like in the all
the time [ __ ] are always like
oh you're lucky you're lucky I've never
heard this you've never heard of that
well I've heard that I've just never
just said this to you when you
um when you um well no I never say it
like in a threatening format I just
genuinely like oh that was lucky like
you were lucky oh no you just told me I
was lucky cuz I hit you in the head and
you said I'm lucky that we're filming a
video cuz you would have knocked me out
oh that is true like that isn't corny
the way I said it okay I don't know no
you you're lucky why I uck you just did
it literally I just Expos myself yeah
okay [ __ ] are like look who
decided to show up oh my god look who
decided leave
see yeah look who also just decided turn
right
back mat you love this Matt's always the
[ __ ] that walks in when they say
that God yeah look who decided to show
up guess who's look who decided to say
goodbye as well see you later when
people say look who decided to show up
it's like you're always saying it to the
[ __ ] you were shocked that
they're even there oh my God it's like
let them live look who decided to show
up oh my God I just hate that [ __ ] look
who decided to be the first obnoxious
[ __ ] in that no don't tell the
video don't do it I'm going to end the
video no not don't do it
that was a oneman show by chriso called
don't end the video no please don't end
that car video I'm having so much fun I
have you I got to go back home no don't
do it no I think you should rename it
mental illness y