hey guys welcome back to our YouTube
channel today is Wednesday which means
you have another fun little Vlog and for
today what we're going to do is we're
going to spoil our friend here
[Music]
[Applause]
Trevor we got Trevor when we were in
fifth grade mhm he's been a lovely pup
ever since yep how old is he like nine I
think he's about 9 eight or nine right
now and he's half Pug half beagle yep
and he's chubby and lazy yeah and today
for today's Wednesday video we're going
to dedicate today to Mr Trevor right
Trevor I know Trevor's dream day would
consist of doing nothing and laying down
but we're going to make you be a little
active today you're going to run around
maybe get some some cheese some treats
go on
walks he shows no excitement for
anything so yeah basically today we're
just going to do all the things that we
know Trevor loves that we want to take
and enjoy and do with him because when
we're in California we don't get to see
him that often anymore so it's a it's a
brotherly Bond today all right a fun
fact about Mr Trevor here is he hates
being in a car while someone else is
outside of the car we never have ever I
think in Trevor's entire existence left
him in the car completely alone but yet
he still
panics if just one person steps out of
the car so we're headed to the pet store
right now to get Trevor some things that
he will want but right when we get there
and park the car we're going to all
instantly get out of the car as soon as
possible including Trevor so that way
there's no Panic ensuing and we won't
pick up food today without getting
Trevor outside the car cuz he hates
being in here so you'll get to come with
us everywhere we go M to
drive we're at a green light and he's
not moving I I imagine we're having like
a deep Stern voice I agree or just like
a little accent like a like a British
accent or a lisp what's up guys it's
okay it's okay it's okay see this is
what I was trying to avoid a minute ago
yeah we have to park and get out we're
going to park and get right out Trevor
don't you worry go go go go go you're
coming come
on go with Chris come on let's go get
out oh my
goodness dude 5X makes him look like
like a little nugget right why is Trevor
sniffing everything I don't know Trev
you can get whatever you want in here
there's a lot of options we got some
playology here I think he's more
interested in the floor which is so
unsettling cuz probably like there's so
many like things in here that he's
smelling so many there's so much
stimulation for him should we get one of
these hats [ __ ] no that's for like
that's for girl dogs SE a friend hey
friend you like the worst dog leash
holder I've ever seen you want me to do
what is this Kong easy treat gross
terrible terrible you think he'd enjoy
that that's nasty all right let's take a
look what's Up's up you the dudes from
YouTube yes the D we're filing a video
right now how are you want to say hi yo
say hi to our dog he's trying to we can
take a photo of if you guys pet him 10
times because today is all about him 1 2
3 4 5 6 Seven 8 9 10
welf or
something this is she said it wasn't you
I'm being
we're taking our we're taking our dog
out on the town today all right let's do
it hold on let me get him in the phot
here pick him up
ready oh he's scoring it's okay all
right watch tomorrow's video it's going
to be this so of course see you guys
later have a good
one Trev you want a big dodo bird no
he's so the only thing he's interested
in right now is getting out of here
Trevor this is like the side do you if I
was a dog I'd love to just like oh what
I mean okay was going from the neck okay
we go classic tennis come on Matt that's
what if Matt was a dog that' just like
the toy he get like I feel like he he's
probably most interested in like food
are there like good treats somewhere
he's so love this it has like little
like like um patches stitches feel me
what is like feel me yes we're getting
we're getting some legitimate sniff
action going on he looks interested
finally let's go to the food I think
that's what his fat ass is mostly
interest let's
do just [ __ ] on the floor matt don't
even say that I just literally caught
myself like playing with a dog toy for
like 5 Seconds you were gone and I was
like very like like enjoying it a lot
Presley has this does he yeah the red so
I mean oh the Celtics Celtics game get
him that Chris is he a medium I feel
like he's an extra large he's look at
the size of him he's not an extra large
he's a tiny dog Trevor this you
oh yeah that's it that's it that's it
that's it Trev I don't like basketball
though either so you're going to have to
suffer with me yeah no he loves loves
this yeah he loves pepperoni we get him
this he likes these I think let's see
what Hy wants Trevor which are you more
interested in well he's closer to that
one really he just picked the left one
okay yeah yeah so thank you CU I'm both
on the ground he literally was closer to
the red and he walked to the yellow one
and knocked his out on it you were
horrible can you shut your mouth thanks
Deluxe bedding he doesn't need a bed he
already has the whole couch he doesn't
even sleep in his bed oh is that for
cats yeah no is that a dog I think it's
a dog I mean he's an animal he's an
animal regardless cuz like this is what
I would want I don't think he likes like
gnawing on something he's not like a
bone
fan no can get him a jacket this is the
type of [ __ ] I be on as dog she doesn't
need nothing doesn't like like he
doesn't like outfits they we're trying
to spoil we put get him a denim jacket
that's ridiculous we're already getting
him this and I feel a little bad
actually wait hold on there's a hat he
doesn't need a hat he doesn't need a hat
he just talked about this let's get him
a I have expensive
taste okay let's get him okay let's
to wait no cuz he might need a tie that
is definitely he might need a Nick
little socks little socks he doesn't
need a socks get in the socks he might
need a tie though no I think are those
for cats those might actually be for
tennis ball tennis tennis ball is
classic let's get the toy you like Chris
yeah I'm getting a toy for Chris which
is hilarious no this is the one that was
intriguing me like oh my God like look
it it like goes I was like literally
like this that's too big for him he's a
small dog I is this is he going to this
is perfect right good tennis ball mat
and that's good I think we're good yeah
let's go all right guys we got that
stuff for Trevor but we're not going to
Vlog in the car because it's so hot and
obviously me Matt and Chris will
sometimes take the heat on and not put
the AC on for Content but because we
have Trevor with us we have to
prioritize putting the AC on so we'll be
back in a minute Trevor what are you
doing what are you sniffing
huh oh Trevor by the wishing well what a
Vibe
ew Trevor go peee I love his camo collar
he's such a tough guy you want to take
part in the Vlog what do you want me to
do twerk no that's actually the last
thing i' want your [ __ ] ugly ass to
do all right Run free little puppy and
he goes to the fr he has a field of
grass behind him he runs straight for
the exit Trevor come here you lazy rat
look a field of grass and oh
water good boy oo
yummy yummy really quenching his thirst
I was worried he like wasn't drinking
water earli there
yeah good boy drink drink drink do you
want one of these do you want one of
these oh look at his
tail he's about to get a piece of bacon
I'm not giving him a lot cuz Dad
overfeeds him and I don't want him to
throw up
sit
bum tell everyone to
subscribe say subscribe speak say
subscribe speak he's not going to do it
f b lay down no get out you can't do two
different commands I have the treat paw
and lay down Sit lay down good boy uh
good boy TR what was that little head
swivel you see that he like went like
this and turn around eating it for he is
eating it no he's not
second oh there we go good boy boy he
loves these I told you picked them out
himself remember when he picked them
out remember it was an hour ago yeah but
he picked them out too
hot oh you're so
cute you're so cute TR you're supposed
to play with the ball you're not
supposed to just sniff it you just got
back oh look at him he's kind of got a
Gallop to him
took them long enough no that's what I'm
saying never going to have that that's
that's not appealing to him at all okay
we'll see Trevor come here TR cheese
instead [ __ ] a pop cups no I'll show you
how to Nick are you a [ __ ] it was Chris
you want to know how look he look most
look
look good boy good boy is it going to
fit very calm you're very nice right now
boy Trevor there it is wow
yeah Boston Celtics looks pretty
comfortable look at his neck fat I know
he's too big for it
hey he looks uncomfortable honestly no
he doesn't If he if you stand him up he
does not look uncomfortable at all let's
go wait hold on Trev Trev got that [ __ ]
on on the
drip you do have a lot this is what I'm
talking about with why we didn't buy
Trevor dog bed today is he has this on
this couch and this is the best seat on
the couch you can't even sit here and
like put your feet up and relax cuz his
bed's in the way and then there's a dog
B on that couch so he's just he's double
dog beded up Justus come on oh [ __ ] out
of here that was our team I know it's 12
nothing yes wait that's actually
impressive I don't care but that's good
it pop y w wo wo oh it fell never getet
it find it your butt ow he bit my hand
and you got [ __ ] slob over my bed
always remember you are braver than you
think stronger than you seem and love
more than you know it's a quote from
linnie and the Poo no way is it actually
got that Mary Lou that's cute time for
bed all right we're going to end this
Vlog you left boogies on the side we're
going to end this Vlog doing whatever
Trevor wants today by doing his favorite
thing and that's sleeping through the
night it's
gone come on Trev come here this guy
what is this the most energy you had all
day it's like time for bed you did he
not eat it did he eat it he ate it
what's the confusion what are you
looking around for you ate it Patty no
you can't leave oh Trevor look at me
Trev Trev he doesn't he think piece look
Trev come here look it's all gone it's
all gone sit
he's crazy this dude
Trevor this is this is heartbreaking he
ate it and he doesn't know that he ate
it Trevor Trevor you consumed the tree
it is in your
belly this is actually Psy psychotic
what it's gone dude it there's nothing
left it's time for
bed are you sure he ate it cuz this is
like delusion no he ate Trevor he ate
the whole thing Trev hi you ate it look
at
me what's going on oh oh he's crawling
you find anything probably
not thank you Trevor for being in our
Vlog today we love and appreciate you so
much hey
[Music]