hope yall don't mind him meating my
pizza during this video oh we don't mind
a
bed and all the things that we did we
said we going to travel from the island
to Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
all why
because hey guys today we're going to do
that raing your pets again cuz it was
really funny last time we really had fun
doing it so we're going to do it again I
know it's kind of soon and it's like I
don't like doing part tw's like back to
back cuz then it's just like chaos but
this one's worth it AG I think we're we
have a lot of like Parts D also said he
really liked this one so start cray cray
meet
Jerry I screenshotted the same thing
what is that you have a crustation in
your hand you are holding a full-blown
crustation what the [ __ ] is that and why
is it the size of this [ __ ] girl's
arm I've never seen a really small girl
I hope that's a really small it's a big
ass slug or something what the [ __ ] is
that no that's insane I saw it it made
me sick I literally was like ill in my
chest when I saw I like Jerry no hate
like how apping is that I just don't how
you can love something how can you hold
it and name that [ __ ] a pet is
for love I cannot love that like that's
disgusting bro the fact that like you're
comfortable enough to even name that
like Jerry is like appalling to me like
that thing first of all it's name should
be Gary I just said that I agree you
didn't say that maybe I just thought
it I literally had it on the edge of my
no I think [ __ ] nasty some weird [ __ ]
Matt would do when we were kids like
just own a slug and name it or something
it's not even like a hermit crab a
hermit crab I could G that's a full slug
in a shell ridiculous what's a slug in a
shell called a snail oh that's a snail
yeah wait cuz it did have a shell so it
is a snail yeah Google it kid no if
you're going to [ __ ] talk out of your
ass at least turn around so I can hear
you better
what is the difference
between a slug and a snil it all comes
down to Shell yeah a snail a it's shage
for sure shage 100% like a slug is snail
has a shell and a slug does not correct
correct but can a snail like leave it
shell right and become a slug what so it
could be the same slug can be a snail
snails lowkey snails lowkey be slugging
see this makes me really sick because
I've held a snail before and been like
so cute but then I'm appalled by a slug
so maybe I'm just judging them based off
of their shell and I shouldn't do that I
think snails are more tolerable sorry
sorry it's okay because you can like you
can um like you can grab them by the
shell you're not just feeling gush and
mush oh my God how one time I stepped on
a slug and I slid on the ground my foot
was oozed it was like snail guts through
my toes imagine that Nick get out of
here dude disgust disgust is what fled
through my
soul
that looks like a rabbit save that that
looks like a rabbit that looks like a
bunny rabbit out of a hat do you see
that thing face it looks like a
walrus I'm so
Disturbed I'm so that's crazy I'm so
disgusted that's crazy that's crazy that
literally looks like a walrus bunny
rabbit slime
mutant crossover I don't even ever want
to look at my phone again no for real
next holy Fu this person said mine's
dead is that okay and they're genuinely
Sitting Waiting for
permission all right we got three dogs
Reagan Willie and Mac yes Willie Willie
and Reagan sadly have passed away but
Mac is still standing I want to guess
who's who okay this is the first one you
got to tell me who you think it is got
to be wi that's got to that's rean oh
brother look at his
steam he's got a lot on his mind for
sure big ass Dome he got the cranium
head he's cute though he's so cute I
like the little white triangle going on
yes he's got like white on black on
white he looks like a little oh he's
cute actually I really like him I like
his little tie he's ready for St
Patrick's Day maybe he looks well
behaved yes now this next one is very
elegant pup this next one's Willie will
makes perfect sense holy [ __ ] look at
the Dome on him where did you get these
dogs it literally looks like he ate a
[ __ ] pool ball no literally looks
like he ate the [ __ ] his head would
be yeah like the perfect size of a hold
on I have to show yall something give me
a second wait let's just meet let's just
meet um wait no no wait Mac Mac's the
last one standing hold on just wait stay
on this dude the other two that we just
looked at died what the [ __ ] is that
name Willie Willie look at Willie for a
[Music]
second
how did you have this video just ready
to go I don't know I saved it the other
day thought it was funny that was Willie
right there save that video all right
well let's do a brief moment of silence
maybe for Reagan and Willie since
they're no longer with us M moving on um
here's Mac that was a very brief one Mac
is the last
one is that the only photo you could Ur
of Mac looks like you got tackled when
you took the photo off dude it literally
looks like you just went hey Mac turn
around and Pat him on the butt quick he
look pissed these like look like other
dogs if they were like pugs you know
what I mean like these don't look normal
they look like mini big dogs legit I
want to know the breed they're cute as
[ __ ] though I love rean William Mac 10
out of 10 mhm I agree this is Pebbles
the hamster he 1 years
old ooh Pebbles looks cute oh his hands
look oddly human yeah that's really
disgusting if you like really zoom in
I'd be like that's little baby fingers
on that thing yeah he's cute though he's
enjoying his cucumber okay that's a
really good photo of
him what are you doing Matt that's it
that's the picture you got this is also
her Turtle named
squirt really cute lce really
good who the [ __ ] is this guy I didn't
mean to go to that who is he where is he
at what are you doing you're scrolling
through everything I can't find his
name what's this motherfucker's name
he's got a Croc on his head what the
[ __ ] I feel bad
take that Croc off him he looks pissed
is he biting the strap or is under his
chin it's under his chin she really saw
Tik Tok Trend he was like all right
buddy he looks angry I take that Croc
off him fire take the Croc off his Dome
please all right here's
Cody a happy birthday Cody he has got a
little elephant hat on how beautiful
love he just looks happy to be there for
sure I don't know where he's at but he's
happy wherever he is like how does he
how does a dog sit so elegantly with
like a party hat on blow my mind Trevor
would lose his mind and like bite us all
that dog's cute though who's that who's
that Leo Leo looks like he runs the
beach Leo looks like he's on a honeymoon
or something yes Leo and Willie imagine
them together on a date at the he
chilling on these
Pebbles ah those rocks look really
uncomforting though yeah you wouldn't
sit on those no I'd sit on he was there
he looks like a photographer just
traveling the world ready for his next
day look like a big adventurous dog he
does he looks like an an um Alaskan
sheer 10 out of 10 Leo I forgot to get
this cat's name but he looks so like he
looks angry what the [ __ ] are you doing
that's what he's saying he looks like a
cat from Coraline low key a little bit
but oh he looks pissed how angry is he
like he's like [ __ ] [ __ ] you the [ __ ]
you talking about someone just stole his
catnip and ran with it mhm for sure they
buried it next someone shot his mother
oh I screenshotted this one because he's
three-legged Leo oh Leo three leg three
leg
Leo legless
Leo that was terrible but imagine I
think I've said this before my history
teacher in high school at a three cat
named tripod no it's our friend no no
it's history teacher who History Mr
Blake Mr Blake really uhhuh also has a
three-legged yeah that one's just stupid
that's so cring tripod get it three
legs try triple it triple oh connection
to Leo look at look at look at little
legless Leo that's crazy that he's still
able to walk legless Leo is mean it's
true though it's not really mean
literally the truth if someone who
literally doesn't have a leg and you why
you don't have a leg why is so normal
for some cats to just not have legs I
don't think normal well I feel like I
see I see like out of all animals in the
world I feel like I'm seeing most
legless cats well cuz they're like house
pets like same with cats and dogs you
never see like a legless Like Elephant
cuz it's like no one's really like able
to fix that and it's like in a wild and
it would have too much weight to support
yeah like all light imagine taking my
leg off all right walking around with
one leg in the wild like you'd be a
hooligan there's no crutches imagine
making an amput elephant leg that'd be
tough this is they done it before seen
it this is sunny and Annie and they best
friends oh that's beautiful ready ready
ready to see are you guys ready to see
right his SN are you guys ready to see
Sunny alone are you ready to see Sunny
alone it says this is sunny she tucks
her toes in to keep her warm wo isn't
she so cute that's like the magazine
cover dog that's a calendar pup right
there and this is Annie okay Annie's on
a the cover of a magazine Annie's legs
up like looking off into like lady in
the [ __ ] but like a different font
these two oh that was bad what I hate
the different font thing just cringe to
me it's okay like I liked it Matt I
agree with you I don't know why I try
sometimes no you can try something oh
Heidi yikes fix your neck Heidi needs a
haircut where is the neck looks like
Blackbeard bro got a [ __ ] got a go
Heidi what a name for a dog I know our
dog's name is Trevor but heidy is crazy
he's oh wow I feel like I'm looking into
a person's eyes
SC what I don't um it's crazy he's got
like a full beard that's this dude's
ugly as [ __ ] look at
W same dog oh my God he scared the [ __ ]
out of me what's he doing same dog got
to get his angry just such a narrow face
like I just want to get a rubber band
and he looks like he needs a bath his
nose or something he looks like he need
aath he cute no he needs a he's got some
crazy loose straight hair yeah he needs
a haircut a he's cute though he's a joke
ugly ass dog I hate this dog actually
like this is like kind least favorite
type of dog looks like he just like did
something bad he looks naughty like ooh
like he's like no he's G like a white
person smile that I do like like yeah
it's giving just like he just said like
he just proved you right with like
hardcore facts you know what I mean it
looks like you just said yeah right
buddy no he just gave you like eight
statistics like oh well actually that
wouldn't happen because of the numeric
laws okay he does that
[ __ ] oh wow what is that little beans
name who's that this is a pug oh my God
there's no way that thing can walk walk
it died last year yeah he looks like
Blastoise the Pokemon straight up put
him side by side that's literally
Blastoise the Pokemon oh my God the girl
said like she really misses him oh I
feel horrible I mean if you fed him last
he'd probably still be around no hate no
hate he literally probably died cuz he's
huge Nick you can't see that I can't he
needed to be on a diet that's all I have
to say oh my God but that's no hate cuz
genuinely he was probably like you know
dogs don't have the valve in their
stomach to be like Oh I'm full like
that's like a genuine you're covering
everyone with your phone like that
that's a genuine like fact like dogs
don't have the valve like you could just
continue to feed them like my grandma
you have a valve no you have a thing in
your stomach you have what you grandma
with no cuz Grandma used to always like
whenever Trevor would go over he'd be
like sniffing the ground cuz he's a
[ __ ] dog and she's like oh he's
hungry let me feed him like pulling out
Cheerios like Grandma not hungry like
dogs are always hungry that's the whole
thing like all dogs eat but yeah yeah
this dude he looks yeah he's got a he
looks like a we're switching to the CH
look how long his nails are he's digging
into her whenever there's a small little
dog I just want to throw it like I just
want to toss it what how that's not nice
no I've never like actually going to do
it you know what I mean tell me look at
Google Blastoise and tell me that's
literally not the evolution of Squirtle
no yeah it is his face and everything oh
little pay the Pug yeah pay died oh I
feel horrible for that pug Chris you got
to put your phone down I'm not going to
get anyone and that's a stray cat and
then we can name it oh Golden Noodle
perfect um Sunny like of Meatballs go
okay
okay oh no yeah this girl had a chickens
same girl that had the slug at the
beginning really yeah makes sense weirdo
Jer and Hillary the hen oh God I'm
actually really scared of chickens like
chickens terrifying I thought you were
going say scared of you know that weird
if you take a chicken and you go like
this its head will stay completely oh
yeah stabilized they got a stabilizer in
their neck they're just like this and it
just doesn't other way around whatever
like I'm just really I'm really really
bugged out like freaked out by chickens
I hate chickens are just gross bro I
just would never consider chickens like
a pet oh oh my God I just need to think
of like when I have a is it true that if
you cut a chicken's head off it can R it
runs around for like five what for like
30 more seconds yeah no [ __ ] way
don't search it up yeah no I'm not going
to search that up Matt next oh my God
I'm really dep like dep by that this
person has three cats Leo is the black
and white one I don't know why he looks
like that LMAO Freddy is the ginger one
Dusty is black white and ginger she
passed the
fifth nice to her oh my God she passed
recently rest in peace okay this is the
first one his name is
Leo oh my God oh my God oh it look like
he has a black eye oh my God he looks
like he's just like got told he's like
the worst cat ever it looks like someone
just punched him I I I'm going to say
what I'm going to say but I feel bad
what the white spot looks like a dick on
his face I was going to say that does
look like [ __ ] I was going to say
that he looks so sad yeah he does I
feel move that I feel so upset for him
me too it looks like like he just got
told the worst news of his life
literally yeah oh no this actually makes
me feel terrible it looks like a meme L
like a meme the next one we got is
Freddy the ginger one oh [ __ ]
Freddie E where are his arms and legs e
is that his tooth yeah those holy [ __ ]
that's vort that literally looks like
Voldemort yeah literally that's crazy
that's disgusting this where is his and
legs like which one is which she looks
like that's his hand that's his foot
that's his foot looks he's playing
twister like what is going on they spun
it and said tail on green and then
[ __ ] okay next one Dusty black white
and ginger oh yeah you're looking Dusty
he need a duster
justy Dusty actually looks really cool
that's the most unique looking animal
I've seen in like my life I think the
giant slug has him little beat but I
mean yeah I'll give no this one's cute I
think Dusty's cute I like Dusty Dusty
Chris don't be rude he's Dusty this is
my dog named Bruce oh he's cute what
Bruce is just
such oh yeah it's just like a
toy Bruce looks like such a like Bruce
is just like such an american dog like
an american dog name like I just want to
see Bruce at the cookout on the 4th of
July he look he looks like he should be
on the side of like a burger restaurant
that's what I'm saying like he looks
like Bruce's brew house and he sell
beers and alcohol and
alcohol I like him he's cute what Nick I
just like I'm getting a lot of snout in
my face he's a cute he is cute though I
don't like his color okay honey honey
look like screaming dude that dog is
scary no it's not in that it's a it
looks like me in the first car video
ever he dressed like a bumblebee yeah
and his name is honey it's cute no
thing's ugly as [ __ ] dude it looks like
I got honey on his face and you wipe it
off all stickying
like that nasty move on is that honey
yes honey glow
up oh my turn around for this and I
trying to be all o I'm asleep okay honey
you're hating too much Chris I hate this
stupid dog Honey's cute Chris look like
she literally got like chopped up right
then and
there oh my God oh my God I'm actually
scared of looking I feel like I'm
looking at
Medusa oh my God I'm going to turn to
stone look at this ugly [ __ ]
just looking at look like a seal this
lady's just oh oh oh
oh oh my God this lady's walking across
the highway without without even taking
a [ __ ] sneak peek if she's going to
get nailed by a car she's eating
cigarettes eating them eating cigarettes
I thought it was a thing of apple juice
eating cigarettes I thought I saw that I
thought that was apple juice she's
eating cigarettes chewing on a cigarette
oh that's so gross that's so ineffective
at least smoke
it whatever okay this is hold on last
one I got
Dory ugly ass [ __ ] literally
bring that dog to the circus I don't
like him so disgusting it looks like oh
my God I don't like dogs that get like
upds and haircuts like that that dog's
going to the salon more than I am and
that's a problem no the problem is that
she's not and she needs to she needs to
get a haircut right now I like this is
Luna
o it look Luna looks just like someone I
know Luna looks like she just ate
[ __ ] was it [ __ ] what's his name
the other one no like if you go like
this like cut that off it looks like a
person Nick what you're crazy it looks
like she ate eight Warheads in the
[ __ ] lemon juice before she took this
photo her teeth are like
this ugly ass though the chatter teeth
Emoji big cat oh my [ __ ] god big cat
dude her and Blastoise would have got
along so blasto you just name that dog
Blastoise oh my God that looks like
actually like a bat hanging from a like
a cave it does it actually does look
just like a bat holy [ __ ] Roxy poor girl
Roxy dude poor girl Roxy looks beat up a
she's smiling like a
person I'm really
uncomfortable actually I'm really scared
but she's happy I'm terrified yes oh my
God that was terrifying
my dog Oreo and she's too get creative
I'm sick of
Oreo monster enough fluffy fluffy fluffy
[ __ ] snow white like I it's like you
know it's the ugly ass one you know what
I mean yeah it's like the malti with the
burning eyes and a red underneath like
oh my god get rid of Bella my
God anding what you saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
that we did we so going to tr from the
island of Madrid we had a lot of plans
but they
all why oh because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different
don't [ __ ] my brother