and we're live holy
[ __ ] miss me and all the things that we
did we said we going to travel from the
island of Madrid we had a lot of plans
but they
all is there anything I can do to make
you more comfortable no how you here
relax oh my God I forgot when I'm
driving I always do that [ __ ] with a
[ __ ] seat belt on not going anywhere
bro you're such an idiot
no all right we asked you guys on our
group account to send pictures there's
so many hideous ugly [ __ ] dogs in the
world that are just gross no no actually
a fan submitted and said rate our dogs
so Nick said oh my god let's rate
people's pets and then he put on the
Instagram story rate all different types
of pets so you guys sent in your dude
your birds your cats your dogs your
lizards your cows your horses your mice
your
mom your mom and we're going to rate
pets and we asked you to send their name
too so that we can address them by their
name keep in mind this is all a joke and
if you get your feelings hurt cuz we
don't like your pet grow up you got your
feelings hurt yeah grow up it's just
it's just like a fun and game we don't
we actually love all animals we're very
animal friendly tribe over here I have
like a piece of chicken in my ew oh his
name is hurry oh my god get hurry a
napkin right now holy [ __ ] is that hurry
hurry got a dirty r r y yeah he's in a
hurry to go get some [ __ ] food look
at his mouth does he have rabies holy
[ __ ] get this dude a napkin right now
he's he's looking at the owner
please we got a spell no we don't Nick
Nick and Har both going to look like
harur literally no we're good that was
it wow look at that [ __ ] Jesus get bit
by something look like he's just got oh
no no the light died Nick you [ __ ]
amateur hold on r h one to 10 dude I
give har a two I give har a [ __ ] wipe
that nap I can't rate this poor dog
until [ __ ] smudge off his like dude
they he's got dirty ass lip it's like
like if you had a mess on your face and
you were like give me a napkin I was
like oh and took a photo of you first no
it's genu like we're raing I'll rate him
when you send me a better picture
correct no he's so cute but just a
little filthy a little filthy that's
what I'm saying I can't rate until fix
up your dog and then we're good no he's
not she people are going to get all mad
I can like feel it if they get mad if
they get mad [ __ ] get hurry and her
name is Ora what okay cute very
camouflage true like I only see that
thing's head very nature he's cute or
she's cute yeah one out of 10 boring I
want some more like I don't know why you
even showed that one if I'm being I want
to see him like in the Gage all already
I got one I want to see them doing
something like show me your her name is
Betsy oh bro Betsy Betsy look like she's
up to no good she looks like Santa's
little evil elf look at that thing look
at those teeth oh my looks like she
needs help bad reminds me of [ __ ]
she's got clean white nice straight
teeth though reminds me of Bentley she
just looks mischievous like she looks
like she's up to [ __ ] no good no good
at all this is skunk
e skunk does not want to be held by
whoever the fuckun the ground whoever's
holding skunk needs to put skunk who's
naming the animal skunk I'd love that
name if I'm being honest what why I just
think of introducing your pet oh that's
[ __ ] skunk like dude it makes it seem
like you don't even want it Rhymes too
much with junk to me you know what I
mean what if someone was talking a skunk
and like you didn't know you'd think
like a skunk skunk and it's like it's
like everyone like plug their nose and
run the other way which was that little
thing W it's hot in here dud tell me
about it I'm sweating I don't even have
a shirt on underneath so I'm really
sweating okay this is someone's dog
fudge e e a is fudge missing a leg no oh
no he's just running oh God Action Shot
fudge fudge he looks so cute look at
fudge fudge is on the move oh fudge is
actually so cute fudge is a calendar dog
if I had a dog one like he's
January fudge if I had a if I had a dog
just belongs on the headliner of a Pet
Smart yeah if I on a dog food this like
the benl ass oh my God yeah he's eating
carrots and peas every night I know it
no if I was wild CAU sandwich no he's
eating
fudge so true no if I had to own a dog
like tomorrow I'd buy fudge like fudge
is so cute cute his little tail he got
one of those retractable leashes too
which is
crazy I hate I hate I hate hate hate
[ __ ] with a retractable leash
letting their dog roam around yeah no
they let the dog roam like 20 ft it's
like reel the [ __ ] in he's not a
fish like what are you going to let him
tripwire the elderly like pull that
[ __ ] back especially with a name like
fudge you know where the [ __ ] that
fucker's going at all and you got to
call them over I can tell by looking I
tell by looking in fudge's eyes the
owner's got no control over what fudge
is doing he's living life he's running
around fudge is a beast all right this
is
Cabo also he Cabo's also got [ __ ] on his
face bro clean your dog's lot lips he's
got a full like okay I know people might
be mad like oh you were mean to hurry
like you were making fun of him because
he had [ __ ] on his face this
[ __ ] got a suit on but he got
dirty lips yeah like how's your dog
going to be in a goddamn suit but he's
got [ __ ] on move in a little dude I'm
sweating I like can't I'm like really
hot switch no bro do we have a shirt
[ __ ] world CL do you think we have a
shirt in the trunk no but we can switch
we don't no I'm fine okay I just need
the AC for like 30 seconds we're
interrupting today's car video to plug
cut the camera podcast on all platforms
get ready it's coming very soon watch
the trailer it's out now on the cut the
camera podcast YouTube
channel okay back to it this
[ __ ] is named Figaro or F
yeah he looks like he's in like this
[ __ ] looks like he's in the
movie secret life of pets no for sure
like he's got his CER Chris wait they
said let me line you up here bro he said
yes said you want to go to the groomer
he said absolutely today's the day Chris
if you were if he was in secret life of
pets and they were like you need to be
his voice actor what would Figaro sound
like yeah I'm
figuro so it's you no okay for a little
bit more attitude
he's a little more
Punk like a little you know every Sunday
he go in for a oh my God oh my God oh my
God this person supposed to be a soccer
fan so they Nam their dog messy like you
know like yeah the the name suits
regardless of soccer oh no [ __ ]
is messy oh my God you got pink eye bro
needs [ __ ] crutches with those thin
ass bro I've SE I've seen thicker
[ __ ] wings at Wing Stop than I really
want to I really want to reply to this
DM and say correct like this is messy
I'm like yeah it is like you're
absolutely right terrible her name is
brownie let's
see oh my god oh brownie is peaceful
brownie is so cute Brownie's mysterious
looks like she's seen some things she
looks like she was there for like some I
think naming animals off of their color
is a little overrated yeah brownie Oreo
cookie [ __ ] sugar crumb get out of
here has ever even been C or I make that
that's not a food that was the whole
point what Matt said he said color
nothing to do with food oh idiot yeah
when you said cookie I was like uh I
don't know what you Cookie like someone
sent a man and said this is my cat his
name is Daniel and it's like a
person okay that's really scary we're
going to just all yeah skip past smile
and
wave he's a non- crusty white dog aged
10 rare oh oh my God he's standing on
his own that has to be a stockage
[ __ ] human that's a stock image
that's this is a human being oh my God
oh my God another one with paper thin
dude oh my God oh my God someone please
Photoshop this dog onto a pogo stick
please he's in the perfect position he
looks like [ __ ] Matt in sixth grade
okay crazy oh yeah he's ready why is he
standing like that go to the next one I
don't like it okay that dog freaked me
out dude I don't know something about
him he looked too human
like yeah somebody's inside that
dog there's a human mind in that little
wee brain a ton of animal what is oh she
oh oh oh your dog's ugly we're moving on
oh my God that was so mean but it's true
that dog is
ugly we need some good ones coming
through
oh look at him his ears he's like oh he
looks sad though yeah what's his name I
don't know let's look there's a bunch of
dogs um oh wow oh my God she has a bunch
of oh my God
whoa that dog looks just like Trevor if
you don't know Trevor's our dog he's on
the right of the screenshot and then the
other dog's on the left but I'm in shock
wow wow Mabel looks just like travor oh
my God Maple CLA CLA looks a little
frightening Clara is scary Clara reminds
me when I walk into Laura's house and
Bentley's there oh we can't rap this dog
why he passed away this
summer beautiful angel rest in peace Sam
Sam oh he looks so cute and he's got one
of those little Rubber Chickens you know
the ones that are like the that crazy
noise I know he did well I'm happy that
Sam had owners that loved him me
too what if they neglected Sam no she
like no no no this my dog named Ralph my
horse's main name is Sharky but you can
call her beauty or Dewey or Dewey which
isar is
fine good like girl we didn't need to
know like we just got we need the B oh
my God is that oh my god I didn't even
see they sent a [ __ ] photo of all of
its [ __ ] in a pile that's nasty first of
like name your horse Sharky dropped a
deuce on the ground I just needed the
base oh I wish I was a horse I don't
know why this person gave us like a
biography about the basic and a photo of
its [ __ ]
ugly f f cute little best friends is it
a pug and a cat I can't see yes they're
so cute I have yet to see any an my God
he's so cute that's like that's another
magazine oh my
god
wow he's just so well behaved look is
look at him put a bow tie on him take
him to
dinner yo if you had a boring ass dog
don't send
it I think Trevor's boring
no he's not bro Trevor's rare
okay I love eating like little Gummy
Bears because it's like I feel like I'm
destroying a little Colony against her
they don't this is my homeboy
Charlie
oh he s with style oh my God Charlie
said oh you're taking a picture let me
pose real quick hold on that's his spot
he said Charlie said oh you're what's
that on the ground a hamburger for his
birthday
Charlie got the burger save the photo
and screenshot it this my homeboy
Charlie dude Charlie's so cute because
and another thing
too Charlie looks like you just said
like oh take a photo for the stering
little triplets he said hold on let get
ready for that video he knew he was
going to get some views he's so well
trained sitting there with the burger
right in front of him though I know
right like usually most dogs would just
eat that [ __ ] immediately are not ready
for Ziggy Ziggy
oh God Ziggy looks like a black polar
bear wouldn't that just be a bear a
black bear yeah Ziggy looks like a
[ __ ]
bear Ziggy looks cross Ziggy got Ziggy
looks like she opened the wrong bag yeah
Ziggy got a lot on her mind for sure you
didn't get Ziggy's angles right at all
yeah
uh- that looks like Ziggy took a selfie
Ziggy said # hacked literally bro Ziggy
took some flick Ziggy zaged right before
that oh oh wow look at Elvis Elvis looks
like a that's a that's a Google search
ain't no way that's her dog
that's well it's definitely not her dog
no but Ain no way herat Elvis looks like
a
um I thought that was a hamster so the
dog I literally saw it quick I thought
it was a hamster you guys are crazy I
don't know it's the angle angle thr us
it looks
like [ __ ]
work oh my God what is this
dog bring that [ __ ] to the dce
holy
[ __ ] holy [ __ ] Bella Bella B Po Girl
Bella hun
Jesus Bella needs to get those teeth
fixed dude Bella needs
something
God feels so
oh look at that we can't attack the
dog's hygiene I feel terrible brush your
teeth wow Bella she said this is Lou
please include him in your video okay he
asked politely a that's not real that's
got to be a photo from Google why do you
think that cuz he just looks so
long guys chill oh
two pugs Mario and Luigi no way y Mario
and Luigi's crazy oh which one's which
oh that one's got some
eye [ __ ] looks face tuned that's
okay you guys that's okay Mario and
Luigi two pugs that's so hard bro what a
moment if that I like the blonde one
they're both white are you just saying
that cuz his eyes
crooked that's like 90% of the
motivation yeah damn it Nick not going
to lie okay
oh my God what is what is it her name is
Barbara hi Barbara look at all the grass
on her nose G
gross why is that gross is it a cow or a
donkey I don't know it's a cow I can't
even tell hi Barbara oh dude I want to
own a barn one day
Dexter Dexter's a dog in the [ __ ]
video I love him so much cute as shito
he I [ __ ] love Dexter oh my God cute
whoever named him you need a ward that
is a [ __ ] beautiful dog name oh
Dexter two photos he's so cute he has
like the perfect nose o I'm Dex he he
has like the dog nose def this is
definitely February oh yeah in the
calendar Dexter means business he looks
like a real English like he looks like M
like he looks um a Dexter yeah he looks
like like a super spy I want to find
puy spy movieo I saw one earlier and I'm
so mad I didn't screenshot it it was
like a cat and it had a [ __ ] cloak on
and I wanted to react to be like is this
[ __ ] like Jedi like is he going
to what did I just hear I don't
know
oh oh my [ __ ] words is he a witch or
is he in the rain what bro's got a rain
coat on like
Michael ready to go outside
hio hippo poo I don't know hippo dude I
Love It I Like Him holy he is cute he's
so Stout like he looks so small dude I
think he'd be fun to hang around with
this dog is a pony that thing is that
thing this is actually my biggest fear
of a dog yeah like I just know no this
one looks like Bigfoot like right here
like if you like put some trees in the
back like that's big foot no I don't
like bing bong bing
bong bro you got to realize you're going
to be calling these dogs out in the
street Bing Bong yo Bing Bong that's
crazy yeah I don't like that one that
one looked really [ __ ] you look too
human likee like that dog looks like he
got a car and a purse and family to go
visit anything about him all right thank
you guys so much for submitting your
pets to us for this video I had probably
the most fun I've had filming a car
video in a while and I I think that that
was super fun me too so thanks for the
carard idea as well Haley was the name
of the girl who gave us the carard idea
remember we no hate to the dogss we love
all dogs yes this is all for ComEd
unless you're
Bella no hate full this is all for
comedic purposes all animals are amazing
yes but um actually what was I going to
say if you want us to do a part two of
this like this video if you want us to
do a part two definitely let us know and
also we're going to start posting more
like hey what car videos do you want us
to film um so look out for those stories
and start thinking of your ideas write
them down your notebook your phone text
them to your friend and then get ready
to tell them to us when we ask and our
new cut the camera podcast on all
platforms is coming out very very very
very very soon I'm going to put the link
in the description to all the socials
for that so make sure you're subscribed
to that channel follow that Spotify
follow that Instagram follow that Tik
Tok cuz everything's going to be you
know you want to stay up to dat that's
what animal would you
be what animal would would I be
yeah an owl why you just want to be yeah
I'd want to be what what about you Nick
I don't know but thank you guys so much
see you soon how would you
be I would be a serpent not true Nick
I'm a [ __ ] world class
CER saying how you miss me yeah you miss
me and all the things that we did we
said we going to travel from the island
to Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
all a why because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving different don't be
saying nothing when p with other [ __ ]
for my brothers