all right what's up guys let Nick sit
down get in your seat dude
M come
on what up everyone stop spinning the
coin what's up everybody in front of the
table is $3,000 of debt yes basically
30s 20s 10 fives threes twos and ones so
we're $3,000 in debt our goal is to see
if we can get out of debt or see how
much doubt we can get how much debt we
can get out of we're going to scratch
some tickets and our ultim goal for this
entire video is to get this 3,000 to a
lower and then higher number I'm hitting
big first one all right I doubt it all
right hold on Nick has been making fun
of me cuz I've been talking about
neighbor tickets and all that type of
stuff no the neighbor ticket is the one
that's next to it in the machine so like
a lot of people don't buy back to back
because like this see how this is this
is ticket number 23 that's ticket number
24 we're going to lose no matter what
what is this cross word it's a toad
totally awesome Tak a multiple craze
wait where's the instructions gems
diamonds pearls gold bars like what
next no we a winner no way off first
ticket no way Nick wait what a dude
don't tell me it won but it just says
ticket oh if it says ticket that's the
money back so I think that's 20 we we're
a little knowledgeable because of our
our time at Star Market at the desk so
ticket basically means they'll exchange
this losing ticket for another $20
ticket that's a little stupid are they
is this ridiculous this is like a loser
no it's not it's a it's $20 worth of
scratch tickets which is in my book is a
$20 bill correct that's not true we're
not counting that as money off the total
well we're not counting it as a loser
it's not a loser are it's a loser well
we have not profited money I have a
winner no way how much I don't know I
didn't scratch the number off yet oh on
28 28 prize multiplier are we ready hold
on wait where are we at 28 is one of my
winning numbers 28 right here Nick are
you ready yeah that that's the only one
that matches only one yeah five bucks on
a $10 ticket wait time 20 yep wait
what's 5 time
20 0 and profit let's
go all right 28 right here
matches this 28 which is $5 time 20
that's 100 bucks let's
go this is so stupid
loser
[Music]
loser what winner guess how much how
much how
much please ticket no way dude well I've
never seen this before in my life an
exchangeable ticket dude we're going to
have to go back to the 7-Eleven like a
ton like I'd rather lose you know I'm
just getting edged Matt that's crazy
pause it has a little pineapple logo I
like it [ __ ] stupid I'm going let me
search this up right crash back I don't
like having to think I just want to know
if I threw my money away or if I'm a
winner correct going to be see gamblers
addiction Link in description seriously
you're never going to win this is not a
good
hobby dude this ticket is an absolute
task
dude four no one one no I'm like like
nervous to get another ticket until
Chris is done
trash this sucks imagine if we won
$30,000 Nick shut the [ __ ] up trash I
don't like like the bonuses and [ __ ] you
know yeah just tell me give it to me
straight how do they manufacture these
and have no thieves that's what I'm
saying bro ass I feel like I'm like
working in like veroa Salt's dad's
Factory to like get her the gold winner
hold on ticket ticket [ __ ] join the club
have the word hop or no hope this kid is
[ __ ] stupid give him another CU I was
covering the okay hope hope obey and yet
and those are the only words I have so
that's three words
$4 yes that's a dollar profit yes it is$
four winner how
much ticket stop [ __ ] okay so this is
just a $4 ticket hey that's four
bucks four bucks all right I'm doing the
another crossw no you're not put that
down I think we should just try to do
all the cross we will but you don't need
to do that have fun trash I'm not having
fun show me the money oh God that's a
good one that's a good name all right
guys what's up um so we're I know we're
in the middle of doing the scratch
ticket video right now so it's weird
that I just popped up in the middle of
the car but the other day I said like oh
if we film this video if one of you
[ __ ] idiots get one of those fake
scratch tickets I'm going to be so mad
and they were like oh that's such a good
idea blah blah blah you should have done
should have done that and I was like
wait that was a good idea I should have
done that but now that I said it out
loud and they think like oh like I
wouldn't do it I think now it would be
more believable especially with this one
cuz all the other ones like like the $2
ones and everything came in the but this
is a $5 one and it's literally I checked
the exact same size as the other one and
I said that I I was not going to get a
fake ticket yesterday and I overnighted
this and it came today so I think that
this could fool them so I'm going to do
my best attempt this is a $5 ticket and
it's going to
show that we won
$100,000 so 73 11 and
9 I like this one it's very simple we
should keep this
one
12 I like can't do this near you guys
cuz I just want to watch you do
it
19 32 did you lose I'm losing so far
24 28 on Last Chance 30 no oh we got a
winner Nick no way it's going to be a
ticket watch don't say winner anymore
unless it's [ __ ] all right we got to
pray it's not a ticket guys come on show
me the
money oh what
100 is that 100 or a
th000
100,000 what the [ __ ] this is a fake
ticket this is a fake like one of you
guys bought this one is a fake no oh my
God one of you bought this as a
fake one of you bought this as a
oh my God I bought that on Amazon this
morning did you a f yeah and I put it in
that pile I knew it right away I knew it
right away godam I knew it
right I knew it right away yes I knew to
do that that was good no cuz guys the
reason I didn't think it would be that
is cuz Matt show me the money it looks
like the fakest card ever it looks so
simple it looks like the fakest card
like this one it's simple I should have
known I was buying the reason it's so
the reason it's so funny too is Matt
suggested that idea yesterday and then I
already I went to the car to record that
oh wow you're crazy I know I did so good
that was a good prank Matt that was good
good job thank you all right back to it
we're doing the Pac-Man one have anyone
done a Pac-Man yet no I like it though I
like Pac-Man I have Pac-Man tattooed
don't no I don't do I have Pac-Man
tattoo no I don't you're [ __ ] stupid
why did I think I did I don't know cuz
it's something you get
I'm going to do I'm going to do a cross
word one get used to that all right show
me the money this [ __ ] sucks this is
just a whole lot of disappointment we're
going to end up with a [ __ ] toothpick
for our kitchen table no literally we're
sanding
away I'm going to [ __ ] need a quarter
Zone shot after [ __ ] 10 more tickets
Matt did your heart drop when I grabb
the fake one yeah like you like a little
scared yeah cuz that's why you went to
gra grab this one and I said no come on
have some fun yeah yeah let's I'm keep
doing those until we win this one's a
ticket see what a terrible piece of
advice do that one until we win TV what
huh I don't know what I'm saying TV I
like the ones with cute little symol
symbols and just like it's chill like
it's like apple orange I'm like yay I
feel [ __ ] give me a rainbow give me a
rainbow win nothing [ __ ]
are you sure you're playing it right no
can you check before you rip them in
half all this work making me want a
Cinnabon oh my God you have it t wow
that smells really good Five Five Guys
I'm the best I'm the best guys if I get
a e we might become a
millionaire are you [ __ ] kidding me
Matt you're 50 come on
that was five bucks baby really yeah
[ __ ] yeah Nick five bucks no way again
Nick come on nowday piggy bank key [ __ ]
you doue for a hit right mat that's a
loser heart key da [ __ ] you do you ever
feel like man this is probably stupid
yeah this decision yeah I thought from
the beginning we were going to [ __ ]
lose we literally paid for manual labor
but one one of these could have like 30
grand no it's not it could it could
hypothetically it's the thrill it's the
thrill I'm [ __ ] seeking the thrill
right now the thrill come on oh times
two prize five what are you say
$10 it's the thrill we were seeking the
thrill wait wait are we there is this
real win no another two
bucks oh watch out watch out he's on a
hot wait this is a big winner I I feel
it more coming 24
what 31 nothing oh win another two bucks
let's go 14 day hold on hold on this
ticket's hot right now it's on fire 11
11 wait wait we'll go back we'll go back
no do it just do it do it now yeah
another two bucks okay okay okay yeah
yeah yeah 16 17 18 bucks go 18s bucks
can we even win 18 that fast spot to
hit words of a true degenerate hold hold
on
to that hold on to your [ __ ] Crown
cuz if this is a crown we win
$3,000 it's not going to be give me the
crown it's a
lobster guys why do I feel like we're
going to make it back we're not going to
I think we're going to no Chris stop
licking me I'm not licking you no all
right 40 bucks ain't bad 40 bucks ain't
bad at all if we hit like a th we need
to win like 500 something Nick I was
asking for a lot I know but we spent
$3,000 we should be able to get at least
1,000 back I'm praying on at least that
big loser yeah I need to play more this
is how many we have left all right so
we've won
$327 so far which means we are
$2,673 which is better than I thought
still better than I thought I don't even
think we're going to say safely get to
2,000 in debt Nick one of those is a big
winner I feel it we'll get we'll get 673
come on guys like one of those has to be
like 10K crazy bonus no [ __ ] chance I
swear dude there's no way we can empty
out every [ __ ] lottery machine in the
[ __ ] Los Angeles County and we can't
[ __ ] hit big like actually what are
you doing it's dark in here what do you
you have a penny I'm about to hit a
million dollar you're not going to get a
million dollars I swear to God I am Matt
are you ready to Be A Millionaire
billion dollars give me aab billion
dollars give me a billion dollars give
me aab billion dollars 33 three I hit no
you get us my God what' you get us wait
we have to get hype if I hit it okay are
you ready I'm
scared bre oh my God I'm going to jump
on the table if we hit it Chris what if
it's like just $2 no if it's if it's
over two bucks watch me jump like I'm
going to literally hit Saturn
what is it what is it
$4 is it
recording are you [ __ ] stupid Nick
you just made me hit my hand you idiot
me my own blood one of these is about to
hit like huge don't scream put the
brownies away no I'm eating leave me in
my brownies
alone I want
brownies come on baby take me out of the
deck just 200,000 200,000 we're creeping
in on the back me a
Nick that was my piece of the brownie
it's my brownie ew you look
terrible thank you it's my brownie it's
like all your mouth and [ __ ] shout
Trader Dr all right there's some lady
there
and she asked us if we had any pets what
what's going on I'm TR okay do you have
any pets we were like no do you and I
was like oh I have a dog like I said oh
I have a dog but he lives in Boston my
parents still
and she like oh yeah we all have
that and I was like okay and I was like
do you have any pets and she was like
she's like yeah I have four cats but I I
feed about 500 I was like
what and she's like oh I work for like a
the um like she worked like a shelter
yeah and uh yeah she's just always
feeding the Strays really yeah she's
like I go through 50 50 lb kibble bags a
day
holy [ __ ] out of her own pocket you
think yeah she's oh we hit what do we
get show me the [ __ ] money $3
actually yeah $2 three vicious ass
shakes let's get it come on all three of
us no okay sit down plus five bucks
let's [ __ ] go give me the money give
me the money give me the
money guys I'm going to wait Matt yours
is plus two ch is plus five
yeah Nick Nick Nick Nick ni settle down
buy my [ __ ] a first class ticket to
Paris we going to [ __ ] in the Eiffel
Tower we going to be pounding the walls
Nick Nick stop
okay [ __ ] give me a kiss on the
lips give me a [ __ ] year of Fortune I
hope so Nick you're freaking me out
right now shut the [ __ ] up oh no 10x
prize holy [ __ ] holy [ __ ] please don't
be a dollar please don't be a dollar
please don't be a dollar pleas be dollar
should I do it now please please don't
be a dollar hold let me do this last row
first oh my God Chris hold on we're
going to be millionaires show me the big
ticket I'm taking my girl on a yacht
hold on wait a second on chill you're
freaking me out all right please don't
be a dollar wait okay so Chris is at a
point it says 10x so whatever this
number he scratches multiply it by 10 we
win that wait so we're dead on
everything else though right this is
Major this is Major please be like 20
bucks three three three times 10 10 $30
30 that's a
big 30 bucks is Si that's good that's
good Nick be happy it ain't going to get
me to Paris I need to do this
faster our [ __ ] table's going to be
half an inch half an inch less no I
think I'm cutting through it every time
I do it a chest I don't want a chest I
want a thumbs up
[ __ ] wow winner no for
real the ticket you dumb
[ __ ]
$3,000 are you serious no I'm lying
you're an idiot like why would he like
are you serious I just was I was being
optimistic and it didn't
hit
nice good
work you need to stop doing that cuz I
thought we just won like a million
dollars I can get a smoothie and I don't
have to think twice about it I can get a
smoothie with this six [ __ ] bucks
give me one of them no I'm no they're
mine oh mine give me one of those red
hot cash you get one kid give me another
red hot cash no they're fun right
they're mine they're mine give me
another no there's so many there's other
options for you I want one I found it
first I gave you one already give me
another no please please I need them
please I want the red hot no there's so
many one more look it here right here
Nick give me one more red H you ask
again you don't receive shut the [ __ ] up
kid you're addict holy [ __ ] my Red
Hots oh 10x no way it's going to be a
dollar bucks 30 [ __ ] bucks [ __ ] ew
you just spit all over my face 30 that
30 bucks to go get a
facial oh
oh give them give
him the red I think this is 50 no I I
think this is 50 fact check another 10
on a red hot come
on
$30 $30 oh my God oh my God you don't
know [ __ ] about the
game what you don't know what it [ __ ]
takes kid stop flinging the dust at me
seriously stop
get
away
winner 25 [ __ ]
bucks get the [ __ ] up get the [ __ ] away
from
me no way you hit for 25 oh yeah let's
see if I got more actually
yeah what what Nick wait I'm wrong I'm
wrong I'm wrong what' you
think what' you think we won
on I thought it was five bucks no way
you reacted like that for $5 how much
did you think we were going to win give
me another of those I like
that 20 bucks I'm a loser
$20 all right guys we're done with
scratching session number two
but thus far in this video we' did one
scratching session together Matt Chris
went to Summers smash I scratched a
couple alone and then we just did a
second scratching session together in
total we have gained
$611 which brings us to a debt margin of
$2,389 still which sucks ass we need one
of these to be like a $1,000 winner
otherwise we are severely definitely
going into debt disclaimer we're also
not telling you guys to go play the
lottery you shouldn't go play you will
literally lose your money we do not
advise this this is for entertainment
purposes in order to bring the luck we
each brought a lucky device or object to
today's scratching session my lucky
item
is the fake $100,000 winner cuz this is
this is
manifestation and it's it's channeling
the luck even though it is fake it's
channeling the fact that this is a
$1,000 winner into into the Vibes I'm
channeling winning with this orange
hat that's it I have no explanation this
is like it's giving me good luck it
reminds me of my favorite ever Abraham
Lincoln because I was already a winner
at some point I figured I'd just bring
my versus to trophy so that I can really
embody Victory and being a winner crazy
I love it I hate it when like they put
so many numbers on the card and and
they're like oh it's because we want you
to have so many opportunities to win
it's like no you want so many
opportunities to Edge me oh my God I got
$50 let's [ __ ] go Matt hold on get
lit he did the multiplier open it oh 30
bucks 30 oh no oh we lost my head feels
like it's 25 lb no
[Music]
literally I haar I say something like
that it's like the last thing someone
said you know what I mean like you're
like my headphones look like no
literally
and then it's was like awkward
silence I wish we had a paper shredder
so I could just instantly put this in a
shredder isn't that the name of the bad
guy from Teenage Ninja Turtles no it's
the Sensei Shredder shred is that's
Splinter Splinter Shredder Shredder is a
bad guy Splinter is Splinter is the
master the Sensei the rat Don't Call Him
a rat that's no he's Sensei I hate that
a clover doesn't win money like that's
like a good symbol right you want know
what I think I think this lucky number
sev's card like you lose a lot and then
one of the cards has like 10,000 on it
you think so yeah because I I haven't
hit one like not even close on any of
these that's literally the lottery like
that's what this is spent some money at
the lottery living life like I hit the
lottery can you stop talking yeah like
this ticket and this ticket are like the
same thing it's just like different
different
game 75 $75 yep N Get Hype Plus 75 [ __ ]
I feel like I'm next to [ __ ]
slash like
literally Ghost Face Killer next to me
doing some tickets I'm never going to
win a lucky number seven it's never
going to happen there's two left you're
like making me nervous that you like
care this
much
what 100 bucks
Matt actually yeah no we should I want
to go back and bu go back back and bu
the rest he's so convinced there was a
good one I dude I swear to God someone's
at home right now hitting a million
dollars on the lucky number s that's to
oh my God ticket it's a ticket it's a
ticket burn it in hell did you eat all
my Doritos chips I didn't eat a single
one no the that second bag oh yeah I eat
the rest you told me to eat the
rest I'm like freaking out right now I
need
Doritos okay okay this is that was crazy
all right guys with today's earnings we
are at
$876,000 which brings us at
$2,124 in debt still you won the lottery
with me as your brother yes I did and I
would I wouldn't trade you for the
biggest winen ticket ever can you get
your hand off my stomach thank you all
right guys I'm tired and have a headache
so I'm done I'm doing one more I'm also
done I have a pounding headache dude I
need Doritos Chris get the [ __ ]
Doritos you're grown
them $110 sorry not a winner sorry not a
winner not a winner app's not working
not winner 20 s not a winner all right
30 30 bucks off off the cross wordss is
not bad guys we just s the Tik Tok
scratching one of our $30 tickets to
promote this video and we just hit $200
on that ticket it was crazy which you're
taking up space that no one else is
taking off surprised cuz you want to
take it up don't you that's the whole
point of me moving my elbow cuz you want
cuz your elbow's hitting sitting in my
little bubble I'm in my little bubble
and your elbow's still managing to hit
me like this like this like this your
elbows are also still legit legit you're
like this you're L scratching tickets
like this if you have you have
headphones on during this video so I
have headphones on because half of this
video is going to be sitting here
scratching it side don't don't care
don't care don't care don't care
YouTuber Matt stolo kills sibling
Brothers I can't wait for that to be the
new
ticket
ticket okay what if someone just came in
the house and like give me every [ __ ]
ticket or your don't even say that and
they just like started like like hitting
us and stuff and they like took one of
us for hostage and they did the whole
like like this like behind the back like
they were behind me like this what would
you do I'd [ __ ] do what they say they
have guns in four someone comes in give
me every [ __ ] ticket or your
brother's dead and they put me in a
headlock and they got me like this I say
I'm keeping my tickets kill them if you
want oh like what if someone like tied
stop scratch tickets no what if someone
what if someone like tied to like a rope
on our roof and then they jump down like
burst through this window like the glass
shatters they land on the table
huh wait you get the prize off of the
coin hold on let me see it hold record
this on your phone I can't see record on
your phone so you can edit what if like
the FBI thought we were like can you
stop cord I can't see that far okay then
I can't see your stand up stand up open
your eyes I'm not moving the [ __ ] how
can you not see I want you to go like
this like put it way closer to my face
stand up if you want to record you
record it you record it you're next to
him I can't see give me it then give me
your phone you have a phone you're the
editor okay I'm scratching I don't care
you Matt stop Matt stop stop for a
second Nick dial in I'll record it I
can't see Matt hold it up I can't
believe you you're like ridiculous I
cannot see that far I cannot see read
that yes that's in big bold [ __ ]
shiny letters Matt get up and come over
here if you want no just take a deep
breath calm down and hold it up Matt I'm
going to hold it up okay look look it
hold on you see let me talk Matt's doing
it like an idiot that's why thank you
he's like holding it like this like
trying to show you something like a
secret I scratched these numbers first
these two matched so I get that prize
and this prize they're both $5 so we
already have the $10 for the ticket okay
now uncover a coin symbol win prize
shown we have got three Co coin
symbols I don't know what all right
let's see what's there what's behind the
coins $5
W5 another
$5 wait something horrible is going to
happen why I just had the most actual
insane Deja Vu ever based off the
scenarios you were talking about like
one of us getting like killed or like
actually like it was exactly like this
except there was a legit
murderer us like I swear to you I
dreamed camera off I dreamed camera off
no it's I'd rather keep that on no like
camera off your genuinely genuinely I
had a dream once that the three of us
are here but genuinely I actually you're
freaking me out cu I don't like this
[ __ ] I know I is the car like is going
to
burn winner where
suck move your elbows don't wipe your
ticket dust on you like this a coin on
this one means nothing but on that means
a free 50 bucks which is why I'm like
why all right everyone Nick is
scratching the last $10 ticket all we
have left a 50 bucks actually yes Nick
another 50 bucks $120 on his ticket what
a big [ __ ] ticket crazy good [ __ ] ni
all right there we go 20s 30s then we're
done oh another another winner $10
another $5 30 bucks again yeah I made
money back or who just won
$18 no one no one why did I write that
down I'm scared for no like you're like
the past 10 minutes you've been like
freaking me out I feel like I'm not even
with my brother I know I feel like I'm
with like alien Nick or something why I
right I'm scratching the last ticket go
hit me in the face I didn't hit you in
the face [ __ ] yeah you did I felt
your forearm on my nose it's on camera I
love when you say [ __ ] that's like on
camera I I didn't hit your face I grazed
your nose you hit my face I grazed
that's annoying you made contact with me
when there was no need to Scrat your the
lottery can I have a sip of that coke ow
you're stepping on my foot fat ass
you're going to break my [ __ ] feet
good you're an idiot I didn't step on
you
yeah let me get a sip of that you loser
you're a loser last ticket I already
scratched the bonuses and there's
nothing there so we're going to try to
match the numbers here we ready let's do
it okay
loser oh I hate that the last one was a
loser all right guys before we wrap this
part up just want to say there are some
tickets that when you scratch off you
win the ability to get another scratch
ticket but you don't win money so we'll
see you in a minute when we're
scratching our rid red deemed scratch
tickets that we
lost you just said that like terrible
explanation terrible all right everyone
it is finally coming to an end this
video has taken so [ __ ]
long the proof is in my hand the proof
that no one should play the [ __ ]
Lottery ever correct we walked we walked
into this challenge with $33,000 cash
bow
negative $965
I have $2,000 and or
$2,035 in my hand so we
lost a lot of money [ __ ] this $35 we we
lost we lost ,000 basically essentially
essentially we lost $11,000 out of all
the tickets we bought three of them were
over $100 we won shockingly more than I
thought I agree still not worth it and I
think the only reason we did well is cuz
we had so many but the thing is too with
the lotteries like people do it even
when the odds are so low cuz they think
they're actually going to hit like a
billion qu million dollars yeah like
what's with that thought process yeah
but it is I think they're fun to like
give as a gift for a birthday or like
play once a year but like seriously guys
gamble responsibly please we just we're
,000 in debt whatever we'll survive like
this video if you want to see us try
again that's a lie I'm not doing this no
matter what yeah like this video if you
like videos like this where we like
experiment stupid
things basically if we shred our money
is going to be the next one putting
$1,000 in a shredder is literally what
this video could be whatever see you
guys next Friday thank you so much for
watching and we'll see you guys next
FR Friday
[Applause]
[Music]