I feel like I'm giving decob Hooters
girl in this shirt what did you just say
so I feel like I'm giving decup Hooters
girl in this
shirt yeah you got some nice knockers
[Laughter]
[Music]
H all right ni I feel get freaked out I
get freaked out when I hear that camera
beep and I literally look and I see like
crisp pink Panther like moving toward me
like this like I'm like what is it's
going to be hard really really hard to
contain yourself I know you're going to
get
excited but I got a package give me a
second do you have any I have no idea
what this
is look how gross our table is that I
know I'm trying to avoid recording fries
gummy
candy this here the coconut Dr Pepper
kid said it's here Chris ordered this on
Amazon and he was telling me all about
it and I I interrupted him like a minute
30 into a sentence I go oh I don't care
I don't care about the coconut Dr Pepper
well you guys saw us make coconut Dr
Pepper the other day in our video and I
thought it was like a universal like we
were excited to try it no I was like
Chris that was just you I don't care
clearly I'm on my own I don't even think
this is in stores yet I have to get it
on Amazon Fresh okay that means it's in
an Amazon Fresh store thank you that
means who you T taing Sam he's mad cuz
he bought that [ __ ] first but mine came
first I bought that like extra priority
[ __ ] I live closer to an Amazon Fresh no
I don't Nick stop talking about Amazon
Fresh all right say goodbye on there's
another package on the door that I
completely ignored let me grab it do you
guys know now that the podcast has been
over for a while can we like all agree
that it was a good decision to end it
for our mental health Nick let me see
that new space camp packaging so
convenient I could throw this right in
my pocket throw this right in my bag
perfectly fits all three of our jumbo
size Tu and it's so cute we also have
the two packs the flavor packs if you
have a preference I don't have a
preference I'd buy all three of these
flavor packs we haven't decided where we
want to go yet today so I figured let's
put the camera up and we can decide on
camera right I look like a scary monster
protecting my layer like in this that's
how you always look
okay especially when you like look like
when you're at the top of the stairs no
need to elaborate on it
you're good you're good let's just leave
where are we going I don't know put the
camera away and let's leave and then put
it back up when we figure it out dumbass
let's go toward Melrose I want Happy ice
I want to go to there's one decision you
guys want you want to know what I hate
like actually you want to know what
makes me nervous when I see people and
they're like get ready with me because
I'm running late and I have to be there
in 5 to 10 minutes put your phone away
don't film to get ready with me get
ready is there a monke monkey on that
car there is you see the monkey on that
truck anyway why is this too bright yes
it's too [ __ ] bright why are we
filming get ready with me like when
you're literally like it's like leave
the [ __ ] house if you're in that much
of a rush or if you're going to be late
to something that's important I agree
you're like oh my God I'm getting ready
to put my house out of the fire that it
just caught on and you're not moving
remember when we threw cheese at an
Amazon truck just like that I
too I was like good time wo cuz I have
no problem just sitting up like this and
you can see me equally you're like 12
what wo you you didn't what did I point
at a car and a drive incorrect incorrect
you're not just you guys just aren't at
my observant level like I'm the most
observant person in the world sorry you
don't speak you know what I mean
normally a normal person would go whoo
this is what I'm saying I wanted one of
you guys to like Edge on my no one cares
you want us to edge you a little yeah go
ahead no I was going to say is um both
those cars had the exact same license
plate except one letter
different tell me it isn't
true I supposed to we this I think we
should get pizza before we get happy ice
that's my decision where do you want to
get pizza we want to get
pizza we want to get pizza Matt do you
want a pieza of this like wheat [ __ ]
right here Buck weat yeah Chris you need
to sit down no get me
one are you
I love these so much [ __ ] we I love
these I'm surprised I could reach that
this is what this is what I didn't think
I was going to make it but I did it's
right there this is what farmers use
smells like it this is what farmers use
as a toothpick like are you serious like
on the ranch yeah when they cuz why do
you think there's so many like of the
videos of the farmer like with in their
mouth like all right stop that's like
dirty dude that's like Earth it's not
that's what Chris that's it's a natur
it's God stop throwing it's God it's
literally God's tooth bck where did that
just go that stick you through oh what
should I just how do I get rid of this
do I throw it back outside right back
where it came from leave it in the car
you picked it for Matt it's a flower a
base at home you want oo that guy's
mirror got hit is that the Epcot ball no
is not in Florida what is that see I
feel bad sometimes like sometimes
there's I have two emotions when I see a
stranger in public one is I want to cry
and I hope nothing happens to them ever
bad like I'm like oh they look so sweet
second
I just want to punch them in the face
okay wo look at this lady what head to
toe in the pink
where pink backpack pink skirt like the
pink Tu shoes and a pink hat those are a
choice she actually looked really nice
looks
horrible that's good you know I was
driving there once and um there's some
dude holding up a sign and it was like
please make donations for this funeral
mhmm and then he was holding up the sign
the the next week that I drove by there
with the dude that was holding the other
sign's picture like they were just like
holding each other's picture oh my God
that's crazy do you know one time I was
on this street driving and I saw a girl
in a fresh love Hoodie right there that
blue box yeah isn't that crazy I wasn't
with you guys nuts I remember that I was
there you were there yeah oh yeah it was
pretty fun three
umces yeah what do you guys want to
drink uh um I'll just have a water
photo you want to take a
photo cheese say cheese
chees baby can't get his drink open I
don't think it's a Twist Off I think
it's a qu I got it no you you know he
didn't take it off of his mouth he did
it the other day freak me
out don't do that don't do that don't
actually don't do that CU they can I'm
I'm not even recording this like put
that they can do it they have a bottle
opener no record it record no this I
don't even want to look at him I'm not
looking at him you're going toak don't
break your tooth it freaks me out oh my
God you're so impressive dude look at
that he can do it with his
mouth Nick take
this no way Jesus Christ Jesus Christ
the kind soul in there gave us an extra
because one of the slices was small he
said what a
guy you're smelling that too right
what it smells like like like like Funk
yeah it smells kind of like um I don't
smell anything bad I hate when you put
your chair all the way back cuz it like
forces me to like sit just just say
something speak up wait I want that one
this one mhm I want that one guys Prime
kind of looks sloppy today but I don't
know what's going on it smells a little
funky doesn't it Chris you told me you
tried pineapple pizza the other day for
the first time how'd you like
what when and
aware absolutely news to
me absolutely news to me here what Nick
give me this you and Chris can fight
over that box
okay hello we're fighting over it so
Chris how'd you like the pineapple pizza
you tried for the first time the other
day and why did I not hear about it the
other day I was in my
room oh no I'm I put so much parmesan
cheese by
accident you were out of the house Nick
I was in my room and I was hungry and I
was like I really love like meat on my
pizza like I love any form of
meat okay yeah so
in your room thinking pepperoni I yeah I
love pepperoni I love ham I love bacon
ground beef you name it I'll eat it if
it's meat on my pizza okay I'm helping
you yeah yeah go ahead and then I was
like you know what I kind of want to try
like like that Hawaiian style like like
sweet and savory Vibe so I instead of
just getting pepperoni I when did you
order [ __ ] Pizza I got pepperoni
pizza with with pineapple on it and I
atee it for the first time disgusting it
was it was all right would you eat it
again no no if someone I was with got it
and I needed to like accommodate to the
group I would eat it again mhm a
a
a oh my God wait she's so cute they both
look so happy together oh my
God she was cute and then this there's
this couple where this guy thinks he's
too cool no no him holding him holding
her water bottle is really cute like her
water bottles like the same color as her
shirt this is really cute too guys we
people watch like way too frequently
yeah we do you guys remember the first
time you had pizza no absolutely not a
baby
suck what I like kind of do what
pizza the first time I ever remember
having pizza was on Christmas Eve really
yeah wow when did we get pizza on
christm christm Eve how old I was like
four probably
okay you don't remember the first time
having pizza no but I remember my first
time having an avocado anyway I hate
this girl's bag I was about to say I
hate it I hate it it's hideous stupid
anyway
what Nick why did you say the the end ah
what is that such a crazy Choice yeah is
her are her pants ripped
that's like a there's like a crocheting
yeah that was like that's like terrible
is that the
Slender oh my God I'm actually really
scared Matt oh my
word I feel like we should
move is that a machete a machete mat I'm
not joking no he has like a long foreign
object uhuh o ooh ooh okay wait poor
lady just gave him a side the side eye
like I thought oh my God his pants are
at his ankles what's in between his legs
uh-uh he's he's got pants on brother oh
no we're good okay can we take this
anyway I got to sneak a photo of him so
if he starts yelling at me can you take
this okay this cleat on his baseball
cleat
on look at all these higho this idiot
just do his [ __ ] football on the road
all right guys status update we finished
eating pizza or Matt's about to be
finished eating pizza eating his crust
I'm making Matt drive me to the store
cuz the other day I got a is that a
orange poodle yep died ah I'm taking a
photo look at it my window hurry up Nick
hurry up hurry up oh my God hurry up
[ __ ] Matt go upep upis you got to take
it you got to take it I can't see it
[ __ ] [ __ ] dude we just ruined it that
would have been so that was a legit
orange it was like Cliff you see that
you see that orange dog that was crazy
like a clown I
know for real have a good one have a
beautiful day man oh my God that is
thank God you talk to a stranger because
that's the little like that's thought
there was a [ __ ] CL he gave me a p
sign I was like I need to ask this dude
if he just saw that he thought I was I
thought it was a clown do clown dog oh
that was so good so funny did you see
that dog he said oh my God I don't know
what brings me to do [ __ ] like yeah like
you never talk look oh so cute Nick take
a photo of them oh so cute a that I love
[ __ ] like that I love
it [ __ ] I love that [ __ ]
cute you guys look great
[Laughter]
try again try
again it's too much to do that was so
embarrassing mat Matt put you F crazy
these people are taking photos right
here Matt and I go look I literally Matt
Scrolls on go you guys look great I got
zero response that was ridiculous that
was horrible that was really funny
anyway I don't know what the past I
should have been wearing shorts today
and I'm wearing a sweater and I don't
know what the past two minutes were that
was a lot and very chaotic hot that we
drove by I knew you were going to say
that when I saw that dude on oh the guy
with the hat no oh I knew you were going
to say that too Nick you can see you
have to watch the footage back it
literally like my eyes jolted my arms
are but we're about to run into the
store go shopping and bought a belt here
the other day and the belt that he
bought is too big it doesn't hold his
[ __ ] did I tell you this where have I
been and I'm not getting the update I
bought this belt the other cuz I really
liked it and I tried it on in the store
when in reality I just like wrapped it
around me real quick and I like just
guessed and I was like oh yeah I fit and
then I got home and it like didn't serve
its purpose guys we're forcing our we're
forcing ourselves to do less triplet
related things so we have more stories
to talk about yeah like we've been going
out on our own I've been ubering places
cuz we're trying to get Nick I can't see
you it's okay cuz we're trying to just
get we're trying to just we're we're
trying to get more memories like on our
individuality and like we want to that's
a good choice horrible you're an idiot
yeah you're dumb we're just trying to go
what are you doing I'm fixing it right
there that's
fine
oh oh no she's trying to sell her
something is
she what is I feel like I am like I feel
like my past 10 minutes are not real
like she just gave her a literal plastic
bag that was clearly empty and a rose
we're trying to go and do individual
things that when we come together we
have more things to talk about and
content and just stories and and
everything me Sam and we're adults we
need to not be up each other's ass
anymore yeah me Sam and Matt went
shopping the other day and I bought a
belt that was way too big so I need to
return it and get it in my right size oh
my God a wish flower is that what I used
to call these what a wish flower that's
a dandelion a wish
flow Matt don't ever do that are you
serious someone it out
the equivalent to blowing it out no it's
not what is going on I thought it was
blowing it out hold I'm going to blow it
out Nick it looks so dark fix it you're
a
YouTuber y don't tell anyone all right
take
this that was fun thank you try again
[ __ ]
look at you look at
you oh I twisted my ankle look at all
that
slush look at how cool mine looks yours
looks really Co which one is yours sour
apple and
watermelon are you creaming over
it no like if I was like normal like how
I am and if I touched something really
cool if I was in like a freezer I'd turn
like green and then if I had like water
on me I'd turn like like red yeah that'd
be sick
is my mouth still red from the slush no
all right my coconut Dr Pepper is cold
now so can you Vlog me try
it what are we the coconut Dr Pepper
Channel or what yes we areally all we do
is talk about coconut Dr Pepper
now smells really yummy smells like the
beach actually sniff it oh it does smell
good it smells just like the thing we
tasted the other day mhm but you
smelling that it smells like the beach
like it smells like Cape
Cod what do you like C thing no I'm I'm
making sure you have the ey sure is it
good I first I sniffed it I don't know
yeah then you said okay sure like do you
smell like okay sure it kind of smells
like the beach why do you look so tall
with your boots take them off are you
insecure m- okay be noisy what is your
thoughts Mt it's like cool if you like
coconut but like that's not my vibe lame
answer lame answer you try
it I feel like you're going to love it
Nick yeah you're such a beachy vibe
yeah it's like good it just doesn't
taste like
Dr that was scary Nick has that like
beach vibe to him like as a person like
you're so Beach Vibe your FaceTime the
camera is freaking me out guys he's
looking at me like like like a scary kid
like I feel like I can't disagree or say
anything or I'm going to get like eaten
alive a moment to reflex St triplets
stera triplets stera triplets cut the
camera cut the camera me Nick Matt Matt
I don't know where yours is this is live
from when we post our live this
literally only has like four YouTube
videos on that entire Channel yeah I
mean so does like so does Matt yeah I
have like four I don't have my plaque
yet because I need to surpass like a
certain amount of videos like I don't
even have many enough videos to like
that's insane have a pla gu that means
you have to post I need get the st's
live back up and going in I know but
that means you have to go twitch live
and just like that the Vlog is over
goodbye you guys are weird you're
weirder
[Music]