all right [ __ ] we're about to
eat the greenish shake
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
is it just like is it a Grimace Shake no
it's a shake your ass I was gonna say or
is it a shake your booty
bro
dude a valid question what if they're
like oh we are ice cream machine ain't
working more of a validation we're going
in there and we're ripping the lady out
from behind the counter and we're making
that idea a better valid question is
what if the Hamburglar ate all the
gremet shakes while he burglarized the
burgers
[ __ ] him
[ __ ] mayor MC cheese there's a character
named marriage yeah it looks just like
Nick but with a purple cloak on that's
how I envisioned mayor that's crazy
[Music]
are you vlogging yeah right now uh-huh
do you see what's over my shoulder an
extra mile
no it's McDonald's
what they're such a long line yeah
everybody's here for the Grimace
everyone's here for the birthday party
girl was just 52 years old now shout out
Grandma's bro shout out Mayor McCheese
McDonald's says congratulations to class
of 2023. that's so sweet [ __ ] them
okay bro do you know when we graduated
in 2021 I was actually scared of like
the meme like you know like 21 like I
was actually like I was like oh my God
yes like I was like our whole class is
gonna be like a meme okay anyways if you
guys are unaware of what we're doing
tonight we're getting the Grimace shake
for grimace's 52nd person you sound way
too not excited bro
if you guys are unaware of what we're
doing grab Miss grandma if you're
unaware of what we're doing or who
Grimace is Grimace is a character
featuring McDonald's
land I feel like I'm watching this it's
McDonald's land commercials now known as
Ronald McDonald's best friend oh my God
he was introduced as a villainous
character called evil Grimace oh my God
how crazy who stole people's shakes
how soothing so now for his 52nd
birthday he's giving everybody his
purple juice into someone known for
sharing the joy of shakes with his
friends oh oh my God he turned good
so Grimace is just a purple Beast
birthday parties involving several
McDonald's Land characters including
those attending grimace's birthday in
2023 like Mayor McCheese I cannot wait
to be one of the people that are going
to Grandma's Burger
I can't believe he's 52 time flies
remember yesterday when Grimace was
stealing the shakes
dude you just found out about him what
oh my God
music
music I'll give you 200 bucks if you get
out right now and you're not trying to
like be and go up to that guy and go
could you lower the volume just a little
bit please
honestly it's a party it's Grandma's
birthday so I don't doubt them they're
like
they're like pulling up with the tunes
food looks really good
I can't believe this song right now no
problem take your time
I can't thank you this song right now oh
my God it's a great reaction like I feel
like I'm really getting to know her oh
my God just wait till we order one
billion gremish shapes oh my God you get
the the L meal day oh my God El Mio Del
crumple grimace
[Music]
I want one billion grammar shakes you're
saying Grimace wrong Grimace I want
every Grimace Shake on the menu
I want the person I need to not be able
to even go ahead
Grimace Shake we need one million five
of them
what size all medium please no small
um and then can I get a medium fry
you definitely got some jiggle to him I
hope he doesn't steal our shakes hold on
it's definitely not deep Bro he's bigger
purple he's got to sound like a little
baby no in my head he sounds like a 52nd
birthday and my head is
my head he sounds like Barney Barney
was Heavy bro
he's a Barney these are really hot I
feel like I made [ __ ] [ __ ]
immediately ew dude I'm kind of scared
honestly what flavor is Grimace do you
think I'll [ __ ] purple um no thanks I
mean I'll take three thank you
there you go Chris Grimace let me shake
I want my grandma
's a try the Grimace this [ __ ] actually
looks foul like just know this is what
flavor is Grimace see I don't know
don't sniff it I can all again is
whipped cream so
bro what the [ __ ] is it what's a shape
a shake yeah I thought it was a McFlurry
until I just looked really look at it
well let's all just try it
should we do it one at a time I don't
know anything why is there having on two
okay very similar Gogurt yep it tastes
like yogurt and I hate it
bro Grandma you're a [ __ ] idiot and I
hate wasting food
no I'll drink it I'll drink all three of
them no you won't
all right come on another Pretend We're
not gonna throw this [ __ ] out sorry
McDonald's this is bad if you like
yogurt and you like yogurt consistencies
go for it Grandma's Shake is for you
bro like I feel like the limited edition
items are either a slapper like you're
you like can't wait for it to come back
like groom is 53rd I'm back there
or like Chris's 53rd or just like pissed
there's no way this is good for this
thing like how the [ __ ] are you gonna
bring back the McRib but then give us
grimaceous Shake hey guys we're at
Wasteland on in LA on Melrose this is
crazy the fact that you just said L.A
we're in L.A
so this is like a thrift store Chris
tell them because I'm not on the camera
this is like a thrift store but it's
like higher end stuff I guess okay bye
[Music]
the music's really [ __ ] loud but
we're gonna shop
my eye like this one is like looks the
wrong way a little
um head to the eye doctor
I have stuff but I'm waiting to go to
the fitting room so
I might not get it in there okay am I
the only one that got something yeah
you're the only one who found the keeper
[Applause]
[Music]
throwing a happy ice to get ice dude
some guy when we were in the thrift
store had like the worst concert at a
concert worst shopping etiquette I've
ever seen in my life like he was on the
opposite side of a hanger rack and just
yanking [ __ ] that I was touching or like
pulling it off the hanger like just
taking it from me I'm like okay dude
have fun waiting for you it looked like
we were like competing it was wild there
we are oh my God
happy ice rating
um
I just got a bite Chris shut up Matt
what
eight out of ten eight out of ten
wonderful right 10 out of 10.
it's good that one record me no
want to record me
flip it over it's okay now hey guys
I got
you record me
I got cherry and watermelon it's
wonderful happy ice makes me happy
[ __ ] me not on some crazy sponsorship
this place actually has been like my
favorite thing on this Earth recently so
go happy ice we're going to El
restaurant
and they have corny stock images of
people eating pasta and we took a photo
of Chris last time we were there so I'm
gonna print it out on this printer and
then hopefully we get sat in a place in
which I can hang it up oh that's huge
what the [ __ ] should I finish smaller
it's a great photo though it is a good
photo
what's going on
the bread is so good dude
[Music]
so awesome
we're not in the right spot okay it's
gonna be nothing did I even hang that up
huh I didn't hang it up why I got scared
because it's so big look it's gigantic I
need to get an actual version of this
photo in a 4x6 put it in a black frame
and get sat in the right spot in the
restaurant because you know at the
Cracker Barrel when they do this like
where this prank originated they like
oh maybe McDonald's but like yeah what
do they have in McDonald's just Google
it but they used to like I don't know it
was just like it would have been out of
place I need to make it look real good
except it stays forever and every time
we go we can see it no then I I'll show
them what I got but it can't be in my
room okay because I'm redesigning
[Music]
this is what Matt got at Wasteland
anyway this is what I got
stir I got these pants from
don't say the brand name you can't keep
them okay okay ready
I got these pants
and they're very um
Wild West cowboy
thing but I feel bad because Chris wants
them but it's weird this waist is too
big okay
they don't they were they're a little
small for him his waist is too big next
thing next thing this next one Nick
found but it doesn't fit in either so
just those are so small
can I see it okay
next thing that's all I got dude that's
all you got yeah I thought you got black
jeans
no I got things actually
all right are you recording yep all
right guys that has been this week's
Wednesday week
all right guys that has been this week's
Wednesday video I hope you all enjoyed I
know it's awesome let's talk and it
wasn't really a specific point in the
video which don't do that nickel okay so
I'm sorry this video was a little crazy
and there wasn't really a set Rhythm or
Pace at all but I kind of love videos
like this I just wanted to say do like a
proper outro like normal YouTubers
because our podcast is released
um
I think when this comes out in about
five or four days so keep your eye out
for that it's called cut the camera
podcast on every single platform
Instagram Tick Tock YouTube so go
subscribe you can go watch the trailer
now to get a good idea about what it's
gonna be like go watch the trailer now
and then cut the camera podcast YouTube
channel but I'm gonna put a little clip
from the trailer at the end of this
video right now so you can get a little
taste all right guys that's all all
right guys that's awesome see you later
[Music]
or the pros of cons of pros of cons pros
and cons correct I was disagreeing with
what you previously said pros of cons
yeah but I know what you were supposed
and
then what you're saying how you miss me
yeah you miss me and all the things
[Music]