we got another
[Music]
Banger I can't wait for Nick to walk
in look I'm never leaving the house
again so about a month ago we surprised
Nick with a mariachi band when he came
home from Tokyo Japan Australia
yes and you guys really love that video
really shocked Nick so me and Chris
thought what better thing to do than
that again except not a mariachi band I
think it's like a good thing if we just
keep Nick on his toes when he comes I
completely agree all right so here's the
plan Nick had a space camp meeting to
plan content for his new shirt which
gave me and Matt about a 2-hour window
to transform our living room into a barn
Nick woke up early and got a ride from
our manager to let Matt sleep in but in
reality we woke up right when he left
and started Transforming Our Living Room
what is up guys I'm interrupting today's
video to tell you about our sponsor
SeatGeek me Matt and Nick have been
wanting to get out of our house more and
go to more Live Events and right now is
the perfect time everyone can use our
code stol 10 right now and get 10% off
any tickets on SeatGeek whether you're a
returning customer or a brand new
customer there are so many artists
touring right now like post Mone Billy
eish Sabrina Carpenter Charlie xx and
SeatGeek has you covered plus the NFL
the MLB the NHL and the NBA seasons are
all here and SE has tickets to every
game every ticket is rated on a scale
from 1 to 10 so look for the green dots
and avoid the red ones green means good
and red means bad no matter how many
times you've bought tickets off SeatGeek
before using Code sternol 10 will get
you 10% off your next order so take out
your phone open the seek app and add
code sternol 10 to your account you guys
definitely shouldn't wait you should do
it right now because this offer is only
available for a limited time and a big
thank you to se geek for sponsoring
today's video Nick loves this [ __ ] yeah
he does do you know what this is yeah
what it's a BN tapestry actually yep
here there's a crowbar you look like
[ __ ] you need to hold this back up
come
on you look like a
henchman oh dude it's fully diagonal
yeah I guess youd let go of it when I'm
holding it there well that's on you dude
how's that on Meo it what are you
talking about that Mar you using that
big ass thing it's easier it's
permanently in our wall forever now you
lot the s for somebody who doesn't know
what they're talking about it's up to
you to hold it straight I'm not up at
that level you got to like even the
thing you want me to elas to arm this
one no I'll hold the I got this I don't
need you to touch this hold this
up hold this shut your [ __ ] ring off
someone's texting me we're filming a
surprise mat obviously I'm going to get
text oh no it's just
Nathan miss
you I think the Ducks will love it h you
probably should put it more to the right
cuz it's not fully in between those two
where's our Hammer I don't know that'd
be so funny though I really hope like
the second he walks in like a rooster
just like yeah he opens the front door
he's like up this going up the stairs
and he look he he's like why is the cage
in the kitchen and then it he turn the
this is going to be great obviously this
takes up way more room than the mariachi
band so he's probably going to catch on
earlier than like it doesn't matter it's
going to take him way longer to register
the fact that like shit's moved around
man did I tell you I um I on purposly
like requested a hedgehog like a little
hedgehog you did yeah cuz I wanted to I
that for
personal you want pet the Hedgehog like
we got the all the Barnyard animals and
stuff and I like personally requested a
hedgehog okay so they're bringing a
little hedgehog just for you it's for
all of us but I wanted to see him the
most attemp I just talk about the fact
there's a duck in the living room well
forgot there's a turtle there cuz of how
loud the duck
is come on
in good boy it's
a hi oh my
gosh hi Mr goat well hello oh look at
the face
pumkins it's very friendly un like most
hog oh my God
Chris Matt he love this I know you do he
is
yeah he's really
cute oh my
gosh that's so cute here's going like it
does
hey Nick hey what you up to hold
[Music]
on F ignore the thing blocking the door
you got to what the [ __ ] is going on
come up here what the [ __ ] is
happening don't be too loud you're going
to disrupt the animal like I'm never
leaving the house again I'm never
leaving the house
again I'm seriously
over hi you're so pretty nice to meet
you of course this is oh that's a turtle
this is Buster Buster hi Buster Buster
don't leave like I can't leave the house
anymore hi that chicken is creeping me
out
wow oh my God oh my God like I'm not
even surprised anymore s the Desert
Turtle this is Buster he's a goat oh my
God what is
Happ chicken the only C the black one
Nam soy sauce they don't have names yet
not the other the black one does her
name is
soy so the the other ones don't have
names not yet can I name one maybe
absolutely guys duck our duck's name is
Lou right Lou hi Lou that's sugar the
pig
sugar um hey um you want water foret
these
yeah I forget these oh um they're peanut
and Snickers Peanut and Snickers they're
really um
Chris what's his name is
head buster come here Buster can you
call him like a dog like his Buster I
don't know the turtle freaked me out
yeah dude I was hoping that the duck
quacked when you walked in cuz I wanted
you heard something and I was like what
is going on spping the wall oh oh oh I
hate that chicken I hate that what's the
chicken's name so so no no no
no okay crazy we'll go crazy she's very
sweet okay you have to hold
I'm I'm hey Shelly come fet them come
fet them oh Nick there's a um a bonus
animal that I requested named jono it's
a big animal no it's not oh
there oh my
god oh you're the
cutest oh my god do you want to hold him
no no no
ni hold him if you don't I'll take him
away I F him no he's so he's let's do it
okay how do you give him to me like this
oh I have to support his belly yeah oh
he's oh oh take him back
hi jono his name is Jona that's really
cute I love this guy he's he came
upstairs by himself he literally has a
collar on yeah like he's just like
chilling here like why am I not shocked
anymore I'm not
shocked this is crazy that bunny
literally looks like something I'd see
on the street like a regular yeah in
Boston yeah I want you to hold the
chicken no I really don't want to touch
the chicken I like that's the one thing
I'm not going to do I'll touch we have
the opportunity you have to no I'm not
holding the chicken hi Dono Don's super
cute look so
cute what fun come on and if you guys
want you're more than welcome to take
the leas and walk Buster like outside if
you guys want surprised you weren't more
shocked I mean you were screaming I was
he told me not to scream CU I didn't
realize it was going to be more than one
animal like I got to the top of the
stairs and I saw the goat and I was like
hey and then I turned and there're so so
much more so much more take him again H
ton I take him I don't know how to grab
just grab him like go under his belly
his belly's warm I'm so scared of you
wait ow Chris take him back away take
him back instantly I just don't want
like I didn't sign up for this pleas
touch soy no I'm not touching any of the
chicken not I promise you I will leave
again that was part of the video you
have to at least try to hold the chicken
this turtle is on a mission I'm not
going near chicken I'm really not can
you hand him the chicken no I really
don't want the chicken no CH just pet it
no
you that's the Nick that's the thumbnail
of the video Nick faces his fear of
birds and chickens you have to do it I
don't know
man it's her favorite chicken the
sweetest little chicken ever well the
others are unnamed so yes you have to do
it kids are scared of the chickens I
told them the black chicken she's very
nice come on Nick anyone else go ahead
Nick little
kids go do it like I'll say hi I don't
want to I don't want to in M oh it's
very sweet oh hey oh she feels like a
like someone's head like it just feels
like someone's hair you should hold her
no no I don't want to do that
wow hey chicken I like her little
haircut she fixes it every
wow every single time I've held him he's
just like immediately kind of like moved
and like not wanted to be yeah he
doesn't he likes the adventure oh Matt
you got to keep I just can't even get
him can't even get him how do you
know you got a try neck just let him
climb up your arm what is happening what
is
happening like hey sugar come here you
remind me of the pigs I saw in Japan but
the pigs in Japan were mean and angry
and fighting and you're so calm me
yes sugar agrees yes did earlier yeah so
she's going to get really big right yeah
she's a Chinese pot belly so we gr about
150 to 200 and about 3 ft long so about
a long Buster but not as tall wow but
she's going to get M
sugar do you like it's just crazy I like
yeah yeah I know drama
sugar dude yeah he was laying in the Sun
that was on the floor earlier hi
Shi e the buckles on your shoe look I
know look
it oh my God I really do like pigs
though like I don't know how to like pet
a turtle Oh no you're good you can touch
them on their shell they feel everything
on their shell it's a part of their body
so it's technically their back so it you
can pet her you can scratch her she'll
feel all of it oh my
God Buster can't get over his reflection
he's like oh my
God handsome go I was saying he would
look great in the suit right Nick what
like he would look good in the
suit he's so funny oh my god oh ducky
Lou Lou in the camera where do guinea
pigs come from Peru I think to
Peru
hi oh that was the cutest thing I've
ever seen did you see that no the bunny
stretched Matt what yeah spine no
no oh like buddy I know like take this
look and he's like no grab
me
Chris hold him he Blends right into my
shirt
sneaky he's soal they're so
cute are you good are you okay it's okay
is he nervous
you're shock well cuz I just look down
again oh there's Turtle over there and
then the duck is right here wait do you
want me to take him of
course oh
that's
sugar sugar
sugar hello B piggy I oh hello piggy
hello piggy hello piggy HG I need
you no no the bunes are
so that's all I oh you like the air
conditioning it's a desert Turtle Matt
oh do you think Shy loves your room mat
or no yeah looking her go it's a mess
right now don't mind thank you so much
for bringing us all theim of course
thanks for having us I'm glad it was a
nice surprise for you oh my gosh I am
having so much fun one of the the nicest
um uh reactions that I I was I had no
idea that this was happening and now I'm
just so happy you're here it was nice
I've done um I've done a petting zo
before for a YouTuber and he was uh
doing it for his girlfriend it was like
a a date thing but when I went I didn't
know that it wasn't going to actually be
a surprise like she recorded her first
reaction like over and over like I get
it like it's YouTube but I didn't know
it was going to be like that it's like
I'm going to surprise her I was like oh
that's cute but it wasn't a
surprise yeah so when they said it was a
surprise for you I'm like I wonder if
it's actually how many
times everything itce I genely not be
more
sh no I could tell wow I just hope he
leaves the house in a good outfit yeah
like it's so funny we're usually asleep
till [ __ ] 2:00 so I walked in there
was a farm here I was
shocked oh look we got gifted skims
that's really cool ni yeah I was
bringing them in but Buster look we got
a gift box from
skims I was going to get them to you
guys that I got diverted come here D I
was saying earlier do you feel to place
him against no not at all I'm going to
place him against I look at sugar and I
want breakfast both both hands under yes
good Matt goodness I'm not supporting
the bunny properly yes you are can you
hold it Matt he's like Matt grab the
[ __ ] bunny off of me like I don't
need a lesson wait so you see sugar look
at him look at him like you want to eat
bacon
yes I love
bacon he's telling sugar I love bacon um
just beware Busters going in the back
it's okay I'm just letting you know that
it's no one step over there no it's fine
you got to go when you got to go Buster
gono hey
gonoo look at P looking at me through
the mirror like who are
you
you're now this is concluding our
petting zoo experience they I didn't
expect to have such a fun little
relaxing afternoon right gono and Lou
you're already all out of there um but
yeah there we're going to why are you
feeding the room we will conclude when
the when the pettings I'm going to miss
all my friends I feel like I made so
many friends today yeah about whenever
however long it takes to get a bunny and
some guinea pigs out of the house we'll
see you when our couch is back over
there hold on I'm scooching over I'm
pushing this
back no you're not just leave it Chris
it doesn't need to be pushed back at all
I'll push you back I'll push you to back
to back to back to back to you Nick how
surprised were you when you walked up
those stairs and there was a billy goat
I could is a billy goat I don't know I
couldn't oh do you want me to [ __ ]
answer the question no God put this put
that poor soul down little Mir cat he
probably hates being with you shut your
mouth you don't know what he likes he's
[ __ ] stuffed go you ate my last starb
burst tonight I did yeah and I want it
right now I just thought of it I want it
go eat something else let's um wrap this
video up yeah sure um literally [ __ ] my
pants like I just like I every single
day that we filmed the video a couple
days ago every single time I've left the
house without you guys and I've been
like coming back I've been like like
what the [ __ ] could I be in for you know
what I mean like genuinely like we're
keeping you on your toes yeah like I was
out today and then when I got home when
I was opening the door I was like or
like the I was like out and I was like
oh my god when I go home later like I
don't know what could possibly happen
and it's that right there everyone
ladies and gentlemen that's the beauty
in it I had a I had a bond with Shelly
the turtle I really likeed the go he
didn't do much but he did enough to hit
my heart you know the all around
experience like I was ready I was
starving and I was tired when we were
filming and I was ready to come home and
shower eat and maybe nap and then I got
up to the stairs and it was like oh my
God you're filming a YouTube it was like
adrenaline but how good did it feel
after it was so fun it was so fun I
loved I I I missed the animals yeah and
also for all of you who want to know um
we had our house professionally cleaned
cuz it smelted like a farm so I want
everyone to know our house does not
smell like a farm anymore don't surprise
me again for a bit I can't my heart
can't take it next time I'm going to do
what the [ __ ] I want it was time we're
actually planning something for you
don't even have to go out the house it's
just when you come downstairs in the
morning was so when when when when we
were um when we were walking the goat
back to the car yeah me and the lady
brought the goat out and a neighbor
Street person pedestrian if you will was
outside calling like his roommate or his
friend he was like telling a story and
then I walked by like holding the goat
on the leash and the guy looked at me
and I could tell that he thought he was
dreaming he was like what the [ __ ] is I
yeah I'd be shocked too cuz he looked
then looked away and then turned back
around he's like that was a [ __ ]
goat looks like a dog at first then
you're like um that's a definitely had
some goat features goat's eyes are crazy
I love animals you can just rock like a
baby is that
I hated holding any of them why cuz I
was just like I feel like I could like
kill them not that I would but I just
like I feel like I have so much like but
thank you guys so much for watching this
week's Friday video
um what else thank you I thought you had
way more no I do thank you guys so much
for watching this Friday video make sure
you like the video if you liked it hit
the notification Bell so you know that
when we post videos but you don't really
have to hit that you just got to know
it's Friday at
5:30 thank you so much
what a good video Matt yeah good job
guys thank you thank
[Music]
you you talking you getting back we got
to get you again is like kind of what I
meant okay got to run it back that
that's I'm so scared thank strippers one
of these times male firefighters that'd
be sick okay dude that' be and with that
we wrap the video
[Music]