what what is
up what do you want you think you get
blue I get
stick oh my
God miss me and all the things that we
did we said we going to travel from the
island to Madrid we had a lot of plans
but they all
disa because of some but it's okay cuz
I'm moving different don't be saying
nothing when I'm PST up with other
[ __ ]
all right this is what we're going to do
ready Matt yeah repeat after me it's say
game of Simon say
Okay Simon didn't say Simon says to do
that all right guys now that me and Matt
both have our left foot fully
exposed this is insane all right I saw
this on Tik Tok and made matter about to
try it out I have to try to take that
sock off his foot and he has to try to
take my sock off my foot the first one
to do it wins
okay I this is like the weirdest [ __ ] I
have way shorter
socks get
way was giggling you're hurting I
wrist no
punching what is what are you
wow no damn it Victory look at that
Barefoot
good that was a good match I my goal is
to just Tire you out until did I have
earrings in I don't
know wo we look like an Oreo our hair
like if we go like this it's like an
Oreo so Chris and Matt just fought over
a sock mhm or dueled and then I was like
Hey children doing that would be pretty
chaotic so then I was like oh wow we're
triplets like let's Google what it's
like to raise triplets so now we're
going to sit here and talk about that I
Googled how to raise triplets cuz that's
such a a broad question with no specific
answer so like let's see it is crazy
that like once the child I wonder if Mom
ever Googled that once the child's born
was Google around when mom was born uh
no not born not born but when we were
born I don't know go no was it anyways
statistics refer to the refer to them by
name rather than as the twins or the
triplets I so true I agree I'm happy
they put that first they know it
literally says like to be and when you
look up how to raise triplets the first
thing in bold is here are some ways to
support each child's individuality cuz
that's really all it is MHM like the
most important part I feel like is like
making sure that all the kids feel
individual refer to them by name rather
than as the twins or tripl it's avoid
dressing them alike as they get older
like it is cute when you're like three
and under like the matching little
onesies yeah I will say Mom and Dad
we've talked about this before but they
definitely just let us do whatever the
[ __ ] we wanted like dude I went to a I
went to a h Camp once with a shirt that
said I love chicken and I drew a piece
of chicken and it looked like a
penis when I remember this can't I
remember and everyone there was dying
laughing and I was like oh my God this
is so good like I'm wearing like such a
cool shirt and they were just like like
everyone was laughing at the fact cuz it
literally looked like I wrote I love
chicken and then drew a dick on my shirt
like straight up that was like a full
thing that happened and like it was a
day it was like in the camp they were
doing like mini short films I don't know
what kind of camp it was and that was
the day they were taking the photos for
like the end credits of the movie so
after that day like a month later like
when Camp was ending like the short film
was done they were like rolling the
credits of the movie and it was like
Nick sternol it was a photo like and it
had the shirt this is I love chicken
with a dick dra on it birthday vlog
it's our birthday today look at how
happy Nick
is yah happy birthday Matt we just ate
celebratory hey it's your birthday too
yay oh my God hey it's your birthday too
yay of course mat get away from me ow
[ __ ] you're going to kill
me
serious that sounded like a movie oh
[ __ ] you're going to kill me
that was crazy I'm recording it's super
it's so dark wait come into the light oh
yes so much better oh maybe worse let me
give you like a flashlight I know it's
crazy care for oh my God yeah no no this
is best she's crazy and she bought every
[ __ ] ticket to a movie theater for us
and now Matt is chasing Maddie around it
I
think they're running around like
Hooligans but yeah I can't let Maddie
tag me look it we have the whole theater
so Matt's playing tag with MADD mhm I'll
I I want in madd's it so oh my God
Maddie Tagg
me that's
[Music]
insane
okay oh my
God I don't to sweat is it worth it chis
huh is it really worth it you have all
movie bro you just tag me don't touch me
I'll kill you seriously I will sneak up
at one point hey y'all what's going on
we're back in my room but it's a
different day it's not it is August 2
well no cuz we were just the movies it's
August 2nd we filed that like two days
ago yeah I don't know where you've been
but like Stuck In Like A Time said we
were just at the movies in the last part
of the Vlog like it's not a different
day according to what they just saw
whatever in my room guys we just got
back from the movies Y and um yeah Lura
shout out manager Lara she bought every
ticket in the theater and then we got to
invite like 20 friends to come and hang
out with us and we watched the spooky
movie that talk to me one with the hand
bloody what why are you shaking your
head he's scared no I just like I don't
like thinking about it like when she was
sucking the toes it was just crazy mov
it was a crazy movie um this video is
kind of short and sweet and we kept it
simple because we like honestly I hate
vlogging on our birthday because I just
want to spend the time with the people
that I'm with and enjoy it so we went to
an escape room today and like that's
another thing that sucks is like we keep
going but we can't Vlog them cuz you're
not allowed to record CU you can't St
what you I like that it's wood cuz I
just imagine like I like to we can't we
can't Vlog escape room we went bowling
it was a lot of fun and then we went to
the movies as well and we played an an
arcade and we got an arcade game no we
won we
wanted where is the board game it's in
the car let's play it let's play I'm
down I love you guys a lot but I am
happy that we didn't really Vlog you
know like I like to like live in the
moment soak it in like a big sponge and
it's dude it's so weird to me that we're
20 because I feel
mentally like an adult wise I feel like
responsibility wise like actually as an
adult I feel like 40 but like
youthfulness wise and me I feel like I'm
like like 14 like actually 15 I think
that this year I know we have a podcast
coming out soon about birthdays so I
don't want to say too much about it but
now sorry the washing machine looks in
there did you put a brick in it it
should be it shouldn't be making this
much
noise is that do you leave your wallet
in
there that's got to be a brick that
ain't a wallet that's got to be
something heavier anyways can I talk
about with our podcast why it it's doing
the next thing can I talk about with our
podcast about Monday yeah I don't care
Fu um our podcast coming out next on
Monday is about birthdays and
um so I don't want to say too much about
it like this year I feel like the least
amount of people have like talked to me
on my birthday oh my God like the movie
talk to me um the least amount of people
have like reached out to me on my
birthday and said happy birthday but I'm
like most happy with the people who did
I fully agree you know what I mean like
it's it really is for me like I don't
know birthdays just remind me of like
all the people I'm surrounded by and
it's just always birthdays are a good
reminder of like quantity quality over
qu qu over quantity cuz like we we it's
also a reminder like not to take people
for granted because the people that
actually show a lot of love like year
round mhm like I had a friend today
texted me that like lowkey forgot it was
our birthday but it's like I'm like
actually really good friends with this
person so it's like you know what I mean
like they have a pass you know what I
mean but it's like the people like
there's people that only text you on
your birthday and there's people that
text you so much they forget it's your
birthday yeah
yeah I'm just happy no one tried to
happy birthday the way back into my life
this year same same same I'm good anyway
that's
all look Smiley and happy I don't need
any more of those like Chris hitting I
had a great day I'm just I'm just
talking tired I'm that clip of you yeah
like I
can't I I think that like mentally
turning 20 years old is like it's
obviously an emotional thing cuz it's
like oh my God you're not really a
teenager anymore but it's like I don't I
haven't really had that feeling yet cuz
it's like I I feel like there's no rush
into
adulthood at least where we're at right
now no like my Instagram ction is so
real cuz it's like getting old is
something I don't want to do but living
life is something I'm looking forward to
oh wow wait that wasn't the ction but
that's better I really get good at this
also I do but no like actually like like
I met guys I've met Cole I've met like
[ __ ] amazing people that helped me
complete goals and like people I'm fully
surrounded right now currently in this
day with people that want nothing
genuinely but the best for me like
literally period and that's why I'm
going into 20 years old extremely um
happy where I'm at I'm optimistic no me
too please clip that cuz ni being
optimistic is like Rarity
I kind of want to get a 19 tattooed on
me because of like the trials and
tribulations of the last year and how
much I feel like I've leared about
myself and what I don't want in the
future and what I want in the future 19
was the most like rock R year but it was
just the most like it was the most I've
learned lots of things let's see what we
accomplished by 21 21 chist the meme I
just think of how much that
we've that was weird I think of how much
we shut off the lights like flickered
it's the watching machine relax who I
thought it was the
aliens oh my God okay I just want to say
last thing I can't believe how I can't
believe how much we accomplished going
from 18 to 19 and from get away and now
from 19 to 20 and it's going to be crazy
what happens this year
20 I can't wait to get drunk next year I
know we say this all the time then
people do make sad edits but I swear to
God if I see a Saturday I'm blocking
someone's account okay straight off why
I just hate it I hate being up like
everyone be optimistic you you want to
see okay I already saw this girl freaked
out cuz I liked her Tik Tok but I'm
showing y'all and she'll freak out again
but I just can't [ __ ] was crazy this
[ __ ] was
[Music]
crazy like that's 2 years worth of [ __ ]
that's actually really like
that one like that that emotional like
that one is like it's just crazy I love
[ __ ] like that it's just crazy when you
post like every single week once a week
for so long that it's like it it becomes
so like routine but like you it BEC so
routine because like what it is for me
is like I haven't gone back and watched
our old videos in a while because we've
been so busy making new ones and just
like when I'm when people see that they
see like oh our journey whatever when I
see that I think of every memory that
ever led to like now from beginning of
this I just think of like myself being
able to look back at all of those and
like yeah I'm like 60 like cuz what
blows my mind is like the first ones
like we had full faith in YouTube and we
really didn't we had a crumb of
Hope look at the
avocado dude there's one where the
turnup goes way too crazy I'm not up no
like the
banana okay and then the Orange Place
strawberry and they all their little
solo
moments hey isn't that so cool all right
y' we are 20 years old thank you so much
and you're excited to see you when we
turn 21 yeah it's been a wild ride 21 21
it's been a wild um no it's been a wild
ride it's crazy like I look back and see
the count of videos we've posted like
200 something it blows my [ __ ]
mind and then what you saying how you
miss me yeah you miss me and all the
things that we did we said we going to
travel from the island to Madrid we had
a lot of plans but they
all why because of some but it's okay
cuz I'm moving different don't be saying
nothing when I'm P up with other [ __ ]
my brother