hi hello hello hi so this is my my
friend Dr Sinclair nice to how you doing
and um I've been I've been sick of you
guys arguing so I'm taking you to group
therapy hi group therapy this is well
well well you guys already know when you
see one triplet on the camera they got
some [ __ ] [ __ ] up their sleeve as you
guys know a lot of people like to
comment when me Matt and Nick like fight
with each other or are dramatic or
scream and yell and it's been a whole
thing in our whole career that we yell
and argue at each other and I thought it
would be so funny if we just make a joke
of this whole thing so I I had my mat
and Nick's team look for actors and I
found a nice gentleman who is going to
pretend to be a therapist tomorrow I'm
going to introduce him to Nick and Matt
and I'm going to bring them to therapy
how are you guys how you feeling as the
time goes on I feel good I think I wish
that it was like how we do it for Nick
where it's like there's no no buildup CU
I I hate buildup it's my least favorite
thing on Earth you hate the edge I hate
Ed yeah I hate Ed so I have guys both
here today yeah I I planned a little fun
surprise um you have to get loose Matt
though you got to be a little loose okay
loose okay maybe a little vulnerable
even
vulnerable I have a big sumo wrestler
coming in you don't stop with the sumo
wrestler bit all right are you guys
ready I haven't done this in year yeah
hello flashback for Matt talk about some
things Matt okay Matt yes that's me I'm
Matt okay Matt okay let's say so Matt
you you said that Nick been complaining
about not eating all day today and that
you guys already got in a fight yes
correct and Kane's drivethru yes we in
Kane's Drive F in the Kane's drive you
wouldn't believe it so what bother you
about Nick's Behavior man all right so
so I wake up today right right and he he
calls me we have a water pressure issue
where if I shower and he showers at the
same time it will cut the water out how
does this lead to the Cane's it gets
there he goes I am so lack of energy cuz
I haven't eaten that I had to get out of
the shower early because I feel like I
haven't eaten enough to even wash myself
properly so I so I try to be a superhero
and I'm like we got to go get you some
food get out of the house okay we get to
the Cane's drive-thru right and he says
I think I just want french
fries I said you couldn't even wash
yourself fully and all you want is
french fries put some chicken in that
man's plate I don't I don't understand I
mean so this was really important to you
Matt that you this is Matt I mean I mean
but it was important that that so it was
important to you Nick yes that you had
to have french fries the or all I could
think of that I wanted was french fries
I think the underlying issue here was I
was I was so hungry but I didn't know
what I wanted to eat and Matt went for
an immediate solution and I was not I
don't think I was prepared for the so
did you guys make a scene at the uh no
there there was no scene um there was
there was internal scene nobody I don't
know no one else saw those Outsiders all
we were strictly in the drivethru but
Matt calls you dramatic a lot I call him
dramatic he call dramatic a lot at least
once a day the funny thing is is a is
someone who's constantly calling other
people dramatic are they not dramatic
themselves for feeling that
way how do you identify dramatic
that's I think someone freaking out
about [ __ ] being dramatic means they're
being dramatic and he's like oh you're
so dramatic like that's a dramatic
Outburst Nick his favorite phrase other
than hello and good night and good
morning is I can't do this I can't right
we so so so I say I say oh oh look at I
what I want so so I say Nick what is it
what wait wait what is it that you can't
do what are you trying to what are you
trying to I think it's like kind of like
um when there's like an awkward silence
barrier and it's like when your your
go-to is like oh how's the weather yeah
mine mine is I can't do this does that
sound dramatic Dr Sinclair please be
honest it sounds like you're frustrated
I am thank you for validating that
feeling when you say I can't do that you
saying I can't go any further what's
going on I think I think we all carry a
lot of stress and the minute that
something is happening I don't want to
do it so I say I can't do this when in
reality May deep down you can
yeah it's not a matter if I can't it's
more if I don't want to maybe I'll start
saying I don't want to do this so can
you think of a better phrase I don't
want to do this maybe better than I
can't I don't know I don't want to is
still like there's there's a possibility
better we're going in the right I don't
want to elude like I still could you
know maybe maybe I need some more time
to deal with this I like that do so so I
can't do this as Sam we also post every
Friday too
and Nick often waits till Thursday night
to do it edit the video to like plan it
so he'll be editing on Thursday night
yeah and then it has to happen by
tomorrow because we post every Friday
and then he'll go I can't do this
anymore but in reality he had the whole
week to pre-plan and edit the video so
why don't you do it so so what are you
doing th so is there it sound like
there's
procrastination yeah but also the only
reason I the only reason I procrastinate
is because I'm the only one with the I
have the ability to procrastinate
because I have a requirement Matt and
Chris can't even procrastinate cuz they
have nothing to do he may edit and that
may be his requirement right guess who
does his laundry Dr
Sinclair let me guess I me this guy
right here really yeah his dirty draws
I'm washing those mhm what would be
under his pants if I didn't wash his
underwear Matt wouldn't own close if I
didn't make the YouTube videos and post
them because he wouldn't have money so
what would Matt would have nothing to
watch but sometimes you and Nick fight
over little things like who ate the last
candy bar or if he keeps stealing a sip
of your drink that one's big the word
stealing is crazy to me so the word
would you say when I ask you to share
one sip of a beverage it's
stealing I think that no matter what if
I took this from you right now and I
took this sip right W wo wo exposure
therapy was this was this not moments
ago your drink but I don't care I'm glad
you had a sip of a drink that I could
literally I still have more in here
right but if Dr Sinclair here had a
drink and I grabbed his that would be a
little different right that would be
stealing that would be that would be
stealing right cuz I just I I just met
Dr Sinclair 30 how long has it been 25
minutes ago 30 minutes ago you know like
I take the drink Nick if sometimes if
Matt if Matt has a soda right and I
don't want to drink an entire soda right
I'll like I'll say hey Matt can I have a
sip of your drink I'll take the drink
I'll take a sip Matt just he does he
doesn't want at time he doesn't want a
full soda but I did and now my full soda
privilege gone like that in a second cuz
he wants a sip cuz now I I'm not that
important you can't just open another
soda I yes but it I'd rather take a sip
of ma drink and not finish my own where
I think that Matt Matt can be willing to
sacrifice a sip for the greater good of
not polluting the Earth with the waste
of another C is that a little dramtic
dramatic Dr sinair a little bit right
he'd rather me pollute Earth I don't
think he can do
this do yes where me Matt and Chris
being brothers and hang out every single
day and arguing every single day since
we were kids I think that the power of
our word
is nullified a little bit because we're
so open with arguing with each other if
that makes sense so it doesn't seem as
intense when we're arguing because we do
it all the time that's good like if
someone ar communic your normal
communication yeah just your normal
communication yeah like our our normal
communication is like if I saw two
friends arguing how me and Matt argue
sometimes it'd be like how are they even
friends with each other but for me and
Matt I feel like it makes sense mhm
that's true with siblings mhm cuz you
can bend that that bridge a little more
yeah so when the when when there's an
argument does he go back and bring up
old things and oh oh yes he's a big name
caller this one well give an example I'm
not going to share No example no example
I don't know if I'm much of a name call
it Nick you really hate when someone
with no profile pictures comments on
hating you yeah why and how does it make
you feel the reason it bothers me is
because if you were if you were face to
face with someone you don't have the
option to like conceal what you're
saying right so the internet allows
people to speak directly to somebody
without you knowing exactly who they are
and so a lot of these keyboard Warriors
what I like to call them and they like
comment away angrily they're doing that
out of they they're holding up an iron
shield in front of themselves saying
like oh I can say all this about this
person because they have no idea what's
behind curon number one right and
usually it's some ugly scary goblin that
lives in the middle of nowhere that's
butting into business that they don't
need to butt into right yeah and you
can't respond no there's it's not worth
responding to it because there's so many
of these little trolls gallivanting away
in a
cave yeah it's a good good analogy of
those people yeah I don't think we can
help you with that one yeah no that's
just that's an underlying issue the
other night Nick said you pick one night
a year to be loud and annoying and Loud
how did that make you feel what what
night was this oh I I have video
evidence I can bring it up oh no no no
we don't need the video evidence no I I
love the video evidence are you quiet
and what's the time at I'm a very quiet
guy yeah I can redirect everyone's
attention to the TV oh Jesus what is
this wa this was a video from the other
night when Nick said I quote you take
one night a year to be loud and annoying
to Matt
you
don't why so that was the other
night M was being loud and dramatic and
you kind of stepped out of your again
comfort zone play Play One More Time
play again can we make sure we got a
good we got a good angle that oh my
goodness brother all right basically I
took some moments from our videos where
maybe we were a little hostile or angry
so we can review them and how we act and
how we act in real life scenarios oh God
nightmare you killed me I was stabbing
person in my dream crying and shedding
tears and freaking out cuz I didn't want
to kill him but in my dream I had to
like
what I don't know I was just thinking
maybe we can have some advice that might
be symbolism of anger yeah so how did
this how did this come about to be
honest with you I don't even
knoww paper towels dummy
thanks a
temper stupid CL you need to go to what
happened here I lightly tapped my
brother look at that start that nothing
about that is light that's what I'm
saying that's what I'm saying the first
like are these comparable off the off
the armrest yeah are those comparable H
so okay so what is the best way heed
communicating when someone's on our
phone on their phone I think waiting for
eye contact okay will help us all or
maybe like hey are you ready to listen
first okay so we should we tap that
person or should we that's up to say
something maybe like if it was gentler
and like not gentler yes like you tap my
phone off my on off the armrest his arm
is on there there's a couple we just say
something right maybe ta I'll use my
words from here on out that's good
Nick if you [ __ ] ever hit me again
knock [ __ ] tee literally that's why I
saying just start sitting here in the
video it's like what you did wasn't
funny well what you did wasn't funny
either oh my God I'm beding
I think this shows our good
communication I don't think so
communication look we we we end up at a
at a solution here Matt Matt intervenes
Matt Matt interven this isn't a viable
solution Matt intervenes and me and
Chris will work out what happen I'm
going to say again I think I may forgot
what I said before the can I have your
attention I think that's more tap tap
thing is not working OB
yeah I think we're done okay I think
that was a good session that was good
does anyone have any final
thoughts of communication or I have one
more but you can go first so well M by
so how so how are we going to do with
touching um L touching more
communication I agree that's a good and
when there is communication listening Dr
Sinclair is actually an actor guys he's
not a therapist oh my God Dr Sinclair
I've been in therapy plenty of not a
doctor mat no you can keep going I mean
what else do what else do I know you as
you know so hey man you're spitting bars
I'm going to be honest I I maybe you're
just good at advice maybe it's it's it's
what you guys are talking about is so
real though yeah really is yeah
especially with the phones and the
communication I would have thought you I
would have thought you would have been
out of here 15 minutes ago with another
client I I'm hooked he's convinced I'm
convinced great great amazing okay there
we go thank you thank you just do what
you did to that so that one thanks Chris
genius genius what's that I know more
about American Girls than than you do
gen Girl dolls is what it is you don't
know anything off
me what the [ __ ] was that God he just
didn't put the I need this one and I
need you
to I don't even know how that's supposed
to go on all right Nick tell them what
we're doing we're taking photos of our
Halloween C costumes I'm a cobra MERS
are Average Joe's uh a true American
story if you haven't watched it you got
to go watch the movie a true American St
it's actually A True Underdog Story it's
the title American it's an American
Underdog Story okay as opposed to like a
Russian Underdog pull the ball out
yeah you
mean I feel completely CH oh my god well
you can dodge a wrench you can dodge
a you will Sam I it you he goes you ow
Sam house
money everything you do in life make
sure you go balls deep you guys are
stupid
perfect um El what else do they say I
don't know when I give your girl the
rist face ain't no chance she coming
back you can dodge a wrench you can
dodge a ball Dodge a ball my balls still
hurt from M through that all right you
know the 5Ds of dodgeball right dip
Dodge Dodge dive duck dip and Dodge you
just learn those five simple rules
you remember to pick on the nerdy kids
and make sure your team is
strong you're done the Flur nobody makes
me bleed my own blood you didn't we
qualif you you didn't even qualify foral
qualifying match oh my God we never even
won a original qualifying match oh yeah
now I remember I know you and tell them
LEF Flur you might got to bring your
bibs cuz it's going to get messy I don't
I'm not doing that best bring your bib
cuz it's going to get messy you got to
say you got to say you got to say you
know you and I know you and you know
that I know that you know
you that I can't even compare I know
you you know you and I know you know
that I know
you bro Sam was already [ __ ] with the
light you can
makeit like who's going to order a Pap
John's Pizza and when that's all I need
to know do it Papa John's or Domino's it
don't matter to me the AC flip the
switch no you shouldn't flip the switch
I
feel he just flipped the switch I just
flipped the switch you think they record
that here cuz they like he probably just
did this and went and then he yeah then
he wrapped it can you tell the viewers
what we're doing please we're about to
make some diss tracks on each other we
went to so what are we getting for put
my life in two pieces this is my Last
Resort what we it's really soundproof
here the most soundof what are we
getting for
pizza get as much meat as you can on it
I don't like meaty Pizza I slap that
meat right on that pizza hello I'm M
your AI assistant all right so what's
the vibe of this track we need like a we
need like a take take this you want to
go in there of course oh [ __ ] Nick we
got to hear him you got to hear what I
sound
like yeah yeah wow kick him out the boo
yeah get out get out I'm trying to make
that drop your pants and lie down right
there
music swag diploma getting sick to your
stomach going to put down the soda and
I'll switch the language so you
understand [ __ ] shut your F [ __ ] I
didn't get it
right I was going to say the last one
wa tough tough that's tough I can't lie
so good
mat I love the kid I hardly
Noah what ask me if I love the kid I
hardly Noah am I her yeah okay that was
so good Matt all right guys Chris Chris
is going to try and diss Matt back let's
see what I can do hardly Noah open your
Bo put it on my balls [ __ ]
[Music]
oh my
god dude you're SI you open your VOA put
it on my balls [ __ ] all ready ready
he doesn't even know what he just
started once he once he does four I'm
going back in there and I'm cooking his
ass with one of his
bars oh oh oh that's the
mic that was that was fire keep going
all right what's next I have you diss me
we going to brawl [ __ ] yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah like diss me and then I think
we're going to maybe brawl [ __ ] no just
say it bro scream it scream it this mean
we going to brawl
[ __ ] scream it you're
angry [ __ ] at the [ __ ] my [ __ ]
you're just saying the other one like a
goofball I can't say it I can't say it I
don't know why this mean we going to
brawl
[ __ ]
[ __ ] you can say like call R Everybody
Get
Low Everybody Get Low oh but they say
like low
low should I do Adas for the whole
thing yeah that's so funny bro all right
Matt's checking back
in wait Nick if you don't got [ __ ] got l
no I was just hot
okay Elite you must havegot you cheap
what did he say Elite all right I said
that shopping spree was a leap you must
have forgot you
cheap that's crazy that's crazy crazy
true wow it's actually good it is good I
am cheap you are cheap he got me bro was
you must you Che out of all of us the
black sheep stop talking about that
jeep he a Jeep he my favorite car
bro not done I'm not done get up
I'm the [ __ ] you we the cl to me
is damn that's crazy oh my God e i he's
out for blood I got to cook I got to
cook he's out for blood hold I have to
cook I was just I wasn't even bro I
wasn't even
[Music]
dis he's he's murmuring right now it's
not even good oh no it's so
good swag I'm a needed diploma sick to
your stomach need to put down the sod
language so you get it got
shut
ask I hardly know put it on my balls
[Music]
[ __ ] everybody get
L like I'm stuck in myow BO I'm in the
snow all around the world I'm s show the
L up with they bit my friend you just a
foe
that shoing spree was a leap you must
havegot you cheap out of all of us you
the black sheep stop talking about that
jeep one bar took a 100 Years bro got me
falling asleep hear the [ __ ] You Weep he
climb to me his seat like I said stop
talking about that you ain't never
getting that track so chill out with me
with all that back you a little I'm you
act hard but M off don't make me take
that swag I'm need a dipl
like do you have like a topic in
mind um we just like
Flex yeah like just like some flexing
[ __ ]
all like goofy flexing [ __ ] like like I
make more money than you I'm cooler than
you I get more [ __ ] than you etc
etc the like I don't care spend so much
money and a good from my heart too many
people in my life
[Music]
they Matt's floating right
now that good I [ __ ] it yeah I
[Music]
think four seasons is a hotel by the way
in a studio eating
pizza yeah I'm just practicing
sing sitting in the
studio looking at
M he's so
sexy I want to rub his
back yeah he got me breaked
up like go are these bars why' you kind
of hit that on
on first time Chris has ever wrapped in
yeah yeah yeah yeah he got me breaked up
F hard [ __ ] yeah I don't know I'm
freestyling I don't know I'm just saying
whatever comes to my
head Chris has never had $100,000 in his
backpack in his
[Music]
life fre all this off
this last one is the
best in my backpack looking fly my Des
snap keep your two [ __ ] I don't need
that keep the T
[Music]
around know I'm a winner got so much
money you would think I got a printer
is that tough
[Music]
yeah I'm sick that bar was so tough Nick
so much racks inside my account look
like the date all right we're done in
the studio tonight fellas tonight is the
night what's going on tonight is the
night that I show you my true form for
the first time oh my God
that's life that's what all the people
say that's life they think I'm hiding in
the
shadows I I am the Shadows Batman
doesn't get dressed he gets oiled up and
thrown in
it don't mind my room in my bed it's
been a mess ever since I started
sleeping in the cave you're sick all
right everyone so my costume is Batman
but it's not Batman it's it's Batman
Nick we'll put it on the screen can you
explain the lore can you explain the
lore of this costume what do you mean
the [ __ ] what costume oh my God oh my
God
pants boots you're not for
real ey black ey
black yeah what are you getting ready to
hit a grand
slam what I like Lego Batman
better Lego Batman is Liam n so so do I
do you know he's retiring from action
movies I don't want to talk about it
look like how we did in that twitch
stream with that like messy hair what
are you talking about boy you know
freaked out over messy hair whatever's
going on right now you're failing how no
there you go you're done you're done
you're done literally that's it it's
complete you already have greasy ass
hair so is it complete I I don't even
think you should have really went for
this look yeah this isect
great like that it's burning it's
burning it's burning it's burning it's
open your
eyes Okay sometimes you get so evil I
forget what I do I have to replay my
thoughts every night it doesn't look
awful at all ow sorry it's going to hurt
close your eye it's [ __ ] closed
[ __ ] it's not the eye that hurts it's
you drilling your thumb into my head
close it here here it was and that's
more Shadow yes like
prior that
enter the what's
Batmobile oh my God what you look a
little
scary they think I'm hiding in the
shadows I am the
shadow I need get in the car lady I
really want mac and
cheese he's spinning the roll way too
well it's cuz he's dreamed of this
forever go back down the street I need
this for your Tik Tok oh my God oh my
God
let's go I'm going to accidentally alert
people my parents died when I was young
it's oh that was so good that was so
good okay wait can you can you just walk
straight the city needs me the city the
moon right behind you the
street Matt wait
wait wait where is he Matt oh my god I
didn't even see him standing there oh my
you're not dead ass he's going oh my the
night is the only time I feel alive oh
my God what if I told you I'm going to
fill up that suit with
blood what does he say what does he
say oh what does he say hold on give me
a second what if I told you I'm the
Riddler if you don't leave I'm going to
fill that suit with blood only one of
our suits will be filled with blood no
is yours are mine oh oh oh yours are
mine that's it
all
right okay all right you're not actually
Bru I know not B you are not B the city
needs me the city needs me enough you've
said that a 100 times get there the city
doesn't need you that bad you been at
this park talking about it all night I
can't sleep you sleep fine you're good
the
rider someone's watching us in the
bushes oh my God Matt over there don't
say that thumb drive how clever thumb
drive not to scoff laugh you want know
what I heard what' you hear CH Bruce
Wayne's a little [ __ ] little [ __ ] ass
ho that's what I heard the news and
media is all made up the news and the
media is all made up I wish I had
Batman's mindset you can't trust
anything on the
internet now it's just secret it's
secretly Matt like coming it's Matt
trying to project his iions as Batman I
have Tred to
trauma dispose on random
civilians where's the Jer all right all
right settle
down we are home from the Batman
adventures oh my God you're
next no no bat, dinner you know I'm a
winner just to fix your swag I'm a
needed diploma and I said that and I was
talking about you cuz you need to learn
how to dress my boy and I can't you want
know that look way better in a brand new
let's strip merch shirt available now at
st.com
hey jump again jump again jump
again my God I love the little kitty cat
on the shirt me
too the merch is now live this shirt a
couple of other ones I think make sure
you get it for the one that you want
sells out link the first link in
description down below is the link link
to our merch website so go shop right
now who won the rap battle inside one
random merch order we are going to put
the piece of paper that doctor Sinclair
was using during today's video that's
technically nonsense cuz he's not an
actual yeah he's not an actual therapist
he was just like writing scribbles on
here but these are all the questions
that he asked us during the videos and
there's some questions on here that we
we answered Dr Sinclair but didn't make
the cut of the video so if you want to
have this paper orders a merch and you
might own this should we we should sign
this oh yeah for sure we'll sign it
let's color on it and stuff and then
send it to them let's do it that'll be
so fun now watch me do this
split joking I can't do
this wait what is Middle bar mad
back guess who's back guess that's a
that's a that's a
Rupal yeah that's a Rupal boom boom
RuPaul says guess who's back house one
know what I give Matt's middle part five
big boom boom boom boom boom boom no no
the last one's got to be
a boom okay this is like insane I feel
crazy cost guys want triplets are down
big thumbs up the five big booms from us
I'm not doing that though and then last
thing super last thing if you guys get
this video to 100 50,000 likes we will
film a music video to the joke song we
made in today's video called bokeh bokeh
and if Sam wants to hop on the remix
we'll do a blend of both songs
yes $ th dinner you know I'm a winner I
don't want to do a music video you have
to if they get it to 150,000 why dislike
and
unsubscribe thank you for watching this
week's Friday video thank you for
watching this week's Friday video we
will see you next Friday make sure you
subscribe Matt we need the light on
halfway through for the outro make sure
make sure you subscribe and like Matt
and if you don't I'll kill you oh my God
[Music]