try everything hey people welcome back
happy Friday I need to stop like I think
about this right I love the moon can I
tell you can I tell you two things oh
wow it's tell you don't love that you
know it's so funny go you guys will
always find a way to cut me off of what
I'm saying no go ahead you were talking
like I didn't even hear you Nick had the
[ __ ] million ideas before we left the
house he what Nick don't do that is he
opening Tik Tok like to scroll around I
have something to say did y'all have
y'all ever like seen something like this
pop up on your phone and you're like and
you're like damn bro that was lowkey me
in a moment of time observe three
identical triplets huh do we think they
look alike no number one thing we get
asked about identical triplets is how we
tell them apart our babies are eight
months old now and I think they just
different babies however there are a few
things that we do that we can use to
tell them apart Cameron the oldest he's
got the biggest roundest face he's also
just kind of the
biggest Dominic has got the spikiest
hair and kind of still the wispi hair
and then Bobo he's the
littlest face and still a little bit of
a flat head the one when they're in
their crib oh I kind of want a baby I
don't want a
baby they're so cute [ __ ] it's this
dog and then Bo this is perfect you set
him down he immed wants to do happy baby
he wants to doog all
dayile they're so [ __ ]
cute does does that trip [ __ ] like that
pop up on your guys for you no I saw a
trip video the other day and it was so
good I we should do Ser reply to those
even though like they're not asking our
opinion right and I'm like at some
moment in time you were just a small
little baby rolling on the ground that
was us three insane insane insane you
know what I mean I really really and now
was mom going here's Chrissy he likes to
do happy baby well I just think of like
I definitely could not be a dad right
now that's this first thing I see when I
read I the thing that I think Dad's a
twin we
triplets what did he just say I don't
know neither do I I hope I have
twins
e sometimes that's how I see Matt those
videos like I just oh ow every time you
put him down he just wants to roll on
his belly y I can't believe we were
babies at the same time like I kind of
like I would like I'd really wish I had
like a personal baby experience like my
like if I was throwing up or [ __ ]
like one of you was probably crying or
something it's like can you [ __ ] off for
a minute I'm exploding diarrhea right
now and I need like my own little break
you know [ __ ] you both I know there's so
many moments it's like it's my birthday
and I'm like I just want to throw
[ __ ] cake at the wall I was like a
little yeah I just know I was
embarrassed at some point to be like
babies with you guys like that's what
you were just saying why are you looking
shocked he said it way worse mom
literally said that when we were kids me
what what what you're
heing [ __ ] his earings upside down
he's stting San holy
[ __ ] the sign of the devil oh my god
dude oh my
I actually was expecting someone to be
standing right there oh my God in what
world did that need to happen you fixed
your earring though we good oh my God I
was scared like a ghost all that because
I have a cross earring and it was upside
down by the way I literally was
expecting someone to be right there
covered in BL holding a machete was I in
the middle of say so sorry just like
like I said you guys will always find
way inter Matt punched me or Matt
slapped me those are $100 glasses
yeah don't do that give them to me no
give me them look at you Matt just
slapped me and it hit the bridge of the
sunglasses right here into my head and I
like I feel a little concussed you might
be I already have [ __ ] Vision I need
to go to the eye doctor okay and who's
problem who who needs both hands with
all 10 fingers to adjust their
sunglasses I think that was the most
Protec us we go down in like most
ridiculous moments in history absolutely
go ahead what were you saying oh mom
always told us that Chris was the one
that was off sleeping schedule annoying
inconvenient I'm so much more
comfortable falling asleep if I know
that like someone else is there anybody
because I when I'm sleeping alone I
struggle to fall asleep for hours but
the second there's another person
present in the room I'm down for the
count see I'm the other way around I
kind of get on edge when I'm near
somebody in my sleep I'm like what if
they like what if I wake up and they
have a gun or something isn't it crazy I
you guys a crazy
confession and you guys
no you guys you guys might think I'm
crazy you guys might think I'm crazy
when I was like when
when say it our entire life our entire
life our dad has been a fan of like
Forensic Files Criminal Minds like all
those crazy like killer shows so I was
always going to bed thinking about like
True Crime like all the stories were
like kids like killing their parents or
like brothers killing each other you
know what I mean like going crazy and
like shooting everyone in his family you
know what I'm saying I used to go to bed
and like have panic and I was like I
hope like mad Chris aren't like going to
like kill me tonight like I used to
think sometimes when we were going to
bed that like one of you like Matt like
might go crazy and like kill me like I
used to like actually go to bed like
when I was like maybe like eight or nine
and it was an actual thought in my head
like oh I hope that like no one in the
family is like one of those crazy people
Nick that's insane is that not crazy not
worth the freak out I thought you were
going to tell me that like one night you
woke up in the middle of the night and
like watched me sleep question and I'm
looking for them for an answer and you
guys do we talk about triplet [ __ ]
enough I don't I don't think we do I
think like it's so an underrated fun
addition to the fact that we're I'm a
comical genius yeah nobody cuz nobody
could replicate the triplet Vibe you
know what I mean hey must be the
money what's it with like babies
teething and like we've just never grown
out of that I don't think it's teething
when you're a full-grown adult it's more
of like chewing and it's a Leisure
activity it's not like to benefit your
teeth or oral um it's an oral fixation
mhm I was going to say your mama joke
going no that one's way too I was
waiting for you I say your mama got I
was I was waiting for him to break eye
contact with he goes he goes with the
glasses like he's my therapist man he
goes it's an oral fixation yeah I can't
and he stares me in the eyes for [ __ ]
10 seconds want to go and take a i think
it's so crazy that there's so many
different types of knots I've said this
before yeah like imagine tying like a
crazy knot I cannot if you want to go
and take a if you're a professional
wrestler what would your like entrance
music be something by Chief Keef like
what that's a perfect you know M would
be yeah some horror movie [ __ ] wow okay
this on
repeat type [ __ ]
I actually I can't listen to wow it's
crazy that that get like makes like
everything 10 times scarier cuz simply
that guy driving by right there just
like freaked me
out you're a psychopath that's this is
why I thought that was going to kill me
when I was no cuz if I'm used to it and
I'm going to go into like the wrestling
thing with that if one of you guys
kill thank you I would think Matt was
going to kill me before you would what's
the what's the craziest conspiracy
theory you've ever like heard on the
internet my favorite is when they like
they find like a missing person and then
like a celebrity and they're like this
celebrity is actually like like they I'm
pretty sure like AV LaVine and Katie
Perry There's like both like a super
severe like theory that both of them are
like missing children that's insane I'm
pretty sure no cuz like when something's
missing and you don't have it you can
make up anything you sound crazy no I
don't no I don't if I got rid of this
football
there's a golden football missing no I
wouldn't say that I'd say like there's a
football right now on vacation not what
I'm saying at
all what I'm saying is like if I lost my
wallet I could be like I lost my wallet
and it has millions of dollars in it
like I need it back okay and then if you
found a wallet that had a ton of
money the whole world would be like
that's his wallet cuz he said that I'm
missing my Lamborghini like no no that's
where my hug
at I I feel like I was going to say
something there's a lot of different
feel like I could have got goad what is
your what is your biggest internet
conspiracy that's what it was that's
what I was going to
say that we're not actually triplets and
two of us are photoshopped in yeah I
don't know who thought that one that
kind of sick that'd be crazy if I was
just like a super surge editor like
ready to edit the day away imagine
making glitch in that exact moment as
you're saying that I can't do that I
don't do this okay whatever isn't it
kind of crazy that I edit the videos
like I feel really great like yes we
collectively have like 6 million
something subscribers but I feel like
it's like the videos I create have
gained us six something million
subscribers that's all me like I kind of
did kind of eat that I know we just
talked about wizards but if you were a
wizard what would like your specialty be
can we not talk about wizard yeah I
don't care I really wish that you didn't
need a case on your iPhone cuz it would
look so much better you don't caseless
people who don't have a case I just want
to like sucker punch them in the [ __ ]
face I'm like you think you're the
[ __ ] cream of the crop don't you
running around with a [ __ ] no cased
iPhone are you sick your mother probably
bought that and you're treating it like
a toy who I forget who I was with are
you sick God I hate saying stories when
I forget who it is cuz then I can't
fully elaborate and then like you the
person again well no I just don't want
to do it and then the person sees his
video and then they're like he's talking
about me and doesn't even know it and
then I have have to live with that who
to say no when I was with somebody and I
forget who the [ __ ] it was and they
broke their phone and like goes into a
drawer and grabs a new iPhone and they
like set it
up why you're [ __ ] with Richie
mck I remember hanging out with somebody
and they like they're like ah this
phone's not working and then goes in
their drawer and like takes a new iPhone
and like sets it up and was like okay
I'm good who is this actually I actually
don't remember remember at all this
who no okay it was someone who like had
spare iphon it was someone who had a
[ __ ] spare iPhone sitting in their
cabin who was this I don't remember it
was like the very are you lying I'm dead
serious lying not lying if I was lying I
would I would just lie I think it was
like the early stages of our career in
La someone who thinks they're tough
somebody thinks they're tough if you
could live in if you could live in any
Video Game World which video game would
you pick call me crazy Jumanji no mine
would have to be like what move what
what games have like really just like
hot characters I need to live my um like
really hot female character energy for I
don't know but I'll join the game too if
you want I'd probably say Minecraft
[ __ ] typical mat answer bookie I'd
farm animals and I'd get hang up
painting seems like i' go outside and
like my own world can I say something
you want me to
go ahead go ahead m m boy um it just
seems like such a simple
life crafting building a little hot how
about this conversation that happened at
the Minecraft headquarters when the guy
figured out the game and he's telling
his friends he's like so the main basis
of the game is you mine new craft do you
think they came up with the like concept
of the game of mine like what came first
Minecraft or Mining and crafting I think
it just sounds really nice together it's
almost like peanut butter and jelly
peanut butter and jelly don't don't
sound that good together yeah but it's
now it does because of how much people
put peanut butter and jelly together
yeah I don't know I feel like I really
need to sit at a burger joint and eat a
burger with you guys very soon no like I
just haven't sat down in like a has this
thing going out of the house and like
fears going places but then we'll like
drive by a restaurant and be like we
need to go there and text like five of
our friends be like we got to go eat
this and then we just don't ever well
restaurants is one of my most enjoyable
experiences I love being out to eat I
think my like top 10 memories are like M
50% in restaurants call me nuts call me
totally nuts I think
that so you got food Island up and
running knocking like every single time
they inside out too I think it's crazy
that you can that that it is so
difficult and I have to go to like the
post office and the store and get my
photo taken to and the DMV to get an ID
and a passport and all this ridiculous
stuff but all I need to get a key to
someone's home is their house key I I
get that why do I have why do I need a
real ID or a passport listen listen I
don't work there why do I need to get
like an ID or a passport and I have to
bring my birth certificate my
certificate of birth onto this planet
I've never called her someone call a
birth certificate or certificate of
their birth I if I lurked outside your
home and I saw you put a key in the
flower pot I could take that key well
you already have it at that
point you're right actually you're
totally right no but I don't even have
to go make it to make it but then I
could take it and distribute it to all
my my my my crazy friends no but have
you seen no no cuzz with the speed that
that they can make a new key you have
enough time I could return it to get it
back
that's question I could take the key of
someone's doormat which is such a
stereotypical thing no hold on you want
to know what I hate about you go ahead
go I have to say something it's like
eating me
alive say it hey guys I want to say
something real
quick hold on that's as simple hold on
hold on
Yell I agree here's what Here's my
thought on that situation and how unfun
this isn't a TED
Talk yeah yeah yeah
yeah dude what is going on and the other
day that happened to me too and like all
go ahead Nick you're freaking me out I
love you but you're
be see that was fun I feel more inclined
that's a lesson right top 10 matte loud
moments in car I'd like to see that I
would like to see that I would like to
see that should I do just immediate like
I really would like to see that should I
should I make all 10 of them in this
video no no is too it's so crazy to me
how you're just King chill you chill
like if I was this relaxed as you I'd
like have to do like a thousand jumping
jacks if I this like relaxed I'd like be
burning Burning Alive Burning Alive you
want to know you want to know what's
funny you want to know you want to know
what's funny I feel like I'm listening
to the turtle and Kung Fu Panda Kong
Kung Fu Panda he always says Kong and I
just let it
little plastic thing dogs bite
on okay dude it's a kung kung Panda it's
K you're saying Kung Fu it's Kung Fu
whatever my bad I don't know the [ __ ]
G it's so crazy I can't speak like any
it's crazy chines that's such like a
good word like everyone knows Kung Fu
and that's so
Chinese no no I think how hard of a
language Chinese
can you stop you know what I mean I
can't say anything else but I can say
Kung Fu it's funny to me how my point
always gets gets proven you know
and you guys said if I if you were in my
situation you'd just be burning you'd be
on fire yeah I think sometimes I am and
and oh yeah sound it and the funny thing
about
it there's no choice sometimes dude like
I love that like ik is
Swedish oh yeah that's so awesome cuz
that's the first thing I'm thinking
about when I buy something from Ikea oh
at least it's Swedish it's not what I
mean at all look at me another stray
hair on the tippy tip of your head want
know what I'm going to do one night
while we're filming a car video I'm
going to call up somebody like 99
friends and I'm going to tell everyone
you look at 99 friend oh I remember what
I was going to say oh my [ __ ] God I
kill remember what I was going to say
have you seen that that thing that it
was like this girl like heid G to call
Sam and CH gbt 98 times her wow you just
said Sam mcrath and chat gbt are my only
two friends [ __ ] up uh have you seen
that girl like this girl got mad like
her ex-boyfriend or something and she
put a 100 keys outside with a key ring
and all the key Rings had like his phone
number on it and then she scattered them
in like different parts of the city so
people were like finding the keys and
going to like be like oh I should
deliver it to the guy and like calling
his phone over and over and over and
over I just found out something new I
just found out something new one what I
love when someone saw something so
specific like that video and they start
the conversation by oh my god did you
see that video where D and then by the
time you're halfway done with your
sentence you probably can assume neither
of us have seen the video you know what
I mean cuz it's so specific that we'd be
like yes we saw that video my thought my
the only thing that went through my head
is the fact that if somebody I don't
know if someone you break up with has
that much time to do it yeah I'm going
to speak for you you're doing too much
you're clearly psychotic and need to be
still thinking of that person to the
point like you are in the RO I'd be
flattered if someone did that to me cuz
it's like oh you're still I want someone
tires like I want some going to fight me
and slash my tires like oh sick now your
grandma's Hedges are about to be cut up
I'm going to go to your house and cut
Grandma's oh that'll get you bye guys
we'll see you guys next week enjoy your
weekend you are so loved by St triplets
we cannot wait to see you
later
subscribe subscribe we're on the road to
7 million subscribers so make sure
you're hitting that subscribe button
[Music]