Don't talk about English.
What's up everyone? We are now in
louder. What? What's up guys? We're in
Japan.
Just come look at this vending machine.
FC refresh shot.
Chris, you got to get it.
What do you think that like tastes like?
110 yen. Can I
look at these kids beggars?
Look at you. Like
Nick, come on.
Say, "Daddy, please." No. Yeah.
This is like genuinely my mind and
Chris's first trip of our entire life
that it's just the three of us here.
Like genuinely just the three of us. So
really crazy. We were just eating. We
were just eating and talking about how
unbelievable it is that we're here.
We never thought we would ever come
here.
Especially by at 21 and just us three.
Yeah. Crazy.
22 in a month. But welcome to the vlog.
Gorgeous. Oh, it smells like Pepsi,
I would imagine. Figured. Is it
delicious or no? Yeah,
it's like Pepsi but a little more zing.
Pepsi Zing.
Hey guys.
Hello guys. Chris got Chris Chris got
really dizzy and lightheaded so he went
back to the hotel
and he's being a baby just in general.
It's really hot. So I guess it's hot.
It's hot in Japan.
Me and Nick are starting his vlog. I'm a
big fan of apple drinks. And look at
irresistible is crazy. So we're going to
try this smiley face apple juice.
Look at the cap.
Cute. Okay. Okay, you ready?
Cheers.
I like how it just like looks so like
like you could like just drink this.
Like it just looks so susceptible to the
drinking.
Matt, I watched the click in your head.
As an apple fan, you've got to be losing
your mind now.
No, this is really good. It tastes like
apple juice for babies, and I kind of
[ __ ] with that. Apple juice for babies.
Oh, it's kind of delicious.
Does it not give you like a baby vibe?
Like a 2-year-old would [ __ ] with this.
Heavy.
It probably is for babies.
Mhm.
I like it. I' I'd get it again.
And Nick, you look like you lost another
20 lb.
Really?
Yes.
It's just being down.
I think it's the shirt, too. Flex on
them real quick.
No.
Why?
You just look built. Like you look
I'm not built.
You do. You look like a mammoth next to
me. Like you look like in a good way.
Like strong. This is strong.
You're freaking me out.
Take a picture. Smile.
I'm really worried for
Good morning. Day number two in Japan.
On our way to breakfast. Chris is still
feeling dizzy.
Welcome back to the Stern of the
Triplets vlog. Matt and Chris are eating
French toast.
How are we supposed to do anything when
it's this hot?
It's a good question. But you're
prevailing and you're doing an amazing
job despite what your haircut says about
you.
Get
Oh my god. That was good.
I'm trying to keep I'm trying to make
sure we get a good vlog. I'm having a
fun time. I have to pick up the energy
cuz Chris is hot and he's normally our
maniac. You know what I mean?
I know.
He's normally our our maniac.
It all happened. What are you vlogging
in that orientation for?
What?
You just spun the camera toward me and
you're we're in a square shape.
Dude, put your phone away.
You have to blur that.
Why are we in a square shape right now?
It's um it's 5X.
It's retro.
I don't know.
Sorry about that orientation, guys. I
Oh my god,
I can't believe
I started recording from a photo format.
They hate to see an American feeling a
beat in Japan.
Burger today, burger tomorrow, burger
forever. Like, I kind of need that
written across my chest in bold black
ink.
It says play games and I saw
play games.
I saw a bunch of skill cranes last night
and I'm going to win one of them. Let's
[ __ ] go.
Yes,
I'm so excited.
I hate that guy.
That evil thunk from Toy Story.
No, I hate him. He's like evil. I think
he turned on Woody and the homies. I'd
turn on Woody. Of course you would. Give
me more.
A little Care Bear. Mom loves Care
Bears.
You give me more.
Wait, wait, wait.
Can I have some?
Nick. Nice.
Nick.
Nick. Oh my god.
I'll get a first try. You'll be
Chris. Chris.
Oh my god. That's so close.
That was a good grab.
I don't even think it's getable.
You win. That's a win, right?
You got that.
That's never losing.
Oh my.
That might be ideal. It's got like a
tilt to it.
Wait. Drop another. Drop another. You
got to drop another on there.
Just hit the machine.
Chris, no. Chris, no.
I just won this and Matt doesn't know.
Where is he?
Look at this thing.
That's crazy.
No. That's so cute.
Isn't it unreal?
How did you get that?
No looker.
A no looker.
You got it, Matt.
No. Don't Don't say [ __ ]
No.
See the cat poster above you?
The cat poster above me?
No, I don't know what's there.
He's like looking into outer space. It's
amazing.
Do you know what you're going to get?
Nope. Cuz you're been you've been
holding the menu for a whole gone. What
did I just say?
I'm going to get a Wagu burger,
fried onions, bacon jam, and cheddar
cheese, but no bacon. You want to know
why it's bacon jam and not bacon jelly?
I wish I could I'm so hungry. I could
eat Kirby right now.
Nick, don't say that about him.
Woo! I can't wait to eat.
One fried Kirby.
He just doesn't know it yet.
He's sick to his stomach. Chris, no.
Don't even play. Don't even play. Can
you put him back, Matt?
OMG.
dancing at the movies cuz it feels so
mystical.
I love your hair, Nick, and I love your
hat.
Thank you. I appreciate the comments.
No problem.
This is actually like cinematic, like
movie level, like with the skyline
behind you, Matt. Like, you could say
something crazy right now and it would
look intense.
The city is mine.
Let's go.
We're all getting ice cream. Yes.
This guy's awesome.
Hey,
what is he doing?
I don't know.
And just like that,
it's all gone.
I really am.
Fat, fat, fatty.
[Laughter]
I mean you
[ __ ]
Uhuh.
Ow. You take it too far.
Always takes it too far.
Way later.
I can't see.
Don't you wish you could?
I have my dick out. I don't care.
Well, I'm gonna peel on the floor.
Is this in my room?
On the floor.
Oh my god.
Did you pee on the floor?
I just peed Nick. I'm peeing on the
floor.
Nick, turn it on.
Nick, you're cleaning.
No, I'm not.
I just pissed all over the [ __ ] wall.
We'll see you guys later.
You're annoying.
Are you [ __ ] kidding me?
All right, guys. Me and Nick tried this
two days ago. Chris is going to try it
now because he's finally with us.
Whoa.
Give it a shot.
Baby juice.
Yeah.
It's good, right?
Mhm. Wouldn't like a 2-year-old like
[ __ ] that [ __ ] up?
Are you like messing with me?
You look super muscular.
Me
like super built. Honestly,
don't do that. Don't do that.
I'm joking.
Who are you talking about?
Nothing. Nothing. Nothing.
It's a long story. I don't have time to
explain.
Not that funny, bro.
What's the Yo, get out of my face.
You have to tie your shoe. I feel you
guys just had a inside joke about
monsters.
Good night.
There's glass things in there. Like I
wish you didn't just drop that.
I didn't mean to drop it, Matt.
Wow.
Hey, cheese.
Nice.
Hey,
Chris, where are we going?
The other store.
Let's go. You were just at the chain.
Got these and now we're on the way to
the other store.
Dude, doesn't this feel great, Chris?
Yeah, it feels You feel the breeze.
That's I think this this drive is going
to be like comically short. Yeah, it's a
3m minute walk or one minute drive. So
I hope I don't drop everything I own.
Oh my god. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
That was like I feel like I just burped
and got there.
Just spawned in. Let's go.
Hey everyone, we are trying ramen in
Japan.
The first time I've ever got in a fight
over it cuz Chris isn't sure if he's
going to like it.
First time I've had ramen in my life.
Chris is just asking for a plane and we
were ordering on his
Well, Chris is asking me. He's like,
"Nick, am I going to like it? Am I going
to like it?" I'm like, "Unfortunately, I
was born with my own mouth, so I don't
know what yours is going to enjoy. I
know what my mouth enjoys."
Of course you do.
Everything. It's hard for your mouth not
to enjoy something.
My mouth enjoys being shut.
We know that. I hate everyone.
The flash hasn't gone off once, by the
way. Because I haven't put the flash on.
The flash should always be on on those
types of cameras. Why? All the photos
are going to be bad.
I Nick, I literally read this. Flash on.
Then use
flash off this. You should always use
the flash.
Matt, don't listen to him. Why?
I'm the king. He's a hater. Fine. Here.
I might have been.
Is
that good for you? Nick, what has been
your favorite part of Japan so far?
My favorite part is probably being with
you and Chris.
Really?
Yeah.
That's not my favorite part. Chris, what
would you say your favorite part is?
The heat.
Can you guys stop being annoying? My
favorite part is honestly just spending
all my money irrationally.
Okay, that's my favorite part. Yeah.
Nick's favorite part is that everything
is in yen. So, you just got to swipe and
hope he has enough. I'm like, yen? Here
you go. Nasty girl.
Nasty girl. It's
a similarity to Top Ramen.
Yeah, figured.
You're eating it.
H. You're eating it. I've never had Pop
Ramen.
[Music]
Are you an idiot? I'm dead serious.
Lying to my face in Japan. Okay. Lying
to my face in Japan. It's all I high
school. All I ate every day for 10
years.
I literally wouldn't even know how to
make it. Like, I'd have to read the
directions.
You're insane.
Stop laughing like that.
I just recorded you for a minute without
you knowing just to show you like what
you move like.
I'd probably be really upset.
I want to go to that the ski the arcade
and try to win.
What are you saying? the unexpected
moments that make things memorable,
right?
Yeah, exactly. Um, yeah. Um, well, that
sounds good. I'll talk to you later, I
guess.
Absolutely. It was great chatting with
you and if you need anything else, just
let me know. Have a great one.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
You're very welcome. Take care and have
a great rest of your day.
You were blushing. No,
I wasn't.
Yes, you were.
He said something super funny.
You were blushing.
Imagine if that's how someone looked
through a curtain like, "Oh, what? Let
me see how it's
sick." And then like clapped it like
that. You're sick. New curtain method
unlocked. This is how this is how we're
looking through curtains all of 2026.
You're going to break it. It's honestly
very like easy. Like no more lugging
around with the nifty string.
Wow. Shark Tank vocab instantly. No more
lugging around with a shifty spring.
Nifty spring.
Nifty string.
I kind of like this a lot more cuz you
don't have to like hold the current.
No, but it's for a quick peak rather
than being like like you know how some
people are like, "Oh,
it's a hassle to be yanking on these
tangled."
Yes, Nick. You get it. It's like, "Oh, I
want to see outside." Like, that looks
like creepy. This it eliminates the
creep. It's more of just like, "Oh,
yeah, that's outside."
Yeah, but now you're like wrinkling
though. No, it's not wrinkled at all.
It's It's actually a um It's a fiber
knit fabric that's meant for squishing.
Nick, come on. Thank you.
I think that's Cel.
I don't give a [ __ ]
Oh my god. I cooked. I cooked.
[Applause]
[Music]
No,
you gave up on me. Whoa.
And you gave up on me.
What is that?
Baby Peach. Mario. Are you hyping? It's
Peach.
This is actually who I play with. I play
with Kitty Peach.
Way off. Peach. Not way off. Not way
off. You have no idea what you're
talking about.
Look at that crab. Stop.
Oh.
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh.
It's thory. It's thievery. It just it
picks it up like firmly grasps it and
then it lets it go.
I don't know what's with that. Like it's
kind of [ __ ]
cuz that's the thing about skill cranes
is it's not even about skill. It's not
even about skill cuz the machine it's
about machine. It's about maximizing the
[Music]
Oh my god.
Oh my god, man.
Are you serious? Oh god.
I tried so hard to win that [ __ ]
stitch and I couldn't get him.
This is Curious George, right?
Yes, it's Curious George. The Curious
Monkey.
under his arm.
Nick, more. More. More.
Take the camera.
[Music]
I don't have any more actually.
Nick. Yes, you do.
This is 10,000. You can't put 10,000 yen
in them.
Wait. You could. I get a 100 coins.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Let's get as
much as you can.
Oh my god.
You're never getting that. They're never
[Music]
What the hell? They're picking it up. No
problem. And the claw machine's just
letting it go too far. See it?
On my last coin.
I see babies in this arcade game with
more self-control than that.
What are you doing?
That's the most far back I can go. You
have
Yeah, but you need to go that way more.
You're coming from that direction.
That's where you need to go.
What does that mean?
You're going too far this way. You're
delusional.
[Applause]
[Music]
Let's just get Mario. Are you dumb?
What are you being the rudest person
ever for?
Oh,
no. Nick, forward more.
What am I? I don't understand what
you're saying.
I've picked it up every single time.
And you got it. Oh.
Oh my god. You got robbed. Put the last
one in.
Which one should I go for? Mario.
Right there. Mario, you have to. He's so
close.
That was insane.
Guys, where is it? We got to get my boy.
I'm putting every dollar in here until
we get him.
Nick, I'm dead.
That's not logical. I'm not. If I get
like Piglet, I'm going again.
Piglet's the joke.
I agree.
Piglet's the [ __ ] dope.
Oh my god.
You're kidding. I actually got it
though.
First try. I've never seen you more.
Oh my god. Cuz that's like What are the
odds of that?
I think you've had enough though after
this.
No,
I think so.
Next, please. You can you need to learn
self-control.
Let's go.
Oh, you need to learn to watch out
behind you. Literally.
I could spend all day here. I really
could.
Nick, can I have
No.
A little Just one. You're done.
Five. Done. Five more. No.
Power Rangers.
Matt. Matt. Wait. Matt.
[Music]
The smile on Matt's face as he throws
yen out the window.
It's just like Ellie didn't buy a $4,000
bullet bag yesterday, right?
Not $4,000. I think we got it.
Can I get one so we can twin?
No.
Can I have three coins?
No. Can I have three?
No.
Stop putting things in my pocket, Matt.
You're an adult.
No, I just need you to hold on to it.
I'll take it. Can I have three? I'll
take it. Can I have three? Put that in
the Can I have three coins?
I'm asking for my money back. By the
way,
I give you one.
Look at that. Look at them.
You're telling me you don't want to get
one of those?
He's really rushing. We normally do a
bunch of different food challenges on
our channel, but this time we're going
to do it and actually get the stuff from
where cuz we normally we did a video
trying Japanese snacks. They were all
bad. They were all bad and I don't think
any of them are authentic. But we're
here. We're in the place and we're going
to buy a bunch. So, let's go. Let's go.
Ham.
This one looks the most fun to me.
This is Baskin Robin strawberry
cheesecake. Okay.
Girl love me cuz she say she want my
baby. Baby baby.
Not even close to the lyrics.
Is it not?
Wo.
These mentos I bought last night because
I really [ __ ] with them. And then Nick
reminded me that we're filming this
video today. So I paused and I bought
these. But we're going to try them now.
Let's do it. Thank god you said
really. That was like much more
important than
Well, I wanted to give proper
introduction but Chris just didn't.
Introduction is the word you're looking
for.
M.
It's orangey goodness. I feel it like
feel like a mentos like burst flavor.
Like I feel it like go all over me kind
of.
I'm not getting that. Neither am I.
Really?
Yeah. No, I'm not getting that.
This I'm most excited about. Look, it's
cotton candy, but it's pure white. Like
it literally looks like like a cloud.
Like dusty air. Take a small bite.
Tastes like literally nothing.
You ate it.
Like literally nothing. Doesn't even
have a scent. Ready?
Wow. Doesn't have a scent at all. This
is literally pointless. This is
pointless.
It feels like I'm eating like a pillow.
Like dead ass. Very similar to like a
crispy cream donut.
Gone in a blip. I feel like I could kill
you with this. Like use this instead of
[ __ ]
I feel like I'm eating insulation.
All right, guys. On to uh snack number
three. What is this? Hi-Chew minis. Oh
my god, they're in ball form. Which one?
Yes.
Take some.
Way too excited about that, buddy.
Approved. Not good.
Which one did you have?
Yellow.
Yeah.
Wait, I'm getting something bad. It
tastes a little dusty to be honest.
That's good. I'd hate to finish a bag of
these. I know. I've had so much food in
my life. I need to eat something I'm
excited about. And these are not it.
Why do you do that? It's just like I
need to get it out. I need to get it out
of my throat. Fourth snack.
Pokemon gummies.
Be the worst person ever.
Pokemon gummies. You know, it takes a
lot to be the worst person ever.
Can I see it?
They're mini.
Oh my god.
Show the camera.
No. The size of those are so we're going
to fall.
Look. Look.
Oh, they don't taste good.
They do. I like it.
They're not.
I'm a big fan of these cuz they're
wrong. They're so weird though.
They're like They're like chalky.
Those are like a mid, but they're like
All right.
They're not good.
Those I'd say six out of 10. Little Bob
Dogs.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. I need to take a
picture of this. It's so cute.
Literally, these are probably going to
be gas. Open it up. Oh, I'm dizzy.
You okay? Drink some water. I don't need
three of these. Is this Is this going to
turn into gum? I hate [ __ ] that's gum.
Mm-
Oh my god.
Blueberry chalk. I like it. Not a fan.
Oh my god. It's like really shocking me.
Well, yeah. You're putting your whole
neck into the bite.
I don't know. I This is my favorite one.
Look how cute this is, though. So out of
what?
Oh, it's the cutest thing ever.
Like it tastes like Fun Dip. Lick a
stick to me. Like I just the work part
of Fun Dip. It's
the best part of Fun Dip and it tastes
nothing like that. Lick a stick. Okay.
Gay guy.
What is this?
I don't know.
I don't like that. This is going to be
the [ __ ] gum disaster.
Hold on. Hold on. This is going to be
gum. I'm It's going to be so cold.
Hold on. [ __ ]
Hold on. Chris, can you wait? This is
100% gum. Look at the way it's like
chalky.
Oh my god. This is gum.
This is
Yep. I'm chewing shitty tasting gum.
It's not gum.
[Applause]
Nick,
I'm sorry.
I felt like
not good.
Okay. Well, are you like not that bad?
Can we move to the next, please? I have
to get that out of my face.
Okay. Me and Nick both had the pink one.
The pink one is not good.
Oh my god. That's one of the worst
things I've ever had in my life. All
right, these things might be fire.
The pretz.
I really like the name of them. Pretzel
gets the point across. Pretz
doesn't smell good.
Like a meal and like zapped into a
stick.
This is the best thing.
This is your type of vibe. Not
like a full meal zapped into one thing.
I hate this.
Oh, my favorite. It's your vibe, not
mine.
You should do the ranking here cuz I'm
going to give it a lower ranking than
you want.
I just love it. 10 out of 10.
Stick cheese. Like it's like bad cheese
and chicken.
You mean cheese sticks?
No, like stick cheese.
I don't like it. I know what a cheese
stick is. I'm not
When I was next.
Okay. I think this is like a strawberry
punch in the face.
Sounds like a great time.
What is it? What What are you
experiencing there?
I think it's cola, actually.
Like co cola fizzy right off your palm
ASMR. Hold on. Actually, be quiet.
Okay. My full mouth was over the mic.
Like the mic was in my mouth.
Imagine,
man.
Okay. Almond crush pocky.
Ooh, almond crush. I want that pocky or
pokey
party clap.
Chris,
you're getting almond.
you're getting almond on my bed.
Oh my god. Really good. Give me one.
Can you taste me? Give me one.
Give me one.
Put the [ __ ] thing in my throat.
Your uvula.
I don't know, man.
Tonsil.
Sure.
Either or.
So good.
It's the best thing so far.
Best thing so far.
Baby grind on me. Do you remember that
was a trend? I was about to say random
confession.
Jelly beans. Yeah, pretty
straightforward.
That's a pickle.
What? No, that's in Japanese.
What did he say?
If those were reading glasses, that
would have been
Wait, don't open them like that. Give me
Give it to me now.
Those are really good.
Have you guys ever [ __ ] seen Haribo
jelly beans? Jelly flops.
No, man. That's [ __ ] jelly flops. No,
that's [ __ ] jelly belly.
These are like 9-year-old me would be
freaking out.
I don't like jelly beans.
I never have.
I wish I was even remotely enjoying
anything.
Did you have the white one?
No. Eat it.
The white one is fantastic. It tastes
just like the jelly jelly bean gummy
beast.
I'm most excited about this. Hold on.
Let me show them the packaging first.
It's like wafer ice cream cones. These
look so I [ __ ] good.
Um there's the vanilla.
Vanilla. Strawberry.
Strawberry.
Christian, go strawberry.
Of course, I have to get the strawberry
one. It's
just cute and pink.
Oh, it smells so good.
Wait, I actually probably would like the
strawberry more. Oh well.
Wait, should we can we do like a in the
middle three something?
Dude, what?
[Music]
Why are you puffing all over me?
Oh my god. Can I please try the
strawberry one? Actually,
I love the strawberry ones of those. I
knew.
Oh my god. Good.
Oh my god. I feel like the vanilla one
would be the best. This reminds me when
I used to go I don't want this.
the hospital as a kid.
I used to get these all the time.
Okay, I would say second best thing
we've had today. My favorite. What was
your favorite?
Those almond sticks.
Oh, those are good. All right, guys. The
last thing that we are trying is this. I
think it's matcha. Oh, no. It's Dubai
chocolate. Pistachio. Dubai chocolate. I
think all Dubai chocolate's pistachio.
No, I don't [ __ ] understand this.
What's going on in the world? What is
Dubai chocolate? What does that even
mean? I don't know.
I don't think I want to try this. Oh, it
smells good. Kind of. I like pistachios.
I don't know if that's like a crazy
confession. No, it's good. I'm going to
literally throw up, but the consistency
kind of like blows.
What do you think, Nick?
Here's what Here me it tastes like [ __ ]
Here's here's what I'm going to say.
Here's what I'm going to say. [ __ ] It's
not bad, but I'd rather have a Reese's
cup. And I agree. You know, you know, I
love when Reese's makes the funny little
shapes like the Easter Bunny. I like
when they do the funny ads and it's like
I like when an ad commentator has like a
super deep voice and he's like, "You
want my chocolate?"
All right, guys. That was us trying some
Japanese snacks in Japan. And we will
see you guys next part of the vlog. I
don't know if this was the best idea
ever cuz all three of us are allergic,
but I know we should have done this late
in our day so you could take Benadryl
and go to bed.
It's worth it. If we all walk around in
swollen places after this, it's feel
like very worth it.
The guardian of the doorway.
Wait,
he looks like a man. Like a literal
person.
Snacks for cats.
Who's the lucky kitten? Matt, this guy
[Music]
Matt behind you.
Not hungry. You are though.
Yes.
Eat.
Chris, I feel like they look oddly
human. Like I recorded one and he was
like
staring at Chris. Hold on.
No. Move.
Oh. could just push me.
Push me in the cat cafe, by the way.
They're really like crazy. Like, they're
big and gorgeous.
Come on. A couple more pieces.
Me and Chris can't stop laughing at Matt
because he's so obsessed. Like, I think
he keeps looking at us to make sure we
haven't gone anywhere. But I think if he
could stay here for the rest of the day,
he would.
[Music]
The cat got on the counter.
I don't know if he likes me or if he was
just being greedy.
Greedy little munchkin. Look at them.
So cute.
Do you guys have coins?
No, we have no coins. Matt, you've used
all Matt, are you regretting using all
of our coins at the skill crane or no?
The
slightest little bit.
It's not coming over.
Oh my god. Hi, kitty friend. Goodbye.
That was incredible. Goodbye, kitty.
Go Chris up the stairs.
See you later, bro.
Hey guys, we are headed to our favorite
barbecue place. We went the other day. I
came here when I was here last year and
it's delicious and amazing. And we're
going back and we're 2 minutes away. I
just have to say I've always wanted to
play Pokémon Go in the streets of Japan.
Is it living up to your expectations?
It's amazing. I'm having so much fun.
Flavors.
I still need to learn to master
chopstick.
I I've mastered it. All right.
This is good.
Yeah, that's pretty good, actually.
What are you touch on my chin for?
You had something on your chin. I'm not
touching it for fun.
You have a kind chin. You know that,
right?
You have a kind of chin. I like
Are you cooking like a good boy?
That was a fiery inferno. Holy [ __ ]
What the heck?
What the heck? Hey
Nick,
what the
A bunch of a bunch of nut in the
streets. That's crazy.
I'm so for real right now. You got to
try this. Hurry up. What? What? Try it.
Spin the camera. Try it. Chris, please
try this. I'm so good at
this. Look like this could easil This is
like viral meme potential right here.
Try this. It's good. Eat it. It tastes
good.
Try it.
Come on.
Isn't it crazy?
No, it's good.
It's so good.
Okay.
No. No. You eat the crunchy bit there.
[Music]
Guess
we're going up.
That [ __ ] creme brulee I ate all to
myself, half asleep in Italy. Someone
sent me that video. That was the best
moment of my life. Were you recording
the whole time I was talking? That was
the best moment of my life. And here you
you heard me caught off guard sharing
about that [ __ ] thing. It was this
big all to myself. And look at what I'm
dealing with now. Puny [ __ ]
Is this wet, too?
What? Nick,
this is wet.
What's
my hands are wet? Can you tell me?
It's not wet.
It's not. Kirby absorbed all of it.
He's what?
He absorbed all of it. I'm wet.
Thank God for him.
Do you want to explain your current
situation at all?
No. You need to learn how to [ __ ]
pack your bags. This is wet. Like this
is soaking wet and it smells like I'm
not going to be able to like
It's not that big of a deal. It's a
little damp and it's cuz a face mask
exploded.
You zip this side up. You zip this side
up. You have a perfectly good suitcase
to go. You stuff that fat [ __ ]
in the middle and that's what your
suitcase is.
This is wet and sticky. Like that's
going to ruin like all the [ __ ] on this
side.
No, it's not. No, it's not. It's a
little damp. Ruin all the [ __ ] on that
side. No, it's not.
Yeah, it is.
I promise to god it's not. It's
also your fault for like having so much
stuff.
Well, like I'm just thinking about this
logically. I have to bring Kirby, so I
have to get another suitcase. Carry
Kirby through the airport.
No, it's that simple. That's the only
and effective way to do it. I'd rather
wheel a suit.
The reason I'd rather wheel a suit.
Listen, if you zip the face mask up in
this [ __ ] like this, how I had it, it
would have been fine. It popped cuz you
stuffed Kirby between it both sides.
No, but I I don't want to carry Kirby
and I think I need
Put him in your backpack. My backpack's
full cuz I have our vlog camera.
Take the vlog camera.
You don't understand. It's not
I could get Kirby in your backpack.
No, you couldn't.
Yes, I absolutely could.
No, you could.
Okay.
You can get Kirby in my backpack without
me looking like a ninja turtle.
I don't think
it's not my fault.
Done.
Curvy's in there.
Yep. Kirby,
he's in there.
Kirby's in there. It's safe and sound at
the bottom.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Oh my god. Watching you guys try to pack
for the last 20 minutes has been the
best thing ever.
Can you just like
A face mask exploded. Nick,
can you just check what's wet? Because
my hand is sticky. I can't tell. Check
over here.
Dry. Dry. Dry. Dry.
Check over here.
Little wet. Dry. Completely dry.
Completely dry. Completely dry. Can you
be honest and take your little bit wet
along the seams where the face mask
exploded?
Yeah, I should keep completely dry.
It's nylon, though. It's not like going
to stick. Just zip it up and you're
fine. No,
but I don't want all the things in there
to be sticky.
Nothing's going to be sticky. And it's
all closed. It's going to go in a
machine washable.
Do you promise?
Yes. Now that Kirby's in your backpack,
you're living free. Like, but it's also
like now you're going to find something
to complain about in your backpack.
No, if I know Kirby's with me, I won't
complain.
Our vlog camera is going to like break
and then you're going to be like, "Well,
it's cuz you stuff Kirby in my
backpack."
If that does happen, that is
100%. Obviously,
you're just like suck at packing.
Like the thing is I could spend 60,000
yen and com and this would all be over.
I could put everything right in my sight
in one suitcase. Boom. And check this.
You going to pack the second suitcase?
I will.
You can't even say it.
No, you will.
I will.
What are you going to put in the second
suitcase?
I
this belt.
Okay.
This leaning on the [ __ ]
wet everywhere, man. I'm sorry,
dude.
Oh my god.
No. No. No. No. I just don't want my
stuff to get ruined.
Nothing's ruined. The only person
ruining your life is [ __ ] Kirby.
That's it. That's the only person.
It's not true.
You put a pack of like a jelloy face
mask in right in the back.
Who packed for me?
I did and then I thought it was over and
you stuffed Kirby between the two. Nick,
it's the only reason it exploded. It
would have been perfectly fine.
It's just soaking wet.
No, it's not. If you go buy if you go
buy a whole suitcase.
Feels like it's going to be unwarable.
No, this is
Does it look like ridiculous?
I I promise the backpack is not what
looks ridiculous right now.
Like, but my thought is all mystery
solves.
What's funny?
Holy [ __ ] Look at his outfit.
If you left Kirby here and I bought the
exact same replica to our house, I won
him in Japan. I'm not leaving him
behind. Like, what is going on that you
think that that's okay? Do you have a
heart?
I'm done.
I'm not letting this happen. You're
You're not buying an entire suitcase cuz
you don't want to carry Kirby to the
airport. Can you warn me or
you are [ __ ]
like that's the thing that's like that's
what's bothering me is like I'm a
21-year-old adult and you have and you
have no superpowers over me. Like you're
not my boss. You're not my mentor.
You have a scope of how much money how
money works.
I do. You make a good amount of money.
You're a young successful gentleman. So
now it's like, "Oh, now I'll just blow
I'll get another suitcase cuz I want
this." The service charge of an
overweight bag or the damage to all my
items is going to be more if I try and
fit Kirby in here and if I listen
listen. I just bought nice new glasses
and I have my laptop.
Okay. Okay. Listen. I put my laptop,
nice new glasses that I bought and
and our vlog camera in there. I put
Kirby in there. I make the backpack
really really tight. A security guy
throws my bag across the [ __ ] place
when
or during the [ __ ] security
down through
if something happens or if I [ __ ]
bump into something or something goes on
or I put my bag down. Even lightly
putting my bag down if it's that
comfort.
You realize he's a pillow, right? It's
like actually it's like putting bubble
wrap around all the stuff. Bro,
it's like actually the only reason it
broke something in here is cuz you're
cramming it between two closed sides of
a suitcase and you have a packet of air.
What happened in there?
You're not sandwiching shut. You're just
oh putting it in the backpack and then
you're balancing something
and then I'm going like this zippers and
[ __ ] pull.
No, you're not. Did you see it placed
inside? I'll like give him a shove or
two just to get it to the bottom. Just
to get it to the bottom. Now he's at the
bottom fully there. not going any
there's there's no hindering anything
right in the middle peacefully right in
the middle or right on the side very
easily just have to get it to angle
itself microphone placed right there
much pressure on all sides
there's no pressure there's no pressure
at all there's there's room I can fit my
whole finger around it
zip it up
no room
zipping it up
peacefully zips closed
Do you think anything in there is going
to break?
Nothing's going to break. My heart's
going to break if you go downstairs and
buy another suitcase cuz that cuz you
don't want to carry this.
This is a standard backpack to like
carry it through the airport.
Oh, I'm going somewhere.
I think it looks a little better on you
right now.
Kirby's not going to like burst open in
the backpack. The only reason it
happened in your suitcase is so a
[ __ ] airbag of a face mask here.
If you zip that, what does it look like?
Is it reasonable?
This.
Can you close it?
It's going to look fine. It's flat.
Flat. All you have to do is close it and
zip it.
A little heavy underwear in there.
My dirty underwear. It's
looking like it looks normal. Like
Yes, I do. I know for sure.
I've packed your bag for [ __ ] eight
years, Nick. I've I've never seen a
suitcase this jam-packed. And I can
still guarantee you it's nothing's going
to break. The only reason your face mask
full of air broke is cuz you jammed
Kirby's fat ass between the suitcase.
I don't
If you buy another suitcase, I'm never
person to travel with says you. You're
the
[Laughter]
go right now. I'll go right now. No,
you're not. Yes, I will. I'll take my
bag.
Nick, you're not.
Nick, do you understand how many years
have I packed your luggage?
I don't know. You dress like an idiot,
first of all.
Yeah. Okay.
[Music]
Where's that? Stop.
This would be ideal.
Baby,
[Music]