this is the most ridiculous scenario
I've ever been in in my
life says the one that's shut
[Music]
up stop talking all right guys um
welcome back to a Friday video this
one's a little different cuz we can't
drive the car cuz Matt has Co so we're
in our garage and you're going to ask
why can't Matt be with you or why Matt's
not with you guys cuz he has Co how are
you going to film a car
video we're going to use modern
technology show them Nick yes all right
guys here's the rizzler there he is it's
Matt he's never look better it's GNA be
a little difficult to Riz y'all up this
car video but I'm never the type of man
to turn down a challenge so Matt who are
you what are you talking you talking to
I'm talking to Nick yeah what he said
it's going to be difficult to virtually
RIS me up this car video okay let's tape
him up up top I don't know this is why
I'm confused yeah
just you have to keep going let me know
I'm up yeah we will M this tape's not
strong enough we're going to need to
go get some
gorilla I think y I can listen to music
while I
wait all you got to get the bottom of
the iPad
okay Matt your forehead is kind of like
not on the screen no you can Center it
now okay this so should I like lean no
you're good no I think that's good you
don't even need to take the bottom it
looks like you have a cool it looks like
you have a looks like you're wearing a
headband it looks like you have a cool
yellow headband on it looks like you're
playing
sports no it's a little up it's a little
up up no a little a little
more higher that is not a
headband then who said head band look
here it looks like you have a Halo on
does it one just burp it sounds like
meatballs did you eat meatballs it
wasn't Matt oh yeah definitely wasn't me
I forgot that you're not here I can
still see Matt like hey I'm not I'm not
g to let you guys interrupt me because
I'm a computer
screen okay you want to know who I feel
like
who fornite move over a little bit
you're so close to showing us right the
other way no other way right where your
face is there we go yeah why do you feel
like him cuz like look it's just a head
he's just in a fish bowl yeah all right
I feel like I'm I'm ordering Moby at
like a really like Chick-fil-A yeah like
at a really fast food place cuz you have
the headset on too it's always my
pleasure
hey your burps are like disgusting Matt
how good do you feel oh my God I feel
great I feel great I feel great it
literally smells like meatballs in here
cuz Chris is like drinking Pepsi and
burping I don't know he didn't even eat
meatballs I had pepperoni did you
pepperoni just tastes like meat like
there like the air the air I'm in sounds
like me air he just ainer he just ain't
shower in a
while no that's not true it's just it
smells like meatballs kind of true I'm
gonna say everything Chris hates that I
say about him because he can't do
anything yeah you're gonna stop saying
it cuz it's not going to go in the video
You're G to stop saying it it's not to
go in the video all right Lal nerd holy
okay moving forward Matt you you
you a screens shooter your internet
tough you you won't say to my face
you're nothing but an iPad tape to a
chair hey Siri what's the
weather let me check let me check 49
partly
cloudy with a high of 69 and a low 47
all right can we get a wind
update h a wind update
no that one just blew right by me oh
Gody come on give us a wind update like
a miles per hour shut the up I'm
not going to give you a wind update
you're in a car it doesn't
matter well don't know it's
embarrassing you guys are 20 years old
and the reason that we have to do
like what's going on right now like why
I'm literally Leviathan from fortnite
and you guys are in the car that's
parked you genuinely can't move a
vehicle isn't that embarrassing
you're 20 years
old either way we could either way you
we'd have to drive the car and then
you'd be like you'd be an iPad where I'm
sitting corre how embarrassing is it
that like we get like a long metal pole
with like wheels and then just push them
around like that like this is actually I
think the craziest thing you ever done
question see y'all can't say we're not
dedicated to our crash anybody that says
we're not you're wrong I'm
literally a head right now I
can't wait to see edits of Matt
with this clip of him literally an iPad
on the wall all like this is
actually
unbelievable all right Matt stop all
right moving on today's topic because
Matt has Co I probably look like
Rango with my eyes going in different
directions because I don't know who like
I don't know where to look do I look
right at the camera
like I'm talking so look where you would
look to like look at
me today's video topic because Matt is
an iPad cuz he has Co and Chris does not
have Co and I already had Co and he has
to be on the Internet is we're going to
be talking about about Internet devices
robots AI modern technology there just
like five jokes that he rotates out and
then once there's five new ones he
throws the other five away and put puts
the other five there what are you
talking talk about can we talk about
that what are you what are you saying
Matt I don't know CU it's just like his
joke palet is just like he has to sub
them out Matt your speech palette has
been more today via iPad than any other
person anytime you've ever been here
you're Cho to just play in a car video
more when you're literally a
digital you're VR like at this
point you want to know why you want to
know why why because I can just manually
lower the headache like
that isn't that crazy like I can
manually lower the headache oh
wait smells wonderful no idiot burping
in my face how crazy is that all
right what would you do if you started
to like walk into grocery stores or like
like like stores like the cashier is
just like exactly what Matt looked like
right now like I bet you there's not
it's not going to be that long till we
go into stores and the cashier is this
is can you lock the door do you know
those Tik toks where the person has like
they're like operating a mini golf
course and it's like like mini golf
online no and you can like yeah you like
you aim that's Matt right now it's like
the skill crane yes exactly I feel like
I'm playing online mini golf with Matt
right now which is so stupid
leave your house you lazy shits
holy you're doing online mini golf get a
grip dude holy
imagine so many better things you
could be doing online than playing
online mini golf imag name name three
things better than online mini golf name
three things better online than mini
golf video games anything that
you can't do in person and stop
being a lazy it's a virtual world
soon we're going to be doing everything
online I hatef though we golf Turn Me Up
with the we golf we golf Turn Me Up yeah
because that's you that's you telling
the character what to do virtually
attending still no no no and they're
still like you're still
like like doing the and you're still
with friends and family virtually
virtually attending a mini golf course
is crazy what what do you feel about the
stores where you can go in and just
leave with stuff and it just charges you
as you
exit beats the whole
fun what's the fun buying I don't
know TT receipts is top three though I
love te text receipts the tap function
is super fun and easy tap is nice tap
everyone loves tapping their card yeah
apple I so extra like kind of like
bending my C to the tap you would like
doing it extra making everybody's life
difficult what you mean
Matt it's pretty self-explanatory like
Chris would be the type to make things
extra no he was saying like extra not
like making extra steps but like doing
like a fancy move before putting his
thing on the tap and then I said what I
said oh I I just wasn't sure cuz you
know you're a AI right now oh no
no no I fully got it okay I was checking
I I hate going to Chick-fil-A and like
like this exact scenario which is weird
is like this exact scenario of us and
Matt has happened to me in a Chick-fil-A
drive-through before where like I've
gone through and it's like a girl in her
bedroom taking my Chick-fil-A order what
you guys have seen this no
M have you ever got yeah did you get
food from the mystery bedroom you guys
have seen this like you go maybe not her
bedroom but like you've seen like the
FaceTime Chick-fil-A workers for sure
Nick you make stuff up actually Google
it you still sa my pleasure I don't know
that's a good question wait up let me
look FaceTime Chick-fil-A girl imagine
clocking into Chick-fil-A via home
Chick-fil-A iPad Matt you're not be able
to see this obviously
looken
Del
is she home at home answering her
chickf Playa at at home mat
that's ridiculous that's ridiculous let
me screen record these because it's not
let me save them but yeah that was an
actual thing at Chick-fil-A is the exact
scenario we're in right now I love how
she still has her uniform on what's
going on Matt wait Matt what's going
on
Matt I think he's updating he's updating
softing we have
a hold on he's loading first ever
software update all right are you back
what what bugs were
fixed um I can speak a little bit of
Spanish now okay okay SI that's basic
that's basically it like there's two new
emoticons but new emotic what did you do
if someone was in the garage with us
shut the up like just there was a
random Str oh my god dude you're
actually creeping me out do you ever lay
down in your bed and then you're like
you like trick yourself like you're
laying in bed in the you're like oh
there's just someone in the corner of my
room right now and I'll look oh yeah
there's no one there sometimes I look
and there's like a shadow of my jacket
and I'm like they are there what
is what are you saying that's hello in
Swedish oh hello
hello this kid's not real all right
thank you thanks
Matt
what' you say what is up with the
different languages what' you say that's
still Swedish it just says
subscribe subscri why Swedish is this
the new update yeah I was expecting a
different language to tell us ready
ready
ready oh I like the way that one sound
what was that
one that's French toast in
Swedish French to what an awful
joke that joke I'll taken too
far say it again do you hear that French
toast oh
did it it's like did heard that in
a rap song it sounds like a rap ad oh my
God all right kill it it sounds like an
ice song
what would you guys do if we went
downstairs and there was like a little
Robot Man and he's like hey I'd love to
assist you today what can I do for you
i' throw it away and hope get the
out of my house you guys if robots if
robots could exist as of tomorrow and
they're like all right everybody can go
buy a go buy an assistant robot you're
not buying
one no that's just what I'm saying is
genuinely isn't it not crazy that like
in like 30 years we could go like like
one of you guys could have a kid and
they could be like Oh I'm going to my
friend's house like they go to their
friend's house and like they just like
go in like a VR world all day and go to
like like hang out like virtually or my
God they're going to have like collab
virtual realities where like like ready
player one type where I'm going to
able to like put my VR headset on and
like Chris is going be able to put his
VR headset on from his room and we're
going to like walk over to each other
like in the VR world like Minecraft but
like you can enter in VR not take but I
feel like we're good where we're at with
technology I fully agree no I think we
need another I think we need another
rocket ship to the Moon hello
was going to make me sick oh my god when
people can start touching each other on
like VR and
that's insane no just yes yes but
not where I was about to go tell us
about where you were going to
go the second something from like the
generation that we're living in right
now gets called
vintage I should be in the ground wow
that's deep I just can't believe like
the shut
up stupid joke I'm not making I'm not
making a joke you idiot you just
can't understand it you saying that's
steep made it seem like it's as deep as
a bow of soup like real about it
wa can I just say random off topic let's
do top three technology things in movies
that you wish were real in your life and
is when I kiss
her Spy Kids microwave where they throw
like the oh the little packet
Bench Warmers I was gonna say
that oh I just spilled my drink fully
agree tell us about it Matt the
the dude and he's just like what's his
name it's like R2 but it's like the dude
with the white R2D2 not R2D2 but just
not R2D2 the other robot the other robot
guy not
R2D2 it's a completely different Rob
completely different robot I love this
song you just added another robot into
it for no reason not not Wall-E not
R2-D2 not Wall-E not R2-D2 just a
totally newa chewbaca is not a robot
what's the golden Chewbacca is not a
robot what's the golden guy's name
B22 no it's like bb bb something like
get out of here it's not golden he's
orange he's golden he's a little baby
orange thing definitely Chris we're
talking that's bb8 that's BB bb8 that's
who we're talking about no we're talking
about the golden guy the gold dude
Midas Droid his name's Droid stupid name
stupid his name is Droid Droid I feel
like if I was a Star Wars character I'd
be him like it makes a lot of sense for
me Matt what would your Robo name be my
Robo name yeah if you were a robot what
would you name yourself you'd be like
the self-proclaimed one it wouldn't be
Droid wouldn't be Droid that's for sure
what's everyone's favorite like robot
name like if you were a robot I don't
know I haven't thought about my robot
name enough if I had to pick one right
now I'd probably just do like my
initials like it's the most robotic you
know like NBS yeah sure you have it
trash how about you say your initials
and I say your initials and you say sure
yeah you mean yes you mean
yes sure I'd be like Mr nuts and bolts
oh gross be me freaky as no it's
not nut like you would be Mr nuts and
bolts like you're just weird no and I'd
be like handy like I'd be a handy robot
yeah I'm pretty sure you'd be pretty
handy with that name like nuts I'd be
like the Auto Body service robot I'd be
the Matt shut the up you screen I'd
be the burger bot and i' just
get
[Music]
mat did you just he Nick
Matt let's repeat the same joke so many
times Matt did you just hear what Nick
said his name would be no I'd be the
burger
bot and I just get everybody whatever
meal they want hey it's the burger bot
what's the word Burger bot we need to
trademark Burger bot no we need to
trademark Burger B I wouldn't be
surprised if in a couple years we go in
a fast food place and you get
Burg and the Burger brought to
you the burger brought is going to exist
and we need to prep the burger do you
guys remember when we went to H oh my
God salmon cat no CPK CPK and the
little yes the robot
puppy came over and gave us our food it
was I thought it was going to bark I
wonder if we're going to become an
immortal species of human beings by by
like potions and like spells and stuff
going be or robots like I wonder which
rope will take like fantasy or
technology well I think that like we're
going to be able which one's going to
elongate like the human race is going to
either be like technology or like
fantasy and like Whimsical spells and
Stu am I going to be able to drink a
potion and then live forever or is there
going to be like a Droid that like
sticks a hard drive in like my neck or
okay and then I'm just like existing
forever cuz I have my hard drive
in dude the burger bot I genuinely think
like right now we should get that
patented because I agree you're not
patenting Burger bot you enter
McDonald's or Burger King or something
in like 20 years from now I will
guarantee you there will be a Burgery
with a burger b a burger you're nothing
with Burger bot dude me and burger bot
could take it to the Moon Matt I
don't think you really understand me and
burger bot can make it all the way you
literally are the burger bot kid I'm
talking to the Burger bot you're you're
literally right now talking to the same
software Burger bot's going to be built
off of so maybe close your
American cheddar or swiss like come on
yeah literal Burger bot remember the
episode of Sam and Cat where they would
go to the restaurant and it was like
call like Bots and bolts or something
and they would just get food served to
them by robots that's like I don't
understand how like wait another thing
with technology I don't get is like how
can this happen in movies but not
real life like if you're going to
CGI Thanos and the
Infinity Gauntlet and like all this
and he's going to wipe out the universe
how can we CGI this that
doesn't exist that's what I want to know
like anything that should be CGI should
be possible Nick what the that's my
theory like if you have the technology
to virtually create it if I can watch
this why is it not real create it do use
more of that tech make it real Nick they
listening to they could virtually cut
you in half then put you back together
what does that even mean we need
more also side note totally side note
with technology and stuff we need shut
up dumb dumb
idiot you're little you're literally the
burger ball I'll lower your volume right
now I'll lower your volume I'm out of
breath now hold on what I'm saying is we
need we need more mad scientists
what like where where are the Mad
scientists that are that's what
I want to know who's inventing we
haven't had a i where's the newest
invention we haven't had a new
invention I want to see the wheel the
Cyber truck cyber truck who gives a
about the Cyber truck Elon Musk oh he's
making another car congratulations I
don't care what okay I don't care when
the new tech is like another car another
you want to see like a fly what I want
to see like a droid actually I
want to I want to see bb-8 Nick what
this is what I'm talking about I'm not
of a bb8 Nick imagine if we all could
have our own little personal I want a
personal little chef robot that just
Cooks me my meals and then
robots don't have emotions robots don't
have emotions or just because you want
it doesn't mean you need it robots don't
have emotions or like a heart or
anything thing it's like this robot it's
literal job is to serve me my
food I could get a little sloppy robot
to just throw throw meat at me
here's ribs here's steak here's a
cheeseburger it's a robot that
want know what the robot's happy it's
the only emotion I can feel this robot
could be hardwired to to get joy from
bringing me a
Burger the burger bot that's the thing
the burger bot is going to he's going to
hardwired so that his Joy is bringing
people overwhelmed he's going to just be
so happy to bring people Burgers
it's going to get some point where he's
like burger burger burger going to order
a hot dog and he's going to lose
his it's like the fin scour BB the
what the what the flinck Cloudy with a
Chance of Meatballs no that's exactly
what you wanted no it's not Matt is
literally ketchup and Dill Pickles away
from becoming the burger bot yeah
would what would Burger Bots like arch
nemesis be like who would try to take
down Burger bot mat I need to hear you
and Nick eat all the Burgers it
sounds it sounds like right now you're
bigger bot your burger bot's biggest op
and that's not cool no Matt's
Burger I'm not Burger bot's biggest up
to be frank I just don't care to be
frank oh my God hot dog reference no
yeah Matt Matt's like Burger bot's
number one Defender average Burger bot
fan over here that's literally us
literally the opposite fcking meatball
mat meatball Matt versus Burger bot The
Showdown of a
lifetime who wants the
meatballs Burger bot Burger bot
Lane Matt Matt you can't talk all this
about Burger bot you're a
bot you're a computer bot if I
literally edited sesame seeds on you
you'd be the burger bot and that's
what's driving me crazy this robot
it's weird weird I agree there's
nothing more better than than human
interaction there's nothing more better
okay you can't correct someone's grammar
while you're literally an iPad you
literally are spell checking you're
spell check K just control
Z my head ass what's our word count for
the video all right guys thank you for
watching this Friday's video obviously
this is a unique one it's never going to
be like this again unless one of us gets
Co again probably but yeah we still
figured out to film a Friday video we
missed the podcast on Monday so we
didn't want to miss both in a row so we
made sure to film this um Matt should
test negative in the next few days and
we'll be back to normal so I'll be
negative tomorrow yeah but for now I'll
be negative but I'll be keeping it
positive also sorry because I'm assuming
we have a weak ass photo dump from this
week we spent the whole week at home so
it's probably like one thing all right
Nick what do you have to say um what I
have to say is the moment we hit 6
million subscribers and we're super
super close we're going to be doing a
mer drop y'all don't even know what's
gonna happen we have a lot of plans for
6 million subscribers so help us get
there and we're super excited for the
the life of our content we're going to
be talking to you guys more frequently
soon we're going to really hammer in the
hammering what our plans are post it
back we have a lot planned and we're
going to talk to you guys soon but go
click the merch Link in our description
make sure you remember that site it's
always going to be in the description of
these videos so when we do do a merch
drop you know exactly where to find our
merch link and do not buy our fake merch
and also did you just keep that I just
said dooo in that sentence almost made
laugh out loud I dring myself all right
Matt it's on you peace out
[Music]
y'all