is the car not locked why are these ni
the car is locked you left the lights on
you idiot [ __ ] rats oh my God you're
sick yeah
[Music]
mother oo is it good
milk it's great yes Baby W do you hear
that beeping as well yeah that's what I
was looking for so carb start poisoning
down sorry I brought you a little sucker
M I don't want a little sucker but
that'll little pacifier for the baby
Nick do you want one I do sour apple or
cherry green green
Green is the green one good um dude yeah
I want
it
awesome that was crazy I wouldn't even
have eaten it after he sniffed it like
that
either I'll pick it up after go pick it
up you'll pick it up now no I won't yes
you will't it's a lollipop [ __ ]
Okay and we'll get ants ooh ants oh I'm
nervous you're messy you do that in your
room you get you get dirt you get dust
you get ants and then you sneeze all day
long and then you're the first one to
ask questions why are my allergies so
bad cuz you're a literal sounds like
dirt and lint ball and I lead a happy
life that's awesome thank you and you're
Mr Perfect [ __ ] shave your head
bald throw in a silver hoop ear I can
call you Mr Clean that's not that's who
you think you are right now and that's
not it yeah go clean up Mr Clean thank
you anyways guys really quick before we
jump into today's video I know I'm not
sure if you can see the tire behind me
cuz I don't know if like you can I don't
know if you see back there there's a
Tire in the trunk we popped our tire and
we had to SP bear on right now that's
why even though Matt can usually Drive
we're still in the garage yeah we had a
bad day for the starting little TRS
today but it's okay cuz we're going to
progress and have the most positive Day
Ever right in this car me like that I
think that might be like the worst thing
ever ruled on myself cuz of this
lollipop like a baby but yeah we popped
the tire today unfortunate event we
survived though we pushed through and it
was tough for all of us but we made it
here Nick shut the [ __ ] up all right
we're good right you're good I'm good I
who you're talking about the collective
unit of the three of us the car got it
you want the rest of this no God why
would I want the rest of it God for make
sure you dispose of that kindly maybe in
compost you're the weirdest person I've
ever like what I just don't want you to
be upset if he throws it like on the
ground or something moving forward happy
Friday welcome back to St tripet YouTube
channel it's your boy Nick Matt and
Chris today we are going to be
discussing I do that every single time I
eat one of those it's a whole thing
though now it's just like a mint shut
the the [ __ ] up it's not a mint it's
green apple you're green apple your
mom's green apple
CH I'm going to throw a sound effect in
right when I say that okay I don't care
you can you please don't
like it around yeah no none of that the
jury has consulted and we deem you
obnoxious like are you good are you okay
all right fantastic yeah you're being
weird as [ __ ] yeah if weird as [ __ ] is
French for that [ __ ] then
yeah you're a sicko anyways lunging
toward me with both Open Hands is crazy
wasn't both open hand went like my hands
kind of actually went back so I don't
know what world you're living in I
disagree it's like this speaking of I
don't know what world you're living in
cuz I'm the king of [ __ ] carrying out
get that in your mouth cuz I'm the king
of transitioning YouTube videos today
we're going to be talking about oh my
God this is so good like the king is a
stretch the I'm the yeah I'm the K the
king is a stretch Len the king can you
guys stop I'm the king you've done it
like four times probably transition
YouTube videos like really well because
I said I don't know what world you're
living in and today's topic is about
alternate universes so we're going to
discuss what world Chris thinks he's
[ __ ] living in oh my God I'm the best
in this topic we don't have any like set
plans of discussion I just want to know
like in an alternate universe do you
think like I think there's endless
possibilities and that's why I picked
this topic today because what we're in
this universe this is all we know this
matter this fiber this being this is who
you are right feel yourself make sure
you're like wow I'm here feel yourself
Matt feel yourself I'm good but moving
forward we're going to talk about Al you
feel yourself mat I'm good I don't want
to like come on we everyone he does he
already did it earlier I saw
him um but listen but in unison I feel
like we should all decide that match at
least feel himself a little bit there we
go there we go you're that was clean too
the way you did it like get off me an
ocean breeze so sorry oh and my breast
stinks I think what is this
for there's two options
oh
guys me and Nick watched the worst movie
ever tonight that's not the topic yeah
let's carry on to the actual topic
there's probably an alternate universe
out there where me and you left the
movies tonight skipping on our feet with
excitement of how much how good it was
no that's not true is that not crazy cuz
I think of alternate universe people are
like oh alternate universe what if
there's like an alien version of me and
he's like he can speak like a million
different languages and [ __ ] I just want
to know if we are living this exact
moment but like blue just a quarter of a
universe over and I know we talk about
this before so I know people are going
to be like do you get deja vu this is
the year of progression this is the year
of moving forward we are in an alternate
universe we are in this universe do you
think there's an alternate universe
right over where they're like oh my god
do you think there's an alternate
universe and yeah there is cuz we're in
it cuz that's the thing they're saying
oh aliens don't exist because there are
no planets out there with what like
humans need to survive who the [ __ ] said
there isn't like alien slug magma who
said There who who's to say there's not
like a magma slug on on Mercury right
now oh there's no their heat conditions
there aren't suitable for life for you
Mr President but what about the magma
slug Nick do you know what I mean though
who's to say you in your human shell
that there's not a magma slug planet
that just be in our universe though but
in one on one of our planets oh yeah I
was getting a little sidetracked when
people are thinking oh there's alternate
universes right and like what am I doing
in an alternate universe they're
thinking of an
obscure human activity that they cannot
do they're like what if there's me but
I'm purple and I'm like really good at
painting cuz I'm not purple and I can't
paint who's to say they're not playing
like an alien game that we can't even
imagine because we're not there cuz
people are like oh in an alternate
universe I'm probably like the best
fortnite player ever in an alternate
universe I'm probably so good at
painting in an alternate universe I'm
probably so good at cooking in all these
alternate universes people are probably
saying oh what if this happened this
happened this happened how about they're
probably playing alien version of
connect for croquet in a [ __ ] magma
field walking on magma Rock You Love
magma great word you think there's alien
Elderly Homes where they're just sitting
around [ __ ] watching movies together
as the elderly and drawing playing bingo
no they're playing tackle football
correct no not even they're playing God
knows what not even if we can IM more
int if we can imagine it it can't be
happening there could be anything else
we just can't even say our imagination
is Limitless what if our imagination
true what if our imagination is limited
think of the wildest thing you can think
of Matt tell me um an animal with wings
something elephant that can fly that
lives in Antarctica an elephant that can
fly that lives in Antarctica you just
thought of that so we can all
collectively us three and the viewer we
can all was that the first
time the fourth wall directly us three
and the viewer can imagine an elephant
so to speak flying in speak right cuz
you said it what if and I I could
contradict your thought oh what if it's
a cheetah flying in the desert it' be
like oh what if it's not that what if
it's this but if the fact that we can
speak it we can't even imagine the
things that could possibly be going on
yeah anything I say could be wrong cuz I
can think of it okay what if there's
something that they're doing that I just
can't even think of they could be it
could be a blood bath in a nursery home
and the last one standing get
resurrected back to life but also you
just imagine that see my point yeah
today when the guy changed our tire he
goes you want to hear a terrible joke he
said no I just remembered right now he
was like give you a dut for the trip
home do you remember when someone gave
me a free donut after accusing me of
stealing an apple juice yes what pisses
me off is when they got the car wash guy
with a spinning the arrow outside or
like dressed up as a little character
like a tire dressed up like a character
yeah like a hamburger come eat our
hamburgers no I want the person behind
the counter dressed up as what I'm going
to eat how happy would you be if you
went into like Dunkin Donuts so to speak
and a donut took your order how about
let's use AI for good use instead of AI
this AI that let's get AI donut hash
years to take my order of Dunkin Donuts
how thrilled are you I want a strawberry
frosted donut the strawberry frosted
donut replies coming right
up that's it and then you get your
strawberry frosted I feel like it would
be more thing like he'd kind of be like
I think he'd flirt with you if you order
exactly what he is oh my gosh true yeah
like I want a strawberry frosted donut
he'd be like like he kind of size you up
you want give me 3 hours I'm off of work
in a bit oh my God I don't get like the
whole like FL flag Arrow spinning cuz
it's like where am I going correct down
up flying upside down correct you're
just may those are the parallels to the
alternate universes you don't know where
to go we're pointing at universes I feel
like I just cracked the [ __ ] code I
think they spin it around and it just
aims continuously at the place and like
majority this way cuz it would just look
ridiculous it would look ridiculous if
they just kept like pointing it to the
left or like sh it you know what I mean
they got to give it a twirl they don't
they could just put it on a post and
leave no cuz the whole entertainment is
there like a ton of movement just to
make the sign more like whoa there's
something going on no put they need to
put this like bop it shake it spin it
twist it go in there go order a burger
imagine if there's a guy standing right
next to a sign that says car wash this
way and he holds like a Smoke N throws
it at his feet smoke and then he's gone
that would be
very that would be false
advertisement how how are you going to
get to the car wash no it's just an
arrow like it's not advertising that
you're CU if I see someone disappear via
magic I want to as well I'm ditching my
motorized vehicle hello I want to
teleport do you think in the alternate
universe there's like the stern
quadruplets no I can't believe like
painting walls is like a thing what like
how about you build the wall the color I
want that's a great Point not true at
all we should go to like a like a like a
a circus where there's like human
pretzels and all that stuff I'm good off
that again know what I'm saying like say
it again oh when was the last time we
went to a [ __ ] circus and why do you
recall it so fondly shout out big Apple
Man Big Apple Circus they made their way
around I'm going to leave the Cal
triplets behind and join the circus
that's a great that's a great little job
for you I'll tell you all about I'm not
even going to tell you guys what I would
do at the circus I'm just going to
pretend I'm I'm already there and I'm
putting on my show okay I already know
what you'd do I'm going to say or I have
an opinion on what I think you'd be
doing at the circus come one come all
welcome I can't have this video of me on
the internet I'm screaming I'm yelling
can't do that I just literally was going
to act a fool for another 30 seconds and
I thought digital footprint Nicholas Ser
what about in 5 years you're trying to
be taken more seriously and this video
comes up of you [ __ ] hooting and
holling about what you you're going to
do at the circus come one come all to
the Nick stolo show take your seats
you're going to want to sit right there
it's the best seat in the house I'm
going to get where where I'm going to go
there
I I'm going to put up my little ring and
I'm going to say I'm going to jump
through this ring right in front of you
you jump through that i' give you oh you
think I'm just going to jump through
this ring okay no what this ring is on
fire
and I'm going to light this ring a
Blaze
Blaze you're insane dude and I'm going
to head to the back of the room and you
may say Nick are you are you yeah thank
you don't hold it too far I need to
still see you know they're going to say
Nick are you going to go to the back of
the room and get like an oil or a soap
to slide through the hole oh my
God I'm going to say no pass me the
gasoline just dip myself in gasoline on
fire yes right we need that element of
risk oh he has a talent he can jump
through a tiny ring yes but can he risk
it all that's the question so I'm going
to dump myself in gasoline my hair is
dripping I'm covered in gasoline and I'm
going to boom pop through the ring come
out the other side a blaze
blades okay and then they're going to
have the the the there should be a kitty
pool that you got to like land sh I'm
going to land in the middle of a sand
pit it's going to look like it's the end
of me everyone's going to like no he's
gone forever no do you know what they're
going to do when everyone's worried
about me what roll out the tarps cover
me in the blanket I'm going to hit a
button fall through the Trap floor
underground fall through the Trap floor
underground I'm underground now these
people don't know they're worried about
me oh should I come back up onto the
tarp like at be like Oh I'm fine
everyone no you dropped down from the
ceiling no oh [ __ ] your for 5 years
that's when we queue the elephants Matt
they come in run around tiger whole
Show's going on where did that guy go
next show I do the same thing and I'm
just always back you're always thinking
oh my God this was his last show and the
carnival was around before social media
right so there's no buzz there's no
spreading the word oh Carnival man dies
Ring of Fire a blaze none of that
everybody thinks a the end of that act
they think they're the last about this
the end of that act oh my God you guys
want to hear something really sad don't
ruin my [ __ ] Vibe though no I won't
it's not it's chill okay there was um a
carnival like do you know how they take
it on the road yeah for all to see mhm
yes and they drive around on like trains
and stuff um one of the carnival trains
caught on fire and there was a bunch of
like exotic animals inside Chris what
it's chill it's chill yeah Len I'm
[ __ ]
listen listen the police caught up to it
and they opened the cargo like the
trailers and stuff and they're like
they're like pulling all the animals out
they got like zebras camels like all
these exotic animals are just like on
the side of the road somewhere and like
dude's like come on come on like cuz I
was watching the video cuz I saw a
burning train and the GU like get out of
there get out of there and I'm expecting
like human beings or something a [ __ ]
zebra jumps out and I was like huh I was
like what the [ __ ] and then another
another one and then he goes in to like
turn the the corner another one and then
I'm like I was getting nervous cuz I'm
like he's going to turn it's like a
clown car zebras are just
always video I was getting nervous I was
like he's going to turn the corner to a
[ __ ] lion if he's not careful so I
was getting really scared and then I saw
a video and then afterward it showed
like a montage of all the police
officers with like selfies with like the
zebras and the C amazing yeah like they
must have saved them all I take Nick for
more of a tight RPP guy M okay that's my
next year's act after the okay the ring
can't i' taken this this act around the
world and then I have a whole other life
ahead of me of a new act or or the seal
the [ __ ] beach ball on his nose seen
it done it what I never got was like
people that are like painters going on
like America's Got Talent and just like
speedily doing a painting it's like what
are you going to do paint again next
week hello I wasn't saying it like that
I was just thinking that's crazy that
they can do it so fast I used to hate
sorry I used to hate when people would
sing on America's God Talent I'm like
take it to American
Idol
oh that's what you were going to say
took the word right out of his mouth is
what he was implying really I thought he
was saying here's all my [ __ ] words
and you're just going to interrupt me
all the time was that it a little bit of
both okay yeah and what would you do Mr
Sir if the [ __ ] Carnival came to an
end there's no more boys and girls that
want to come watch the show are
you that that's me when they think my
ACT is all dried up and old no you don't
know about next year's circus I'm going
to be back on the road and better than
ever do you guys want to know if I if
the carnival didn't have Carnival Food
would it be as successful no nah yes
[ __ ] I can't focus on [ __ ] if I'm not
humming cotton candy down my throat okay
dude hello where are the Skittles I'm
trying to Taste the rainbow while I'm
looking at this man jump through a
blazing fire well I also want some
popcorn I want some like I Want Candy
Apples
candy I love candy apples idea fully
forget
remember that's the craziest thing
carnal act I'll take this memory right
here that you forgot and put it in your
head oh my God I here it is I remember I
knew you would go ahead here it is it's
crazy if I made a movie do you want to
know what it would be tell us all about
it he's gonna make a blueprint of the
[ __ ] um Bank and he's like robbing
the bank robbing the bank like and then
he's like steals all the money and then
he's like oh my God we're 20 minutes
into the movie we're thinking oh my God
this main character that we've been set
up to love and care about for the rest
of this movie is dead I'm not putting
this in the video it's the best movie
idea I've ever heard I don't even put in
the he goes into the bank all right I'm
going to cut that up but I'm going to
keep like bits and pieces all right guys
well thank you for watching today's
Friday video it was um it was it was the
ball welcome
Camal okay Nick had a rhyming outro
didn't expect that one to come out but
um things just happen naturally at the
circus the end of this video I'm going
to breathe out and go and then I'm going
to edit Flames take on the camera okay
no you're not we had a stressful day
today and then I'm happy to end it with
a good car video we're on the road to 6
million subscribers so hit the Subscribe
button down below hit six hit hit get a
hit the Subscribe you got it you got on
Nick you got it hit the Subscribe button
so we can take this circus on the
road okay you're not going to edit fire
I know you're not going to you're too
lazy you're too lazy
you're
[Music]
lazy