The end goal is achieving fully
autonomous driving. We allow automakers
to compete with Tesla by bringing to
market cutting edge autonomous driving
systems. We've raised over $und00
million. We'll see very very scalable
commercialization happen. But I would
say that starting a company felt like
drinking from a fire hose. When we were
pitching kind of like seemed like a pipe
dream, pure R&D for 2 years. There was
zero product development during that
time. Everyone thought it was crazy. But
we committed to that vision. We actually
carried out the research and we were
able to make that work very much all or
nothing and it might take a long time
for the world to adjust. My name is Li
Berninski. I'm the CEO of Helm AI. Helm
is an AI software company focusing on a
unified approach to autonomous driving
that goes all the way from L2 plus
through fully autonomous driving L4. We
have partnerships with companies like
Honda and we allow automakers to compete
with Tesla by bringing to market cutting
edge autonomous driving systems. The end
goal is achieving fully autonomous
driving and there are a number of
technological and commercialization
challenges along the way. These days,
one of the key areas that we're focusing
on is AI based simulation, leveraging
generative AI as well as our
unsupervised learning IP in order to
create a unified approach to solving
autonomous driving that essentially
unifies both partial automation and full
automation. First got interested in
self-driving cars and computer vision
during undergrad. So, I was part of the
UCLA computer vision lab while they were
competing in our grand challenges.
We're in the offhighway vehicle
recreation area.
So we just did our first autonomous path
tracking test and I just thought that
was a very exciting area and was
focusing on computer vision at the time
but decided to pursue mathematics in
academia for about 10 years with the
intent to come back to the space when it
was more mature because I saw that as
the key bottleneck to AI in the sense
that the biggest challenge in in reading
research papers in AI or computer vision
was ultimately a mathematical you know
just a question of do you understand
sort of the equations right so yeah in
some sense I looked at math as a tool to
be able to solve AI down the road the
goal was always to come back to the
autonomous driving space in the war
between humans and artificial
intelligence this is for 33-year-old
professional go gamer Lisa D Elon Musk
he plans to equip all new Tesla cars
with the hardware needed for full
self-driving capacity around I would say
2016 it became clear that the technology
was really taking off in terms of deep
learning. There was an inflection point
in where AI technology was going with uh
deep learning at the time and
simultaneously there was a very clear
opportunity that it was the right time
to jump into that space because what I
witnessed was a lot of companies making
certain decisions that I actually didn't
agree with. Right? It was such an
inefficient space at the time that it
was very clear to me that with the right
approach you can add a lot of value.
Right? because uh it's a strategy that's
kind of stood the test of time as
opposed to many companies that peaked
early and then died off or just kind of
ran out of money and what that meant was
that there was an opportunity. So after
my academic career moved back to
California to start
Helm Co was a very kind of a tricky time
for everyone obviously but also in in
the automotive market in particular
because it basically caused a halt in
production. The Corona virus is idling
one auto plant after another. All the
different auto factories and all the
automakers had to immediately start
dealing with that issue versus
everything else. And I think it caused a
bit of a delay in the deployment of
autonomous driving technology. But
beyond that, I mean, I would say quite
exciting. I mean, ultimately, I I I
don't know if it was like I think the
challenges were there, but they like
were outweighed by how exciting it was
to like start a company, you know, make
a truly uh deep tech bet in the space.
Our first 10 hires were basically all
just very, very strong researchers. Any
one of those people could have easily
walked away and done something else.
Some of those people even made certain
sacrifices of their academic career to
come work at Helm because they were very
excited about the vision. And I think
that helped us really mold the
engineering culture. When we were
pitching Helm 2016, right, unsupervised
learning was kind of like seemed like a
pipe dream almost, right? Um, but we
committed to that vision. We actually
carried out the research and we were
able to make that work. So that was uh,
you know, quite exciting. So I mean I
guess like there was the fact that you
know for 2 years we were essentially
developing that technology and there was
zero product development during that
time. So it's pure R&D for 2 years very
much all or nothing. Um so you know uh
obviously there's risk involved in that
but it was a very creative time so I I
mostly just appreciate
it. an Uber self-driving vehicle that
flipped. Uber is now banned from testing
its self-driving cars in Arizona.
Tonight, Tesla confirming this car was
in autopilot mode when it crashed in
Northern California
back in 2018. Kind of foray into
foundation models, even before that term
was coined. What we used that foundation
model for was to essentially build an
autonomous driving system that we were
able to show actually outperforms the
systems you were able to buy in the
market by pretty wide margin. So we
essentially conducted a series of tests
where we put our autonomous vehicle on
uh very steep and curvy mountain road
scenarios where essentially you have to
make very rapid driving decisions as far
as you know taking the various turns in
a challenging uh landscape. And we were
able to achieve much better
disengagement rates uh up to a factor of
200 better than what was out there on
the market. And that is how we got the
attention of some of the brand name
automakers in the world in the early
days. In the last couple of years, we've
been doing a lot of innovation in
generative AI and combining that with
our in-house technology which is called
deep teaching in order to close the gap
between AI based simulation and reality.
So essentially that means how do you
simulate driving data or driving footage
sensor data from driving without
actually having to get into a car. And
there are many advantages to doing that.
For example, very large fleets, right?
They can be useful for collecting data
in order to address difficult corner
cases for autonomous driving, but the
rate of occurrence of those corner cases
basically goes down exponentially as
your system improves. And so end up
actually paying exponentially more to
gather interesting data as you get
further into the development process. So
it's really not a good property. And
what simulation allows you to do is
generate all the interesting data
without actually having to deploy a
fleet. For example, Tesla that has a
very large fleet. Other automakers don't
have access necessarily to internal
fleets that are that large. So even if
they wanted to take the same approach as
Tesla, they would not be positioned to
do so. The only alternative to doing
that is essentially AI based simulation.
And until very recently, it wasn't
possible to generate highly realistic
simulation data. But that's very much
changing these days due to the advent of
generative AI and combining generative
AI with technologies like deep teaching
provides a highly scalable uh simulation
platform that allows you to essentially
deploy a virtual fleet so to say instead
of a real world fleet you're just uh
learning from existing data. So that's a
recent inflection point that we're
definitely you know proud to be part of
and contributing to. Vid Gen 1 and World
Gen 1 are foundation models for
generative AI simulation. Vid Gen is a
foundation model that creates highly
realistic video data from a multitude of
different cameras, essentially arbitrary
cameras, arbitrary locations. Worldgen
is a foundation model that takes a
further step in that it actually
simulates the entire autonomous driving
stack. You can actually use Worldgen to
technically to drive a car because it
does make predictions about what's going
to happen next. So if you input data
from your autonomous driving stack,
it'll tell you what's going to happen in
the next several seconds and that
includes the path that the vehicle
should take to perform certain actions.
You can actually use it to drive. So
it's technically uh you know a
self-driving system that not only
functions as a simulator or in a
simulator environment, it also can
function in the real world.
Yeah, basically how to actually convince
a customer, how to develop a
relationship with a customer in
autonomous driving space. Um, I think
there's kind of two important aspects at
least. So, one I think is, you know,
seeing is believing. Not only having
kind of marketing materials or video
demos, right? actually being able to put
somebody in a car and have that
autonomous car navigate unforeseeable
situations um I think is a very powerful
sends a very powerful message about the
robustness of the technology and the
product and secondly I think that
working on a production contract there
are going to be kind of other contracts
along the way right I think it's not
really possible for a major car company
to give a production contract to a
supplier as the first contract so
there's going to be some sequence of
contracts along the way and so I think
that being able to execute on those
contracts and deliver exactly what you
signed up to deliver is critical because
ultimately what you're entrusted with as
a supplier is providing not only safety
critical technology but technology that
is absolutely necessary to have in a
certain timeline because you're talking
about a production program that has to
launch in a particular year where you
know a lot of money is a lot more money
is invested into that than just the
money being paid to one supplier. So,
it's incredibly important to be able to
meet those deadlines. Maybe a third
thing I would add is just not only
demonstrating your current state of
where your technology is, but
demonstrating the the difference from
one time to another, right? So, being
able to show, okay, here's where we are
at this point in time. And then in a
month, we expect to be here, right? and
actually showing, you know, showing that
differential and allowing them to
measure not only kind of your position,
but also your velocity, so to say. When
it comes to technology
development, especially when you're
going after such an ambitious play like
autonomous driving, kind of requires
quite a lot of conviction. The hardest
part about it was just if you're a
researcher, I think that your key job is
really okay to to perform the research
and then you put it out there. And sure,
there is some marketing aspect to that,
but it's not nearly as significant, I
think, as what you have to do for a
company. And generally, as a startup
founder, you have to wear so many
different hats. People say when they go
to MIT, for example, that it's kind of
like drinking from a fire hose. I never
had that experience, but I would say
that starting a company felt like
drinking from a fire hose. You know, in
our particular case, I think we were in
some sense working against the grain in
that the vast majority of the funding
went toward companies taking a totally
different approach in that they were
pursuing pure play 4. And you know, when
I first started to engage people about
the fact that we're going to really
focus on partial automation as the key
market, you know, everyone thought it
was crazy. But I I think that it
basically just emphasizes more kind of
this this notion of the importance of
like having grit or something because
you can't expect what you think to be
the predominant world view and it might
take a long time for the the world to
adjust right like I think we only
started seeing signs of the world
adjusting to our point of view some
number of years into the company right
maybe four years in 5 years in right but
then every year the our position has
improved prod not only as a function of
the technology and the product but also
because our strategy was adapted to a
certain worldview that we believed would
essentially would eventually materialize
and that is now happening.
[Music]