well welcome welcome back and yes the
rumors are true Matt got a
haircut the rumors are true so did you
though yeah but we don't care once you
get a haircut then it's just like oh we
can't wait big reveal do you I got this
like all in one go you're not going to
like the way that taste have you had one
yet nope give us a live you're not going
to like that
flavor for
bird it's yummy let me try it again why
are you pluging your nose then it's
yummy
I forgot when you chug you need your
nose hold on is that true well you got
to breathe no [ __ ] way yeah oh no no
no we can't have you drink this though
if you're going to burp a lot oh yeah
cuz Matt doesn't like it no I'll just
burp straight burp police that's my
badge no burping oh God if you look
around and see it oh
God oh my God almost died
what would we have done if you just
threw up all over your there just you
were just covered in puke we not even
five minutes was think vomit the other
day I bent down like over like to grab
something
uh-huh oh I like I'm like it's like um
an uhuh like keep
going okay telling a story who's this no
but the other day I went I bent down to
grab something and as I grabbed it I
like leaned forward with my face like
down I I went like that almost threw up
on the floor wow I've like almost puked
a lot in my life like there's I have
vivid memories of just like my mouth
filling with puke and then like going
back
down keep that to yourself yeah there's
like dogs that are working like N9 to
FES there really is like can9 dogs
they're working 9 to five yeah what's
the he's like hiding on I wonder what's
like the insurance policy or like the
payroll on that oh is that mint yeah
want to kiss what what do can9 dogs
get paid can I tell you something when
do they get paid are you serious ma they
don't get paid they're dogs through
extra treats and
snacks like obviously they're working
like did he expect them to get money
imagine like that's the currency like if
they get a five star dog do once it
receives a check thank you I'm headed up
going to the bank no you go to the bar
with some friends and drink I was a
check idiot what would you guys do if
you like got a letter in the mail and it
just said from Willy Wonka and then you
opened it and it was a golden ticket you
said that so like so like um like you
were part of the movie and then it said
from oh wait they don't go in the mail
they don't go in the mail they're in the
chocolate yeah yeah and like this is
real life like if I even if they mailed
me it's like a piece of chocolate and it
has the golden ticket with it and it
says like on it and it says like it says
pending immediate arrival at the Willy
Wonka Factory not going you're going to
get there and going be a bunch of naked
old
men what and then right when you read it
trap it says right when you read it it
says immediate invitation to Wily
Wonka's chocolate factory must freak
your [ __ ] upon arrival and you have to
get there and immediately freak your
[ __ ] what like what would you do what if
really Wonka like you got a Golden
Ticket said upon arrival you must IM
immediately freak your [ __ ] I'm not
going like I'd go probably I'm not going
to freak my [ __ ] with Wonka I well
willly Wonka OG I'm talking like way
back but that makes it even more he has
willly in his name oh my God I'd be
pissed if my name was Willie but anyways
you you bloody Willie I'd go if they
brought me straight to like the
Everlasting Gob stoer you're yeah of
course you want an everlasting Gob
sopper what's really the difference
between Oompa Loompas and Smurfs if
we're really talking about bread and
butter here at the end of the day okay
when it comes down to it Oompa looma
Smurfs what the [ __ ] the difference
Smurfs work harder and they're not
lazy o yeah I disagree well no The
Smurfs movie we really don't see them in
their natural life because the whole
show they're escaping New York oh that's
true yeah so like come on the Big Apple
gargam I would like to see them in their
natural habitat y what's his face is bro
garam yeah I just said his name why' I
forget I don't know Gargamel's wand is
like so
perfect wait hold on hold on wait wa
kind of sus that he made Smurfette as
well there was all guy Smurfs he goes we
need one of these little [ __ ] in blue
you know what I mean in a girl we need
one of these blue little [ __ ] in a
girl form like what was gar that's kind
of sus you want to know what I don't
like what going out in public and seeing
couples and somebody sitting on each
other's lap or like making out go get a
room get a go I love it I look at them
I'm like hm I think if couples Nick what
I'm thinking if couples were making out
outside I think they expect them they
expect themselves to be like this is us
this is us like out on the street we're
here I think that more people instead of
being gross out being like Oh what are
they doing when you see a couple making
out you go like
this stare into their soul okay and
don't look away and then if they stop
kissing and they like look around I want
you to look at them like
this don't break eye contact at all just
if people are making out outside why
stare at them why think of how awkward
it'd be you're making out with somebody
no I'm awkward I feel awkward you're
making out with somebody on a bench in
public you're thinking oh there's no
consequences to these actions you turn
and someone's staring at you you can't
continue to make out with somebody in
that scenario no you
can't
a okay dude just reset the camera if you
get a second yeah screaming like that
was a crazy choice that I just made I
agree oh person right
there why would you say that cuz there
was a person yeah I was expecting a face
right here in front of me behind do you
know the um what's it called what was I
going to say oh the scenes in the in the
in like Marvel hero movies where it like
slow MOS hero movies where it like slow
MOS and something crazy happens like
like and then like you see like like the
camera like swings in and like there's
all these parts happening whatever like
and then it like it keeps going through
we can provide to the conversation the
second you get to the [ __ ]
point isn't it crazy we met so long ago
[ __ ] dude what like I just knew
you boy do we have news for you I know
like I just knew you guys since the
beginning like for real for real don't
touch me like for real we knew each
other like since the jump yep like I was
[ __ ] my pants next to you okay
that's real I pissed the bed we
shared there we go I pissed on you at
some point for sure yes sir think about
the amount of gross things we've done
with each other super
close don't say that oh my
God that's so gross like bro y for real
like when we were like imagine like I
remember having like when I have
nightmares I do it like dogs do like you
know when dogs like shake or try to rub
in their sleep I do like I'll have a
nightmare I'll be
like I have Disney Channel ass
nightmares you know when they have a
nightmare Disney Channel yeah I'm
like in my night you know I like I'm a
sound asleep like jolting out of bed I
feel like people who are having
nightmares are waking up way too
peacefully for like what they're doing
in their sleep imagine getting up from a
nightmare just getting up and doing a
task right away no like when I wake up
out of the middle of my sleep like a
nightmare or something I have to lay
down and like really no matter I have to
check my surroundings no but imagine
someone has a nightmare imagine someone
has a nightmare they get up turn their
light on and like start like going right
out the house or something [ __ ] like
that's weird weird I can't even shower
I'll like put soap in my hair and go
imagine dude flash drives were OG can
you stop I miss gross and annoying gross
and annoying no I miss needing a oh my
God I missed shopping for school when I
had like the list of requirements and
needs I hated that [ __ ] that was the
worst no like sometimes it was fun
required needs what a crazy way to say
requirements adding a word that doesn't
belong in the sentence do you guys ever
wake up and like it takes you a full
minute to like realize like whose body
you're checking into like I'm like
there's a person right there by the way
he's like walking to our car it's kind
of scary looking okay no he's good it's
good it's good just saying he was like
walking like really slow to our car but
go ahead continue oh do you ever wake up
and it takes you a minute to be like I'm
Nick I'm in this bed oh I'm here again
I'm here again no like like I always
forget who I am until I no and then I'm
like okay I'm Nick this is my bed this
is my life like I wake up I get no no
like when I'm asleep I'm in such a
sleep when I wake up I see things I'm
just something else no like when I first
wake up I just see things what do you
see like just things that aren't
actually there like make them up in my
head come on
give me a little detail
okay Nick oh my God that sounds like
when SpongeBob had like all the statues
of him creating like the the music Nick
can you listen to what I have to
say doesn't it put the clip put the clip
the clip and put it in there like like
I'll look and I'll open my eyes and I'll
look at like the fold in the blanket and
I'll think it's like someone's head or
like a leg okay like and it just freaks
me out and it takes me I have to like
squint my eyes and go like this and then
like look again and then I realize it's
actually just like what it is but like
sometimes like my my brain when I first
wake up and open my eyes is like
calibrating figures and that's why I
tell Nick when I sleep in his room he
has to move a stuffed animal cuz it's
like an otter stuffed animal but it
looks like like it's just like brown fur
and long and like like kind of like wide
like it's like this and brown I'll open
my eyes and I'll look and I'll think
it's like a rat if I first wake up and
I'll scar you want to how people like go
to bed Nick give me this [ __ ] bottle
I know there's water in it stop blowing
in my ear [ __ ] I knew there was water
in it so most right so did every viewer
what everyone knew there was water I
thought it was empty just stop blowing
in it [ __ ] I'll start a band
back here give me the you yes I will
going home good night see you later Guy
what's it like being tough you took my
roll good job oh tough guy see a tough
guy good job going home you standing
right there like a [ __ ] idiot if you
want to view Paradise give me my
sunglasses now you don't have a choice
beg for them not doing that give me my
sunglasses now beg for it okay I'll
literally go home you idiot so why is it
me my sunglasses now it's not a one-way
Street it's a two-way street and look
look
look what I was saying before you
decided to be a big tough guy not a
tough guy okay how when people like wake
up in the morning Nick blow in that
bottle again and I'll put this
highlighter through your [ __ ] throat
actually so [ __ ] obnoxious and you're
doing it right here in my [ __ ] head
you're in my head get out of my [ __ ]
head I wonder how how you see yourself
sometimes let me get my Google gaga
translator so I can understand what
you're saying all these [ __ ] and
moans
okay you're [ __ ] idiot you're
actually stupid it's just funny cuz you
could be
like radar you're way more
more [ __ ] in the front seat oh
GL oh and you have ugly hairline at
least when the glasses come off me I
don't look terrible you know what I mean
the hat comes off and oh it's Doom time
for you [ __ ] Doom time Doom time
yeah that's how I feel when I look at
you you are doom you're literally
impending doom as a human being
impending mean impending is like
foreshadow like it's going to come like
in the future like it's about to be
there it's about to come right there see
par such little kid you're such a little
kid so what you're saying is Nick's got
time
baby near
future oh how could I stay mad at
you guys this isn't funny this isn't
funny at all and you're being obnoxious
actually unfortunately when when people
go to bed or first wake up you know how
like you have to lay there like oh I'm
so tired I just can't open my
eyes yeah
yeah
sh yep yep when people say that when
people say that what's going on you know
what I mean like when people are like oh
I'm just like I'm just so tired I can
barely keep my eyes open or oh I'm just
so tired I just can't open my eyes you
know what I'm talking about mhm you know
what I'm talking about
yep I kind of have the opposite
sometimes where it's like I'm so tired I
catch myself just sitting there looking
at the ceiling like this with my eyes
wide open I don't do that I don't do
that
that I'm not laughing I'm not
laughing okay only one of us is tell
only one of us is telling the truth you
had a rosy red nose you look so
cute 10 times funnier don't slap don't
slap my elbow get your elbow out of my
[ __ ] space it's not in your space
John Cena get out of here right here
this is my space elbow is in my space
elbows in my space take this and clean
yourself off you're
dirty
insane like we need to
that thank God I'm in
park that's all I got to say CH the type
of guy to complain that his dut has a
hole in
it get it cuz the donut comes previously
cut or DEH hold whatever you want fact
yeah my ex claimed that his
great-grandfather invented D donut holes
in which donut hes who in do you like
donut holes did the donut you like them
well where I'm from we call them
munchkins just like you get out of here
was his name Hansen gregory no a that'd
be cute like if when he died like put
little munchkins on his
Tombstone Chris you're the weirdest
person what I saw a photo of his grave
when you Googled him and I feel like if
I invented like such an everlasting
thing I've on a little munchkin on top
okay well there's no [ __ ] munchkins
on his grave yeah clearly cuz up you
bring them you're an idiot how am I an
idiot if I invented the munchkin put a
little munchkin on My Grave and then
what about the person that invented a
dildo there just stick dildo on top of
their n cuz that's like not like that's
kind of private okay munchkins anyone
can have enjoy munkin okay sure I mean
it's up to them I don't want to judge
all personally I think it's a bad look I
agree but I think a cute little munchkin
like a powdered munchkin I actually I
didn't invent them but I wouldn't mind
I'm going to invent something big and
then I want to my grave like
what I'm going to invent Nick's biggest
smile you can't put that on your grave
idiot I could put a picture of Nick
smiling why would they put a picture of
Nick on Your Grave cuz I made him the
laugh the hardest but that makes no
sense I think you should get like you
know when like people are swimming don't
get water in their nose yeah like the
thing that pinch their nose yeah get
that in duct tape and then put that in
your grap like [ __ ] takes you out
that's kind of
rude back up a little
bit a lot the camera can't even see you
at this point just locking eyes at me
it's freaking I just love you Nick I'm
enchanted by
you here goes the Swift piece here they
go oh my God can you take those yellow
glasses off so I can see your big blue
eyes take that hat off and give the
world the void of that forehead
I know wasn't going to happen
so
yes did you just blow your nose in your
hands I blew up I blew I sucked up you
blew up
yeah that wasn't even
funny
wasn't even
funny hey he blew up hey I blew up I
just came up I'm big now I'm a big shot
I need to tast you bad though yeah I can
tell what's your favorite Nick edit my
favorite stop talking both you I'm
cutting this out my favorite Nick edit
is the one of the Hawaii video when he's
leaving the restaurant yes I love that
one mine's from the prison video when he
has the OG mullet and he's like
walking you need to literally you know
know what I'm talking about I don't I
don't you just actually stuck your
fingers in my
tank me like [ __ ] it I can on my balls
like
weirdo all right guys thank you for
watching this week's Friday video we're
going to be back at you Monday with a
podcast episode Wednesday for some sort
of video Friday for a car video and we
will see you guys each of those weeks
just want to let you know to go down
there and like that this video If you
like this video and then you're going to
be so close to the Subscribe button so
you should definitely click that as well
while you're down there and also me Matt
and Chris just and while you're down
there get back
up cuz you never want to stay down and
then me man Chris just did a re-release
of some of our old merch which sold out
shockingly in under 30 minutes and when
our team was shipping out the merch I
slipped some signed sticky notes that
said random things into a random eight
orders so make sure you're checking to
see if you got one of my sticky noted
merch packets and go to the description
and save our website
www.o.com the only place to get real
stolo merch everywhere else is fake
anyway remember that website and get
ready because we are going to be
dropping a whole lot more this 2024 and
we are on the road to 6 million
subscribers so go hit that subscribe
button get us a 6 mil quick and then
we'll get a merch drop going for you
guys we're super excited about what 2024
has in store and we'll see you next
week Miss me yeah you miss me and all
the things that we did we said we going
to travel from the island to Madrid we
had a lot of plans but they
all because of but it's okay cuz I'm
moving different don't be saying when I
post with other [ __ ] for my brothers