okay we're live
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things
basically it's something that's gonna
put a bit it's like you talk about like
what would put a Victorian era child
into a coma and if you don't know what
the Victorian era is
because I don't even really know I just
think far away I'm gonna google it
because I don't know what it is
we're going to talk about things and it
basically means like what would just
like absolutely flabbergast and over
stimulate like Victorian era and British
history the period between approximately
1820 and 1914. so old as [ __ ] yes yes
what would it what would do it for you I
know exactly I have one I have a list
Bluetooth I saved Bluetooth is my
[ __ ] my eyes so I don't understand
how the [ __ ] anybody like imagine going
way back in when and being like yo at
some point there's they didn't even like
know like phones exist that's why we
have to go broader you have to go like
you have to be very specific Wi-Fi no
you have to be so specific
drive-throughs no hold on everything was
a big deal for them imagine taking one
oh the average like that Thanksgiving
every night they took the tomatoes from
the farm their own backyard and
harvested dinner and carrots now imagine
this that kid you bring them to the
Avatar ride of Disney's Magical Kingdom
holy [ __ ] the wait in line they get look
at the big blue like screen Avatar they
probably think they're like actually
like and then they get there and they're
like oh we're turning you into your
avatar and then you're like oh my God
you're in I would take on the Avatar The
Minion one
the minion right you literally become
the minion they turn you into a minion
and then you walk into that bro they
never turn me back no like I feel like
what up minions I'm still a minion what
do they say like that [ __ ] that was so
crazy come on DC blue
okay how about this dunkaroos I haven't
even in my life ever had a dunkaroo
neither have I but imagine like giving
them just like hey
you probably like had those things they
eat probably like Nate loves them oh my
God he gets a birthday cake one
but imagine there's chocolate girls a
dunkaroo I'd be like oh this is like
absolutely terrible I'd throw up I
almost just throw up imagine like I
don't think how much money would it take
you to eat a dunkaroo what uh do it for
free yeah I try one try one I feel like
like with the time you don't know what I
don't get it's really like
dunkaroo a dunkaroo who comes up with
these names bro what are they well it's
like you dunk it in and Rue
like maybe it's like Scooby Snacks like
oh like Scooby like you're embarrassing
yourself like Nick cut that out for your
own like for your own sake
oh my God record
where'd they all go they're on the side
of the side on the curb that's a funny
thing too a curb rat at the dumpster
ratty rat record
there's like seven of them there's none
no
we need to bring cheese one day
that actually works
I'm being so frail she's worse let's
come here with a bunches like anything
works on them oh my God
hold on right there
there's like three of them
where right over there
you guys are tripping
right there oh the other direction oh my
God that was the size of a [ __ ] cat
dude
okay we're gonna move on okay how many
how many rats are in your 100 foot
radius right now take a guess 100 foot
radius 100 including underground
everywhere Chris like up down left right
I don't want to say like 500 or 600
that's crazy I'd say like maybe 50. 50.
like I'd say ease we're usually in like
200 range has to be 200 range like are
we including like dead ones and servers
and stuff yeah 100 foot radius 100 feet
radius oh 100 foot radius is way less
than I thought that's really scary I
think 50 is honestly a great answer 50
yeah it's on the money thank you
stop being a baby 100. Nick look I'm
sitting in my car and I can count seven
like eight feet away well they keep
going back and forth yeah
seven Max then they're just going around
they'll love them right there they're so
look at it yeah
oh my god dude what is going on is that
raccoon in that trash where
something moves in the trash something
moves in the trash somebody go over
there and throw something in it
something yeah I'm the classic horror
movie that'll get sucked in by the
[ __ ] do it the trash boy jangler or
whatever the [ __ ] it could be what was
it what would the trash killer's name be
the dumpster Destroyer that's a good one
the dumpster District there's something
in there okay let's we're off topic
Defender we're off the dumpster
Destroyer anyway Nick I'm putting your
window back up that's why it's cold an
in-depth skincare routine oh like
imagine showing them like all your steps
like can I be honest I hate like I never
I don't get it I feel like if there's
that many products and like like people
aren't that much different for like one
person to need these eight in this
person correct correct that's correct
it's like hold on another thing that I
don't get though is like a good
threesome I don't know if I'm wrong bro
something in that [ __ ] track I don't
know if I'm wrong you're freaking me out
sorry I don't know because I'm not like
I don't do makeup right yeah but what I
don't get is like makeup routines and
like watching someone else's for advice
because I don't do my own makeup so I
don't get it but like like I feel like
if I watch like some girls like 20
product in-depth makeup thing I'm not
gonna use it it's like the same as
right in the light and then he scurries
away like it's like you're watching Bob
Ross paint on a canvas but you couldn't
you couldn't do it you couldn't
replicate what I'm saying is like like
like if like if some girl is like a 20
step thing there's no way if you did the
exact same 20 steps like no person would
look identical is that I guess so
because everybody it's not like guys
basically look like there's it just be
like the same like like your face would
look how their face looks with that man
you want to know another thing I really
don't understand what and I didn't learn
I don't know [ __ ] about I don't
understand when people like when I was a
little kid not like a little kid but
like when I was like nine nine ten
little kid okay but I think little kids
you could be like three five toddler
five you know I'm thinking I'm a little
bit grown up but I'm not a grown-up
I'm a little boy 12 minute right section
let's just get there whatever it is like
nine to like eleven okay and I'd like
wash my face with like a bar or so
and then like last year
that's nice what are you talking about
nine but it's like I remember washing my
face with a bar of soap and I think mom
walked into the bathroom or I don't know
maybe it was a friend that was over but
they were like don't don't do that like
don't wash your face to the bar soap
it's not good for you but like the way
that
different about this than this
yeah what's the difference why can't I
wash here with a bar soap but I can wash
here you're so correct but also things
what do we also think about like you
could go like this so correct you were
like yes look look I'll use this I get
hair hair's done I'll use this has a
tattoo on it right if I go like this and
I go like that like that bird ain't all
the way over there you know what I mean
my skin moved because I just like moved
it you know what I mean like your skin
all the way around is in the exact you
know what I mean whoa hold on do that
again like if you just pull your skin
like I could go like this right now it
looks like his arms on like the back
half of my arm but my Skin's just moving
you know what I'm saying so it's like
for your skin your skin on your face
can't be that different from the skin on
like the back of your neck and you're
putting soap and you put soap on your
back you're going like
the back your neck no I kind of cut the
soap off here
you don't like go behind your head I go
way behind yeah I know I get behind I
guess but do you know what I'm saying or
did I just sound crazy how much money to
get flip-flops right now
toe put cheese in between all of your
toes except for the one that already has
like the flip-flop hole and walk around
here for like for like for like two
hours you guys don't understand that
ratzer is gonna eat whatever Crumbs are
around we don't need cheese to attract
them like it could be how much it's
classic though
like realistically we're at McDonald's
right so they're getting like a little
piece of McDonald's bun or some good
provolone I agree well they don't use
okay okay
the least amount of rats Chris listen
the least amount of rats possible to get
you would you stand over there in a
circle of breadcrumbs or a circle of
American cheese breadcrumbs guaranteed
the bread I feel like I'd be terrified
regardless okay but how much how much
money how much money is how much money
to walk around and flip-flops right
there I feel like they'd be too scared I
feel like they'd be too scared to do
something about it you think there's no
way a rat would I feel like they're all
like looking
such a dumpster Searcher you see that
they don't team up and like nibble at
your toes too oh I don't like that
okay we're gonna go back we'll just
absolutely Gob smack a child
the entire show The Masked Singer
like imagine trying to explain to them
like like oh it's they're singing but
it's like when they talk it's like a
manipulated voice and then when if they
do bad and the other singers do better
than them we take their mask off and
it's somewhat of like high Fame and then
and then other people are trying to
guess who it is based off yeah and
there's like a panel that are also just
celebrities I think they think it's way
more serious than it is they'd be
thinking executions the second the mask
is off get them also speaking of wow
yeah you're going speaking up what about
like sliding in speaking of TV shows oh
God yeah they'd be like what do you mean
imagine like a full episode of Dance
Moms and they watch fire hydrants like
Abby Lee fire hydrants we just have to
walk hours to the well to get water and
now what are you so what are you telling
me that the hoes in the corner yeah but
imagine Abby Lee Miller and the dance
moms too like they had to watch an
episode I love it I feel like an episode
of SpongeBob would [ __ ] them up more
than enough the gorilla one no the the
dream episode
that one's ridiculous that one almost
put me in a coma when I was a kid yeah
it was crazy okay I gotta go through a
purple robe I have another one weird as
[ __ ] imagine portraying to like a group
like they're I'm gonna put you in the
setting they're they're sitting down for
their annual or daily Feast right
they're ready for like Papa to bring
back like the bread that he got from the
village and you know like Mom's
home-cooked meal what are we talking
about Victorian children like I still
don't get what we're talking about like
it's kind of just like
like old old generation so long ago like
so long ago what would shock that person
so much if you just like that's from
today's agent if you just put it out and
expect to like acted normal what about
like a car tire I was getting to one
though
you know what I'm saying like I was in
the middle of like getting of course
you're getting the one but I'll put it
in the present I feel like LED lights
would [ __ ] me oh my God like a strip of
light no lights that would just change
like alter a little bit like imagine
those white strip lights and they go
pink how [ __ ] amazing they think
they're aliens whoa dude yeah like you
switch it and they keep going they're
like
yeah
listen to color you probably get
beautiful colors that they haven't even
thought about yet then you click the
button but also behind your back to what
I was saying imagine like that they're
sitting down for a family dinner dad
came home with the bread from the
village mom just cooked the meal and
instead you're like nah I actually have
a meal for you guys instead
Wendy's four for four is for everyone in
the brown paper bags like a brown paper
bags
at Wendy's where's the profit mark four
things like that how much are you paying
for I feel like Wendy should also throw
in a dollar to eat they should do a five
for five and give me a a single Benjamin
right is Benjamin 100 he's 100 he's 100
yeah we want Washington like imagine
like you get like four things and then
like a dollar bill what about like an
aluminum sign like a big sign like a big
sign like a big oh my God imagine from
like a Macy's and like the M fell off
the building you gave them like the M
from a Macy's sign they would think it's
like the the [ __ ] Almighty they do
like Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy that's
probably how we feel with like
old [ __ ] hey but I also think if we went
back there and they had like gave us
like a thing to churn butter I'd have
the same reaction if like I gave them no
I'd be like that's classic That's a
classic
the ability to go into history they
don't have the ability to go in the
future imagine all your memories about
churning butter or just don't have it
right right and then you show up with
like the knowledge you have with a
blender and they show up with the
knowledge they have with a butter
churner wow what would your thoughts I
never really thought like they're
creating butter and then you don't I
don't even know like I hate butter what
about a petting zoo
oh no I feel like they had I feel like
it was more of like they had no they had
like their goats in there that was a
terrible one for me yeah [ __ ] it's okay
no I think they just do more confused
why the animals don't belong to them or
why they what about just clothes
no they had clothes no like clothes
nowadays I have the best one like
imagine getting imagine giving like
like sterniological smash no like a like
one of those well sure but like a like a
like a
NASCAR and it's like you give it to them
NASCAR you know what I mean why'd you
say it like yeah like that was crazy
let's get like getting like NASCAR you
know what about pop rocks oh my God oh
my God they're like like actions we
should do a reenactment of something
like I have to pretend that I'm like
this is papa no give me no I can't know
what it is like yeah okay you have to
Blind Side me okay so you're that I have
an accent I feel like I should no no
just leave it classic okay picture this
one would you do
hey I'm gonna bring you to a super fun
activity that we do all the time come
with me laser tag you're walking no no
oh my God
be gone you think you die correct laser
if everyone's drawing these guns at me
and beans
I was gonna say a ball I'd be like a
ball pit like like a pit of like the
colorful like I feel like laser tag is
way Crazy Light beams of Fire coming
from a gun like the noise
oh my God and I like when someone shoots
your vest and it's like I think oh my
God yeah no that's severe like right
like severe trauma get like a lot of pop
rocks and like
see how many we can eat all at the same
time yeah okay I'm gonna order them okay
all right
okay hold on I got a couple more that I
want to say a Chuck E cheese animatronic
oh my God don't scare me what about that
ticket muncher
um
the ticket muncher is the OG Munch bro
what about like slang just in general
like imagine I walked out to like like
like someone from that time and it was
just like that's cap oh like you're fit
is your captain like lingo yes like oh
your fits eating up like you're slaying
right now they'd be like they'd be like
what the [ __ ] did you just call me I'm
not slaying I'm not good I'm not in the
battlefields great Heavens
great my great pippy was slain three
weeks ago correct they get all defensive
I feel like oh so you're eating he's
gross maybe like no they'd be like oh we
already got oh my God that's a big
chunker
oh no we already got dinner for like the
week yesterday like they think that it's
like like slaying the animals oh my god
dude that was crazy I meant more like
like like like like something simple
like how do you think they feel about
parking like when pigs fly like who's
the first person to go when pigs fly
who's like they're kissing
what am I missing
oh they froze I'm gonna get it on camera
[ __ ] this [ __ ]
they see it
he's right on the edge right there
see him he just jumped away I don't know
if y'all saw that I think we're kidding
there's another rats no we're legit
seeing every single rat in the world
you're getting out to check this yeah no
I'm not bro I'm gonna literally put this
right here in hope I don't care
and go check I don't know you check I'm
not going out Chris man I bet you a
million dollars is just fine all you'd
have to do is step out and double check
[ __ ]
oh I have to sneeze I don't know what I
don't get and this is gonna like
actually sound really really like maybe
smart
tell me I'm confused like do you know
shut the [ __ ] up Nick
sometimes Nick's voice just like the way
he speaks
it kills I was interested wait to hear
what I have to say
do you know the amount of things in this
world that are like disposable you can
throw them away get rid of them yeah why
are disposables called disposables and
when I say this what the [ __ ] is a
disposable like a vape or like a Oh I
thought you meant like when I say
disposable everyone's like oh a vape
like a disposable I thought of the
camera people called it I thought of the
disposable camera but think of how many
things are disposable really correct
like a tissue could be a disposable shoe
an ass wipe how do you think they felt
about
and that's why it's a disregard how do
you think they disregard what are you
saying disregard unguard [ __ ]
I'm on that same [ __ ] thing fencing
can we fence for a video oh my God yeah
okay why why is it fencing more known I
saw that [ __ ] Wednesday and I was like
damn I need to get a piece of that
yeah like it's so like Ugh
a sword fight but no harm can we defense
like absolutely I would mess you up all
right let's find out sensing place and
try to do it we should fence in a room
full of fences and make it like a cage
so we're fencing through the fences the
fencing fencers
they fell through seat warmers
oh my God they must have thought they
were on fire
I bet you they did for sweet warmers
back then they probably got like a large
like watering tin they filled it with
wood the watering too not a bucket or
like a pan a watering it filled it with
wood furthermore the watering tips
and then quickly flipped it over that
fire just heated them up I don't think
they just I think they just sat on cold
I don't think they attempted to I agree
warm anything they're like dogs our dogs
knew do we just cat dogs or dogs been
around oh my god when did dogs come into
play like I look at this movie they say
like horses and [ __ ] like did they have
just like let's just Google it when was
the first dog like did they have like a
boxer Did they know the breeds
they have dogs
that's a good question don't act like I
was crazy when did I feel I feel like
dogs are new the earliest known dog like
fossils came from Europe but DNA Studies
have implicated East Asia and the Middle
East now a large DNA study is lining up
with the fossils suggesting dogs
originated in Europe 90 000 to 32 000
years ago 19
000 not 90. gotcha see so like I feel
like they're new
is
well for like a [ __ ] living species I
guess like that's new
I feel oh my God you wanna know what
could be insane to think about there
could be a wild animal right now that is
like totally normal to have as a pet in
like 100 years
my burp smells spicy
and all the things