I feel like my hurl that's not good yeah
why I don't know it feels like soda no
bro
and then what you're saying how you miss
me
I got a tattoo y'all my head this isn't
like I had special I'm not a fashion
trend for those that are gonna like make
yourself I don't think anyone thought
that was a [ __ ] fashion you have no
idea what people will say sometimes when
someone thought that the X from when we
went to an event and you're you got the
X on your hand for being yeah they
thought I was just like what did they
think it's not a tattoo that's a dad
thought as well
dad called me and I was like did Matt
get it okay dad like but let's think no
I actually talked to that on the phone
this actually reminds me dad called me
and he goes he goes oh my God I almost
had a heart attack I looked quickly when
I watched the new video about the X on
your hand was uh was a tattoo and I go
Dad if I was getting hand tattoos I'd
think it out a little more than just an
X yeah because really what would you get
I said golf clubs that said my dad's the
best golfer across my Knuckles and he
was laughing oh yeah I miss you Dad
what are you doing if you go to a new
food place and you try a new food you're
like it's so good and you try it for the
first time
and you're allergic to it like deathly
getting an EpiPen and hitting my guy
with it well I don't think I'd know I'm
allergic till I leave the restaurant if
I'm being fully honest you're definitely
allergic to something like that it's
gonna hit the second year no I think I'd
eat it first and then like really let it
sit and then I wouldn't know that I'm
allergic to my throat is closed
do you think restaurants have epipens
like in case uh really no but they got
phones I can call the police no they
should they should have epipens need to
be like prescribed they should also have
like time like things I'm pretty sure
that you can't just go and buy one can
you yeah you can I could go buy an
EpiPen I think you can tell your doctor
I want to buy epipens like yeah yes but
I couldn't right now well it doesn't
matter because like if you go into like
yeah the hair if you're going to
anaphylactic shock like you need an
EpiPen you have to end up at the
hospital so you have to call 9-1-1 and
all ambulances and fire trucks I'm
pretty sure have to have it you wanna
know what I think they should invent at
least two but what I'm saying is like I
couldn't go get an EpiPen right now so
like [ __ ] call the doctor I don't
know yeah I'm not doctor I'm not Dr
Chris restaurant thing I'm like yeah I'm
not Dr Chris what would I think that
they should invite her shut up [ __ ] you
yo you just interrupted me like being
all sad on yourself oh whatever
yeah it's a bummer
bummer's crazy yeah Chris can you go
ahead and see what you're gonna say how
about you say something oh fresh clean
shape
since when dude don't talk to talk to me
all cute like that like I don't need you
to be talking about my little eye look
what would y'all do if you were on Earth
when the asteroid no hold on wait go
back
to the next thing about the EpiPen in
restaurants I think that they should
invent a machine called The Hacker
and it's a big machine that every
restaurant's required to have and you
can decorate it like to your restaurant
like say you're not really very
important yeah so you have like a really
floral New Era Vibe like Cafe
like it's the new era like it's the new
guy guitar
it's youth it's fresh God forbid you
finish
Jesus Christ
it's called the hacker right we got that
and if you're joking like you need the
Heimlich you just sit in it and it like
like knows like your body type okay this
person needs to have like and the
Machine starts doing it why the hacker
because heck like you're hacking it up I
thought it was like gonna be like some
like no not internet hacker like like
okay yes and so basically this machine
just like it's kind of like a roller
coaster thing that like comes over the
top and on your diagram and it's just
like and it's like doing the Heimlich
like right like you stand up and it's
latched to the wall because that way too
much I feel like it's way more I just
want to see this machine decorated
but they put roses no because what I'm
saying
using their flower petals shooting
everywhere no yeah it's like because you
want it to fit the theme like how would
it look like a song
[Laughter]
so no one's allowed to show
get in the [ __ ] hacker you look like
a fool me exactly like look at you like
no if someone does the high look if
someone does the high look and you don't
go to the hacker you're choking like out
of style out of fashion yes you need to
choke like it's 20 23. exactly go to the
hacker like go hack it up this is insane
but no basically the machine is like
specifically designed to help every body
style every body type and it's just like
really so it's an inclusive no but it
really like because I feel like I feel
like to be honest it's sucking like it's
closed you know like Technic listen I am
technically like heimlich certified I
have the card so do I yeah would you
rather a like machine that is built for
it or me to do that honestly you what
what are you doing if you go to re-watch
The Wizard of Oz in the yellow brick
road is pink but they constantly call it
the yellow brick road like they Follow
the yellow brick road and it's there's
not yellow and it's just pink the whole
time yeah and they refer to it as like
the yellow brick road I literally really
probably going to the bathroom
stare at myself in the mirror for a
solid like 30 minutes and just question
everything about me
okay and I'd get something pink and
something yellow like pink lemonade
because it probably includes both right
people how many just both just pink
what are you asking I probably just shut
the movie off maybe that was stupid okay
you wouldn't question it one bit
stupid I said one what would y'all do if
you were on Earth when the asteroid came
to hit the dinosaurs
okay bad answer stupid smile
what
you mean bad question you answered what
if they just answered hey what if no
no he hey someone's whipping it what if
they just scramble the alphabet like
it's adg one day oh I hate that bro and
you have to relearn it what's your
favorite I feel like right now is this
what's your favorite part of the
alphabet
you switch the flow a little bit Yeah a
b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p oh
it's like h i j k
is that right h i High
jk just kidding oh my God it's like hi
just kidding
H I J K L M N O P yeah LMNOP is hard bro
you switch the flow
throw a beat on the ABCs I need to hear
that but nothing like that it has a beat
that the goofy Kidz Bop beat I want to
drill beat like hyper pop beat for the
ABC okay
hold on let me see if I have one here A
B no what would you guys do
if you could go back to kindergarten but
with like not like the knowledge that
you learn in school but like the life
lessons like you all the life lessons
and all the things yeah me and
kindergarten would explode he does not
have the bandwidth to like you you went
through all the life lessons you had but
like your your size you wear in
kindergarten and you have to like you
still don't know like your times tables
dude I think I'm on that level right now
like I think I'm just kindergarten level
smart but I'm learning from all the life
lessons I experience that's how I like I
genuinely feel that that right like you
just described exactly what goes on in
my head okay like I know colors so much
alphabet and little spelling and poor
reading level so would you know would
you go back to first grade and like the
life lessons you have you're nice that's
nice Chris put your hand down first up
thank you so what would you do would you
like would you drop out and be like okay
[ __ ] school like oh I've learned like
you tried to like being with the friends
I would re I would relive I would relive
school I thought it was a great fun I
hated school 24 hours left to live what
would you do this to God I want to be
duct taped to a skateboard and go to the
tallest skate ramp of life like super
tall I'm just gonna skate down it that's
really weird if I fall and die I was
gonna in hours anyway I think if I knew
I had 24 hours left to live I'd do
something that like people don't do
because like you could die doing it oh
so Chris's answer literally my answer is
no I don't want to get duct tape to a
[ __ ] skateboarding you don't have to
you can just do the skateboard the duct
tape portion was to add an element of
spice and Pizzazz to my
to my thing I thought it was so that you
could see what snake you're just foolish
no I'm not yes you are you're [ __ ]
foolish get out of my face okay
what if I died tomorrow but everyone
thought it was you what would you do
tell them it wasn't no like everyone's
promoting like your death but it's
actually me like they're like rest in
peace master and it's actually me like
you died and I'm alive I died you're
alive but everyone thinks that I'm you
just correct them oh that's actually my
biggest fear ever well like I was if I
was alive and one of y'all died and
people thought it was me I'd feel so
guilty inside why oh I don't want to
talk about this move on move on move on
story
no why that's giving away my secrets
it's not it's funny I don't want people
to know that just tell them no because
one day if I like become really strong
and powerful that's why and I don't know
Chris has two tests
tell them I'm actually for real why I
don't want the internet to know okay
about your tetanus shots
okay like not the actual shot but like
just the knowing of the amount of do you
feel like you're like a little bit more
immune to like rust
I'm not WD-40 I'm just a [ __ ] human
being that's what the tetanus shot is
for
eign
foreign
I hate that that's called the blowing
raspberries it makes you really
uncomfortable like we didn't have to
bring his formal title in here no like
I'm just saying like whatever oh look at
this it's like it's a clap like oh I
hate that that's called an Applause
you're a goofy as [ __ ] no yeah that was
so cool I'm just saying like wow when
it's on like movies and [ __ ] it's
somebody like
when someone does that in movies I hate
that like the subtitles it says oh my
God can you get out no I wasn't gonna
throw up or anything I just almost did
whatever whatever I'm done moving on
what would you do if you were Spider-man
[ __ ] probably splitting around what
would you do if you could only eat
seafood for the rest of your life never
eaten what would no bad answer what
would your breakfast be I don't like
seafood I'm allergic to myself no you're
not
allergic to anything
so I must be allergic to you
good one burn put your gushers away
stupid
why relax because over there just
gushing all up in his mouth
allergic to most Seafood I know you
always think I'm playing like this game
salmon is gas I like salmon salmon
dealers I can't have shellfish
that's my answer
it's giving blowing raspberries
that's what it's called
that's what it's called I can't have any
Hard Shell Seafood
okay you know he's making fun of me
saying what I should have said instead
of no absolutely not yeah no I'm not I'm
saying alternate is it hard shell like a
shellfish like Lobster's hard
hard shelled what do you it's called a
shell girl
it's another [ __ ] shell I don't think
a shut up I don't think dude oh my God
today
me and Maddie ordered food and I went to
get it and the doordash driver had a
turtle shell necklace on like it was a
rope and like a turtle shell like this
big dude like a turtle
ew now
you act like you don't do that every
video no that was stinky and he blew it
on me you do that every video not blow
it on you yes you do [ __ ] you
Nick I'm gonna kick your ass
we have a Hibachi spoon in here for the
lucky winner
ceramic I thought it was plastic my
apologies I would have never thrown it
at you I have a question yeah
ow [ __ ] what would you do
if somebody was in there like you have
to pick right now on the spot
your hair you can never cut it again or
you can never trim your toenails again
hair
trim your toenails again
I'd much rather be able to trim my
toenails than cut my hair I'd file my
toenails now look at this stuff isn't it
neat wouldn't you think my collection's
complete yeah they should do a rap remix
I want a Disney Princesses just bars
subtle button the new movie went crazy
sorry
it's nuts
you don't know his name it's like asking
Who Ariel is like what's the mermaid's
name again it's the [ __ ] like main
character of the movie relax Neptune
didn't mean to try in
whatever so close again oh my God this
is Neptune bro the planet I don't know
isn't it King Neptune that's SpongeBob
oh that's probably what he's thinking
then yeah but it's not I am in The
Little Mermaid
bro I hate that tough guy in Manville
whatever in SpongeBob what
no when they when SpongeBob and Patrick
are on the journey to becoming a man the
big tough guy
the spiky shoes wouldn't you think my
collections combined I said something
about King Neptune and just being him
he's him man you guys say crazy random
[ __ ] that makes no [ __ ] sense and I'm
tired of it why that's like like that
that's like literally what you have done
for years crazy random [ __ ] that makes
no sense ears everything I say has
statistics and logic that's very
incorrect I think we just started our
own business firm what I don't even know
what that means like us three should
really execute like really good work and
some imagine if we were like in suits
yeah we should do stocks we should start
doing the costumes in the car video
again
we should invest in what the stock
market in Google yes I see Google on a
high trajectory I like to invest when
the stocks are low Buy Low sell big I
don't know what any of this means
Buy Low sell High sounds really good
yeah that's what you want to do with the
market as well when the house market yo
yard sales are such like an amazing
Place
[Laughter]
holy [ __ ] why I ate them were you
talking to me about yard sales nothing
good all shabby junk Chris shabby junk
that's crazy where have you ever you
were telling me about yard sales the
other day when you bought a piggy bank
for three dollars and there was a 20
bill in it and you made 17. correct
there's a good come up with the piggy
bank worth it nope why were you even at
this [ __ ] put the 17 for free
probably it was in a yard sale what was
it it was a flea market oh
flea markets are liters are big yards I
love yard sales though no yard sales are
lit do you ever go to a stand at a flea
market and you can just tell that all
the people are like like they're
reselling [ __ ] that's like
goofy you know what I mean that's most
of them no no like some people are like
making their own product or doing their
own kids no business you know
I haven't seen it what would you do if
you went up to 11 18 they charge you
like 50 I kicked the table over and I'd
say buddy find a new if you're if this
is your life of business you're gonna
need to find a new route
wow so you're just gonna I guess you're
just gonna give it to me straight I'm
just gonna as a kid I'm gonna say buddy
you got your you got high hopes ahead of
you if you think somebody's just gonna
walk by and spend 50 on your lemonade at
the end of your driveway I tell them as
profit margins or I don't know that's
what I'm saying somebody's got like
you're averaging 59 a cup somebody's got
to teach them
I'd probably just pay the fifty dollars
take a sip of the lemonade spit it out
so that's not worth five cents
it's time to figure it out really yeah
it's time to really think about it and
figure it out because what you're doing
right now is not gonna cut it
tastes like gold that tastes like ass
the chunky lemonade powder at the bottom
do you stir the [ __ ] pitcher yeah
flavoring inside dummy your mom's making
this done a single thing to help all
right dude what did you do pitch the
table oh one leg oh you couldn't you
just pitch one leg to do the rest
because you are you have muscles you
have no strength to put the table out
here yourself I'd say pick up that
picture of lemonade you probably can't
even pick it up pick it up
pour me the glass yourself I'll give you
fifty dollars it's like both hands
shaking it's like all right you're 12.
like what a fool you're crazy what if he
does 50 plus tax like he makes you get
like like he's like 50 like what that's
crazy you give him 50 he's like oh it's
actually like 50 27.
until you're lucky I don't take 27 cents
and throw it at your [ __ ] forehead
you ugly little kid
this is gonna get demonetized yeah
probably
that's why I said it calmly honestly I
didn't raise my voice so maybe we have a
better chance I don't think it matters
if you say anything that's demonetizable
at any volume look at this stuff what
isn't it neat yeah
wouldn't you think collection is great
are we done
we should let it go let it go hold it
back anymore
Let it go Let it go dude
uh
on what the cold do never bothered me
anyway
[Music]
huh wind in the sky
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me