[Music]
Hi everyone. My name's Lee Holmes and
I'm the founder of Supercharged
Food. I'm looking for
$200,000 for 20% of my
business. Supercharged Food started
about 5 years ago after a struggle that
I had with my own health.
I woke up one day and I literally could
not get out of bed. I had hives covering
my whole body. My hair was falling out
in clumps around me. I went through what
I found to be a very complex medical
system. Doctor to doctor, scan to scan,
more clumps of hair, and I was put on a
concoction of drugs, immunosuppressants,
anti-inflammatories, steroids that blew
me up like the Michelin man. From there,
I looked to food for answers. I created
recipes and I put them up on my blog,
Supercharged
Food. The blog became really popular.
Everyone loved the delicious recipes and
I wrote my very first book, Eat Your Way
to Good
Health. And it became an international
number one bestseller. I've since
written four bestselling
books. One of the main new parts of my
Supercharged Food website is my online
4-week heal your gut program. It's based
on my latest book, Heal Your
Gut. It's put together with a team of
experts. People do the program online.
They get recipes in their inbox, and the
testimonials have been so outstanding
and fantastic.
We've also got some supercharged food.
Would you like to give it a try? Sure.
Absolutely.
So, Lee, that was $200,000 for 20%. So,
you're valuing your business at $1
million. Yes, that's correct. Thank you.
So that's the mint chop chip smoothie
that you're having, Naomi. Looks
fantastic. It's dairy free, sugar free,
wheat free, gluten-free, everything
free, as my daughter would say. So yeah,
what am I eating? That is a vanilla
custard with gelatin, which is really
good for the gut. Right. What am I left
with? You're left with a beautiful
salmon chowder, I think. And there's
also some pesto and some beautiful
lemony herb crackers. Cracking the
pesto. This is yummy.
So what is your business? So, the
business is my online website, the
digital platform. I have an online
store. It's my program, my four-week
program, as well as subsequent programs
that I'm putting together. There's a
2-day maintenance program, and it's also
ebooks. Can you just run me through your
income streams and the revenues you get
from each? So, my books, um, I've sold
120,000 units, so I get income from
them. But the books are not
included because I already have a
contract with my publisher. But what is
included is my program, subsequent
programs, the products, the store, the
online store. The online store has sold
$65,000 worth of products in the last 12
months and the program has made about
$94,800. I really like your business
model. I think it's fantastic. Thank
you. The thing is though, it is all
about you.
It's your reputation. I think you've
done an amazing job on selling 120,000
books which build your audience. But the
challenge for us is that it is all about
you. So, had you thought about that?
I have thought about that. The great
thing about it is we we've got the
digital platform. We've got the
audience. You can run weight loss
programs through it. You can run all
different programs through it. You've
got it there. It's ready to go. It's an
amazing structure. Could you train
someone else to run those programs? Oh,
yes. Yeah, definitely. You can get a
community manager. I'm just the face.
Good day, Eli. I haven't said much of
you, Steve. How you doing, Steve? Um,
where are you from? I'm from England
originally. And yesterday, where were
you from? Oh, Bondi. Bondi, Sydney.
Um, I don't believe the whole the whole
superfood thing and stuff just drives me
insane. I think that uh my my first
reaction is, can I please have some
bacon with it?
[Music]
So, um I'm not a natural for this uh
this segment.
So, I'll I'll bow out. Okay. Thank you.
Steve's out. Four of us
in. My concern is you've just excluded
probably the best part of your business,
which are your
books. I I recognize your
[Music]
books. Um, I'm out. Thank you.
Your business is very bankable. You've
got cash flow. You're you're the
brand. Frankly, you are the unre
repeatable miracle of your business,
which is a risk from an investment point
of
view. I wish you
well. I'm out.
Look, I I've got to be creative in my
deal to be able to do a deal because
it's it's the valuation is is very
difficult to get to. Yeah.
So, the offer I've got for you is
200,000. I'm splitting it in half. So,
the first 100,000 will be repaid to me
uh by $10 every time someone comes in
and does a program.
The reason there's no interest on it is
because it's paid within 24 months. So
it's basically interest free. Yeah.
Okay. And the other 100,000 I will uh
buy as equity. So I'll buy shares full
fully
shares but I want 35% of the business.
Thank you.
[Music]
I'm going to make you an
offer, but I actually think you need a
business partner. I think you need
somebody who's going to run your
operation for you. So, I'm prepared to
put a business manager into your
business. Mhm. Are you going to fund it?
Yeah. Who's funding that? It It has to
be funded by the business. A reasonable
salary, not a big salary, what usually.
So, you're prepared to have her pay for
your business manager, but she'll
provide the expertise. It's okay. It's
pretty generous. That's okay. I I think
this corner need is right. She needs a
business partner. That corner is a lone
shark.
No, she doesn't. How's that a lone
shark? It's $100,000 interest free.
There's no lone sharking at all. They're
not even letting me give you an offer.
They're so selfish, aren't they? It's
all about them. We're here for you. It's
all about them. You pay for my business
manager, but it's all about them. Oh,
please know me. Actions speak louder
than words, mate. Lee, I want 50% of
your business for 200,000.
But you get a business manager.
[Music]
Okay. Okay. What are you going to do?
Thank you, Naomi, so much for your
offer. Because it's 50% I feel like I,
you know, it's half of my company. Um,
so I'm a bit overwhelmed by
[Music]
that. Janine, you are the biggest
inspiration to me. I love your story. I
love your journey. I love what you've
done. I love your business acumen. I
love your attention to detail and
everything about you.
[Music]
and I'd be honored to work with you. Wa,
that's a yes. Well done. Well done.
Have a lot of fun. Well done.
Congratulations. Congratulations. You're
already a brand, so now you got to
build. She's a great business partner.
Well done. Thank you, Lee. We'll see you
out there. Oh, Lee, was there anything
you didn't like about her? No. Oh, okay.
Just checking.
You haven't met her yet.
I I want someone to say that about me
once. Just once. So, what are you
looking forward to the most? Working
with Janine and getting to know her a
little bit better and taking the
business to the next level. How lucky am
I?