why does this car look like it's gunning
at me where Matt why would you
ever
ever I only say that when I think it
Nick so when you're like oh my God is
she likeing
handcuffs what she looked like handcuff
looking at this is 3 weeks old bottle
soda actually longer than that the whole
time we were in La this
three weeks it's not cheese [ __ ]
it's not going to get
better K thinks it's Pepsi's wine he's
putting in his wine cooler waiting for
it to get right all right guys today
we're going to film ah I'm good all
right anyway today guys we are filming a
video look at this I perfectly wedged a
glasses lens between my eyelid and the
bottom you're so weird look like
Terminator oh my God you want know what
that just reminded me of you're going to
get it going to guess it if I wait long
enough think about what you did I had an
eyeball patch one eye a pirate when we
were younger remember when you put the
soccer
ball Nick had a soccer ball like one of
those one of those tattoos it was Matt
it was me it was Nick it was me oh a
poor soul you think this happened to you
it was that me my memories are blending
into yours too that was 100% I'm going
toon on the eye I'm going to be honest I
almost started by talk saying it was me
so I don't know who it was it was 100%
me I think it was I remember witnessing
I did it and then I I remember going in
the hallway okay let's just tell them
let's just tell them I had it you know
those temporary tattoos you're dead
[ __ ] world you're an idiot I one of
those where were you I was upstairs on
the second floor bathroom it with the
green L cloth yeah I did it and then I
looked at myself and was panicking
correct and then I peeled it off it was
me this happened to me happened to us
both no it
didn't the temporary tattoos you stick
on you and then you add water and then
you peel it off and then it becomes a
little whoever did it thought they were
going to put it on their eye and then
when they blink it was going to like go
up in their eye like in the eyelid and
then they blink and then it like reveals
the soccer ball yeah and they I don't
know who was me I put the soccer B on my
eye and I put water on it and then I
peeled it off and there was a soccer
ball in my eye but my eye wouldn't open
and then I panicked and thought I was
like going blind yeah he opened the he
went to open both his eyes and only one
opened and he started like freaking out
it was so funny it was for the sake of
the story it can be you but it wasn't it
was 100% me and I know that if it
actually happened you you'd be putting
up more of a fight about it and you'd be
yelling and screaming I don't think you
would idiot I put up a fight about it
you even said oh it could have been both
of us you're the only one that has shown
any way of swe I said it could have also
happened to you but I know it happened
to me I did did it all right guys
welcome back to another Friday video
today we're going to be talking about
what okay anyway today we're filming a
video today we're filming a video and um
it's going to be like a what would you
do like we're going to give each other
what would you do scenarios and then you
have to react to it I hate when you do
that there's like an no no let's do the
fake yell like blow out all your I saw
this on Tik Tok you blow out all your
air also not doing that come on yes try
it
now scream scream how do you have that
much air in you [ __ ] hot
Jesus see if I if I blew out all my air
I'd still be able to scream I feel like
I
would
okay scream oh cuz that's that's com in
right did I just breathe in more air is
that what I did is that wait how do you
do it
you thought you could do it you thought
you could do it thought going to be so
no yeah you
can't you look [ __ ] stupid dude one
more time one more
time how I'm being cautious I'm not
blowing on
you yes you are try how you're spitting
on me no hold on try again I am what
would you do if I died and you couldn't
drive anywhere and you guys just get my
license yeah I just get my license in
honor of Matt thank you honestly it'd be
less of an honor of Matt and more of a
convenience to my new life and i' tell
everyone my brother used to drive me
around and then he hit the can so I had
to do it myself and he was one of the
best drivers you've ever seen what what
what if you could uninvent
something mine would be I would take
away something really important and
recreate it now and then just like live
life lavishly like I would take out
Amazon i' of a finger and then I'd say
guys I have this great idea we should
list everyone's that wasn't the question
by so you're
just I would uninvent I would uninvent
those
obnoxious cars that drive themselves
with no car with no passengers at all
not even a driver or want to know what
I'd really [ __ ] get rid of those
stupid [ __ ] four little like
four-wheel buggy delivery [ __ ] the
like little like [ __ ] like
stupid [ __ ] Wall-E door Dash WALL-E
oh my God if I ordered something on door
Dash and that thing brought to my house
I wanted to say WALL-E oh my God
literally [ __ ] dude that's a movie I
haven't seen in way too long I love
Wall-E need to watch that again the time
iote
down okay what would you do if someone
was looking at you with a earto ear
smile like this and then just started
crying face I would stab them with a
knife I need much more detail to this am
I like down like a long hallway am I the
no you just woke
up dude this here is rolling this
morning when I woke up this morning when
I woke up I don't know what it is but my
vision has been toast in the morning I
woke up this morning trying to go on my
phone and I was like
no I had to get up and get water in my
eyes I couldn't see woke up the other I
felt like I had to cover a film over
both my eyes have you ever W have you
ever woken up Nick
you were woken up Nick and he just does
that like one eye is wide open but the
other one I don't know if you even try
the soccer ball I don't even think you
could do it if you were like fully awake
like you couldn't do it right like one
of my eyes work I need to go to the eye
Docker I walked into Nick's room and
like we were all hanging out and Nick
was in his room and he was like lying
down getting ready for bed I said what
the [ __ ] going on everybody's going to
bed early and he's got so defensive he's
like screaming I'm not asleep I'm not
going bed he like got up and like back
to the living room I wasn't and it was
so funny cuz well I was mad because
there's a [ __ ] there's a Celtics or
Bruins game every single day this week
and I live in a [ __ ] family full of
people who actually give a [ __ ] all in
Boston and it's like one I am one who
does not care the Celtics game's on I go
to my room I'm laying down I'm not
asleep it's like your oh this kid's
going to you watching drag drag race yes
but do I do I make you guys watch it yes
you don't have to watch our if you slept
during it you don't have to watch our if
you slept during it would I be mad would
I go oh you're going to bed early well
it's a family event it's like dude it's
classic you have nachos and food and you
watch a game nobody had Nach if you had
[ __ ] nachos trust me I would have
been present there was not a nacho in
sight corre not a single tortilla chip
no cheese at all if there was [ __ ]
nachos in the room I would have been
cheering for all of them I would have
known their names and everything I would
have said I would have pulled up the
stat sheet oh my God if you had [ __ ]
chips salsa anything I would have been
present in the world yeah there was no
nachos no there should be next time if
there is Count Me In I'll wear my
[ __ ] Jersey to the living room but
what if it's nacho cheese okay you're
[ __ ] I'm
not me after those stupid I'm not even
courtesy laughing at that what if you
woke up tomorrow in a different body and
it was like a dream of you living this
life but you were someone else and you
woke up and gained the knowledge of what
that person's actual day-to-day life is
do wait do I have both knowledges woke
up in your whole life as you as a dream
and you wake up in someone else's body
yeah you're just not I'm doing nothing
cuz I don't realize that it wasn't a
dream well I feel like I'd wake up and
then have new knowledge of who I really
am that's what I asked that was that was
included in my question that was
included in my question here he is
welome to the I yeah just lead life I
can't believe like I'm sorry like I
can't believe how monotone you speak
like you were just joking and you like
CL here yeah yeah welcome
to Welcome to the conversation if
someone walked around behind you you
your entire life and narrated your like
life and actions who would you want it
to be oh my God it couldn't be you Nick
that's one that's not the question no
let's start with people who couldn't be
Nick for sure why did you guys call this
video would you rather no it's not a
would you rather get it through your
[ __ ] head we're doing a what would
you do Matt it's what would you do
scenario there's no alternate okay John
ponz where are you what Matt one of you
made it a [ __ ] no we didn't make it a
would you rather it was a what would you
do that the first thing I said today was
what would you do it was like a what if
it was like what would you do if what if
okay good Nick do you know how we were
just at that red light and I kept
telling you I see things like in the
corner of my eye do you want to know
where I get it the most it it freaks me
out because it's it's like 100%
consistent like every time I'm Jing Mak
nervous you got to get there every time
I'm doing the specific thing and I'm in
this exact location 100% of the time I
look to the right and like check if
someone's there every time 100% say it
say it you have to no you have to try to
guess I'm begging you what the upstairs
bathroom brushing my teeth or like
shaving or something in my
room upstairs bathroom same I thought
you talking about my room no same no in
our house here yeah same 100% of the
time when I'm brushing my teeth I like
look cuz I think like Mom Dad or Matt
are like right next to me every 100%
never failed to not check last night I'm
brushing my teeth and I like literally
like flinched and I looked no one's even
upstairs and then I did it again the
next morning I was shaving this or yeah
last night or this morning whatever I
was shaving in the mirror same exact
thing I I saw like it seems like
someone's like running by and then I
check every time and there's nobody
there how can have attack it's so
[ __ ] SC and it's like 100% consistent
like it's never not thank God I don't
brush the camera's over there and you
you're the whole video I'm talking to
you guys yeah that's fine but like but I
have a bad I have l l haircut now bad
haircut so I have to hide it but no so
what are we going to do about the videos
that are already
up that was good that was take speaking
of Matt roasting your [ __ ] real quick I
have another question like if we hosted
like a comedy roast okay what would you
guys say about me like what would be
your first
roast um
um there you go can't even think of it
you guys suck I'd already cuz you're
just a
Sunshine yes that's why I wore my yellow
I'm just like the sun okay yeah I don't
know I'd have to think about all of
those what you have to think about
something to roast me on no not true not
true I just want to hurt your feeling
said I'd have to think the first thing
I'd say is oh hey everyone Nick's here
he um stole Big Bird sweater needs to
give big bird a sweater back right away
crazy do I let them know where I got
this maybe this is a hand me- down from
Chris's closet I know that is true I
can't I can't roast a sweater it was
mine yeah I the fact that you guys have
nothing to say blows my mind I could
think of [ __ ] for so Qui Nick manages to
bump into something in an empty [ __ ]
room he's always bumping into [ __ ] he
manes all you guys got I'm good manages
to complain about everything that
happens like no matter what you don't
want to know what I got for this first
thing I'd say when I walked in if it was
about Matt is oh my God guys Matt showed
up that'd be the first thing okay that's
good right yeah they like oh guys we're
here at the roast of Matt shockingly
Matt made it out of the house he's
actually present in the room wow big
shocker mhm all right what would you
guys say about me I'm going to say all
right guys um in honor of tonight being
such a special night with the roast of
Chris I just love a 5-second Moment of
Silence from
everyone like amazing that's the least
Chris has talked in [ __ ] years yeah
that' be the first thing I'd say I'd say
beat me black and blue get this boy Matt
out of
here is that a man Matt the type of guy
that keep his hedge is nice and clean
like he'd like go outside and trim his
little
bushes I had a every morning totally
Nick's thing yeah I have no idea toally
I wouldn't care and have overgrown my
hedges would have names I feel like this
is hedgy
hedgy It's the type to say the dumb
version of like the word like instead of
like what is going on I'm The Brightest
Bulb ever no instead of like tent he'd
be like the rning like the like lame
version of something no the person who
do it is right get away yeah you do that
no I don't I actively do that no you use
like who is over there nobody stop
looking that way if you could eliminate
one word from existence what would it be
mine would be no [ __ ] saying yes
to me it's not Nicki it would be from
your vocab too
dumbass people don't really ask me
questions they know better mine would be
the double meaning words so like the
first one I'm getting rid of is bat cuz
it's like bat the baseball bat and bat
the animal and then everyone would be
like what is this nameless creature like
what is it like I would just give bat
one meeting instead of two and then
trick everyone and then be they everyone
would be thinking what do they say at
baseball games he's up at swing he's up
at bat we can still keep that one that's
the bat we
keep
get I thought you understand I thought
you meant they were all gone no just the
animal version wait isn't there three
words it's bat bat and what else isn't
there another B you're thinking of
battery no you're thinking no I'm not
you're thinking of blue blue yeah oh
blue and blue blue blue and then feeling
like okay I don't know maybe blue blue
and blue feeling blue color blue and
blowing that was crazy it was like a it
was like a um party thing that's what I
envisioned like I envisioned the party
okay yeah you could only own a kayak or
a canoe which one would you want I don't
there's no [ __ ] difference yes there
is a canoe is deeper and shallower a
kayak is more on Surface a canoe I would
pick a kayak it's way more trusty in the
water but a canoe you can like sit up a
kayak you have to be like leaning back
like I don't like that I relax no kayak
is way more like for beginners like it's
easier to fall in a canoe than a kayak I
think okay then a kayak you just can't
shift your weight okay like why' you ask
us if you have every answer King kayak
is asking me the question it's like you
you're clearly the professional you need
a job at the [ __ ] Bass Pro Shop
selling kayaks if you could go back to
any point in your life you lived where
would you go probably go back to like
Cape Cod and I would legit like eat
bubbles after really wait we are talking
physical
location or a time
period wait what are you talking about
nothing Nick in heart why
nothing Matt spoke to
me I felt it right here is that the
question yeah you hit the nail on the
head okay Matt likes to critique me cuz
I think I make him feel old like he's
just as immature as me but he's like a
slight variant CH you being in the car
is that's not a good that's not a good
excuse at all you could be on Mars
nobody needs to hear that you have to go
[ __ ] pee pee and poo poo I have to
pee bad congratulations what do you want
me do I told Nick cuz you're like
slightly more mature than I am I'm
slightly more mature yeah okay like if
I'm at ground level you're like like a
safety cone like of immaturity above me
yeah you're still touching it like
you're still touching me would you say
just the safety I the craziest thing to
me was he said that you are slightly
more mature than him and then you came
back in the car and he went like Chris
that wasn't good that wasn't a good
thing in your defense's at our entire
YouTube catalog who's more mature as a
human being I think sometimes you have
to Screech to just get the full like
that that's a fact like that's a reset
you know I mean how do you feel about
that sounds pretty immature if I had to
answer thank you if like a group of
people is talking I need I need to get
my I need to get my eyes checked when
when I laugh room or like I'm in a funny
situation tears just tears that's me too
that's natural that's natural I think
personally that our and we should go
pick up a kindergarten and and we we can
have a kindergarten replace Chris and we
see how well they do I'd beat that
[ __ ] up i' you can't replace me
okay I would grab that little
[ __ ] by the shirt and yank him
out of the window and you'd see his
shins hit this part of the car that's
the thing if he told me he needed me to
stop the car to go potty it would
actually reasonable I think personally
that our viewers have this scope of me
as like triplets with you guys obviously
cuz we're triplets and we film every
video together but I think car videos
and Vlogs and being with you guys is
like my ultimate Peak jokester like
goofball you know what I mean like I am
so funny and Goofy and jokeful with you
two and that's about it like when other
friends join and other people are around
I'm I'm not acting this rambunctious and
crazy and that doesn't mean our videos
are like an act but like the viewers
really only see like the super unserious
side of me you know what I mean yeah and
that's just like it made me like this
exact moment in the car made me realize
like oh my God no Wonder all these
people think I'm like a look at the
scope you gave them when yeah cuz every
time we're filming together it's
obviously all three of us it's never
like just me in a vlog yeah you know
what I
mean I got some cool new red
shoes like I'm trying to think like
where where do we go with this are you
no I'm done I just really needed to have
that moment to speak with you guys and I
appreciate you listening um thank you
guys so much for walking walking for
walking well these boots are made for
walking thank you guys so much for
watching this week's Friday video we'll
see you guys we see you guys on the
internet turn on post notification that
you never miss a video and the first
link in the description down below is
our merch link so we don't have a merch
drop live right now but save that link
CU When we do drop merch it tends to
sell out quick and you're not going to
want to miss it so thank you guys for
watching hit the Subscribe button before
you head out we will see you guys later
yes we will and keep in mind we have
been severely debating cutting out
Wednesday videos just saying I'm ready
to do it when you guys are just just
giving you guys that warning yep
[Music]