Nick what are you doing
[Music]
W should I get low low lowow low low low
shy had them Apple Bottom
Jeans boots with the fur don't fur in
the hole why never not the
camera stop making that noise please and
swing in The Wire right there all right
oh there's a bag in that Chris check if
somebody no you don't open straight bags
that's rule number one yeah but it's
rule number one so what Nick just the
somebody bought something and they
didn't take it though could be a free
pickup no what if it's a
gun empty bag it's an empty Marshall's
bag all right hey everyone welcome back
to this week's Friday video it's a sty
little triplets we're back in Boston
feel how cold these little balls are
okay can I feel the little balls yeah
feel howold they are freezing I want a
paintball gun and I want to fill it with
frozen paintballs and just Pelt little
kids
Frozen Pelt is such a funny word to me
is it a pelt also like a like a fur coat
that's a felt no your mother Nick I'm
going to ask Mom how she feels with you
calling like saying your mother in all
the videos ask her all right guys I'm
going to start the video with my first
question wait I love this mat this is
this is off the chain don't make a big
deal don't make a big deal don't make a
big deal this is great though I'm off
the chain what are you Melanie Brown the
Spice Girls that was off the chain do
you remember she's the host America's
Got Talent I love melbe I do too I'm a
at were you like a Mel kid or a Heidi
Clum kind of kid melb for sure but at
what but at what not Heidi Clum okay you
can go I know you're going to ask when
can I start my intro go for it there's
there's no intro was just a question
just [ __ ] do it okay um so I've lived
in New England my whole life until just
recently we moved to California like 2
years ago right yeah I still don't
understand why we're shoveling snow
before all of it hits the ground that is
true you're going to have more to shovel
in an hour well I don't I don't
understand no cuz if if it's like oh we
got 6 to 8 in of snow why shovel two
sets of three when you can go out and
shovel 6 in of snow I just think overall
we're doing it too
early like I I think that's what he just
said that's where no I think we need to
go in the
middle like I tell us more tell us
more what Matt's saying is like you keep
going what is that bever give me a sip
you want some a pineapple what Matt
saying is he thinks all the snow should
fall and then we shovel it can can you
stop [ __ ] repeating
people like Hello Matt is saying and he
says what you said we heard Mo on you
have a secondary thought I think right
when it's in the middle is when we go
out to shovel what's in the middle cuz
that's what I was just what I said
should I shake this first like no you
shouldn't okay
won't what's in the middle to you once
at like 4 Ines of snow so what I just
said we shouldn't your mom I lit raise
your hand if actually give a
[ __ ] I don't you did you don't yeah you
did you did what I'm saying is
[Laughter]
I can't even do the [ __ ] jokes right
I feel like I'm at the eye doctor and
they're checking my site c a n o n
Canon reading the camera I'm that no
like ially feel like I'm at the eye
doctor I feel blind with oneand lens
look my eyes are
watering okay let's move on and nap
about the snow I know you're happy you
have so much room back in there I love
this
car
God like there's just so much more space
if someone came back here they could
comfortably sit next to me sure or if
someone came to attack us I have so much
wingspan to fight them off two very
different things yeah I wish that I was
like a medieval not medieval I wish I
was like an old timey detective I had a
fun little game that I made if you guys
want to play it I want to play more than
I want to live oh my god do anything
I'll play I'm not going to I hope that
when I pass away one day that Jeff R is
at my funeral and he says the tribe has
spoken everyone walks out and he snuffs
a torch while people are leaving my
burial site that's my ideal dream I
swear to God if people are like Nick
stola would love this and I'm dead it's
like you don't know what I would do and
I'm not here to tell you shut the [ __ ]
up when I pass away I want Jeff probes
there okay okay we can organize it
hopefully and do you want do you want
him to say like he couldn't the tribe
has spoken that's it snuff my tour wait
he says nothing else Matt have you seen
a [ __ ] episode of Survivor yeah do
you want people to do the challenges
first no the tri has spoken light my
torch out that's it send me off I'm
headed to
Ponderosa where is that it's in Survivor
it's the house that the jury goes to to
wait till the next meeting didn't even
know give it a Google give it a Google
it's an accurate
fact can we play your game oh my God a
private Resort the show the show
calls Ponderosa thank you wow actually
[ __ ] it's cuz like the OG Seasons they
used to show you what was happening at
Ponderosa can you play can we play the
game you keep talking you keep talking
give me whatever you're eating what is
this I don't really want these I thought
this would be jky give me it I'll eat
it no I just want to get an update of
how you guys feel I feel great how
awesome I don't want this [ __ ] ass candy
it's great it's great okay it Frosted
Flakes it's they're great if you were
talking about you say it's great they're
great if you were like whatever [ __ ] off
basically I wrote down no way that's why
I don't do it no wait you like have a
full game to play yes Nick I'm so
excited so basically I wrote down a
bunch of things that kill a certain
people per year what yeah so it's
basically like hippos killed this many
people a year sharks killed this many
people a year I'll get them all right
I'm going to read two of them m and you
have to guess over under okay okay
sharks are at
six yeah oh my gosh that's insane six
people ding sharks grow up everyone get
in the ocean what like people are afraid
oh I'm afraid there's a
shark that truck is doing a burnout over
there what a [ __ ] I hate loud cars oh
my God I was just so ready to [ __ ]
drive away you should have saw the
[ __ ] oh my God there's nothing I hate
more than people with like big engines
in their car
ooh
what are you pimping out Mommy's car cuz
you're finally old enough saved every
penny you could to throw a muffler on
that little thing [ __ ] yourself get out
of here I don't care dude we see some
interesting characters I just I hate it
I hate loud car engines grow up you're
not impressing a single [ __ ] soul on
Earth I want to see if he does it again
It embarrasses me how tough of folk may
think they are by revving an engine in a
car yeah it's so embarrassing go home
feed your family feed yourself go eat
there's always better things to do then
[ __ ] rev your engine get away go eat
all right what about the dogs 30 to 50
people di
next WoW Nick that was good you give me
so so
so he's doing little
Donuts I'm the toughest [ __ ] in
the
city oh my God I'm really embarrassed
yeah this is so time of GRA my car super
fast I can't take you seriously these
glasses I keep forgetting I have him on
this is so embarrassing what if he's
like trying to like impress his friend
dude if he's with a girl right now I
hope that she makes it home safe and
never goes to hang out with this [ __ ]
idiot again oh my God okay you're on a
first date right oh brother you're on a
first dat scenario so Nick you get
picked up on a date and the guy has like
a super cool truck dude I already don't
give a [ __ ] okay up in Santa SLE you
could tell me to take public
transportation you could pick me up at a
Target cart I'd be fine I'd be happy
with anything okay so you get picked up
in a nice big truck a super cool truck
and he's like he he goes into the
parking lot you guys are just talking
blah blah blah you're having a good
night date's going well right he says
hey sugar lips you like my big
truck oh my God shh you get you're on
timeout for the next minute no words
better leave that [ __ ] trap of yours
seriously Nick he go the next minute if
you speak I'm punching you he goes like
this he doesn't he doesn't like Direct
to the fact that he's going to do it all
right sweet shut up you you're on
timeout for real ni he just I'm actually
setting a timer you shut the [ __ ] up
Nick he just goes like this he just goes
watch this oh watch this is brutal shut
up Matt can I tell you my actual thing
yeah I'm screaming bloody murder as if
this [ __ ] is trying to kill me
scrolling down the window I'm going let
me out out let me out that's you asked
that's what I'm doing if I'm in a car
and the person's like look at this I'm
going to rev my engine drive you around
like a [ __ ] Maniac psychopath and
annoy the whole [ __ ] neighborhood and
wake up Auntie Sue down the street
that's just trying to go to bed cuz she
has a [ __ ] actual day job to hit
tomorrow morning you're like annoying
the neighborhood yeah shut the [ __ ] up
I'm genuinely doing that I'm screaming
let me out of this [ __ ] ass car bring me
home I'll walk I'll call the STS come
pick me up fly me home what I'll do
anything to get out of I'll roll home
I'll sumersault home literally get me
into a hill I'll barrel roll down I'm
not going home in your car I'd rather
literally step on glass and drag my feet
home
actually I'd rather step on glass drag
my feet all the way that is such a sick
visual yeah I don't care I hate cars I
think we should take Nick to like a what
do you feel about like an organized
racetrack though that's pretty cool it's
more fun sure I just don't care you're
moving a you didn't invent the truck
there's people far cool than invent the
truck you didn't invent the [ __ ]
mobile if you invented a race car and
then you race around sure props to you
or if you're a professional you're
actually doing it in sport you're
awesome but it's like are you really do
are you providing a good that no one
else has done before if you're don't say
all that is this guy Donuts in your
parking lot at [ __ ] 12:30 at night is
he providing a service that anybody has
can't do what I'm saying is I think is
he serving good pollution I think
organized driving is cool like organized
races I think putting the city in an
annoying like whatever at 12:30 at night
go home go to bed was also dangerous you
know oh and danger he could die he could
tip over and die ladders or peanut
allergies oh what oh I forgot to I
forgot the I'm like what is is this a
would you rather a preference thing no I
think that it has to be wait Nick answer
it as a would you rather would you
rather always have a ladder or peanut
allergies dude everywhere you go you
have to carry a ladder around or you
just have peanut allergies dude come on
the ladder is clearly more of an
inconvenience imagine going into a
restaurant it's like oh you can you
leave that outside now I have to bring
my 9ot ladder to dinner with me where
are you leaving that thing I'm in this
car where would the where would it be it
was on you understand your limits if you
have to carry a ladder you we never said
it I don't care you give up a peanut
butter I don't i' give up I don't
believe it I'd give up my favorite food
I don't believe carry what carry around
a ladder all the time no one said how
tall the ladder had to be it could a
step it could be like a step stools can
double as a little bag like they look
like a don't care no I don't know think
about like working it's like you show up
somewhere you have like a ladder with
you just seems like a lot yeah yeah I'd
rather have a peanut allergy people
can't see the peanut allergy inside but
they'll always be able to see the ladder
and that's
deep okay okay but what's catching more
bodies the ladder or peanut butter
peanut allergies M I have to say Ladders
because I feel like everybody that has a
peanut allergy they're just getting the
EpiPen nowadays I feel like it's really
hard for it to like fully kill you
peanut shockingly only 13 people died to
a peanut allergy last year let's go well
I don't know clapping is still
appropriate yeah that's just not a lot
compared to ladders what is up with
peanuts how many ladders
300 telling you oh I did I get the
chills falling off the ladder is rough
yeah dude falling to death anyways to
dude I remember when I was in carbon TR
imagine falling to death that's so sad I
don't want to think of it I falling to
your death plummeting stop dude stop
crazy just a slap on
the the yeah insane and a itic shock
isn't fun either though I want to see
this dude do another donut Matt you're
no better than anyone else better than
it's funny
500 for one for motorcycle crashes for
motorcycles higher or lower motorcycles
that makes more sense you had it where
it's like we picked underrated word that
sounds exactly like the experience
barf like what like the word barf I know
what you're going to do that's actually
my least favorite word I think it's
corny I think it's goofy I think there's
so many Alternatives that are way just
think someone they eat too much candy
and then they get off a ride and they're
like oh I'm going to Bar it fits perfect
actually it's cold I'm cold oh you
chitty witty next I want to know
skydiving is only 11 people yeah I knew
it would be dude we didn't even [ __ ]
play the over under well that was for
motorcycles we can do that now oh oh
that's motorcycles 500 over under over a
th000 under under I'd hope it's under
1,500 oh my God that's so unfortunate
1,500 damn over under I'm saying under
for oh my God that's not the answer no
holy [ __ ] over under under over under
over
over 3,500 over
under is that the answer I'm going to
just keep over under oh my goodness over
yeah this is crushing you're pulling my
t no I'm not yes you are you're 6,000
over under don't say that Chris um over
over no [ __ ] wait get off your
motorcycle in one year 6,000 a year yes
oh obviously what 6,000 6,084 people
died to a motorcycle wait say it again
[ __ ] this game that's the number huh
that's the number
6,084 Nick you can't have us laughing
this is terrible guys 6084 my
heart I agree this [ __ ] hurts oh my God
I agree go your helmets on helmets
aren't going to really do anything if
you're going to die I Google no that
actually don't say that cuz helmets help
a lot see I can't I'm sorry is hel
really going to prevent death is I'm
falling off a motorcycle no actually
seriously no humor okay if I'm flying
off a motorcycle no humor I and I no I'm
not trying to be fun it's a serious
conversation if I'm on a motorcycle and
I have and I and I have a helmet on it
and a crash that is going to kill me
helmets could save lives yes okay
without a question sure well did I ever
tell you peanut allergies yeah right
yeah six 13 1 13 13 13 13 shout out to
my Brave peanut allergy survivors I love
you
all hippos hippos or vending machines
vending machines I know this they can
just joke it's obvious they cuz they go
to like shake it and then it falls on no
[ __ ]
way that's how they di machine I thought
I thought it was like lobing their arm
off and then they like I don't
know dude if I had to a vending machine
I'd be pissed that's like an
embarrassing don't have Jeff at my thing
if I died yeah tell him okay vending
machine is 13 dude compared to hippos
500 hippos no yeah hippos are killing I
bet Hipp like
if I'm getting super super old and I'm
just like why he on his phone Nick I
don't know if I'm like when the heavy
machine Falls
over oh my God it's got to be little
kids right let just jump on the top and
oh that's so sad I know I can't D
getting smooshed is like smoed oh I love
that word smush smush
smush it's a terrible day I'm the worst
okay no when I'm like super super old if
I'm like not remembering [ __ ] and I'm
like going to die like and I'm like
super old just let a hippo eat me I just
want a hippo to like that's kind of
satisfying if a hippo is just like
crunch you know no that's awful you're
sick and that no I'm not you are okay
have you seen the videos of hippos eat
watermelon or no yes I say this okay
okay that's it you just said don't say
this right coconuts or alligators please
coconuts it falls off the
tree the cartoons what does that
actually happen in cartoons or does this
make believe Le Nick people died of
coconuts no [ __ ] way that's why we're
playing this game Nick I just can't get
behind that coconut allergies are pretty
severe too though imagine sitting under
a coconut tree then you just get th
there's no way boink
Thum oh my God was the word I like
smoosh awful awful awful awful
alligators or coconuts alligators all
day alligators has to be eight people
die to alligators no a year don't tell
me more than eight people are dying to a
coconut falling on do you want to guess
coconuts or no 13 is do coconut
allergies count no Nick well that's a
pretty severe coconuts I would have
saidon mean allergies I would have said
coconut allergies Nick I'm talking about
physical coconut so you're telling me
that if a person dies via a coconut
anaphylactic shock you cannot deem that
person dead via coconut it would be an
aelactic shock oh you're right let's
talk about the peanut butter deaths that
was peanut butter allergy that's what I
said just wording whatever y'all are
Nick stop trying
to so they're dying what are they
getting like what is our slingshot stop
what do I look like my God so what is
happening someone slingshotting a
coconut at their face they're sitting
under the [ __ ] tree
and
no a Coconut's like no out of the tree
guess how many people per year it can't
be more than a coconut yes how many
two a [ __ ] duh those poor souls get
how many people die getting struck by
the Light
that's not on my statistic sheet [ __ ]
search it up all right hold on coconuts
I love coconuts electricity or
toasters what does that mean I keep
forgetting your like previous question
what is electricity like just like like
what like you're like rewire or
something got to be equal though like if
you're dying via toaster does that not
count as electricity I can't believe you
said that cuz it's equal 300 each 20
people each year di to lightning that's
crazy there's some cute stories about
people get struck by lightning and like
they're holding hands with like their
love and it like there there's like
enough body that the electricity doesn't
kill them if they weren't holding hands
they'd be dead true thing that's crazy
actually love is
electric what is this we should all walk
around holding hands just in case
lightning strikes I agree and maybe skip
that we go faster even in the sun you
never know birds are accidentally
poisoning your self who gets killed
don't even tell me this I don't even
want to know how many people
accidentally poison see I feel like I'm
more of afraid of a bird attacking me I
don't think it's going to lethally kill
me when you said accidentally poison
themselves in my mind I didn't think
like like oh accidentally putting like
[ __ ] in their food or something in my
mind I immediately went to like a vile
like the Kings when they like put like
the yeah the poison chalice across from
them and then like they like mix them up
that's what I thought someone accident
like dog on like I mean like bug poison
or something Deton something bad dude we
need to bring back like fun fancy
glasses like I want to see people
drinking out of chales more often right
why is this why are we exclusivez chales
to the king I'm with that I don't know
can you just tell me this one I don't
want to guess anymore it's making me
it's got to be people accidentally
poisoning themselves I don't
care Birds kill 75 to 100 people per
year you have to be pulling my tail more
than hippos
no 500
30 no he said 500 oh 500 thank you
[ __ ] idiot it's like the top killers
are the big birds like eag the ostrich
emu GE were on it oh no I hate GE yeah I
wish I and then accidental poison is 240
people die to accidentally poisoning
themselves per year that makes sense sad
sad sad yeah this was a sad top IC yeah
it was just a fun thing I saw on Tik Tok
these two guys did it in their podcast
it's like those two guys and they always
like guess people you know what I'm
talking about they do like 30 seconds to
like guess a
person what Nick I don't know you're
just rapidly speaking I they're actually
really cool guys we should like show
their Tik tokers shout out them you
inspired our car video thank you so much
I wish I was a [ __ ] clown I would not
I just want to be a clown Nick you're
about to be so embarrassed no the dude
that was doing donuts in the truck over
there a [ __ ] off there's two there's two
other trucks that pulled up and they're
like sitting and talking about probably
making out grown
men there doing stupid [ __ ] go
kiss I think just [ __ ] like that is gay
dick what like to go support your your
bro doing donuts in the Target parking
lot make out kissy other that's crazy
it's like a gay thing that's crazy like
I'm sorry if I'm like if I'm going out
and like my bro is like doing donuts in
a parking lot let's make out let's make
out what are you talking like it's just
stupid I feel like the Cobra that could
just sting my
prey okay a little weird right I don't
like the terms like predator and prey
just say strong and weak that's a little
crazy all right yeah baby happy Friday
we'll see you guys next week on Friday
I had fun tonight on
[Music]
Friday that's crazy we might be at six
we're about to be at six mil or we might
oh we might I don't want to say thank
you yet we're definitely going to thank
you guys in the next video we filmed for
6 mil we can't do it now because we
haven't done it yet so we're not
thankful yet because it doesn't happen
we have to say the thankfulness and our
true
fruition yeah I need to soak in the
thankful so that when the moment comes I
explode yes I just want to burst with
thank blow up just want to explode to
blow up anyways guys that has been this
week's Friday video go down there and
subscribe it's going to be that red box
if you haven't subscribed yet turn on
post notifications so that you never
miss when we post a video cuz that'd be
so unfortunate you're missing out on
like the amazingness and then while
you're down there you're going to be so
close to that like button like subscribe
do everything that you need to do and
also save www. Stern yellow.com because
right when we hit 6 million subscribers
thanks to you all we're going to be
doing a super special six mil video and
we're going going be going live with our
Stern clothing merch so it's going to be
a blast and I'm so excited and I'm so
thankful for you all we're going to
thank you more for 6 million subscribers
just because it hasn't happened yet and
we're expecting it to be in next week's
video but thank you all for
watching go ahead
man oh my God this kid's a sicko I
[Music]
can't
yeah