is it's really easy to create a company
in gen in demo mode it is a very
different thing to take that beautiful
demo and put it in the wild and scale it
and we've already seen a handful of
companies that you know were backed by
amazing investors kind of blow up
because they weren't able to transition
from that really cool slick demo into
the wild essentially into full
production the biggest question we have
for companies is they come to us and we
like the beautiful demo come to us when
you have a customer that's live
my name is Rebecca Lynn I'm the founder
and managing partner of canas Ventures
canvas Ventures is an early stage
Venture Capital firm that focuses on
investing in financial services digital
Health Andi so some of the most recent
outcomes of canvas Ventures are case
Tech Gabby and futur advisor and
importantly case text was a very early
exit with AI and gp4 and they exited to
Thomson reuter about 650 million Gabby
was acquired by Experian and future
adviser by Black
Rock so I have always been a believer in
in second mover I think first mover
Advantage is a fallacy and the reason is
is that it takes a lot of money and time
and patience to really prove out a brand
new market and once you prove it out you
have a ton of technical debt I invested
in Lending Club and from then on Lending
Club ended up being the largest US tech
IPO in 2014 and so lendy Club wasn't the
first mover there was a company out
there called Prosper who had really hit
the market first the best position to be
in in my opinion of a company is the
startup that lets another company kind
of seed the market prove that there's a
market there and then they can take that
learning and come up very quickly with a
better product and better marketing and
no technical debt I would challenge
anyone to to come up with more than just
a handful of companies that are public
today that truly were the first mover
there are very
few I think the most important
characteristic of a CEO is salesmanship
really a CEO's job all the time is sales
you're selling to your customer you're
selling to your employees you're hiring
people you are constantly selling the
company that in my opinion really most
clearly defines a CO who listens to
their customer and then is a great sales
leader it was Jeff tagney at doximity he
from the very beginning brought on a
customer advisory committee to help
inform him of you know what was
important to his end users in the
product and what wasn't and where to
take it very early on he would bring in
this advisory panel to like an on-site
sort of strategy session and they would
wireframe me of five six seven different
ideas and show them to this you know
panel of end users that would really
feed into their entire product road map
and he did that from the beginning so
when I'm evaluating whether a CEO really
possesses sort of the salesman ship it
becomes blazingly obvious as they're
pitching us you want a CEO who can sell
you on their Vision because of their
excitement and how they thought about it
and that they've talked to the consumer
and you also want them to be incredibly
honest and forthright with you as the
same time because that's what ERS trust
when you're in the sales process so when
we ask a CEO about you know their ARR
and is it booked or is it forecasted
having that c be very open and
transparent and upfront I think shows us
that they are going to not only earn our
trust but the trust of their customers
and that's really important especially
early
on the mistake most startups make when
they're scaling is that they believe too
early they have product Market fit and
they believe they they've got it and
then they go out and they hire a very
expensive salesperson who then wants to
hire a bunch of people and they just
burn a ton of cash too early and then
they have to let that salesperson go and
then go back to the drawing board and
kind of sort out a little bit more you
know what those elements of product
Market fit are and then rehire it's hard
to watch I think almost every startup
does this especially in the Enterprise
space and and our advice is you know
just way to beat hire maybe that
director level salesperson who can help
you maybe a chief of staff that can help
you in in your sales efforts and then
really make sure you scale gradually
when you think you have product Market
fit have some more checkpoints you know
before you go out and pay a lot of money
for a head sales person person before
you have product Market fit you know
what there's an example so case text
pretty early thought they had product
Market fit and they hired a very good
you know Season sales executive to come
in they spent quite a bit of money on
the sales exact and the team and it it
wasn't working they weren't getting the
traction that they had hoped for this is
before they launched co- counil the GPT
4 product the founder to his credit made
a pretty quick early decision to let
that team go and it was really hard you
know the salesperson was great it wasn't
an issue with them it was an issue with
you know where we were at that time with
the product you know it was really about
supporting the founder he kind of saw
also that was the right answer but it
was a hard answer it was a hard thing
for him to execute and so helping him
think through how to message it how to
make that happen and introducing him to
other Founders who've had to make
similar tough choices so that he can get
their firsthand experience and advice
was really helpful often times the
founder does have Instinct and data that
I don't so I first seek to understand
why they're heading in the direction
they're heading and then if we become
pretty convinced that it is the wrong
direction we try to show not tell and so
we we try to find the right people to
introduce them to that will offer them
you know a more complete picture of the
way we're thinking about the world and
often times we get there it's not that
they were completely in the wrong
direction and we were right often times
there's some kind of meeting in the
middle I think the first thing that we
need to do is check our assumptions
understand where the founder is coming
from and then get them the resources if
they do need to make a shift and they
decide they make a shift like help them
on that journey and it does happen I me
there's I think every company it's often
times many stages you has to Pivot
either from strategy or product or
Channel or you know whatever it might be
and when they they get there you know
our job is to help them figure out how
to make that
shift what do you do when a potential
client says we love your product but
it's way too expensive do you give in on
discounts right away or can you
confidently defend your price hi I'm
Peter on with over 15 years of sales
experience at companies like Google
Dropbox and slack I've obsessed over how
to effectively answer questions like
this in a way that builds trust that's
why I created Peter on sales school with
EO to equip startup Founders and sales
professionals with the modern skills to
excel in Enterprise B2B sales this
online course offers real life examples
and ready to use B2B sales Frameworks
that you can incorporate immediately
from crafting the most effective pitch
deck to authentic customer Discovery and
even negotiation I walk through how you
could do it all and limited to just 10
students I'm also offering oneon-one
bespoke feedback on assignments ready to
learn and grow your sales confidence
check out the link in the description or
find me at EO
[Music]
school so there's a ton of opportunity
in gen the clear thing that we has come
to us is it's really easy to create a
company in gen in demo mode to create
this beautiful demo that blows everyone
away it is a very different thing to
take that beautiful demo and put it in
the wild and scale it and we've already
seen a handful of companies that you
know were backed by amazing invest ERS
kind of blow up because they weren't
able to transition from that really cool
slick demo into the wild essentially
into full production the biggest
question we have for companies is they
come to us that's a beautiful demo come
to us when you have a customer that's
live for the CEOs who come to us to
pitch sort of their series A and B
companies and even we look at a lot of
seed deals also the questions I ask are
really about how's the consumer using
the product what have they learned from
the consumer since they started the
company what was surprising to them what
thesis proved what was different and
what I'm looking for is that they're
listening they're actually looking for
that feedback from their users and that
they're listening and they're adjusting
accordingly right that they're not sort
of dogmatically adherent to maybe
solving their own problem that was what
you know the company stem from that
they're listening to what their end
users really want and need the second
thing I really look for from the CEOs is
what gets them out of bed in the morning
they really motivates them to do a
startup because there's going to be
really really hard times in the startup
there always are what is it about them
that is driving them forward what's
going to help them pick themselves up
when things get really hard and Shake
themselves off and keep going and so I
always like to hear the CEO's stories
all of them could easily go get a job
and get paid you know quite a bit of
money at a big company and what is it
about this particular opportunity that
is really energizing
them I was motivated to found cus
Ventures because I wanted to create the
Venture firm that I would want to fund
my startup I didn't start inventure
Capital thinking I would be here you
know a decade plus later when I started
in Venture Capital it was really a GU I
was going to start Venture Capital learn
how they made decisions and I was going
to get them to invest in the company
that I was working on and unfortunately
I enjoyed the job so much that I I
remained adventure with canvas this is
my startup and one of the things I I try
to stress is just be more confident in
yourself one of the most formative
things was you know what my best friend
from business school where we're taking
a leadership class
and we had to rank ourselves we had all
of these things and we had to rank you
know one through five you one being the
best how good you were at everything and
then we had to get up and say what we
ranked ourselves and you know everyone
was pretty you know I don't know modest
or whatever and she's like I'm a one I
was I was like who is this person right
and she just explained in the world of
banking that's the first thing they
teach you like fight for yourself
because you know you're working for
somebody else and why would anyone want
to hire you unless at least you believe
that you were the best possible person
for that job and that really stuck with
me you know why would I expect somebody
to invest in me give me money give me
that promotion if I didn't believe I was
the best person for that job be more
confident in yourself no one's going to
believe in you more than you