I'm really conflicted in a way. I can
see that that AI is right now it's very
helpful in generating many different
ideas on anything. You've seen that. I
both like it and hate it at the same
time. Sort of like how I feel about the
phone. Everything is like this. Wouldn't
I be a lot better at without the phone?
And I am a fan of AI. But I would not
seed to it the ultimate judgment. What
you think is funny or a good song or a
good novel. Remember it is being trained
on
averess but I'm not average. Each one of
us has our own sensibility and really it
depends on whether what your abilities
are. Creator has to understand they as a
human are the ultimate arbiter. If all
of a sudden we are seeding to algorithms
completely then I do think we lose a
certain kind of agency in you know in
our lives. You can find a way to be
great in your own
[Music]
way. I'm Bob Mangov. I'm the former
cartoon editor of The New Yorker.
I was a cartoonist there for 40
years. I'm a researcher in AI and humor.
I like pingpong. I'm pretty good at it.
I've got a very good jump shot. I'm a
person who is perpetually unhappy and
dissatisfied and makes the best of it
through humor.
I think partly I became a cartoonist
because I was pretty terrible at
everything else and I was pretty good at
that. I was always funny and I always
drew. did a lot of different things in
the 1960s and I eventually became an
experimental psychologist but in the
back of my mind I always wanted to be a
cartoonist and at the age of 30 short of
my PhD I decided I would give it a try
and I ended up submitting about 2,000
cartoons to the New Yorker magazine
before finally getting in. I end up
doing almost a thousand cartoons for the
New Yorker and I was cartoon editor from
1997 to 2017. I was interested in
computers. I bought the first
Macintoshes. I started to scan them and
in so in the early 1990s I created this
company called the cartoon bank and the
cartoon bank was consists of all the
cartoons the New Yorker rejected because
I knew that there were many very good
cartoons in that storing cartoons on
hard drives and then when people would
fax or call in I would access those
cartoons and send them to me they and
they would pay for them and The business
that I now have,
cartoonstock.com, is half of all the
revenue goes to the
cartoonist. As a cartoonist, my goal was
to come up with a new idea. So maybe if
you're just saying what other people are
saying, what is the point of your post?
If you're just saying exactly what
someone else is saying, can you have a
new thought on this? What I want to say
in a way is that I'm a pretty ordinary
person. I'm not a genius. Okay? I was
able to make some jokes. I hardly went
to class during those years from 62 to
66. What I'm saying to everyone is you
can't find a way to be great in your own
way. I didn't even start being a
cartoonist till I was 30. Use your youth
to experiment and do everything
possible. The job at the office is
always going to be there. Okay? Don't go
there
first. The caption contest on the back
page of the magazine or towards the the
end of the magazine now and online. And
every one of these images is in and of
itself funny in some way, but it's not
funny like a joke. it still needs a
caption to resolve it to make the humor.
So for many years I and my assistants
just looked over these thousands of
captions. But in 2015 I partnered from
researchers at the University of
Wisconsin to crowdsource all this
information. And so now there's an
extensive data set in which you have all
the captions ranked. And I've done a lot
of AI research and other people have
done AI research on this towards the end
of can computers first of all
distinguish can they be fine-tuned on
this to discriminate funny from unfunny
captions and can we use this data then
to generalize the ultimate aim is to be
able to give AI a sense of humor and
that was a noble effort but that failed
because AI at that time did not use
large language models. It it really
failed on the very first hurdle. It
could not look at the image and
understand what was in it. Here's a
mechanic talking to a clown and the hood
of the car is open and underneath the
hood are many other clowns is also a
businessman. So, it couldn't understand
images like that. It still has
difficulty understanding images like
that. So, I think it failed on that
score, but it did stimulate other
research that I continue to do. I still
think it's not a long way from creating
mediocre humor. It's a long way from
creating deep, meaningful
human. Vincent Van Hook, now he heads
Whimo. He emailed me saying it's great
that we can win it go but we really feel
that we have achieved AGI artificial
general intelligence if we could win the
caption contest. And another way to look
at it is this. In the 70s there was a
genre of art which was called photo
realism. It took a photo and it looked
exactly like a photo but it was a
painting. And you'd be amazed by it. You
would go up to that painting and look at
every detail because somehow a human
being had created something like
that. You wouldn't look at that photo.
If you look 2 years ago, people were
saying, "Oh, it's Dolly 3. Artists are
going to be replaced." I don't see
artists being replaced. You know what I
mean? AI is a tool and I can see it used
in a lot of interesting ways, but I
would not seed to it the ultimate
judgment of what you think is funny or a
good song or a good novel. Even the AI
or the AGI that people imagine that is
robust and safe and all of that also
might not be a very good thing for
humanity and somehow that makes us happy
somehow now what are we doing remember
it is being trained
on averageness but I'm not average each
one of us has our own sensibility if all
of a sudden we are seating to algorithms
completely what it is that we should
like then I do think we lose uh we lose
a certain kind of agency you know in our
lives a human sense of humor is that
about making a joke or getting at it
it's rooted in our vulnerability
it gives answers
to anything we can ask and I think it's
very it's I find it very useful ful for
anything that's factual. I mean the
questions I want to ask it would be the
questions I would want to ask my
therapist which is for instance how do I
deal at 80 with the diminishing
capabilities the physical deterioration
the understanding that death is real and
how do we deal with this ultimate
unintelligibility of being human but if
I talk to a therapist who's my age and
we had a conversation about
it, there wouldn't be any answers
because there is no
answer and AI doesn't know how to tell
you there is no answer. In fact, it's
just going to give you a lot of advice.
You know, you should exercise more. You
know, even though you're going to die,
everyone's going to die. You want to
live your absolutely best life you can
until you die. We don't actually want
answers for anything. We want
understanding and it's only human beings
who can
understand. Understand that it's
like I'm married and I have a child
daughter and I had a stepson and the
stepson
died
tragically. There's nothing a computer
can tell me. There's nothing an AI can
tell me or my wife about that that we
want to hear. We don't even want to hear
from other people, but we want to hear
from other people who've had a similar
experience, who have endured that. So
there I think we get to the existential
questions that AI is useless for, but
people are very useful
for. AGI is not going to have a solution
for that. So that's what I'm thinking
most
about. Mark Twain said, "The essence of
humor is not based on joy, but sorrow
and hurt and wrong." One of the
functions of humor is for it to deal
with our ultimate sorrow. So one of the
main functions of humor is coping. And
frankly, AI has nothing to cope with.
It's like saying, well, can AI master
humor? I do think you can work
collaboratively with it to get it as a
to augment human humor. Okay. But to
completely, let me put it another way.
AI is superhuman at that game over there
of chess. It doesn't even make sense to
have superhuman humor. We're the judges
of humor. And a big fan of it anyway. I
hope not. Or if it does, I hope it does
after I
die. Okay.
[Music]