Burst into the tank is an innovation for
the modern office space.
[Music]
All right, shark.
Hey, you guys be quiet. We're trying to
pract.
All right.
All right. Ah, that's better. That's
better. Try again. Try it again. Hi,
Sharks. I'm Anthony Poochie. And I'm
Nick Poochie. We're from Los Angeles,
California, and we're seeking
$350,000 for 10% equity in our company.
Sharks, it's probably been some time
since you worked in a cubicle or even
sat in an open office desk. But did you
know most offices today feature an open
design plan? While it's great for
collaboration and cutting costs, most
employees are less productive because of
it. That's because employees are
dissatisfied with their work
environment. In fact, a lack of sound
and visual privacy is by far and away
the biggest drain on employee morale.
Introducing Cubic Call. Ta the modern
phone booth. Cubicall is the efficient
solution to the shortcomings of the
design of modern-day offices. Our booth
focuses on the four pillars of privacy
needs. audio, visual, territorial, and
information. So, distractions like
these,
girl, I know, I know, I know, become a
thing of the past.
And our cubicle booths are fully
customizable. They can be finished in a
variety of colors, materials, and even
custom graphics. And those bfolding
doors allow cubicle to fit into offices
where every inch of space is critical.
So Sharks, invest in us so we can help
employers invest in their employees.
Which one of you want to come down and
get a privacy break from Mr. Wonderful
and test drive one of the booth? Excuse
me. I want to try it.
Let me No, we are not doing this again.
I
Oh, sorry. Excuse me.
Oh,
wow. There you go. All right. It's It's
really well. Will you say anything
inside, Robert? Yeah. Oh, you can't hear
a thing in there. Funny. Oh, you can
hear.
What's going on, guys? What?
It's It works. It's really does.
[Music]
Can you guys hear them? Barely. It
barely. It really muffles. It works.
Each booth comes with an air circulation
fan. Comes with a regular outlet so you
can plug in a laptop and two USB
chargers. Why don't you walk us through
the numbers? So, we sell the first one
there, which is our cubicle 2. We sell
it for $6,9.95.
$10,000. And what does it cost you to
make? Cost us $4,200 to make.
And how about the big one? The big one
is $11,9.95. Wow. What was the cost of
the 11K one? That one's $7,200. Now, but
wait a minute. Relation are relative to
that, they're selling theirs for about
$15,000. So, Nick, how did you start the
company? tell us. So, we started our own
marketing agency. It was an open plan
office and it's a family business, so
we're Italian, so we talk very excitedly
and we get involved. Come on. We just
got to the point where any important
calls or any meetings that we had, we'd
either had to leave the office to take
it going to stay stay home. I said, "We
can't deal with this anymore." And after
we put in our office and clients came
in, they said, "Hey, can you give me one
of these?" I said, "Yeah, sure." Once
you deliver it, do you just simply plug
it in and it works? Correct. Yeah. They
do have to be assembled, but as far as
we actually have a video if you guys
want to see it quickly being assembled,
you guys are fast, right? It's with a
little practice. So, yeah, ships flat.
It's super easy to assemble. Nick, have
you sold a bunch of them already? Yes,
we have. We sold about 70 booths. We
sold So, tell us your sales last 12
months. Uh, last 12 months, $495,000.
And when did you start the business?
Last August. How are you selling it?
Strictly direct to the end user online.
I like the solution, but there's a huge
problem here. You're making $1,800 on
the 6K version. Your margins are so thin
that the only way this business works is
selling direct to customers. Yeah, but
that's this is working for them. Why
would they end up working? Guys, it's
not working. You've only sold $495,000.
They've been in business for a year,
Kevin. No, but how do you feel about the
margins? Can you widen your margins? We
definitely can. If we get the investment
able to invest in the inventory, we'll
be able to add another 20 to 30%. What's
the vision? What's year two going to
look like? I mean, we want to get to
$2.5 million next year. That's about 300
booths. And we think with an investment,
we can definitely do that. Do you have
competition? Right now in the whole
market, there's probably about four
competitors that we compete with. Nobody
does a byfold door. It sounds trivial,
but you're putting these in because
space is an issue. Okay, that makes
sense. Yeah. You don't think that a
steel case could come in and undercut
all of the parts of this and bring the
price down by 50%. I I think they could,
but they they won't hit these price
points and these margins. I'd find that
hard to believe.
Congratulations on what you've
accomplished. It's it's great obviously,
but I've got a couple issues. One, it's
capital intensive. Two, when you're just
getting started, it's not unusual,
particularly for some when you're
cheaper, to get orders direct online.
But I think you're going to have to go
to some some other's type of two-tier
distribution. That doesn't mean it won't
be a great business for you two. It just
means it's harder to invest and harder
to get a return. And so for those
reasons, I'm out. But congratulations.
Appreciate it. You know, you're a niche
within a larger furniture market. I
think this is a highly competitive
industry and I just don't know how
you're going to break into it. I'm out.
I totally get it. My only problem is
there are competition out there that are
already doing it and so I think I'm
gonna wait a really long time for a
return on my investment. So
unfortunately I'm out. Okay. All right.
Thank you. We appreciate it. Appreciate
it. I mean just to sort of paint the
picture. So they do say that 80% of all
offices are open plan offices. Now by
estimates there's maybe about 9.1
million businesses you know in the US.
If we were even to sell one booth to
point onetenth of 1% of those
businesses. Yeah. Everybody says that
about a big market. But get it. That's a
kiss of death on Shark Tank. When you
say all you need is onetenth of 1%.
Yeah. That that's never a good sign.
I'm going to make you an offer, but it's
commensurate with the risk. Okay. I'll
give you 350,000. I want 10% of the
company. Here's how I get paid back.
Okay. You realize they came in asking
for 10%. I I'm not finished yet.
Silence, please. Every time you sell one
of these units, I get a $100. After I
recover 1,50,000, which is three times
on my original investment, it drops to
$50 a unit forever. Just what you want
in a low margin business. Look, it's
commensurate with the risk here. Maybe
Barbara can do better. Anthony, you got
to be careful. Kevin is a vampire. He'll
live forever. So, $50 is going to last a
long time. Um, I have a lot of
experience with this, surprisingly.
Here's my offer. It's better than his. I
think this is so complicated. I don't
know what it meant. Mine's pretty
simple. But I'm going to give you the
350,000 for 25% of the business. Ouch.
Wait, wait a minute. That's much worse
than my offer. Are you kidding me? Every
dollar that comes in, you get 100 bucks
and you get triple pay to mine reduces
over time. Mark, Barbara's forever 25%
of the company. You know,
Barbaraes to $50. That's very expensive.
What do you want to do? What do you want
to do? You might want to go in the
booth. We can hear you. Go in your
booth. You want to go? We'll go talk in
the booth.
This is hilarious. They're using the
calculator. Oh lord. Welcome back.
Did you guys hear us fight each other?
You had a word. What did you guys figure
out? So Kevin, we really appreciate your
offer. Yes. Uh it's a little too
difficult for me to figure out and for
the eventual sale of the company. Um
it's not a problem when you sell the
company because they just buy out my
royalty. That's what happens. Many of my
companies that's happened to $1 billion.
Go on. Still a little too complicated.
So Barbara, we would like to counter
with 350 for 15%.
It's not enough. I'm afraid I'd have to
turn that down. Yeah. I expect to do a
lot of heavy lifting on this business
and I have tremendous contacts in the
contract furniture space and I think I
can make the right introductions for
you. Can't budge on the equity at all.
Uh, no, because I want to be excited
about it.
What do you want to do? How about can we
do 450 for 20?
No. I really I feel like I need that
quarter slice to get really juiced up
about it.
Maybe you should revisit my offer
because it has merit.
Actually should think about it. Doesn't
sound like she's going to budge.
Anthony, I don't think these guys are
budging. What are you guys going to do?
What are you on?
Yeah. Okay. Barbara,
we'd like to take the deal. Terrific.
Good move. It's a good deal for
everybody. Thank you very much.
Appreciate it. My pleasure. Thanks
again.
Appreciate it. I think we got a great
shark in Barbara with her contacts. I
think it's going to do wonders for our
business. I see her point with the risk,
but I think it's I think we're going to
do great with it.