hey guys welcome back it is Friday
um
it's Friday and then it's gonna be
Wednesday and we post on Fridays and
Wednesdays so welcome to another video
today we are going to be doing a I think
this could only be part two might be
part three could be part four but it
does not matter we're gonna talk about
most likely too so you guys submitted
most likely scenario for this last video
well it's not confuse people
every day
okay ooh nipple dude that was insane oh
my God what
look at us
look at us mine's not are you guys
wearing both my brand oh I got a shirt
that says [ __ ] Chicken on it so
very different but anyways as I was
saying cool hat thank you it's not hat
it's my hair
um
what was I saying I don't know oh yeah I
don't know what part it is but we're
doing most likely to see you guys
submitted most likely two scenarios on
our Instagram story and we're gonna talk
about those most likely two scenarios
and say who's most likely to out of me
Matt and Chris yes
I feel like I need something
you know no not like a drink like Oh I
thought that's the first thing I thought
of you know
here
you're good as you honestly throw my
headphones around your neck no come on
you can look like a little dj
it'll be cute fine I'll do it but if you
don't want them I'll keep them do you
want some floss floss those dirty teeth
Matt come on just put the head oh we got
the OG sunglasses and the headphones yes
wait look at me
oh yeah can I see you yeah you look cool
that just really activated it all for me
did it it was like Transformer [ __ ] you
know when they like I need Chopsticks
and like the Beats I was playing as the
person I've actually never seen a single
Transformers movie no way so I feel like
I did I was just like eight who's most
likely to be a gentle parent
not me I'm sorry I don't think I'd
actually like I feel like I feel like
it's hard to say gentle because gentle
means like gentle but the opposite one I
think it was like use force and I don't
think any of us would like use Force I
feel like it's more rough who's the
rough parent I want to skip this
question please actually I don't know
like the wording I don't like anything
about it who's gonna like tell their kid
like lay them in line like be like hey
buddy
like I'm definitely the type of my kid
falls and scrapes his knee and crying
like get up dude it's a scrape go wash
it off okay well you'd get like
Band-Aids and hydrogen peroxide and be
all German yeah you got to teach them to
just like you take Falls but you got to
get back up exactly it's all about life
no you'll fall now when you're 35 you'll
have back pain and it won't be because
you're fell yep you know what I mean
actually okay because you have done this
like 30 times this week what you use
floss I use you pick it up or you like
don't play with it I cracked I grabbed
it I grabbed you Nick hold on it's weird
I'm just curious why you were playing
with his used dental floss because I
didn't see it was floss I have dark
sunglasses on but and then I saw like
the line the white squiggle on this
thing and I [ __ ] just grabbed it
because I thought it was lint not lint
no [ __ ] I just figured that out no need
to be rude so yeah what was the multiple
times thing has he done it yes he did it
earlier no earlier today he floss with
like a really long piece of [ __ ] and he
starts and he picks up and starts using
it and I smacked it out of his hand
and then we both put our flocks down and
then I went to pick mine back up and
accidentally picked up his it's really
not that big of a deal you're making it
seem like I like really Crave Your floss
to be honest I don't give a [ __ ] about
your floss well I think it's all due
respect your floss means nothing to me I
thought you were dirty and had a piece
of lint on there well maybe you should I
try to read it I tried to be a kind
brother remove your lid and you were all
dramatic about it go ahead no I was
gonna say floss and correct you but you
but I thought it was if you're gonna
like do all this make sure you keep your
own in line then
If You're Gonna Keep My floss in I've
never seen somebody reuse floss like
that either floss is actually they
actually tell you to reuse it when you
buy the little dinosaur things they're
like oh you can actually use it more
than once if you leave it on your
counter and I literally just saw the
realization of stupidity you know you
did it because you literally were like
oh yeah nobody definitely uses they
literally [ __ ] tell you you can hurt
me I was on your side but that I really
don't they you dude I've been to the
dentist where you used the dinosaur
thing and you're like oh you know you
can like use it again right like is that
yeah
totally a okay to rinse it off and use
it the next day that's totally hygienic
completely perfect health if you do that
like it's not the dinosaur one simple
question it's not but you could
technically and it's not like I was
reusing silly you're insane who's most
likely to get mad over something stupid
probably Nick Chris I feel like yeah
usually I mean yeah you're gonna say me
well you um it wasn't something stupid
you were accusing me of like really
craving your floss I don't care about
your floss okay that's fine
to care about my floss actually I'm in
shock can we move on yeah we can move on
shock's insane I was in shock when
[ __ ]
tell me
keep that thought going I was in shock
when we hit a million subscribers I was
in shock when we did a lot of this I was
in shock when like shocking things
happen you're in shock that I'm talking
about how long you guys just [ __ ]
argued over dental floss is shocking
would you like me to pull up the [ __ ]
Google definition
shocking's insane to uh in an insane you
usage of that word there's a good way to
get shocking it's shocking that we're
talking about the the use of the word
let's it's shocking you're actually
sudden upsetting or surprising event or
experience thank you yeah no [ __ ]
yeah I'm shocked and I'm it was
upsetting how long you guys argued and
it was a surprising oh Red Bull ornament
who is most likely to diagnose
themselves with a sickness after having
one symptom of it Chris Nick no Chris no
nick no I feel like I'm most more likely
to like next most likely to eat a piece
of goldfish even though he's at goldfish
19 years of life I do think I'm allergic
to it Nick thinks he's allergic to it I
do often think I'm allergic to things
that I'm not allergic to at all like
I'll have something I might throw her
and I'll be like
Chris is like back will hurt and he'll
like Google it and be like I have cancer
and that's not true that is true no that
does happen Chris Googles it and then
thinks he's like I have like six months
left to live no because I just really
think that I'm in poor health so when I
have like chest pains I instantly think
I'm having a hard aneurysm yeah like
Chris his he's more severe okay I feel
like it's it's both of you in a sense
where it's like Chris one he has one
major one every like seven to eight
months but you're just ripping them
ripping off allergies out of nowhere
yeah okay so no one but you more
anyone but you anyone but me Matt you
self-rescribe yourself with everything
in the book
it's likely to disappear for a full year
and then just like make some big return
this what no that's like you're making
that up who's most likely done with this
floss well if it says a year then that
obviously entails that it's not gonna be
more than that you're gonna hit me that
was like minimum
like who most likely to disappear for a
year minimum like who's most likely they
just disappear for a year oh I can't eat
with these are never ever said like oh
stated like Graham okay fine
you shut up I like your chicken
[ __ ] I like your hat
I appreciate that I was gonna try and
get somewhere but
who's most likely to disappear for a
year
I feel like it's Nick
you're a traitor oh my God
huh your loyalty to the team
scoffs ominous music plays as the
characters Fade Into the distance
did
that's actually a good point when I just
said I want to tell the viewers about a
story okay
my head's warm as a chicken's caboodle
right now okay what were you gonna say
caboodle yeah what's your story the
other day me and Matt were walking down
the street and it was like really sunny
out and he goes seems like Summer's
right around the corner
and I just thought it was so like all of
us like just so
terrible story anyway that was a story
that was the big story okay we can
definitely move past that quickly I
don't know when you narrate what you're
doing in life it makes you feel like
you're appreciating a lot more I think
you don't narrow it what you're doing I
think you need to narrow it what someone
else is doing
that just totally was the opposite of
what I just said
yeah I agree because I was disagreeing
with him and he goes you're Satan
opposite of what I said you look like a
[ __ ]
who's most likely to buy a lightsaber me
yeah what is it you
you don't even like those yeah who is
most likely you don't even like them
[Music]
I would buy those I love them that is
not true you're not the right thing the
little candies like Sabers idiots the
[ __ ] Star Wars lightsabers Lifesavers
the [ __ ] little well then that's
poorly worded no it's not you're just
who's gonna go buy a lightsaber like
nobody they don't even sell them they're
a fantasy world how about you specific
say from Star Wars wow how are you
specific say why wouldn't they be like
hey who's most likely to want a Star
Wars lightsaber but instead lightsaber
see now you're saying whatever dude
that's like Grandma like you're like old
man my head is hot
so take the hat off don't ever if you
can't tell the difference between
lightsaber oh my God 60 plus okay you
look 60 plus with your stupid hand
on the cup I thought you were gonna at
least say wig
whatever grip that thing like you got
arthritis okay
bro you wanna know what really grinds my
gears oh God like mine is [ __ ]
go not being able to speak you go then
I'm done
let's hear it because this is gonna
grind my gear so go
what grind your [ __ ] gears
and if you like your gears getting
grinded so don't talk to me that's like
the most insane thing someone's ever
said probably ever that's the weirdest
[ __ ] I've ever heard too can you go well
you just like being frustrated and oh
well sometimes Chris go no I'm done I
quit awesome I'm gonna quit you're most
likely to talk in their sleep Matt
Chris
no who I won't say my name I'm what I'm
I said Matt see y'all that was a
question mark clearly no there wasn't
you start saying the comments Chris how
about you yo just set me up to look like
an idiot because you literally said oh
Matt not Chris
no Chris it was mad the way you said it
Chris it was the way you said it was
literally it was the way you smacked us
listen it was the way you just said it
oh my God look at them
I'm not gonna take this kind of
embarrassment shut up I'm gonna place my
hat back to my forehead and never do
some foul [ __ ] like that again
use these because I feel like who's most
likely to [ __ ] dude I don't even
remember the question Matt Chris no
that's what I just had something to make
me feel like an idiot because I it's
okay I'll play it back do you want me to
play it back
I will if you you listen practice back
on
listen you say listen you say how the
story went I'll say how the story went
and then we'll put up a [ __ ] poll and
see who
is more accurate
go
okay I'll go first Matt said who's most
likely a good decision
you're so weird yeah good decision to go
first who's most likely as he places his
sunglasses back to his forehand like
whatever let it die who's most likely to
talk in their sleep Matt
Chris
and I looked at you like who's most
likely to talk in their sleep Matt Chris
that's what I heard I still agree with
you either way I don't care I wasn't
fully listening anyway God I'm getting
hot
maybe take the [ __ ] hat off and not
the sunglasses guess what I can't why
because I wanted to wash my hair today
because it's all a mess I get in the
shower turn it all the way to the
[ __ ] Edge literally all the way 180
360.
15 seconds later
call me a sinner if I wash my hair with
cold water it's most likely to shave
their heads I want to shave my head
I do too kinda so let's do it but then
I'm just like uh is there too oh is
there too much forehead there to show
that to me I feel like we should really
scare the fans and take a month-long
Hiatus and completely change what don't
use big water
a month long like disappearance
disappearance and then come back it's my
forehead what is Chris Hiatus is the
same thing I literally taught you like
you know when you write in a book before
it's like the first yeah but isn't too
big what's it called I don't know how to
shave my ass yeah I don't give a [ __ ]
about your hold on what
like when you're writing an a page isn't
like the first thing you write your
hiatus
[Music]
I think it'd be really funny to scare
the fans and take a month-long break and
not have them see it coming like a
random point and then completely change
her and alter our appearance as much as
possible and then also our parents
[ __ ] turn your ears on I thought
you said alter our parents
no that's my big stupid thing they don't
even post themselves we could obviously
just alter our parents yeah you're funny
you're not who's most likely to eat
someone eat someone's leftovers without
with with knowing that it's somebody
else's and they have intent to going
back and eating it not even looking at
me for I don't know I don't want to say
Matt and then ask your opinion because
we all know that you get confused
because I was gonna do when we all know
you get angry I feel like it's I feel
like it's it's not me I don't eat
leftovers oh my God what put the AC on
it's just something about me
whenever I get hot I get itchy bro and
I'm trying not to scratch myself because
I have dry skin but really bad I think I
got eggs in one
I actually like I love how both you
laugh okay son eczema had today while I
was watching TV and I almost
screenshotted it and texted it yeah I
just have really dry skin it was like
really hard not to itch myself
well it's because it keeps it spreads
out my heat
can I do anything to help I'm just
taking it away okay
let me cool down oh that feels nice okay
who's most likely to cry I have no idea
why you you I agree okay we film a good
video let's go dude sometimes sometimes
I genuinely will have like a burst of
them like I never ever in my entire
sometimes use a burst I'm gonna get
there I've never really gotta like don't
do it let me finish myself
find your head put your arms Behind the
Chair like this no because then I look
silly I'm holding them no I've never in
my life like cried randomly like out of
like being super super sad but sometimes
like when I'm like just sitting around
like a burst of emotion be like oh my
God I'm gonna like lose my mind and
it'll go away in like 10 seconds that's
cool that's nice okay we're gonna just
move on thank God great a great idea
and he sits back down
don't say that
who's most likely to fall off the bed is
one of them I remember when we used to
have bunk beds and Chris left on the top
and in the middle of the night like just
Royal and his body fell to the ground
that was [ __ ] hilarious who's most
likely to join the FBI me no I feel like
Nick's most likely to want to join the
FBI because he thinks he can be all
secretive
I don't really see it happen gotcha okay
you're a [ __ ] weirdo stop itching
yourself itchy he says ubern gotcha like
are you sick I feel like Chris could
join the FBI more than you
I'd really crack the riddles okay those
FBI cases riddles like well technically
it's all life's all one big riddle
that's awesome you just gotta figure it
out no I'm not I'm saying like life
overall is a riddle and every step of
the way is a puzzle everyone has a
different riddle to solve and at the end
of the day
my Riddle's gonna be solved who's most
likely stop laughing
okay yeah who's most likely to get
flashbacks me oh my God flashbacks to
what just flat everything and anything
oh that makes me sad
a lot of flashbacks making me upset
I'm sorry I was like when you think of
good times and you're just like sad
you're not there it's not necessarily
like just good flowers I remember a lot
of times I thought were good that were
negative oh don't say that that's my
flashbacks that makes me upset that's
not regret then you think of negative
situations that really were learning
experiences Chris everything in your
life is positive if it's in the past
because it built you to who you are oh
but I'm so happy it's the past yeah
that's okay who's most likely to walk in
on someone in the bathroom
Matt me my personal opinion is Matt I
treat you how do you talk so quiet and
like say loud stuff you know what I mean
what if that was me I would have said me
and he goes me like it's so quiet but he
wants to be loud just let it out okay I
got you say it again
okay okay until two fours I need you to
bring it he said okay open me yeah more
like it there you go you have a beast I
let him out
okay I feel like you don't really let
out your true like sometimes and I just
need to see it because I save my own
[ __ ] hit the anime things God you have
too much umph bro your umph is [ __ ]
you need less umph as well whatever bro
I can't talk anymore whatever bro
whatever bro I just talk too much and I
feel like an idiot bro you guys got to
help me out here okay dude stop talking
yeah baby stop interrupting people stop
itching yourself
I can't film in the summer because I get
so hot and we can't turn the AC out I
heard myself echo when I hit that D I
said hat
good great okay no but what I'm saying
is I think Matt would walk in you in the
bathroom just because he's a door opener
and like leaves it open like he often
leaves my bedroom doors open so I feel
like that kind of correlates with like a
bathroom
quadruple quadruple quadruple knock when
I go anywhere I agree hello
it's really awkward when you just walk
in on somebody taking care of business
you act like this is like an everyday
occurrence so I walked in if I was
taking a [ __ ] like all gross and you
walked in just how defeated do you feel
like we're both embarrassed yeah yeah so
you just ruin it for the like the person
on the toilet can't get up
yeah they should have locked the door
though what if it had no lock it's your
fault it is that's true be the knocker
don't not knock I agree don't be nervous
to knock oh put that on a shirt don't be
nervous to knock that's weird all right
come on bring It
who is most likely to be the Ghost Face
Killer I love the Scream movies
um
uh I don't want to answer this question
okay
me me me oh you say you don't want to
answer it so I look down and I look like
I'm on my phone during the video
hey hey
Chris is that Chris
nope it's Superman okay who's most
likely to sleep first while watching a
movie Chris Chris
I only say that because you only it
depends you're the one who suggests the
movie if someone else suggests the movie
you're like oh yeah I'll watch it and
then you sit there for 10 minutes and
you're on your phone if I suggest a
movie I'm wide awake oh
[Laughter]
it's in my eye Matt therefore now you
can move it when my plant get on it
my foot couldn't extend what's wrong I
got dust in my eye jackass what the [ __ ]
do you think is wrong I just said it
literally stated what was wrong three
times so this one's in my eye oh it was
dust you're you're like
oh wow you're helpless and I don't mean
wow that was rude blow low
blow I don't mean you're helpless you're
not you're pathetic [ __ ] you go [ __ ]
yourself let me speak I don't mean
helpless in like the term of like the
word helpless usually
listen I mean
stop maybe help us in a sense of you
complain and complain and no one wants
to do anything more than to help you
with the problem you're complaining
about but you don't accept help you just
keep complaining okay that's your water
you can put your mouth you don't help me
a lot tonight oh I'm waiting for it
let's hear it bad joke
it's as simple as a nice cold shower
there's no joke here
yo my nipple really hurts