it's true that at least 50% of the
pitches that we hear are AI every
vertical is being touched by both
software and AI but that doesn't mean
SAS is dead it's sort of why now what's
different why does the world need
another X what's the non AI part of your
product tackle something that's a new
problem area AI is not alone AI is not a
differentiator hey I'm reie Dom I'm I am
a general partner with sapphire Ventures
Sapphire is a growth stage software B2B
focused software investor we invest in
US Europe and Israel we're managing
over10 billion in capital partnering
with companies like LinkedIn exact
target DocuSign looker moft and more
recently companies like monday.com and
glean an Enterprise AI company I started
my career actually not as an investor
but an investment banker I worked for
Goldman Sachs actually in their
financial institutions Investment
Banking you know your primary role is to
advise companies on what you think they
should be doing in response to a
particular situation whether it be
evaluating m&a or going public or
raising some financing that's your job
as an investment banker But ultimately
even after a couple of years I realized
instead of advising these companies what
would it feel like to actually invest in
them and then help really advise them
from the board level having sort of some
skin in the game and chips on the table
of investing in companies that you're
really excited about there's a lot of
uncertainty but yet it's exciting
because these are growth markets you're
you're redefining a market or creating a
new market feel like I'm a kid in the
candy store and learning all the time
from entrepreneurs what they're building
why they're building it what's on the
come and it's just really exciting to
me on the market you want to make sure
there's a good Market size ideally you
want to make sure the company is an
emerging especially at our stage an
emerging leader or a Next Generation
leader one thing we see is category
leaders there's very few markets where
there's three or four players and
they're all roughly similar size often
times the category leader just sucks the
air uh out of a market because they
attract the best employees they attract
the best investors and the most amount
of capital they get the best customers
who tell other customers this is the
only game in town and they're lead just
compounds over time so we tend to look
at not just Market size but positioning
with that market one thing we're looking
at recently given the saturation in this
software and SAS space is sort of why
now what's different okay maybe there's
a company that has an AI angle and
that's going to create some accelerated
sort of growth over the long term but
what else is there's something
inflecting or something changing I like
to say what's the energy in the market
what is the end velocity in the market
you may have a big Market size but
everyone's happy with what they have and
it's going to be hard to go sell new
software into it what is the energy of
adopting a new software and companies
coming up for Renewal uh in that market
I think is critical even if your
business is scaling nicely taking a step
back and understanding the context in
the broader Market is there an
underlying Trend or inflection point or
a pocket in your competitive space or
Market space that might be more
interesting potentially and while your
company's going nicely now there's
another company or another pocket of the
market that can lead to even higher
growth we call it sort of missing out a
little bit on the wave I think that's
critical for some companies which is
incredibly hard to do when your
company's performing well and you want
to just stick to that l but I think it's
also important to understand that
broader context and I've seen that
multiple times where another company has
a slightly different twist or approach
is operating in a slightly different
segment or pocket of the market that has
more velocity and you can kind of take
off with the whole the whole prize one
thing I look for a lot and I talked to
customers about is velocity what's the
velocity of product improvements what is
the velocity of changes that maybe a CEO
or a c make on the go to market team how
quickly are those changes made how
decisive is this management team in
making changes there there's this saying
I'm sure someone said it like grow fast
or die and I think that's kind of true
in startup world there's something about
the compounding nature of sort of
growing fast you almost have to hit that
escape velocity to make it out as a
startup and become some sort of
successful company CU if you don't the
sort of laws of gravity of private SAS
just sort of catch up to you and that's
hard and there's a lot of pressure there
becomes a lot of competition because
people see your company growing fast so
you got to just hit hit that escape
velocity I think this velocity of
decision- making that that you do across
product and go to market in an
organization what do you do when a
potential client says we love your
product but it's way too expensive do
you give in on discounts right away or
can you confidently defend your price hi
I'm Peter on with over 15 years of sales
experience at companies like Google
Dropbox and Slack I'm obsessed over how
to effectively answer questions like
this in a way that builds trust that's
why I created Peter on sales school with
EO to equip startup Founders and sales
professionals with the modern skills to
excel in Enterprise B2B sales this
online course offers real life examples
and ready to use B2B sales Frameworks
that you can incorporate immediately
from crafting the most effective p deck
to authentic customer Discovery and even
negotiation I walk through how you could
do it all and limited to just 10
students I'm also offering one-on-one
bespoke feedback on assignments ready to
learn and grow your sales confidence
check out the link in the description or
find me at EO
School recent marketing conditions are
interesting is highly saturated with
hundreds if not thousands I think the
latest that was of rather large maybe 30
million to kind of 300 million ARR
enterprise software assas businesses
from infrastructures to application
businesses there's a plethora of them
that are out there in the private
markets every single category is
saturated and also getting funded by the
way at the very early stages so if
you're a Founder tackling something I
would say really push yourself to say
why does the world need another X or
tackle something that's a new problem
area tackle something that's you know
never been done before or in a vertical
that hasn't been touched before because
by the way the other Trend I'm seeing is
every vertical is being touched by both
software and AI now ask yourself the why
now why is this important why does the
world need another one of these
companies because ultimately investors
are looking for that as well what's the
difference in this narrative it's true
that at least 50% of the pitches that we
hear are AI already maybe even 60 70%
but that doesn't mean SAS is dead to me
those are still SAS companies AI is not
alone AI is not a differentiator it may
use AI as a technology enabler but it's
not AI is not the product AI is just a
small kind of piece of the product that
they're leveraging in really creative
ways like I said if AI is your full
product there's probably something wrong
and we probably won't invest you have to
have an approach of some non-ai
technology and Integrations workflows
that are are different in and around
that that I think are critical and so
that's that's what people are looking
for I invested in monday.com in 200
maybe 189 what was interesting to me
about monday.com was you had two
Founders in Iran and Roy who really just
had incredible conviction in their own
Direction and vision uh well one they
they presented to me and a group on my
colleagues and it was that night
actually I booked a red eyee over to Tel
Aviv flew out there to spend the whole
day with them and they were shocked and
surprised there was a plethora of
companies here in Silicon Valley that
were attacking the same Market with
maybe more interesting Silicon Valley
logos as customers but Monday and Roy
Iran just had a different way of doing
things I just saw that they just just
had true belief in their vision and it
was very well thought out why they would
succeed it was that founder sort of
conviction I saw that really left an
impression on me that was just really
unique in our time together I think
people sometimes don't quite get that
they think Road stage is just very
formulaic everything's sort of working
and you price the company and you try to
get money in there's still a lot that
has to work out even at later stages and
at monday.com there was a lot that still
had to work out but there's something
that excited me there's something that
stuck with me about that company and
about that meeting that leaves me that
energized to sleep 3 four hours a night
for multiple nights and to me that's now
become a signal I thought it was used to
be a flaw maybe it still is but now it's
a signal to me and that happened with
Monday and that happened with many other
other businesses since our business is
pretty simple in some ways it's
investing in people you like and you
admire that just move you in some way I
think every investor needs to adapt to
the entrepreneur and founder that
they're working with I think if if a VC
is needing to operate the business
that's not really the entrepreneur that
a VC even wants to back in the first
place we want to back an entrepreneur
that says kind of get out of my way I
know what I'm doing here but hey can you
tell me how much I should compensate
this sales person and can you tell me
how many companies of yours operates in
three different distinct go to market
segments are there metrics or kpis can
you introduce me to a CTO and your
portfolio can you sit down with me talk
about usage based pricing models versus
seat-based pricing models and how that's
evolving across your portfolio or what
you think how would you think it appli
those are the questions that VC should
be there to answer versus going in
deeply and really trying to operate the
business dictate strategy too deeply uh
themselves so again I try to adapt to
the company and situation one thing I've
realized from glean to Mondays an
entrepreneur really wants to to walk
with you similarly as an investor and a
potential board member and just just
ensure that you really are bought in to
their Vision have true passion and
conviction for their companies I think
that's still um Paramount in terms of
you know winning a deal and figuring out
what you want to invest in