if I'm playing a match and I lose a
point I can't worry about the point that
I lost cuz if I'm still thinking about
the point that I lost I'm going to lose
the next point in the next game and I'm
going to lose the match the same is true
in a startup we had like seven or eight
people in so I'm in my master bedroom
closet getting a call from an investor
hoping for a yes and we got a no that
was super painful we weren't ready for
that but it motivated us to be better
move faster and things moved on and so
later that year we were raising a series
a and that same investor came back
around actually saying hey I've heard
about the progress I'm seeing everything
you guys are doing I'd love to be a part
of the round I don't see no as a failure
if I'm doing the same thing over and
over and not learning that's failure but
if there's mistakes along the way and
I'm learning from that I actually see
that as a positive thing I don't
necessarily see that as a failure
ultimately that's that's just part of
the
journey I'm be Mami mosaic. Tech is a
strategic Finance platform we hook in to
data sources across the business and
automate a lot of the manual work that
Finance teams would be traditional doing
we debuted as number 97 on the deoe fast
500 and so that's for the fastest 500
growing tech companies for Revenue
perspectives pretty happy to be top 100
on that list and I think it's just a
testament to all the team's hard work
over the last few years to hit those
numbers
[Music]
uh my dad moved to the United States
when he was 18 to escape the revolution
in Iran working three jobs to pay for
college was sending money back to his
family ended up getting two degrees in 3
years and so I think that work ethic
that tenacity was something that he had
something that my mom had and was just
kind of the way that I was raised for me
I think the first time that I really
started to see that in myself was on the
tennis court played competitive tennis
growing up for me was never the most
talented person never the most athletic
on the court but I felt like if I was
training harder than everyone that would
put me in a position to where I would
have a chance to win any match before
I'd get ready for tennis tournaments
they'd always have these National
tournaments over the summer and they
would be in the hottest places so San
Antonio in August which is 100° 100%
humidity or maybe it's Fort Lauderdale
Florida and the weather here doesn't
really get you prepared for that what
that would mean for me is going out to
Palm Springs training and sweatpants and
a hoodie in 100 degree weather for a
week getting ready for those tournaments
and that's definitely the attitude that
I've kind of taken with me throughout my
entire life I think that's the attitude
that you can't really lose CU you're
always getting better and in the long
run we feel like that'll help us
win paler is an amazing Company the
company was just over 100 people when I
joined the finance function wasn't
really built out yet and so we went on
this incredible journey for seven years
building and scaling the finance team
doing close to three billion of a
quarter dollars in Revenue by the time
we left when you've got a rocket ship
and you've got a company who doesn't
have their finances in order the
business was asking these reasonable
questions what's our cash balance how
much revenue do we have who owes us
money and early on because we didn't
have the infrastructure we couldn't
answer those questions ultimately we
were working really hard I remember I
was living in San Francisco at the time
we were taking the first Cal Train down
to paloalto in the morning taking the L
Cal train back up but because we were
doing our work kind of the oldfashioned
way which is using Excel to do
everything we were spending so much time
pulling data cleaning data mapping it
doing the analysis that if the business
asked us an important question it would
take us days or weeks to answer it and
with the pace of business these days if
it takes you two weeks to answer the
question people have moved on they need
something that is faster they need
something that's real time or proactive
paler was step one my co-founders and I
we each went on to be CFOs that other
high growth VCB companies if you don't
have the billion dollars on the balance
sheet like pal had at the time you don't
have a technical Finance team which most
teams don't you're actually in a big
disadvantage and the problem that we
were solving in paler it's Mission
critical every company needs to
understand their finances we realize
that hey everything we did at paler this
is actually something that's needed and
it's ubiquitous for all companies it's
not just a paler specific problem as we
were just getting the company built we
spent a really long time thinking about
the name we bought a dictionary and so
my co-founder and I we probably spend 2
three hours a day just paging through
the the dictionary we landed on Mosaic
the name itself if you think about a
mosaic tile one tile on its own could be
one system of data and that's valuable
but it's only so valuable but when you
zoom out and you've got a thousand tiles
representing all the data across the
business you can actually paint
beautiful Mosaic this beautiful Vision
about the company we're a small startup
we hasn't hadn't raised any money at the
time there's other mosaics out there
it's a somewhat common name and we
landed on Tech because we're a
technology company first and foremost
and Mosaic is really all about pulling
in data from various systems across the
business using that data to plan
forecast analyze do all the most
strategic important work that a finance
team is responsible
for for myself and one of my co-founders
we're Finance people we're not the most
outgoing that isn't really the most
natural thing for us but it had to be
done and so back to us and the way that
we sold and the way that we were
probably presenting ourselves we got a
lot of nose and it's not always fun to
get no when people tell you no I'm not
interested or they don't really
understand what you're selling it
probably took a few months and 50 or 60
NOS for us to really start to figure
selling out the memorable no that we
have actually is more on the investing
side so I remember early on there were a
handful of investors that that we were
talking to and we felt like our pitch
was pretty good at the time we were
starting to get a little bit of traction
and we got kind of late stage in these
processes with these investors and we're
in I think the closet cuz the room
itself that was my office we had like
seven or eight people in so I'm in my
master bedroom closet getting a call
from an investor hoping for a yes and we
got a no that was super painful we
weren't ready for that but it motivated
us to be better move faster build the
product faster build the business
faster and things moved on and so later
that year we were raising a series a and
that same investor came back around
without us reaching out actually saying
hey I've heard about the progress I'm
seeing everything you guys are doing I'd
love to be a part of the real so I don't
see no as a failure if I'm doing the
same thing over and over and not
learning that's failure but if there's
mistakes along the way if there's
something that goes wrong and I'm
learning from that I actually see that
as a positive thing I don't necessarily
see that as a failure ultimately that's
that's just part of the
journey in a tennis match if I'm playing
a match and I lose a point I can't worry
about the point that I lost cuz if I'm
still thinking about the point that I
lost I'm going to lose the next point in
the next game and I'm going to lose the
match so you need to have this attitude
where you analyze that okay what can I
do better but then as you're starting
the next point you kind of it's water
under the bridge you move on the same is
true in a startup for everyone that's
involved in a startup but I think really
for Founders you feel it orders of
magnitude more the highs are high the
lows are low and there's days where you
don't want to get out of bed you don't
know what the next step is but I think
it's really all around persistence and
giving 110% and doing that day in day
out over a long period of time if you're
thinking about starting a company are
you ready to be persistent are you ready
to overcome those tough days are you
ready to do that for many years and if
you are being a Founder is the most
amazing thing but it's it's not for
everyone one of our core beliefs across
the business and we have three core
values but the first one is champion and
the customer the way to improve your
retention is really understand what your
customers want what they need and the
more time that you can spend with them
the better off you're going to be
listening to customers I think two
things are important number one you have
to make sure that you're listening to
the right customer and the the right
customer from last year may not be the
right customer for today or tomorrow so
that's something that you have to keep
in mind for us the customer that we were
serving early on was kind of the SMB the
small Market customer the things that we
were hearing from customers when we had
those customers was our everything that
they cared about in the SMB now the last
couple years the focus for us has been
pushing at markets really trying to wean
off of some of those smaller customers
and focus more on the mid-market and the
upper midm Market we do still have
customers that are in that SMB space
will sometimes sell to them but the
feedback that we hear from customers at
this point we're going to listen more to
the mid-market customer than we are to
the S&B customer and that's just because
of the business that we want to build
and and where we're trying to go and I
think second is it's really easy easy to
fall into the Trap when you have a large
customer to bend the road map and do
exactly what a big customer wants you to
do and you have to be making sure that
you're listening to the broader customer
base and not focusing on what one
individual customer might be saying I
think our approach I'm really proud of
this is we've spun up this team we call
it the rapid response team where it's a
handful of Engineers it's a smaller team
but it allows us to take the requests
that we're hearing from customers and if
there's smaller or medium type features
we'll try to weave those things into the
road map it's a nice way to get quick
wins for customers make them feel like
their voice is heard without actually
bending and changing the bigger road map
that most of the team's working on I
think customers value it but at the same
time it's all lowed us to stay very
focused I think focus is probably the
most important thing is a startup it's
less around what are you building it's
actually more around what are you not
building I think for us as we started
Mosaic we saw other folks across the
business at paler folks legal folks in
HR folks in sales folks in marketing all
other departments and they'd been
blessed with these amazing Technologies
these tools made them better at their
job it made their work faster easier and
on the finance side for the most part
over the last 40 years things haven't
changed you're still doing your work in
spreadsheets um in Google Sheets and
Excel it's Rosen columns and the
technology hasn't really Advanced and so
we felt like there was an opportunity to
really push forward and bring this
technology to the finance Persona a
Persona that has been needing Innovative
technology for for years now so it's
something that we're passionate about
and I think if we can play a part and
make the role of the CFO a little bit
easier I'd be proud of of what we're
building
[Music]