I have unfortunate news and it's that I
have to piss but I'm going to hold it
this whole video oh my God you always do
this I always do this do you know who
you are I Know Who I Am Fam with the
Chris stola that's you Mr pisser what is
up guys and welcome back to the YouTube
channel it's a stola triplets here today
to film another amazing Friday car video
tonight we're chilling we're vibing out
it's a peaceful peaceful night like what
is he talking about it's so [ __ ]
weird we're chilling out like I'm going
to start I'm going to start doing it how
you would do it what's up guys it's
approximately 1:27 p.m. the car's got
four tires we're chilling out there's a
couple trees around here car we're
record we're Bros we drink water we ate
three meals I like your nice pants if
you don't figure out a topic in under I
want to say 2 minutes I am going inside
of our home I will walk there don't say
that cuz the people are like they don't
even like filming me anymore I love
filming CH sometimes will put the camera
up with nothing to say and then like
other than like he's like I got good
video topic and then we'll start do you
like sliced potatoes or waffle fries
right we're getting loose tonight like
no my zipper thank God I would love to
sit in silence Matt and see what the
[ __ ] Chris comes up with of I wouldn't I
wouldn't cuz he just do stupid [ __ ] all
the time all right he literally just
made a little rhyme he said all right
we're loose tonight like what is it I
didn't even no I didn't even mean to
rhyme swear to God I just found out you
said it um seen
I've seen newn I can't do
it
seen I've seen babies attached to
umbilical cords more behave than you no
I'm done actually feel equally as
healthy prior stop talking I'm not
kidding if you guys like I'm not kidding
I didn't say you were kidding I said
shut your [ __ ] mouth did I did I ever
assume there was a kid involved no no
not once did I say you were kidding
you're just unbelievably running your
[ __ ] lips someone said isn't our
rated Channel being discussed no because
we are going to be ourselves on this
channel and everyone is going to grow
the [ __ ] up what are you guys planning
to do for your 21st birthday I'm
thinking
Hooters I want like 50 wings and I want
to like be disgustingly sloppily eating
them while blacking out on beers at
Hooters and then the second I'm like I
don't even want to be halfway done with
my wings I want like 10 down I got 40 in
front of me and then just be like give
me 50 more wings and I'm not even close
to done with the 50 in front of me and
by the time the next 50 come to my table
I'm going to be 10 more done and then
I'm going to leave with 70 uneaten wings
from the table blocked out you should
get escorted out of Hooters for your
21st like you're like becoming a problem
literally my plan I'm going to dress up
as a Hooters girl for our 21st birthday
Nick what I hate that it's like a big
deal to turn 21 everything that has to
do with the 21st birthday I despise and
hate you want to know what freaks me out
a lot let's hear it I vividly remember
attending what Matt can I even speak no
okay I just know it's going to be some
dumb [ __ ] go ahead it's not going to be
dumit okay both of you stop aru arguing
is not fun arguing is not fun arguing is
not fun Hug Me Elmo or Tickle Me Elmo
what is it tickle me this is this is
exactly exactly what I'm talking about I
vividly remember our older brother
Justin's 21st birthday anyway that just
freaks me out cuz it's like whenever I
remember something happening for someone
else and then I'm about to experience it
it's like whoo you know what I mean like
I that's like a very fond memory of mine
which if someone eats a bowl of soup or
you going to eat a bowl of soup and be
like whoa no a big deal to someone close
like if someone turns 50 you're going to
be like oh my God I remember like my
mother turned 50 correct when you're
turning 50 exactly like even when I'm
turning like 30 I'll be like oh I
remember when Justin turned 30 cuz he's
like the perfect age difference so
you're explaining having an older
sibling yeah but I just think it's like
a crazy thing cuz I remember being such
like a young kid and it feels like
yesterday I mean that's emotional I have
a couple things I'd like to bring up in
today's video but I've already been
talking a lot so if you guys want to go
first bring them up and I will I will
gladly speak about it asio Coolio Coolio
who says Coolio you sound like an arcade
game like praising a little kid trying
its best it's like Kio and it's like
they're like midly playing like [ __ ]
knock them groundhog whatever it's
called whacka all yeah KN knock knock
groundhog knock groundhog that was like
a custom one that you love oh I might
make that okay if y'all see a knock them
groundhog I'm patenting it what H what
was going on the other night when we
drove and saw the lady in The Mask we
were driving home nowhere near Halloween
it's what month are we in April and this
lady had like a mask on being followed
by like a semi awkwardly tall mummy it
looked like I don't know what was like
wrapped in cloth yeah the PHA I mean the
Pharaoh came back know what happened we
we like scroll down our window just to
snip snip smidge yeah it was just really
weird and they were like murmuring it's
it felt like a different language but I
knew it was English no I was really
scared because like I knew it was
English like CU I could comprehend it
but it didn't even seem like they were
speaking
like no no it sounded like they were
just saying like adjectives one after
another red greenow blue purple yes
exactly like that correct it was like
purple light pose it's like when I do
those jokes about like how I some things
like it's just like crazy like oak tree
license plate lamp post awkward lighting
yes that's exactly how it felt no but I
was also really scared cuz the second
that she got parallel with our car she
took her NE she looked at it and took
the mask off and I was like if this
psychopath starts running at my car
right now I'm going to lose my it was
really uncomforting and what was really
tripping me out was like the assistant
mommy on the back doing nothing just
like kind of limping with an awkward
stride behind her toet no clue too much
purge mask weird cloak and awkward mummy
was this is coming from someone who
literally cannot walk in a straight line
but sometimes I see people walking so
slow or so bizarrely or like they're
limping and dragging their feet that I
genuinely catch myself looking to check
if their [ __ ] ankles are broken I'm
like are your feet SN in half with the
way you're dragging your [ __ ] tibula
on the [ __ ] cement wrong bone I know
I said the wrong bone I think you com
your your patella is grazing tiles on
the ground and you're [ __ ] murmuring
like I'm in The Walking Dead you are The
Walking Dead bestowed upon me I'm
literally looking at a Zombie Walk Among
the ground oh my God and it's just the
funniest thing it's like I can't even
I'm a crooked Walker I'm a like but I
hate slow Walkers feet draggers unless
you're like medically impaired yourd
thing like obviously I'm not going to
[ __ ] about someone in a wheelchair
moving slow you know what whatever
that's that's like they have to
unfortunately I've never like understood
when like people get mad if like there's
like legit like an ampute or handicapp
person like in the way like they just
lead a sad life like whoever get mad
someone handicap struggling what what be
like like what I've struggled with some
like just anxious thoughts my whole
life and I've discovered a new one
something that something that like what
it's not as it's not as major as the one
trigger it's not as major as as other
things that I've experienced but it's
it's it was there I picked produce from
the grocery store by myself for the
first time every other time I'm going to
the cuz people are going to be like
you're 20 years old and it's your first
time getting
strawberries wrong I I go I normally go
with people [ __ ] idiot yeah wrong I
normally go with people that would just
like they'll handle the berry section
I'll get like the cereal or something
you handle the berries I'll take care of
the correct something like that I don't
really that's what I would do but anyway
I cereal I went to the grocery store for
the first time by myself in the mood for
like strawberries and grapes I lost my
mind
I freaked out yeah you bought bad grapes
I I know I freaked out terrible grapes
not one grape makes the whole bunch bad
oh it did the whole bunch was no the
whole the whole bunch was it wasn't one
bad grape you saying that you are who
you surround yourself with and if you're
around bad grapes you're a bad grape not
true most of the time you saying you get
your [ __ ] hand out of my face I want
to punch you in the mouth I'm going toch
the
mouth I'm being I'm being verbally like
impressed by Mario right now yeah he's
like oh yeah get your finger out of my
face didn't
Balian dude I have a good arsenal of
like accents and like a great arsenal of
like correctly being able to say like a
sentence in another I'm so get in the
car listen I look like I look like I
look like listen you stop talking I hate
when you repeat yourself they're
screaming in a [ __ ] yeah you're like
mac it in Mac it in Mac it in I feel
like Lumiere from [ __ ] Beauty and the
be with these [ __ ] lights on like
this you need to stay in the car I look
like a [ __ ] candleabra you're ruining
my [ __ ] Central piece you saying you
went to the produce section for the
first time alone made me realize how
many places I haven't been alone as a
20-year-old human being congratulations
when we were born it was crazy right so
Mom had me and this is another thing I
was going to say they were like oh my
God you're having triplets right so two
more people came out right after it was
you guys
scar no offense no nothing crazy that
has to be the most alien like thing on
earth is an umbilical cord prove it
prove me wrong you're connecting another
human being by an alternate source of
like a tube umbilical cords are crazy
it's the most alien God bless women give
a shout out say PR let's say a quick
prayer out women across the planet that
give birth to [ __ ] baby children you
are stronger than men will ever be for
that Chris if you have nothing to say
say that so we can move another
Direction I have nothing to say awesome
for the first time in history leg legely
not only is it raining men but Chris has
shut his [ __ ]
mouth dude I feel like bringing a car
seat cuz you have a kid is so extra like
when someone's like like to a new car
you know what I mean like obviously you
haven't in your like if we had a kid are
you actually [ __ ] dumb no I'm not
swear to God listen let me finish let me
finish like right now
if we were raising a kid obviously you'd
have a car seat to put the kid in but
it's like if I feel like if I was
bringing the kid to a like a friend's
car who you are listen listen listen to
me I hope you don't have to cut an
umbilical for or let me finish my
thought it's like if I'm going to a
friend's car and I have my kid with me
and they don't have a car seat I'm not
going to make a big fuss over it just
Chuck them in the car sit down stay
still Chris you're an idiot like a
[ __ ] baby no like just hold him
somebody hold it hold it a baby yes an
incompetent unable to share its emotion
baby yes like like cries for tit milk
baby is what you're saying someone all
that thing you know what I mean look at
us three right say someone was coming I
had a booster seat till I was like 12 10
dramatic don't need it seat Bel no 10 is
crazy I had a booster seat till I was
like eight needing a booster like I just
can't get behind it just get in the car
shut up and sit down oh my stop oh my
God like I don't know people I'm so glad
that you're hopefully years from father
move on guys I'm [ __ ] around like I'm
joking I know the safety I'm just doing
this for comedic effect if you could be
an animal for 24 hours what animal would
you be got it let's pick for each
other okay I'd love to see CH as a fly F
correct so you'd hope I'd die before the
24 hours cuz you guys don't want to be
around no I just hope that you [ __ ]
like you are like it's like it's like
um I don't know I feel like you'd be
like a h a a parrot cuz you'd still
manage to [ __ ]
talk be a parrot cuz still managed to
[ __ ] talk that was really good Nick
Matt I already just made the joke what
is it oh no he's looking for what
animals can't speak I want you to be a
little shrimp in the
ocean it's like it's just so funny how
funny I am and how annoying you both are
Nick you're great I'm sick of his ass
I'm amazing I'm sick of your ass have
you ever fought with each other have you
ever seen a [ __ ] video on of ours
before just thought of something let's
hear it with your finger in the air um I
really want to do that thing where you
get like the hammer in the nail thing
and you nail it in the tree and like the
sap drips out you know exactly what I'm
talking about like those we'll get
through this together Nick when this
happens we'll look we won't respond
we'll nod our head and we'll move on
yeah next no I'm just asking if that's
like a relatable feeling Google it tell
me how to do it and we can do it
together yes ask ask the [ __ ]
woodpeckers if that's a relatable
feeling they don't dude they don't look
for
sap what what else are they [ __ ]
pecking the wood for let's find out go
ahead wood simply because it's their
[ __ ] purpose if a woodpecker was not
pecking wood get to [ __ ] work you you
have some [ __ ] wood to Peck you
little pecker go peck wood what the [ __ ]
else are you
doing imagine a woodpecker like flying
through the air it's like what the whoa
whoaa go you have [ __ ] you have work
to do go peck wood are you [ __ ] crazy
or they're like peering through wood and
holes in the face like little berries
and ants and stuff it's like uh back to
the tree the wood go Peck you [ __ ]
pecker pecker is a great word yeah ah
the peck at wood is to establish
territory W the
wood grandma oh they PE at a wood they
Peck at wood to establish territory find
a mate um and yeah and make a nesting
hole they peck wood or they find little
insects and sometimes that wood is
attached to the building so yeah they
can relate they PE wood so they can PE
wood debate which way should you hang
your toilet paper paper over or under I
don't care I'm wiping my ass with it
what do you think your last words would
be hopefully not like oh my God watch
out like in a car look out get or get
down would be the worst Last Words Get
Down would be awful or Matt do you see
that like while we're driving I know
what mine is what and it's the last word
it's not words mine would be I'd try PE
no I'm going to try really really hard
if I can do it for mine to be
mozzarella mozzarella no just out of
there or parmesan M that's a lot though
I'm going to name my kid sea one day if
I can and his nickname is going to be
parmesan okay next oh my God this is a
good question actually that we've never
answered what was your first ever
concert that you went to this is so
[ __ ] funny of an answer I don't know
Victoria Justice Victoria Justice one of
our friends when we were in like fifth
grade it was this girl that we were like
best friends with and she invited her
cousins M mat and Chris and another one
of our friends to Victoria Justice cuz
it was her favorite artist I think I was
like I think I was like that was like my
early stages of like paranoia and I was
just like it was the first I don't I I
don't think I realized how loud concerts
were I love Victoria Justice day like
I'm not familiar with like her modern
music like I remember all the songs for
like Victorious and stuff but she's so
cool like she's a great person I'm sure
so sweet I agree yeah I also went with
my cousin to see pentatonics and Kelly
Clarkson you guys didn't go to that I
was a really big pentatonics fan and I
love Kelly Clarkson that was like the
only other concert i' had been to
without you guys damn that's crazy I
want to get a pair of pants designated
for dancing so I can call them my
dancing pants that's good and I think
you should buy them you have a fuzzy can
I get it [ __ ] off me I don't give a [ __ ]
I want it there no you didn't you missed
it oh God you should have just let me
get it you should have just let me get
it I don't care what's something you've
never told another triplet do you guys
have like something I like I wouldn't
know that you guys were willing to share
with me on the internet right now
um I guess the answer is no um I don't
have anything like on the top of my head
you guys pretty much know everything
about me like I'm I'm trying to think of
something you guys don't know about me
and I can't I'm trying to think I agree
I think it's so funny that people say
like like people ask questions like how
did you guys know you wanted to moved to
LA and wanted to live with each other
and it's so crazy that people like think
like that cuz it's like no Hate to this
person but like we've never not lived
with each other like we are triplet
siblings so no I guess they mean like
continue to do that yeah but it's like
when did you chose Jo to live together
it's like we've never we never had the
choice to not I mean yeah no we did yeah
when we like moved out I guess yeah but
it's like it's a valid totally valid
question dumb ass you think so
100% 100% to me it's like obvious yeah
it's obvious because of the fact that we
want to live together but to the outside
perspective Nick yeah I guess absolutely
valid question yeah you're right
whatever I can I can take that L
pondering out the window idiot have you
ever shaved your legs Chris did a super
early on in one of our YouTube Channel
videos cuz we had to wax his legs as a
punishment yep years ago that was our
third video ever potentially crazy yeah
and then I shaved my other one so they
matched and I had no leg hair is the
weirdest feeling ever like that's the
only time that I've ever not had leg
hair in my whole life when you were
fresh out dude obviously you didn't
don't refer to like being born frh never
ever ever do that again you didn't have
leg hair when you were a [ __ ] baby
correct what I'm saying is that's the
only memory I like little babies that
are so cute I'm being for real my whole
life I've had leg hair on my head like I
don't remember like being no whole life
I've had leg hair on my head like in my
head in my head when I have memories I
never I cannot recall to a time where I
didn't have hairy legs all right guys
that's been this week's Friday video we
will see you guys on when actually no
Wednesday video this week we are going
to be posting next Friday and it's not
going to be a car video but you know
that that means that's going to be
something super duper special so get
ready for next Friday and I don't think
we have merch available right now but
make sure you keep a note in your head
that the first link in the description
of every single one of our videos is a
link to our merch website where you can
shop when merch is available for limited
time so keep that in the back of your
brain time is up I also did a um job
today for my brand so if you want to go
check it out go check it out thank you
Amen to that wonderful fresh love shop
in the description down below as well
whoa slippery hands Matt oh my God good
video idea Chris shh Matt wrap it up
[ __ ] what y
[Music]