Next up is a big idea for those who
think
[Music]
small. Hello Sharks. My name is Jared
Waters. I am from Portland, Oregon, and
I am seeking
$100,000 in exchange for 20% equity in
my company. Sharks. The world has been
through a lot of big changes these past
few years. A big pandemic, a big
recession. In fact, all of our problems
have gotten too dang big. We need
more cute in the world. It's time to
think
small.
Smaller.
Smaller. Smaller.
That's what I'm talking
about. Introducing Mini
Materials. Authentic, highquality,
modern miniature building supplies for
dollhouse construction, diaramas, and
two-scale recreations. We deliver joy by
the pallet
load. We use innovative techniques to
bring high-quality products that are
made in the USA. And they are as real as
they are adorable.
A real concrete, real wood, even real
metal. Traditional dollhouse companies
do Victorian molding. We do brief
blocks. They do picket fences. We do
jersey barriers. They do doilies and
frills. We do moving dollies and pallet
jackets. That's pretty good. We are not
your grandmother's dollhouse company. We
cater to a new generation of creatives
who make art with fingerboards and
action figures and RC crawlers. If your
hobby is small, then we are the perfect
fit. Now, Sharks, we don't like to make
guarantees about gains, but after one
day with many materials, you will be
able to lift an entire pallet of cinder
blocks over your head with one
hand. So, Sharks, who wants to
demolish a stagnant industry and make a
big deal with many materials? That's
great. Good job. Good job. Bravo.
Why? Why does anybody need any of this?
It's a toy. What are you talking about?
Because people need joy. And everybody
has some samples in front of them if you
guys want to start playing. I'm here to
answer questions when you're done
playing with. Oh, that's
so from someone who has had to wrap a
lot of pallets. This is adorable. Thank
you. When you said this is real
concrete. Yeah. This is real. Yes. It's
actually mortar. It's actually mortar.
Yeah. So cute. Look, even a little buzz
sock. 15 years, never seen anything like
this. Super cute.
How does it translate into sales? Give
us an idea of when you started this and
what occurred. I actually bought the
business one year and one month ago. Oh,
okay. So, the business has a lot to do
with Reddit with the online form Reddit.
Yeah. One of the original co-founders
was looking on Reddit and somebody had
handmade a concrete block and they were
like, "That is awesome." And so he
started making them and then he put it
on Reddit as well saying look I have
this whole pallet with cinder blocks and
people were like I love that. Went to
the front page of our went to the front
page of Reddit again. Dang. So lo and
behold pretty soon they had a very
healthy side business. I came across
this post. Hey I have a business and I'm
looking to sell it. So I reached out via
Reddit and ended up purchasing the
company from them. What did you buy the
business for? 200,000. And where did you
get the money for that Jared? So I took
uh heliloc against my house. So wow you
really you went all in. I did. I have
been always wanting to start a business.
What attracted me to this is it's making
things. And what what are your margins
on this? So on an individual product
basis they go from 50 to like
93% with blended rate of about 75%. Oh
that's not bad at all. What are your
sales? So in the last year I've done
$200,000 in sales. Good for you. Yeah.
And you own it 100%. And you're making
them? I make them. Yeah. How much does
this sell for? Uh, that one without the
logo printed on it is $20. And what does
it cost you to make this? $4. That's
pretty pricey. So, this is really for
enthusiasts or hobbyists that are
probably a little more mature. Is this
for children? Really? Like, I'm trying
to get the the the age like 8 to 12 is
what my packaging guidelines recommend.
What's the average? Um I don't know if I
have a hard number on that that I would
be 100% confident in saying I I do know
generally. Uh so generally well what do
you see on let's talk social media is
that answer my question. Well because he
doesn't know his
demographic in that reason I'm out.
So what do you do with social media? You
know I could see this like doing a lot
of stop action animation and stop
animation. People do stop animation with
things for sure. But are you doing any
of that to increase sales? I am. But one
of the reasons I'm here right now is
marketing is my biggest weakness as a
company. I'm not horrible at it. Tell us
about your background. Uh I'm doing this
full-time right now. I grew up in rural
Idaho, went to a two- room schoolhouse.
Uh and then after I graduated, I moved
to Portland. I blinked and got up my
first real professional job. Blinked and
then was married. Blinked and had kids.
Blinked and had a house. And life just
was flying by. And this like desire to
start a business was always there, but
starting a business and not having sales
just seemed slightly irresponsible for
having kids and having a mortgage. I
love how you said that. You know, I
blinked and 15 years later, two words
have never been broken. Yeah. Life just
goes, "You have a business." Are you
making money on the 200,000? I am making
money. Yes. Are you paying yourself? How
much? I am paying myself. So, so far in
that last year and a month, I have
pulled out about 55,000 out of the
business. Good for you. Good for you.
You know, it's it's really interesting.
I can see a forever perpetual demand for
it from a very small segment of the
market. Everything about it is small,
literally. Yeah. And and that makes it a
difficult investment for me cuz I mean,
I don't know how you blow this thing up.
It's just too small for me. Jared, I'm
out. I'm sorry to hear that. I do think
there is a lot of good upside. I think
it's cute as can be. It's not a business
for me, but I think it's a great
business for you, and I wish you good
luck, but I'm out.
Thank you, Jared. I blinked and I've
been here for 15 years. Um, what I've
learned is if you have a good business,
you can get it to 2 to 3 million by
sheer willpower of your execution. You
can make a fantastic living, but as an
investor, I need to see more scale. I
don't see it beyond that. So, I'm going
to be out just for that. wish you all
the best.
So uh I think there is upwards of room
for Jared entrepreneurs are willing to
take the pain of working working to
avoid the pain of looking back when
you're 70 80 90 years old and never had
tried. Yes. And so you get a ton of
credit for going for it. I think this
business can be successful, but because
it's so new in inventing a new industry
in a lot of respects, it could take
decades, right? And I know that you
don't want to hear that sound of it.
That's a lot of pain. But I I just I'm
not ready to go along for that long a
ride. So, for those reasons, I'm out.
Everybody loves the product. Love it.
You just got to grind it out. Jared, it
is very cool. Jared, you really have
something here. And it'll never happen
fast enough, but when you blink again,
it could be a two, three, four million
dollar business with a million dollars
in your pocket. Yeah. All right, man.
Good luck for Thank you guys.