are we missing a drink yeah you didn't
get yours did you yes I did why would I
not go with the drink did you bring it
out here
like why is he surprised his drink
didn't magically put on the side that's
what I was brought there I didn't
realize you'd be so up to be fair I
didn't bring my Coke out here and it is
out here yeah who would bring every
drink I brought his Coke and then rise
it was just Coke so I left it and got my
own Dr Pepper yeah that's what that made
forever sense
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me
[Music]
hashtag secured this is like secured
periods
just in case there's so much noise
yeah
I forgot the veggies
um can we still get me Dr Pepper yeah
can you taste that I'll taste it Nick
give me that and take these ones
it's [ __ ] clown juice okay
we don't try it and everything today
we're gonna Feast on Wingstop
known as a mukbang no what is a mukbang
I don't like that term I've been trying
to avoid it down the food
I love the word Buck but I don't like it
with a combo bang like I'm a huge fan of
the word [ __ ] search it up what does it
mean dude it sounds like we're in the
Navy shut up
in South Korea a video especially one
that is live streamed that features a
person eating a large quantity of food
and addressing the audience
yeah so we're gonna address the audience
and eat a large so it doesn't stand for
walking down the food and banging in
your throat no it doesn't I mean with a
mukbang going on Chris told me to use
threads and asked you guys random things
to talk about so I did I sent random
things to talk about go and now I have
some subjects and we have 40 Wings in
front of us no
40 wings I promise we're gonna eat Feast
is there any Mock and bang and answer
some questions like this I think this is
the new flavor or just plain did you get
plain at all no no okay then those are
like the new earthy ones whatever the
[ __ ] it was Earth yeah then you say like
all right first question Earth and gerb
or something it's like herb oh Urban
gurb is crazy
drums are flats I'm team drums I'm a
flat guy you're [ __ ] weird drum drum
I just don't like licking between the
flats you're gonna love it it's like a
little game no that's the problem it's
too much of a game we're trying to get
right at it
we're starting with what we know
everything Popeyes was in a restaurant
and it was like a place it's not a
restaurant it's like both no fast food
yeah where is Popeyes though oh
definitely not a place it's Louisiana in
a fast yeah but does Louisiana have a
place called Popeyes
am I wrong
cause I feel like it's like is there
another plane going by yeah
this is just simply the altitude that
does to your ears
anyways what color do you hate most and
why
I love all colors that's a beautiful
name
no I really
but if I have to choose the least
favorite to probably be red all right I
still like red but I hate red it's not a
big fan of it I would say bright yellow
when I'm not sure right yellow but I'm
not in the mood it's very specific yeah
I agree like I can look at bright yellow
and be like okay but like if I'm like
pissed off and you just show me
something bright yellow I'm gonna be a
little bit more Angry trying to think
it's 100 and someone puts you in like a
corn maze
I feel like corn mazes are more green
though because they're not developing
horns well they have like yellow
everywhere I don't know I mean for a
good part there's corn and sunflowers
it's green they're like this in the
corner I don't even know what you mean
it's more green in nature whatever I'm
doing like neon highlighter yellow I
like the white one you add on
that's not highlighter yellow it is but
it's a font it's not a whole style yeah
yeah it's in like 2013.
favorite
[Music]
so long ago
happy dates in a in a video right now I
almost said in a birthday because I was
gonna say happy birthday next sorry
who's gonna try the atomic Wing I'm not
I feel like you're gonna do that yeah I
gotta do a last because it'll ruin my
whole vibe right now I think what's over
here I don't know habanero mango
habanero with atomic which one is which
I don't know figure it out okay
uh this one could be Jonathan
soda's favorite childhood memory
together you gotta Pat it around
is there a wing in there
okay why are you Incubus now look
the perfect dry rub Wing dude it does
look really good we used to be friends
with this girl that used to like there
was a lot of grease on pizza so she'd
like get a paper towel and like
dab the pizza
and Matt used to make fun of her and
then I just no I used to make fun of her
because she would have to put rubber
gloves on to eat food or to eat no
remember that one girl we used to be
friends with and she used to scrape the
cheese off Pizza yeah
sorry that's not so bad but because like
I don't know she had she didn't like the
feeling of Cheeto dust so she had to
like put a hospital gloves on to each
you know that's I just thought it was
weird stop making fun of people
come on I just feel like it's like
what's the big idea yeah see my thought
is if I had to put hospital grade gloves
to eat Cheetos I would just not eat
Cheetos in a crowd
like making a scene yeah to have enough
confidence to wear medical grade gloves
for chip eating she's gonna check me for
a cavity
yeah like I feel like legit that we've
been adults together for like a year
after I hang out right before we all
went to high school and like we were a
freshman you were in eighth grade and
just like our excitement that summer
that we were gonna finally be going to
the same school for the first time
that's actually so I was pretty late
mine was probably we all had school
lunch together in high school was I
there was no Matt wasn't it yeah
I think I just skipped
um skipped class A lot of that a lot of
those times that year inside with you
guys
skipped class
um
and our our homemade Sports tournament
in the driveway what about we made pizza
right on this table
yeah things you don't like about
yourself that
okay good answer good answer no I'm just
kidding that was funny
things I don't like about each other
there's not one thing I dislike about
Nathan I I honestly say this I think
every single time and for me it's Chris
is a [ __ ] pincher
like I'd rather be sucker punched across
the face than be pinched and Chris like
when he gets angry he pinches like a
little crab I hate I hate when
these [ __ ] are in bad moods
yeah that's a good one yeah
when Chris did a bad mood he makes it I
think everyone's problem no I don't bro
y'all raise the pants for if you agree
with me
that's crazy
it's true I didn't want to say it that's
crazy it's true
than bad problems
I feel like Spider-Man that was crazy
what were you saying I feel like Nick
has more frequent like
Outburst than I do I feel like 100
Outburst is like the perfect word Nick
has like episodes like okay did I just
get wet
do them okay I love this question what
what's the craziest thing you do for a
million dollars anything
that's not true
um there's not a lot I wouldn't do yeah
I agree you know but like
and of course there's some things I'd be
like would you streak at a sports game
yes yes fully naked though naked ass
naked yes like all you have is a sock in
your dick and you're running you could
take this off
monkeys you gotta get tackled naked
if you have to streak at any sporting
event which one would you pick the Super
Bowl go big or go home
what are you gonna do you gotta do it at
like something dude what's the what's
the if I were to Street the Oakland A's
yeah is that them they they're like
they're probably gonna get rid of that
oh yeah because they're they have zero
fans oh
like that like they don't sell any
tickets
it's honestly like because I was just
thinking if you streak that your nudes
probably wouldn't even get leaked like
it's crazy no we should
I think we should all uh I actually
really used to like the A's because of
their colors we should just export all
our fan base to them absolutely we
should all we should meet and greet an
Oakland A's game I'm so down I'm
actually where are they from
where is that California is it yeah
let's go is it really Oakland California
is it it's like Chicago California
that's why I'm an Oakland A's fan oh
look at
Monday night's A's game
take a look at that crowd oh my God
yeah we gotta go oh my heart is breaking
like they're probably gonna just and
this is like the the MLB yeah they're
probably just gonna toss the team oh my
God how is an MLB team doing so bad I
mean baseball just went downhill for the
past couple years well do they have any
good players shoot no I think they are
good
I'm just like it's sad honestly next
okay monkeys opinions on monkeys and
they just have talk about monkeys I love
monkeys big stronger I feel like
can I showed me a video yesterday
juice box and he had shorts on you're
just kicking his feet yeah I mean if
we're talking about what's crazy that
monkeys can just like wear clothes I
feel like it's like I feel like it's a
necessity to see the money it's a
necessity to see the monkeys if you go
to the zoo
actually like swing on Vines and [ __ ] is
that like a real thing I know of course
I've never seen that happen name the
plane
no
what about bamboo who thinks they should
have let harambe just take down the kid
I think it's crazy that they like like I
obviously I I can't understand how
that child got into harambe's habitat
almost like a jumped and then they
killed harambe
81. it's like if you walk into a bear
trap and it chops your leg off
if I ran into Nate's house and he called
the police why would they come in and
kill Nate correct
I'm not saying that very good point
well I don't know next time
if it's an Oakland A's player and then
let him go oh my God you guys are crazy
horror movies favorite ones like this is
such a game look at that oh my God stop
showing me that [ __ ]
horror movies least favorite ones
favorite ones can you watch them can you
not wake them up though
all right new plane
what the [ __ ] listening
high five yeah ready yes
[Music]
oh my God okay I see it you take one out
take them
you can do it like that too
[Music]
I feel like we should buy that app that
you can track the planes and then you
can like see where that's going I'm good
oh yeah let's do it that's crazy
what are you doing where'd that go that
was like a magic trick you should have
pretended to like take it out of my ear
or something all right what are we doing
what's the do you suckers off my finger
no before we get into the new Wings
let's answer one more question it says
what is a super unnecessary item and why
I feel like we don't need a comb if we
have a brush
oh we're talking like this anything
yeah I don't even like if you were
outside like
fighting for our life I don't know just
like survival no unnecessary item
I feel like they could have done
something with the brooms and the rakes
where it's like you could just nope
totally different okay I feel like there
can be a way better alternate bubble
wrap like every time I use my bubble
wrap it just like my ship breaks anyway
that was such a bad question then you're
mad at your faith Chris girl not me
let's eat another statues that aren't
like that are like in houses like little
like they're like busts of like a
somebody like come on you don't like bus
I like bus
all right hurry up read the things ready
set go thoughts on mustard I love
mustard
oh
what are you making that stank face
this tastes like [ __ ] candy like
lemon candy mine doesn't taste like
anything
mine tastes like water it's just like
lemon candy shut up and then the plane
goofy [ __ ] I love mustard I like honey
mustard it tastes like lemon heads
I like putting muscle on my Glizzy I
don't like like by glizzies when I eat
them
I like mustard I think this is just the
lemon pepper wing and they [ __ ] up I
agree I just don't taste anything I'm
not that bad of a fan though you're not
that bad of a fan what the [ __ ] does
that even mean stupid
oh I kind of like it
like it's very subtle and fun you
literally urged out ugh when you ate it
we're gonna shocked me I like I don't
like this a little bit more though I
think this one is legit plain
oh take a bite of it
huh
I'm serious this time
I'll let you hold it no
okay he angled it like this
all right I'll look this way
everything
tell me that doesn't say like that's the
point way all right so does that mean
not to have that one yep no no let's
just move on I won't have it okay
I really enjoyed that though
the plain one yeah it was who
because mine was like you had the lemon
one mine had like an ounce of lemon in
the first bite and then it was just good
chicken shut the [ __ ] up you have an
unreal amount of meat in my mouth right
now okay Nick let's play telephone go
who's what's up your name yeah go I was
predicting the question and matched us
to answer it go yeah
[Music]
um
now you're fine
kinda huh I don't hate them
what did you say kinda I don't get it
Krista do you like pumpkins oh I said
would you ask him
I said what's just your opinion would
you really tell him
he said it wrong
oh
I know it's lemon peppers
all right guys that's all we can handle
for wings today I'm not trying the
atomic right now I hate like such a
[ __ ] during a mukbang right now I had
like five I wasn't that I normally eat
triple that and I ain't like a [ __ ]
let us know if you want to do a mukbang
again I love salted caramel things like
well I haven't had something like that
in so long thank you all so much we'll
see you all soon
we'll be back shop our merch down below
Follow Me Down Below dude my door Dasher
was way too excited to give us These
Wings today we should enjoy your wings
I'll be there in three minutes I hope
you're having a wonderful day throughout
like
despite the fact that you do not have
your wings yet I can get behind the flat
now and Nathan gave me a new little
technique yay you suck all meat off
and then what you're saying how you miss
me yeah you miss me and all the things