can you believe it's 7:00 I haven't had
a morsel of food there's you haven't had
one thing to eat yet there's a mouse on
this Earth You Got Dunkin
Donuts you're
right from the island of Madrid we had a
lot of plans but they
all why because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving
different what were you saying about a
mouse I was going say there's a mouse on
this Earth that's eating more food than
I have
today but also
look I brought the Munch cans I
literally forgot that you just said that
where the [ __ ] you get munchkins at bro
sound like hockey pucks rolling around
in a [ __ ] plastic bucket today we're
going to do a good old classic would you
rather that's the topic
today like you always ask as we say it
you know what I mean would you rather be
too busy or too bored busy too bored you
can just find something to do
busy too bored I like getting stuff done
being like oh this this that it's like a
little jigsaw puzzle my brain's
collectively taking the pieces and
putting them together if you're too
bored you can always find a way to get
busy blah blah blah BL blah blah I like
if you're bored just get busy on them
but if you're too busy you can't get
bored I want to be bored I can just
sleep average Matt answer you guys want
to try the pumpkin munchkin yeah I'd
love it I want this but like a nibble
nibble I want it morsel wee bit don't
eat the whole thing it's literally in
your mouth like I don't even like you
made the joke but you got your spit Your
gush your gushy gush on it literally
didn't even get like no I don't want it
eat it n no it's hitting your uvula
motherfu I don't want your UA just eat
it Chris you can have eat it now sucked
on it I don't want this gross ass money
now and now you bestowed it upon your
own presence it belongs to you now if
[ __ ] bestow upon pres [ __ ] out
of here I didn't bestow anything where
did that just roll to I felt it roll
Stow run at 100 mph or fly at 10 mph run
run run at 100 I could just zoom The
Flash how fast does the flash go come on
come on he could stereotypically fly if
he jumped just really
quickly I don't think so right no way no
would you rather prick your finger with
1,000 roses or 1,000 needles same
difference both are stabbing me I'm like
that's crazy i' rather nothing roses you
mean like
Thorns really Mt yeah no the petals just
slice you open okay [ __ ] idiot I like
how you guys call me the [ __ ] idiot
this girl that person is genuinely a
[ __ ] [ __ ] but regardless of that I
used my critical thinking skills okay
eat poop or drink
pee uh-uh no I don't talk about feces
I'm not 10 I'm not 12 I'm not in the
third grade would you rather have a
rewind button or a fast forward button
oh my rewind God rewind rewind rewind
for sure fast forward when you
speak spend every minute with each other
bathroom Plus or never see each other
again every minute let's get naked like
crazy way to word it but yeah it's true
like every minute I'd rather shower with
you guys than never see you again group
decision agree come would you rather
never see me again or shower with me
it's just a lot to take in all I just
like it's so easy we just go back to
back
and wor it's so easy for me to say if me
and you were showering together and just
face like aw from each other if I could
never ever ever ever ever see you again
or see you naked I'd see you naked I
agree just drop it that should be an
easy what up bro I just need to say
we're back Chris is off the phone I
cannot believe how difficult of an
answer you have to that question I I
don't even remember what I just answered
so you coming at me all like this this
is crazy never see me again
ever or shower shower with me
sure sure let's [ __ ] that's fine my I
don't want to shower with you anyway
that's it we're good mat you're such a
Negative person up that attitude I want
you to get strum buoi go like
this go I'm not doing that shake I'm not
doing that come you need some high
energy in I get the high energy without
shaking like a [ __ ] psychopath all
right would you rather meet Abraham
Lincoln or end the bird's existence this
is such like all the exist Birds this is
Nick stolo 2020 core see the suspected
the the suspected answer would be to
remove the birds everybody would think
I'd say that that's what you guys are
all thinking that's what you're all
plotting I'd rather meet Abraham Lincoln
I agree I just want to be in his
presence I want to be grazed by Abraham
Lincoln by his presence by his presence
if I got to meet Abraham Lincoln and he
like tried some sneaky [ __ ] and didn't
have his top head on nah I don't want to
good that's baloney bro bro I would I'd
be so imagine meeting ab and he just
doesn't have the Hat on like
literally dude come on we're ruining the
I actually don't think I'd recognize
Abraham Lincoln if he didn't have the
top hat on I definitely would I would do
you have many pennies you see all the
time you be like oh it's the
[ __ ] from that how many people
on earth right now do you think has a
penny in their pocket not many not many
it's crazy it's a digital world nowadays
yeah speaking of digital worlds nowadays
you just invoke a memory this morning I
buy four Red Bulls from the convenience
store and you know four red bulls is a
difficult carry right I needed a bag I
was trying to hold him like imagin
typical thing I was like oh I need a bag
so I'm paying and the guy doesn't ask me
if I wanted a bag so then I pay I said
hey can I get a bag I said yeah correct
I said oh can I get a bag and he goes
yeah 20 cents I said I don't have 20
cents on me yeah so unless you want to
charge my all right next time and it's
like you're supposed to use your your
words and go would you like a bag so you
can charge me 20 cents it's like if
you're not going to ask me if I want a
bag and I do want
one it's on you what the [ __ ] was that
would you rather eat concrete or eat
wood wood some 11-year-old said this how
do you know they're 11 my 11-year-old
sister said this oh how about this the
other day crazy the other day I go to a
place right 295 I go I go to pay in cash
they're like oh we don't accept cash I'm
like you don't accept the currency of
the world yeah not accept cash is
like see I never have these problems I
always got a little bit of cash and a
little bit of card wa you get it you're
perfect would you rather look into the
future or look into the past you asked
this two minutes ago would you rather
drink pee or taste ear wax
no I'm not in fifth
grade A P poopy ear wax like stop
talking find $100 in public or what oh I
have $100 in a public toilet or $5 in
your poet pocket doesn't matter I'm
getting both if I see $100 in a toilet
I'm grabbing it it depends if it's
soaked I'm not if it's like [ __ ]
written like just covered in poopy good
off that I'm good never drink soft
drinks or sleep with your socks I could
sleep with my socks I don't think I
think I think that people are like so
dramatic when it's like like somebody
would you rather kiss your enemies he's
answer goe go go go I just thought that
was stupid so I just say it out loud I
think like sometimes people are like oh
it's like oh do you sleep with socks on
or off and then somebody was like on and
somebody will be like how do you do that
and it's like if it's freezing out and
my toes feel like they're going to
curdle off like icicles and just chop
off and fall off my body yeah I'm going
to sleep with socks on I always sleep
socks I always sleep with them on and
then I scrape them off with my big toes
and then I just go to bed scrape is a
crazy word no it's not the other day I
put socks on and they and they were no
one asked I put socks on nobody has you
oh my god Nick stop the other day I put
socks on fresh out of the dryer and my
toes were so warm bro that's that was
today that was yesterday yesterday yeah
stupid idiot that's wow I missed the
first half would you rather give up all
your accessories or your stylish
sneakers I feel like I'm [ __ ] like
what's it called Peter Piper picked a
patch of I'm not going to buy shoes if I
don't think they're stylish so is this
like getting rid of all my shoes isn't
shoes technically an accessory no no
they are a need no they're yeah but
they're they're necessity not an
accessory oh you're tough with the rhyme
I'm not trying to be tough with the
rhyme no you're tough with the rhyme
okay sure then I'm tough with the rhyme
squirt squad or cram team
what there's no there's no way someone
spoke that into the world someone
literally said would you rather be on
squirt squad or cream te we're good off
that would you rather only be able to
whisper or only be able to yell whisper
whisper without a doubt me and Matt like
that question is would you rather be
Nick or matt serol it I can't no it's
like so foul I can't even get in the
video say if you
like no this one's actually worse go
hold on let me find it
Go and
and dragged on the
floor how insane is that would you
rather swim 25 yards or Run 100 swim 25
well like that's like that's a [ __ ]
[ __ ] question cuz both of those
things are like granted
easy right I guess so yeah it's like
slight Jog and or J for minutes justar
like what's the goal what am I doing it
for you know freeze or burn to death to
death freeze oh my God I want to be a
cute little ice sculpture that someone
can just keep in their house like Narnia
remember when she did that what Nick
Narnia Narnia watch the movie before
both yall look at me Narnia
you think of Zora I'm thinking of Narnia
okay watch the movie Nick you look like
you're straight both work both work that
was a good example you said up top you
rather have a thousand roaches in your
house or a crack
addict [ __ ] I feel like a roach is a
roach where crack addicts come in all
different shapes and sizes a thousand
roaches though is crazy eat a bowl of
dog food with a fork or eat a bowl
spaghetti on the floor with your hands
spaghetti spaghetti on the floor I've
done that as a BBE I used to dude little
me has definitely gone crazy on
spaghetti on the floor of the kitchen
dude I ate I hate sauce oh I'm just
thinking about it just imagine like a
saucy eating dog food with a fork is
kind of gross oh my God cuz well once
just's human food on you could say so
much [ __ ] about like what condition the
spaghetti's in and most of the time a
pck for sure for sure for sure for sure
especially when you throw in with a fork
cuz like a spoon you could at least just
get it all down and be done a fork you
got to like spoon oh dog food yeah yeah
yeah I thought talking Fork cuz like
you're dripping you're getting a little
bit at a time it's like oh it's gnarly
it's gross dog food would you eat dog
food never how much money how about oh
my God I know people who eat dog treats
who was that weird [ __ ] be
someone who ate who I know exactly
you're talking got think got think [ __ ]
dog treats I don't remember some gross
ass [ __ ] we were literally from
school just like eat dog treats like
they give their dog want to eat one it
was like you know the little baby Puffs
those things are gas so good the Gerber
baby bites I don't know if that's what
they're called delous they're so
delicious I would buy those all the time
know I forget dog biscuits it was dog
food it was dog biscuits not that that's
any better lots of seating or big trunk
space Nick's a sucker for like extra
storage yeah and you're a sucker for
[ __ ] trunk
space What are you accusing me of this
trunk love trunk space you're always
like oh I can pack the car so cool and
you think you're all that he kind of ate
you up I kind of am good at packing the
trunk though cuz you're lazy I like I'm
the driver pack my bags never do that
cuz I pack it and then you unpack the
whole car you packed it wrong well you
don't know what you're doing it's like I
don't want to open the [ __ ] there's a
method to his Madness Nick shut the [ __ ]
up that was gross would you rather be
the rat from Ratatouille or the D done I
don't need to hear anything else what do
you mean I want to be him why he's
eating good he's in control of the
[ __ ] guy he's in a hat come on what
are you saying I don't need to hear
anything else I know what I want to be
what's the other one REM me the rat I've
never seen that movie by the way as well
Ratatouille never you haven't either
neither have I correct trash movie I've
seen it it's just a goofy rat making
spaghetti thinking he's him that's all
it is yeah it's like all right I'm I was
just in it for the food wait now have I
actually seen it fully through it's
something to think about not I really
love the Cars movie bro it's like one of
my such a good film honest to God
doesn't have Emmy or an Oscar or
whatever it needs it how many are
animated movie even win an award like
that absolutely are there are there
three cars movies or two Cars 2 and
planes no cars cars cars three planes
planes one planes two PLS three the
second huh go again another another
which one's the Spy one second one best
one Donkey from Shrek is the second
option of what no I already answered go
I'm done I I've already [ __ ] just
spoke this girl goes lock in track on
your greatest enemy wa there's nothing
else who do you work for crazy bat what
and there's not even a second like it's
not even a would rather lock in track
with your with your en she meant to text
the FBI group chat straight up not meant
for us would you rather be stuck in a
cage with five rats or five Cockroaches
cockroaches easy for sure just SPL them
all i'll kill those hoes looking like
just Just Dance Revolution in there just
Just Dance Revolution two different
games do you know what's the what's the
game two different Dance Revolution and
Just Dance Just Dance I'm going to be
extra just would you rather sniff Matt's
butt or Nick's butt what real one that
someone just said like you you have full
control whether or not you read that out
loud or not and it's just crazy that
you're like have a child every 15 years
or never have a child at all never I'm
already on the never I don't know such a
painful thing to think about CU then
it's like do I does it stop at a certain
age or am I like start 7 would it start
at
15 no start now and then 15 years from
now so 35 a second kid dude imagine mean
10 years apart from your sibling that's
kind of a lot that's a big hunk of time
yeah it's like you're like going to
kindergarten and your siblings like in
freshman in high school 10 Nick 10 years
10 years old rather ride a unicorn or a
dragon dragon dragon unicorn for sure
[ __ ] a dragon I got the dragon merch on
look it a dragon's far more likely to
kill you oh my God my NE and I'm far
more likely to enjoy my experience on a
flame-throwing
object dragging these nuts in your
mouth [ __ ] a dragon it's so corny like
ooh fire breathing it's a big snake
you're talking about a unicorn yes it's
like basically a horse like I know I'll
be safe twoy girl named Lily with a
[ __ ] tutu on no I'm not okay then
enough of the unicorns what are you
saying Nick unicorns are for
six-year-olds and under damn life is
crazy I feel like life is just one big
elongated would you rather question then
we just have to really map it out you
know what I mean like you are
the Explorer Dora at the end of the day
Roo aul it's like you're just picking
paths your whole life that's what I'm
saying like every day we just pick a
path we decide to follow it sometimes
usually when you say swiper might swipe
in and bust her balls a little bit and
be like oh here swiper to [ __ ] around
and like take your your jewelry or
something what what is swiper's goal
what's that be a little prick like it
just shows one it's crazy like swiper
just shows you that you got like nosy
enemies some these people won't know
what Dora is isn't that cra crazy don't
[ __ ] say that everyone know who D the
Explorer is not everyone everybody not
everyone yes for sure I promise you
whatever don't ruin my analogy cuz no
one knows Dora they'll figure it out
believe me that you're touching your
chair and moving it around sit I'm
trying to put it Forward ckey can't
don't call me a crazy monkey you look
like Kirby stupid [ __ ] big and pink
what's up what's
up Matt looks like like Wario okay like
I'm not I'm not even going to entertain
stupid [ __ ] like that oh you're tough
everyone if you think Matt's tough like
this video most liked video on the
channel would you rather swim with
sharks or sleep in the cage with a
gorilla in the cage what's the cage
let's talk about like the survival rate
if either of those things happen you
think you're more likely to survive in a
cage for 8 hours with sharks swimming
circling around you sleep you can't even
sleep there no that's why I'm saying
you're in the cage you're in water
though yes I know how are you supposed
to sleep dumb [ __ ] you're not I just
said okay turn your [ __ ] listen you
said sleep for the gorilla cage no you
didn't swim in a cage surrounded by
sharks for 8 plus hours or go to bed in
a gorilla
cage I'm swimming with the sharks you
got to look what happened to the little
kid
[ __ ] oh my God what I saw a video today
I feel like we can get along with the
monkeys look oh god look look look
literally oh my God not a
gorilla you take it off take it off help
him help him take it
off put your who's saying oh my
God that's sick oh my God who was
saying put it on put on put on bro going
to put
on no
oh my God yo that hum wow like I feel
like if I was trapped in a cage with
gorillas I just that's not a gorilla
whatever like monke gorillas I'd get
along no you wouldn't I'd act like a
baby gorilla and just like it'd be it'
want to nurture me it's going to be hard
for you it would want to nurture me like
I'd be like I'd be like The Jungle Book
like I just get along be a part of the
family you want to be nurtured by a big
strong I don't want to for survival I
would if I was swim with sharks are
being nurtured by a gorilla for 8 hours
in a cage I could I could build a bomb
I'm in the bro he's [ __ ] Jane Goodall
you're getting smoked second you step in
that cage done i' go the cage and i' say
I just hit him with like one like or
throw my [ __ ] or something this is we're
on the same cage here you know what I
mean I'd immediately get naked I'd [ __ ]
on the ground and I'd throw my [ __ ] and
like I'm with y'all get out of here I
feel I'd get away with it I'd be good
for sure oh my God you get naked [ __ ]
with
shark's just going to think you're a
seal you're a snack whatever shark's
going to be it's going to be against you
the whole time though right hours with
the gorilla with the gorilla no matter
what no matter what you have more
likeliness of being built one with the
gorilla than the shark and that's family
you are family if you think about it you
have to put them in that perspective I'm
family with you you got to go in with
the Chill Vibes what if they just get
all Rowdy though I'm getting rowdy too
I'm getting rowdy too it's see I'm one
with them if you actually think about it
there's like documentaries where these
people go into the jungle and just
observe gorillas like from a distance
and they're chill if you want to just be
nice to the gorillas you're good can we
like watch one of those document I love
that [ __ ] I love that [ __ ] like [ __ ]
no other I'd get I'd get I'd get in good
with the gorillas trust no I actually
think and then You' would be jealous cuz
You' get out of the shark cage You' have
no relationship I'd build a bond I'd be
i' have new family but you just said I'd
get out of the shark cage therefore
you're not life threatened in there as
well yeah but you're limbless you come
over with no limbs on your body crazy
Nick yeah unfortunate huh should have
picked the gorilla you could get out of
here it's true I seriously dude I want
to hold a chimpanzee where can we go
that'd be a sick Vlog if we could just
like hang out we could just like like a
foreign country there's like some
countryes jungles where like there were
just like monkeys going around we should
do that where are they in that video
that was such a crazy video he took the
man's dude I want to hear did you hear
how many times that lady said oh my God
Chris come on a monkey was taking his
jack off and putting on I'd say oh my
[ __ ] holy [ __ ] over and over
whatever I agree you're focused on the
wrong thing he's like who's saying oh my
God it's like do you not see this monkey
taking a man's more oh my God if a
monkey was undressing someone and
dressing in his clothes like what is
your issue all right guys that's been
this week's friends Friday video
uh I'm like rebooting we'll see you next
Wednesday and Friday follow us on stern.
triplets Instagram for a photo dump
weekly that comes out the same time as
the videos hit the notification Bell so
that you never ever ever ever ever miss
a video and subscribe to our YouTube
channel if you wish I want to be a
monkey one
day like I just want to be one with the
tribe of monkeys hollering and screaming
no you literally don't like what we just
had this conversation no you literally
don't I really feel like monkeys don't
eat bananas as often as we betray them
too like [ __ ] obviously come on well
like why I just I can't hear from you
cuz we just had this conversation you
disagreed With Me Shut up Nick and now
now he wants to be one with the monkeys
he like I literally just told you about
how my experience is going to go when I
become one with the monkeys now you want
to do it crazy bandwagon people be
careful you never know where they're
coming
from watch yourself kid it's
whatever and all the things that we did
we said we going to Trav from the island
to Madrid we had a lot of plans but they
all why because of but it's okay cuz I'm
moving different don't be saying when I
with other [ __ ] for my brothers