remember what happened last time we were
in this certain parking spot I blasted
Nick with some [ __ ] mango fun yeah I
remember mango fun I remember it all too
well can you put this knife away no if
anyone misbehaves I chop off your finger
one by one okay idiot put that down and
I feed it to
myself here we
go I can't even do that
like all right guys welcome back to
another serol triplet Friday video today
we're in the minivan again I don't think
I've ever been more serious in my life
when you burp I think that's the closest
I I come to almost committing homicide
cuz there's nothing more that I want to
do than see you dead when you
burp wow and I'm not I'm not being
dramatic but no he's not consider that
do you know do you know how many times
I've expressed Chris do not burp in this
car or within the premise of me so then
this is me releasing the bubbles inside
it's a burp rele the bubbles that
Direction and roll your window down how
you just mind your business okay oh
who's this guy I'm dead ass oh my
God [ __ ] feel like I just got struck
by lightning that's how [ __ ] shocked
I was by that yeah you sound very
shocked no I was shocked like I'm like
I'm I have a Stern face yes but I
literally almost just [ __ ] my [ __ ]
pants why is that guy walking cuz Chris
said something and I was expecting like
a guy to be maybe 20t away I didn't
expect him in my like immediate bubble
like homeboy literally came up to me I
was like I'm surprised I didn't feel him
touch me yeah if you drink that Sunny D
you better not burp in my face cuz I
literally will want you dead and I'll
kill you and I'll bleed you to dry in
the city National Park you know I
recently discovered that Sunny D isn't
orange juice is orange drink what do you
guys want to say I don't want to say
anything cuz then you're going to yell
at me I was about to say whenever it's
rainy and cold I feel like I'm in golfam
city but I feel like it's not the vibe
for that so the one of you guys want to
intro the video you must grab Paul
River's [ __ ]
what are we talking about okay um
imagine we're at an Italian restaurant
and Nick you have no cheese on your
pasta and the lady at the Olive Garden
walks by and she got the cranker and
you're like oh oh oh cheese please like
how does that make you feel I would
never say cheese please cuz I'm not a
[ __ ] that barks orders at the waitress
you know what I mean like cheese please
seems like it's like you're just like
being like give me the [ __ ] cheese
well it's respectful you're saying
please oh can I have the cheese no
please can I have the cheese thanks
that's how my interaction would go okay
i' never simplified a cheese please I
feel no cheese please just sounds like
you're really begging for cheese no it
sounds Rudder to me it sounds like a
rude cheese please hold on hold on God
oh my God smile three please can I have
some cheese
please e Chris is that good that was
disgusting uh we have a special guest
today and they're in my pants I have a
special guest oh my God I have a special
guest in my pants what the [ __ ] are I
love her now this is an icon she is
Bigfoot and she got a little bow in her
hair I thought we donated her to like a
kid in Nick said he wanted to keep it no
I didn't Nick said he wanted I think you
did Matt I just think what's his name
Lammy so stup snowy
idiot Matt oh my God put her away okay
we went we stopped and went home so made
different sweatshirt I literally fully
ate mac and cheese in between the clipes
you just saw which is insane to me
rather start your day with 12 sodas or
12 eggs 12 sodas that's disgusting it's
a case easy knock it down you need to go
to a hospital he something disturbing
what I think you have more than 365
sodas a
year Matt obviously that's disturbing
that's like that's more than that's more
than one a day on average but that's
that's obvious that I get more than 34 a
day or not 34 a day 300 what did I even
just say I think starting a day with a
soda is the best thing you can do I have
so many people in my life that drink
coffee in the morning and then they like
they look at me like I got six heads cuz
I crack a cold one and it's like this
and a and a coffee are very equivalent
yeah so it's like me having a morning
soda is the same as yours having a
morning coffee don't look at me like I'm
crazy mine tastes
better that
way just disbelief me see it was that
way can't do nothing about it it's human
rights
[Music]
man all right well me m we're going to
we're going to play this or that God I'd
hate to be in a hot airb or would you
rather hot air balloon yeah it's so it's
like windy and and when would you ever
be in a hot air balloon not now it's too
windy okay that's what I'm just scaming
to the [ __ ] group I just feel like
that's like a weird thing to be like oh
if if I'd never be in a hot air right
now it's like okay no I saw I saw the
huge gust of wind and I would be like I
would hate to be in a hot air balloon
I'd hate to be suspended in the air by a
balloon on a windy day is that a crazy
sentence no it's not it's not but it's
like the fact that you think of a hot
air balloon first is what's crazy my
nipples are kind of hard can I feel them
no experience a constant pain or a
constant itch constant pain I go through
constant itch and it's the worst thing
ever I feel like I'm already in don't
say that don't admit to that the
constant itch no my back obviously would
you rather Skydive or bungee jump bungee
jump Skydive I'd rather freef fall into
a brick wall I think I could totally I
would totally dive like if someone was
shooting y'all I'd dive for come on no I
totally would I swear like action movie
moment catch the bullet and then you die
in my arms and I'm like no like that
type of I don't like that I don't either
I don't like talking about negativity
and death you're painting the picture
here yeah but I was more heroic in my
vision you made me seem like a coward
bleeding out on the street no drink
whatever you want for the rest of your
life but it has to have a drop of pee in
it or just water I can deal with a drop
of pee I can easily deal with it I think
it's healthy for you it like cleans the
system don't go that far I'm serious you
don't have to go that far no I'm serious
people do that sometimes no one does
that search it up no um Pat a hulaan he
did that from dodgeball the fictional
character patches a hoola hand yeah I
feel like astronauts had to do that they
put it through a cycle or something this
is liquid that went into your body that
you don't need so it's just going to
continue to do the cycle I just try to
be more cautious and lean the more way
of water but like if I want a soda I
tried to lean the way of water okay
Avatar thank you no ride a camel in a
desert or be carried by a squad of
penguins I don't want to take the that's
would you rather ride a scooter or like
Sprint for a decade like obviously I'm
taking that's a different question
completely but no but what that one's
stupid cuz one's like a realistic stupid
that one is stupid it's like a one is
like a super realistic scenario like I
could hypothetically hop on a camel and
ride it
but I'm serious the penguins are stupid
no but how many times you going to get
halted in the air by [ __ ] 12 dozen
little 12 dozen that's
144 my bad that was good thank you it's
been a long time since I've exercised
those brain muscles but they are back in
Action would you rather eat wood or eat
glass wood I'm not getting clip s I'm
eating wood so good luck with
that no every SLE I didn't say that
every single time my throat itches I
just wish I could swallow a bottle cap
and just have it scratch all the way
down a bottle cap yeah just those ridges
just get all the is let me get it just
reaching your
throat yo I need to call someone I got
to get out of here that was insane yeah
that was the craziest thing you've ever
said would you rather eat a beastro
mistro cafe or file bankruptcy who the
[ __ ] is beastro mistro I don't know I
made it
up all right someone said Matt's left
ball or Chris's right ball would you
rather have fur or scales on your body
fur fur scales are you serious fur I
could like braid it and like pick the
little bugs out of your back scales are
like I'd feel so slimy and
gross I'm thinking if I had scales I'd
be aquatic like I'd be like I'd be in
the ocean
wrong you'd be a reptile scales fish
scales mermaid scales snakes have scales
idiot okay but I'm not a snake I in this
imaginary scenario I'd be like okay I'm
aquatic do you get to selected animal
when you get there fish have scales be a
fish or SC I'm a human and I have scales
so I'd be a mermaid no you wouldn't
obviously no you would you think I'd be
a dragon you think if a human had scales
they'd be closer to a dragon than a
mermaid what am I when did I say dragon
or you drag that out of my mouth you
stupid [ __ ] that's a that's a land
animal that's a land animal it's not
Dron I'm saying a human I'm saying hey
that was a good joke if that was Nick
you guys laugh he said I'm saying hey if
you're in my face you selected you're a
hypnotist I'm going to knock you out if
you SED scales if you selected scales
you'd just be you with scales I'm going
to be me with fur but him don't call
yourself him you don't have the
authority to call yourself him yes I do
if I'm confident in myself I'm him would
you rather you're somebody who needs to
fix those damn glasses on your phone in
oh and you someone who just
ate would you rather that face in me
would you rather do the cinnamon
challenge or eat a full healthy handful
of breadcrumbs I didn't like this but
I'll I'm showing you the motion of how
you I'd rather do the cinnamon challenge
feel the breadcrumbs would like be worse
how many casualties did the cinnamon
challenge I don't know like at least one
at least one kid was like choking on
Cinnamon oh that's so sad imagine going
out like like your final your final
breath is just F of cinnamon yeah
cinnamon in the air wait that's [ __ ]
up would you rather find 1 million rats
in your basement or one person I'm
assuming dead dead one person Dead one
person oh no no what a billion I'm
assuming the person's dead correct one
dead person I would rather find than one
I'd rather find a dead person in my
basement than an alive
person really yes why well it just shows
that a killer probably did his job and
then dumped the body at your territory
as opposed to what oppos to a man okay
but if the person's there like it's just
like hey you got to get out of here no I
I rather find someone alive than dead I
had a big fear the other day dead
serious I'm getting
CH when we were in La I was asleep in my
room and I had I had such a feel Nick an
attic in his his and I want I want to
look up and we haven't yet I had such a
feeling in my bones that someone was
like standing in my room the other day
was there cra I like turned my
flashlight on and I slowly showed the
whole room in the dark yes cuz that's
why I thought double chills oh I was
telling one of you that I for the past
like month every single day I told you
every single day when I wake up I see a
person and then I have to like rub my
eyes or I blink or I look and I'm like
okay it's not a person but like I see
someone we to start talking about this I
know somebody could be alone in their
room right now and we're freaking them
out no but sorry every single time I
wake up I look in the mirror and I see
someone looking back at me like from
overing from like behind me like on the
other side of my room every single day
and then I turn and I'm like if there's
someone there I'm going to [ __ ] lose
it and I turn there's no one there thank
God every day it's the boogeyman coming
to grab your balls would you rather
sleep on bricks or concrete someone
asked same thing yeah like you're not
giving us much much diversity here
literally maybe the bricks I can like
caress the little crease as I fall
asleep for like some comfort some Edge
yeah literally there's a little bit of
like there's a little edge of some
texture to it a better tactile
experience I actually I [ __ ] with like
when what what that just scared the [ __ ]
out of me imagine how I feel what
happened this bow just fell off my head
and grazed my face I thought I was being
attacked by like a [ __ ] bug I thought
you just touched this and freaking out
no why did I do that did you see that I
was laughing and then I took like proper
etiquette form this I really [ __ ] with
concrete when it has like the little
pieces of black Matt Matt I really [ __ ]
you know when someone pinches your nose
and you just feel like like the worst no
that's what just happened to me or I
really [ __ ] with like when there's like
when there's like a crack in the ground
and then they fill it with tar and then
you go push your fingers into the tar oh
that's the
bestm put your F put your arm against it
and get all warm would you rather never
see each other again or be conjoined
never see you guys again that's a [ __ ]
up question don't ask that that's kind
of rude I would rather never see but
that makes me feel sad to the people who
are can jooin this world yeah that makes
me feel ungrateful and stupid I'm not
answering that question would you rather
live in a tree house or in a cave tree
house oh my God it's a dream to live in
a tree house yeah I want a tree house
but with like a full like give me his
name what is it Chris Peter no yes
Nelson Peter Nelson Peter Paul
Nelson hold on let me lock in oh I got
it Peter no don't tell me I'm going to
rip my [ __ ] [ __ ] hair out it's not
Paul no no you have it say it Chris say
what you just said already screenshot
Peter Pete Pete Nelson nelon it's Pete
Nelson oh I wasn't giving you a piss I
will uh if you guys haven't watched tree
housee master Nelson Treehouse Master
recommend at least one episode of that
he has so much Aura like actually he
literally
goes that's him feeling the tree by the
way solid oak do you have a third
Sycamore maybe that can uh be the base
all right yeah we're going to put a
[ __ ] mansion in this [ __ ] glass
windows beautiful balcony with a heated
microwave a heated microwave what would
you do if your microwave didn't heat
things and it was a a a he microwave
don't touch this oh this place it's got
a heated microwave I can tell I have a
question Nick yeah can you tell the
viewers about your steel toe shoes oh my
God Chris I was at the airport because
in Boston right now and I I love a I
live in LA I I don't know what it is but
by the time I have so many good story
times at the airport and I think that
I've learned it's because at the point
of which I'm getting to sharing a story
with you guys it's at the point of my
airport trip where I am
exasperated I am [ __ ] done all right
I'm mad I'm angry so so this guy I am
blessed with TSA pre-check if you don't
know when you go through airports
security it sometimes takes like 40
minutes you got to take your shoes off
you got to take your laptop out of your
bag sometimes they're 50/50 with it
because they're obnoxious when you have
TSA pre-check you don't have to take
your shoes off and you can leave your
laptop in your bag and it'll just you
can leave all your stuff like it's
supposed to be a way faster thing cuz
they background check you in order to
have TSA pre-check so they know that I'm
not going to do anything insane I kept
my shoes on to go through the metal
detector because I was allowed to by the
people at the place they tell me oh keep
your shoes on I was like okay so I'm
walking through this I'm walking through
the um the um the metal detector and the
and it beeps it's beeping it's flashing
it's going it's going off I'm like oh
I'm setting off the metal detector and
I'm like I knew I would because I have
metal shoes on but they were I didn't
think they told me to keep them on like
I they saw my shoe and then made me go
through the metal detector without
taking it off and he goes oh can you go
back through and come back can you do
that again so I do it and he's like ah
the metal detector is going off I'm like
yeah I have um a metal buckle on my shoe
and I knew about that but like I was
told to keep my shoes on he goes oh yeah
it's the steel toe in your shoe I said
these aren't steel toed shoes and he
said oh but it's it's the steel toe in
your shoe I said no it's the it's the
metal buckle on it yeah and I'm done I'm
just being like Oh No It's the metal
buckle but like I'll go take them off I
turn around he goes he goes excuse
me I I turn around I hear the the creek
of my bones as I spin toward this guy
and he goes no it's the steel toe in
your shoe I said
sir I'm I'm literally on my [ __ ]
knees pushing on my godamn toe I'm like
there's no steel toe in the shoe there's
no steel toe here I'm knocking on the
shoe I bought the [ __ ] shoe I know
it's good and he's like yeah the steel
toe is setting off the metal
detector I go it's the metal Buckle it's
the buckle that's jangling it's the
metal buckle on my shoe I know it is I
know the problem and I'm done I'm going
to go put my shoes in the [ __ ] X-ray
and I'm done I'm done I'm going to solve
it I'm going to solve it I'm going to
solve it I'm walking away I'm walking
away so I walk away and I take my shoes
off and I put them in the bin and put
them on the X-ray when I'm doing so a
woman Cuts me in line and I'm like it's
okay that's fine because I'm
inconveniencing everyone right now by
having my steel toe shoes on and she
walks through the metal
detector and it beeps she has no metal
on her so I'm like oh no what's her deal
and he goes the same guy he's like oh
you've been randomly selected for um uh
security screening go over there when I
tell you I had to hold myself back from
a Hoot and Holler I was like if I got
ridiculed for having non-existence Steel
Toad shoes and then I got the [ __ ]
raffle prize of a pat down at TSA
security I would have combusted exploded
you would have seen my [ __ ] body
shoot over the [ __ ] stars if I got
randomly selected for a prize of a TSA
[ __ ] nut tap I would have [ __ ] my
pants if I already went through this
trouble and I'm then put through a
[ __ ] security bin I'm put through the
[ __ ] metal detector bin I'm done I'm
I'm I'm I'm assuring my patience I
through without my shoes on he goes yeah
see it's working now cuz you took your
steel to shoes off and I I [ __ ] I was
already at the point of like I didn't
even acknowledge his existence he's like
talking about like oh it's you're good
now because you don't have the steel to
shoes I was like I just kept walking I'm
like [ __ ] shut up I love that one
it's just like stupid like you're wrong
it's it's funny too cuz like it it
doesn't matter it doesn't matter doesn't
matter and then like it doesn't matter
it doesn't matter at all if you were
trapped in a sewer what would you do I'd
look for Splinter and the teenage M and
Ninja Turtles Ag and then if I didn't
find them I'd I'd SLO around in the piss
and [ __ ] that the animals didn't come up
to me because I want to like I want to
blend in with everything you to mask
your smell yeah the alligators are
probably like ooh look at that big hunk
of meat there's no there's no alligators
the sewer Gator that's like a Fant
that's a lie okay well you're talking
about the teenage mut Turtles on a big
giant wrath that teaches them ju-jitsu
so the possibility of is it Jiu-Jitsu
that they learned I don't know but if it
is I Ninja Turtles it's not in the name
I thought it was going to be like teen
ninjas what are ninjas what do they
practice all them Mi martial arts
someone literally said would you rather
have your toes slurped by your brother
or your mom go into a coma like dude
you're slurping on my toes 100% don't
stop a rat follows you everywhere you go
or you live next to an active volcano oh
I'd be cool with the rat I'd just name
him like oh Jeffrey let's go I just chop
its head off on day one good luck follow
me buddy I want to play like a really
high stakes bingo game soon say that
again I want to play like a really high
stakes bingo game for like how much high
stakes is clearly high stakes
[ __ ] I'm putting the house on it
really F and bingo were going bankrupt
rather middle part mat or messy hair mat
um messy hair mat was a joke that was
never supposed to happen that was an
accident I look like an idiot it's what
the twitch stream remember yeah I took
my hat off I had hat on all day I was
getting my haircut today and my barber
said to me what's up with all this
middle middle part mat stuff I think
they should just be cool with this
haircut I think you and me both like
this one better said that to
me said that to me that's so nice I hate
like this is like this is like a random
thing to ramp to rant not rant yeah rant
is the word to rant on right now when
we're filming funny comedy videos
especially on Twitch streams sometimes
when like there's like
oh like middle when messy hair mat
becomes a thing as of a twitch stream
it's like bro like did you all find
anything else funny this isn't why I did
that you know what I mean it's crazy
streaming for like a full day and like
thinking like oh I made like such a
funny joke at this point I can't wait to
see that on Tik Tok and then it's like
yeah it's messy hair matte how do you
feel about let's play a game of what
does Nick feel about blank flat soda
flat soda when they're like sometimes it
can be a little fun I knew you were
going to say that [ __ ] psycho [ __ ]
that actually pisses me off because you
want to know what my this is like this
right here is like one my no this right
here struck we struck a nerve this right
here is one of my top three things of
life that's so sad no it's not it's your
what's in your top three you should have
12 eggs instead of no I don't think no
what's in your top three I don't think
Pepsi or soda I'm not expecting to be
soda I'm saying what's in your top three
I don't that makes this seem so
unreasonable for this to be in my top
three like my family and friends okay
like that doesn't count I love soda and
for you to say that like oh sometimes I
enjoy flat soda it's like a mockery it's
the same people that walk around this
Earth and be like Oh Diet Coke is better
than pepsy like I actually get
aggravated because it's like it's it's
like no it's not as good it's not as
flavorful it's not as sweet and you're
and now you're like when I get a flat
soda my nights almost ruined so for you
to go around and say you even slightly
enjoy it just bothers me cuz it's like
oh yeah you're enjoying what ruins my
night all right everyone that's going to
do it for today's Friday video we hope
you you enjoyed this one if you did hit
the like button if you didn't hit the
like button anyway if you didn't go put
the put the down if you didn't go into
the comments and tell us what car video
topics you would enjoy cuz we go down
there and that's how we get some of the
ideas like the one we did today because
somebody said i' lik it when you did
would you rather a year ago so and also
make sure you follow Stern yellow DOD
triples on Instagram because that is
where we got most of our would you
rather questions for today that we ask
each other so if you want to possibly
have one of your questions be a part of
one of our videos in the future that can
definitely happen but you got to follow
St dot triplet on Instagram because that
is where we collect our video filming
data we appreciate you guys so much and
we will see you guys next Friday fr the
only Coke that's more better than Pepsi
more better that's the only Coke that's
more better than Pepsi I just want to be
part of your
Symphony it's me and my girl bertr
truda the Apple doesn't fall far from
the
[Music]