I can't see you [ __ ] you're behind a
[ __ ] beaming light in my
eye what is he doing I don't know is it
good it loses the attitude immediately
well I can't see you and you're pointing
and [ __ ] you're pointing like right
behind the light like I can't see you
love it mat you can't be upset with that
cute hat on you just look too adorable
right now to be flustered yeah you look
stupid with ugly ass
glasses did you see who snuck in the car
the other day who the Tickle Monster
yeah here we go some stupid [ __ ] put
your hands to yourself was it actually
am yeah okay I have a story go ahead
today I woke up wait I feel like we need
something for the story like a campfire
like like I think we're okay I woke up
this morning and I was struggling we get
a campfire in here there's Outsiders
walking
by you're so weird but basically this
morning I woke up and I was really
struggling to like stay awake and like
get out of bed and I kept falling back
back asleep for hours repeatedly ain't
that the
worst okay but I fell back asleep and
when I was going back to bed for like
the last time I was like I fell asleep
like 2:30 to 3:30 like it was just I was
sleeping for so long and in that span of
time I had a [ __ ] dream and I like
bumped into like a
celebrity forget who it was it was
someone who was putting on like a
concert and I went up to them and I was
like Hey like I love you so much like
you're awesome like I I literally love
you like you're my favorite ever and it
was like this massive festival with so
many people there and I bumped into them
before I was like oh my God like I love
you can we take a shut
up ow [ __ ] I woke up in my dream
and I was like how the [ __ ] did I get
here and I was going on
my okay and I was going on my phone in
my dream and it was like the me talking
to that celebrity was me interrupting
their show at the festival and I like
walked up to the stage and I was like
Hey interrupting their stage performance
and I was just like being obnoxious and
it was like all over the Internet like
who's this psychopath that was there lo
and behold I find out in my dream that
when I was interacting with them I was
like drunk like someone gave me a bunch
of like alcohol without me knowing and I
was like slipping [ __ ] in my drinks and
I ended up like getting basically you
just have no idea what the [ __ ] is going
onever at this music festival in my
dream had an interaction in my dream
that I thought was real and then I wake
up in my dream still I literally checked
my phone this morning cuz I thought it
was real I was like I think I got
drugged at like a concert and I like
interrupted a stage performance I woke
up like three times in my dream and I
was on drugs in my dream and not only
that but just the confusion I felt about
like where the [ __ ] am I what's
happening my nose still hurts I was so
confused in my dream it was actually
mindblowing that's insan so much and
I've never had a dream where like I did
something and it's not correct in the
perspective of like what was actually
going on what did you eat last night I
don't know I just should have I think it
I think it was my sleep I think diet and
what you eat and what you do before you
sleep and then how much you sleep has a
big role in what you drink probably why
you have crazy drinks it definitely was
just not enough sleep oh yeah what that
I definitely just had not enough sleep I
definitely just had not enough sleep
that was it no like if you not supposed
to me can you shut your mouth shut up
I've never ever ever ever ever in my
entire life had a dream where I was like
drugged or drunk and I think it's cuz I
am just fully sober like I don't even
know what my brain would process I
definitely like blacked out in my dream
though cuz I woke up and didn't know how
I like got home in my dream like I was
so confused you're insane like this is
weird is that not crazy yeah that's very
weird I was so confused you guys really
have these dreams where you're waking up
in your dream like that's crazy like the
pre- up like that's never happening to
me and I woke up and my room room was
like oddly filled with like arts and
craft supplies I I left that out cuz it
didn't matter but like I woke up in that
room like arts and crafts everywhere did
you do any mm- I was like already done
like markers everywhere [ __ ] drawn I was
like I don't know how I got home H maybe
you were feeling very expressive okay
Chris I'm not I'm not telling you this
to decipher myam I'm sharing I'm trying
to figure it out care you're not going
to figure it out you're not going to
figure it out cuz you're not even trying
to agreed and you're not going to figure
out you are trying to agre you're not
trying to what are you
you chuckle chuckle all right guys today
for today's car video I'm going to be
doing one of my favorite things to do
and I'm going to ask Nick and Matt a
bunch of hypothetical questions are you
guys ready a bunch of are you ready
hypothetical questions are you ready is
this like a good place to sit I don't
know you kind of look really weird I am
really uncomfortable yeah what would you
do if you had 24 hours to live I'd
probably sit there in silence that's
insanely weird that's the craziest
answer I think you could possibly have I
agree I'd probably just sit there with a
24-hour timer behind me like
this I'd get some level of mashed
potatoes okay okay have to from the
store someone cook them order them
whatever mashed potatoes chocolate cake
mhm call and text friends take some
photos maybe call it a day see you're
weird if someone asked for a photo like
I write out like a letter to like my
family whenever like people are like oh
like the question is like oh what would
your like last meal be like what would
your like like death row meal be I don't
care I'm going to die I don't care
what's in my stomach that's the most
psychotic answer ever I do care I want
chocolate cake and mashed potatoes not
together separate separate what would
you do if you were swimming and lost
your bathing
suit um that one I'd probably yeah I
need more I need more of like what's
going on am I at like a friend's pool
and there's only like a couple of us
you're in the ocean no you're at a
resort
oh my God hundreds of people yeah I'd
run do I know anyone near me it's your
imagination Matt you use it okay i' make
a seaweed bathing suit oh I like it run
back to my hotel seaweed bathing suit I
would say I would stand there naked
covering myself and be like hey who
wants to go grab me a towel and then I'd
have somebody like go grab me a towel
and then throw it in the water how would
you cover yourself my hands okay just
making sure what would you do I I would
probably just get up and run as fast as
I can to cover okay like into a bush not
into no that's oh my God I can't even
think of that being naked in a bush
that's really frightening I'd like get
out of the water what if there was like
bugs and stuff oh or like dirt I'd get
out of the water and I'd run over to
sand and roll around in the sand and
cover myself in sand so I don't look
naked I just look covered in sand you
definitely look naked like okay you look
like a sandman you're gross maybe bury
my privates like this and then like
cover them and then that what would you
do if you went into a public restroom
and discovered that there was no toilet
paper I've already done this before what
yes I have no I want to
hear I can't tell you now cuz Matt's
plugging his ears and it's weird and
gross it was after a flight on the way
home from Florida one year and it was
like we I think we were like 14 or 13
years old and I went to the bathroom I
took a [ __ ] and there was no toilet
paper
left so I used my underwear as toilet
paper and then just threw them away in
the bathroom and you're gross how what
else I supposed to do gross you're gross
you're gross I just took my underwear
fully off used it as toilet paper and
then just put my sweatpants on once
again I'm asking someone I have a semi
gross no there was like no there there
was none in the bathroom like I
literally looked underneath like nothing
I have a semi- gross answer go ahead if
there's no one in the bathroom that's my
situation if there's no one in the
bathroom I'd literally get up and walk
to another Stall oh imagine getting
caught and then sit back down and use
the toilet paper in that stall dude yeah
that's a good that's a good move
honestly you have to be quick cuz you
can't get caught if there's no one else
I just really quickly switch dos yeah I
agree like naked just run over I'd
probably do the same thing Nick just
said like get up and go to another stall
or if there somebody is in there and
you're be like hey you got to do me a
favor here yeah oh I I would feel so
uncomfortable asking a stranger but if
someone had to ask someone it should be
me like I'd just be so polite about it
I'd be like oh it's okay like you're all
out help you out you're such a good good
guy so much I know but there's just so
many judgmental Neighbors in this world
everybody's got a [ __ ] dude yeah but
like no one wants to help the shitty guy
you know
ah my fingers are stuck I heard that
echo through my my
fingers what would you do if you were
fully home alone for a week and then on
the third day in you heard a noise in
your
house oh my God lit the police I'd go to
a hotel well what kind of noise I don't
know just like some presence of another
person I'm calling the police I need to
hear the noise that's my actual biggest
fear oh my God I can't even think about
it if I was home alone and I was like on
the third floor or like the bottom floor
I can't be in the middle no I'd want to
be in the middle that's the quickest to
the exit I'd hate to be like out i' I'd
hate to be oh it actually doesn't matter
where I am I don't even know why I'm
saying it if I was in my house and oh my
God and music just started playing no
why know it's even scarier that's my
biggest fear that's actually my biggest
unrecognizable like hey from like a
floor beneath you hey don't even say
that and you don't know who it is don't
even say that that's actually my biggest
fear if I was Hey and you're
like in your house in like a floor
before you like coming towards you hey
no like um like a the stairs creaking
that's my biggest that's nothing what
about like a fridge CL that's nothing
stairs creaking is like already like
that might happen are you moving the
mirror no oh it's c drove by what about
like a fridge and a cabinet shutting
from the kitchen while you're like in
the room over a toilet flushing the
scariest one is just music playing like
imagine you were sitting in our house in
the living room and then up from Nick's
room Just Like Music started playing the
TV turning on that's not that's
paranormal something with electricity
doesn't really bother I'm really scared
of like that stuff no music fully
playing like a record player or
something okay could you think you're in
a movie huh Nick shut your mouth yeah I
wouldn't be scared if it was like
[ __ ] one of my favorite artist like
Travis Scott or like a rapper you know
what I mean like rap music can't
randomly play for me to be inflicted in
fear it needs to like slow jazz like
something you've never heard before like
Frank Sinatra he's the perfect horror
artist no he's
not oh my God this is actually really
creepy and I just made it up in my head
o yeah good storytelling move this could
be a movie imagine one day right you
build a connection with someone and then
like you kind of fall apart and you were
friends for like a year or something
and then you're not friends for like a
year and a half and a lot of time goes
by and then one day they're like hey
like we should rekindle like I'd like to
see you again just come on over like
like the good old days whatever and then
you go over and they like need help
moving something or like grabbing
something and you grab something and
there's like a ton of information about
you or oh my [ __ ] no and like
offguard photos of you out in public and
like just like a list of things like
that they were they've been like
calculating your every move for like the
past year got a knife and stab them I'm
calling the police again I'd call the
police or immediately prepare for
self-defense like don't don't even a lot
of the times in movies when people are
so stupid and they catch you reading
that and they say oh you weren't
supposed to see that sorry no no in
movies stop looking at me like in movies
the usual like thing that happens like
you supposed to see that the person
finds out and then they try to like play
along and like call the police you know
what I mean like they pretend that they
didn't see it and let like 10 minutes
pass while them and the person just
normally inter act it's like I'm not
giving that person any second chances
like they come back in the room I'm
hitting them with like a baseball bat
off the head like right okay but the
thing is I'm not going to pretend I
didn't see it if you had to live with it
constantly being daytime or constantly
being nighttime what would you pick
daytime daytime but I'd make sure that
my house has like several rooms that are
just completely black out that's so
weird I kind of that's so weird I kind
of agree with that right daylight but I
just make sure that there's like at
least two or three rooms I can go fully
blacked out ful agree with see I would
just pick daytime and then wait for the
cloudy days to become my true self well
that's not going to happen cuz it's
constantly Sunny it could still be I
agree I agree with Nick because it's not
daytime it's not sunny it's not like
bright or dark it's sunny or it's
daytime or night time like it can rain
still like rain oh yeah I pick daylight
for sure I I'd pick a day which is
surprising for me cuz I normally love
night time it's easier to
replicate dark than it is the light of
the
Sun that has deeper meaning to it it's
easier to become a follower and not a
leader it's easier to become Darkness
than the light correct it's easier to be
dark and rude than become bright in the
light you know what I mean it's easier
to get on the train of hate of be like
oh we hate that you know it's easier to
join the Dark Side but to get the light
you have to it's easier to replicate
that was a deep message can we all give
him a round of applause that was a deep
M message deep message deep message
thank you God that was a beautiful
message very deep message I feel like
Nick if he was in like a movie he'd be
like the mechanic that like starts under
the car and then like rolls out on the
skate yeah yeah what the [ __ ] are you
even saying I feel like he's the guy who
they need the information from for sure
like oh you got to ask old Randy and
then Nick could slide out and his name
tag be like oh Randy and like you guys
are weird no not ni that's so Nick tell
me it's not and you like have all the
classic storytelling information like
have you seen Donald and he's like uh
Donald came in here like 2 weeks ago to
get his oil CH he's like walking
by regular tuneup you guys are the most
bizarre people I've ever met in my life
and you're the type to have like your
business card if they need anything else
if you need anything just call my number
yeah if you could disappear how long
would you and where how would you do it
what what I don't know try again what is
going on why think blindfolding himself
I kind of feel like I'd be able to laugh
more if I can't see like I just want to
be able to see what's going
on get off me I'll break fingers what
would you do if you were hanging out
with someone you loved and then they
just like dech charged like they were
actually a robot what's stupid like I
don't know how to answer no imagine if
we were hang out with somebody like
mutually all know and they were like
they were like hey what's
up i' be can you stop acting like a
[ __ ] goof no but like they were like
and then they started like steaming and
like you can notice like a a screw in
their neck that would have to that's one
of those things that would have to
happen for me they just were a robot the
whole time I don't know dude do they die
indefinitely no no you have to recharge
them I'm not charging them who the [ __ ]
came up with
LED what does that even mean LED lights
I thought you saying Ellie like Ellie
Golding and that stop
me I thought you were to sing a song
Nick what are you saying why does pizza
come in a square box if it is cut into
triangles I've never seen a circular box
it would make zero sense if a pizza
perfectly fit in the Box yeah you need
cuz you need some leverage to open just
because all pizzas are circular doesn't
mean they're all the same Circle imagine
a pizza box and like the crust and the
ends were like fit like folding over
that's happened to me before no it has
not swear in my life it has I've had a
pizza too big for the Box oh tell too
big for the Box
hey did you love it no you know what I
mean fully did you ever did you ever see
there was this Criminal Minds episode
and the guy just did a bunch of
robberies and murders and stuff but he
wore high heels and different ones so
then they kept thinking he was like a
different height like he was oh a 6'4
man robbed the bank in Westchester
whatever and it was like oh someone
robbed a bank over here but he was only
5T and then he just kept like wearing
different variations he yes like he
would Rob hot platforms whatever you
know what the [ __ ] I mean well high
heels is crazy what's he like strutting
in yes he is Oh I thought I thought he
was fully doing I thought he had like
stilettos on
while what you said exactly the guy just
like kept robbing the banks but like he
was a different height every time so
were there high heels or platforms cuz
that's actually shut up they could have
been boots that's what I'm asking
platforms I doubt I doubt they were no
but it was like the same shoe every time
it was just a different like like so
definitely not high heels there's no way
he no it wasn't actual high heels I told
you this we addressed it a minute ago
MadAss he told him to shut up no you
shut up you're an idiot it was a good
[ __ ] question no there there no
question shut it was a good thing it was
a good story good for you great every
single time you would rob the bank he
would have different height shoes on wow
so cool thanks I know I think that's
crazy thank you it is pretty cool but I
just what the one deciding factor being
height is like well it's like if
someone's robbing a bank and they're
fully in a disguise what really can you
tell the police oh they were fully in a
disguise correct and you pray to God to
find in that dumpster catch him lacking
what oh yeah if you were offered the
choice of taking a vacation anywhere in
the world for any length of time or
moving anywhere you wish what choice
would you make and where would you go my
dream plays forever stupid question I
didn't even understand it all to said if
you can go anywhere you are offer
$50,000 to go without bathing or
brushing your teeth or using any
cosmetic product or cleaning product you
cannot tell people why you are doing so
will you accept the offer or pass the
offer pass you can have a free chip put
in your brain so that you know that you
would know all basic knowledge such as
multiplication tables history facts and
automatically be able to speak and
understand other languages would you do
it yes or no I'm doing it absolutely
without a question I'm doing it but
what's the negative being who I am it's
just I don't know I don't like chips in
the brain cuz then they could like then
one day they flip a switching oh yes sir
and I'm listening to you and you got
full control of my body okay we're going
to move on you can have any type of pet
you want no limit on size or expense
what type of animal would you choose and
why I would get a snow leopard and I
would feel them feed him nothing but
snow beef or no what's it called all
right guys that's been this week's car
video stay tuned for more of a stolo
Christmas and we'll see you guys
soon TR from the island to Madrid we had
a lot of plans but they
all why because of some kid but it's
okay cuz I'm moving
different