Hello Sharks. My name is Kobe Harris.
I'm here today seeking 300,000 for 6%
equity. My company, Kobe's Co., we
believe Mother Nature herself deserves
the best kiss. Sharks, let's talk about
lips. We all have them. We all use them.
But are we treating them right? That's
why I created Kobe's Co. 100% natural,
handmade, and sustainable lip balms that
don't just lock in moisture, they lock
in trust and transparency. Because our
ingredients are so clean that you could
eat them, but don't. We source our
beeswax from happy bees who listen to
classical music all day. And our oils
are pressed from plants who have won
beauty contest. Can you believe that
sharks? Nah, I'm just kidding. Kobish is
made from only four simple ingredients.
Beeswax, coconut oil, sunflower seed
oil, and mango butter. I started with
lip balms, but have quickly expanded to
a lotion bar, lip scrub, cuticle butter,
and even a hand sal. So, who's ready to
pucker up? Kiss the bad ingredients and
plastic packaging by with Kobe's Co.
Sharks. In front of you is an assortment
of Kobe's Coast products so you too can
be a part of the Kobe's hive. Wow. I
love the packaging. So each lip balm is
a tiny little thing. Mhm. Correct.
Smells very flavor. Yeah. We have We
have 10 different flavors. I did start
off with like a traditional size lip up
tube, but since I wanted to be
compostable, you have to be able to push
it up cuz there's no twist function. Um,
so it has to be a little bit shorter. It
has to be a little bit wider. So you put
your finger up there and Kobe, are you
selling in retail with this? No, it's
really all online right now. Direct to
consumer website and then Amazon as
well. Tell us about you. I started this
when I was a freshman in college.
Actually, I was doing research on
packaging and bees with one of my
sustainability professors. Went to my
mom. I was like, "Hey, mom. I got this
idea. It's called Kobes. I want to make
all natural lip balm personal care
products. I need a little bit of money
to, you know, just get the the base
ingredients." So, she gave me 200 bucks.
Went on to Amazon, bought, you know, all
the raw ingredients that I could find,
you know, the beeswax, the butters, the
oils. It really just spent that whole
summer formulating. Um it was like three
months and then I worked as a lifeguard.
So I would ended up towards the end of
the summer passing it out to you know
everybody that I could find. I would go
home from my shift, make 50 bombs and a
little uh hot plate in my bedroom floor,
you know, mixing up waxes with a pipet,
filling them one by one, and then I
would walk around to the pool and then
hand them out to people at the pool. So
that first summer is really where I kind
of started to figure some things out. So
I had a day where I made $3,000 in
sales. That was the most money I've ever
seen in my entire life in my bank
account. I remember it hit. I was like,
I was so excited. I was ecstatic. Such a
good feeling. Yeah. And then I think a
month later, I had a day where I made
10,000 in one day. And then towards the
end of the summer, like two weeks
before, classes went back up. Did the 15
grand in sales one day and went on my
campus portal, exited out of all of my
classes. And since classes were online,
I just told my dad, you know, I'm still
in school. But really, I was just in the
basement making lip balms and trying to
market all day.
So Kobe, your story is so amazing and it
really touched me. I did the same thing
and I I dropped out of college. I ended
up starting my business. So, I hear that
I My dad today obviously looks at me and
he's like, "Honey, you made the right
decision." I bet your parents are so
proud of you. Yeah. My mom was a a huge
proponent of kind of help. She started a
couple businesses when she got out of
school as well cuz I was going to school
to be a doctor actually at first. That's
what I wanted to do. I went to summer
camps for it. I took summer classes,
shadowed surgeons. When I went to my mom
that summer and I was like, "Hey mom, I
think I might want to switch from trying
to become a doctor to make lip balm."
And as crazy as it sounded, she was
like, you know, Kobe, you know, I
understand. You know, go with your gut.
And that's kind of what's propelled me
forward to have the confidence to be
able to do some of the things that I'm
doing. That year we did about 30 grand.
The year after that we did about 200.
And then last year we did 864,000.
Um, and this year we've already done a
little over 1.5 million to date. Wow.
Wow. 1.5.
Like wow.
That trajectory is quite quite large.
But what was it that made that change?
Um, I just learned how to run Facebook
ads, like Tik Tok, posting videos. Um,
that's really what I know how to do.
I'm, you know, Gen Z. I'm a young kid. I
know social media. Do you know your
rorowass, your return on ad spend? It's
about 2.5 to three. Um, okay. That's a
little light, but my question is for an
investor, I look at this and say, if you
know your rorowaz and you know your CAC,
your customer acquisition and I give you
300,000, why wouldn't you just use that
to pour it on the fire? In other words,
you don't need anything else other than
more capital to spend more on
advertising. Sure. What does it cost you
to acquire a customer? Um, right now
blended it's 14 15 bucks. What do you
make on your average order? Uh, $32. Our
main skew was like a six-pack or a 6 to
9 pack. Yes, they're it's a lip balms.
The rest of this stuff is a fraction of
the sales. Yes. So lip balm was about
75% of our sales. The rest of it is
personal care. It's about 25%. This
little unit right here cost $5. I mean,
you sell it for five sell it for $5 cost
26 cents to make. What are you going to
make this year? So, I think we'll finish
the year with around three and a half $4
million. What are you going to make on
that after you pay yourself and all your
employees? I think we'll net about 7
to800,000. So, Kobe, first of all, as a
mom of sons, I have a son about your
age. Um, blown away by your story. Like,
I'm so proud of you. This is not my this
isn't my wheelhouse. I want to buy your
products. I'm going to use your
products. I'm going to tell everybody
about it, but it's just not the right
investment for me. So, I'm out. I
appreciate it. Kobe, what do you need? I
need somebody who can give me a little
bit of guidance. Um, we need a little
bit of help maybe with distribution. You
know, lip balm is a $5 skew, so it's
really hard to sell a lot online if
we're not selling a huge volume. Um, so
I think being in those those checkout
counters, the the point of purchase,
retail would be very very helpful. I
could get you retail in pretty well
every big box. And they do sell millions
of dollars a week in lip balm. So that
but to get the shelf space at point of
sale, that ain't easy because you're
displacing somebody and they're going to
want a listing fee for that. I like the
deal. I'll make you an offer. I'll give
you the 300,000 for 20%. 20%. Yeah.
Okay. I don't think you're worth 5
million bucks. So K, I'll tell you what
I think. Sure. I feel that it's a hard
road once you try to go into retail
because how do you stand out amongst the
rest because there's so many out there
right now and some with the bees kind of
name. Um I really feel it's a great
online business for you. I love it and
you've done a great job but not really
right investment for me. I'm sorry. I'm
out. I appreciate it. So I think you're
going to crush it. I just don't see the
lip balm business as something that I
can really bring the value ad that you
really need. And so for that reason, I'm
out. Thank you, man. I love this. And it
reminds me of my story. You know, my
mother's the same way. She wanted to
start her own businesses, but uh you
know, life happened. She became a single
mother and uh she had to uh work a bunch
of jobs to make sure that I was okay.
Sure. So, she wasn't able to fulfill
that dream. So, so uh we kind of got
together and mom helped me. So, I really
love this. I love the idea. Um, I I just
don't think I want to be in this
business. I want to be in the Kobe
business, though. But this is not the
business I want to be in. So, I wish you
all the best. It's not for me. I'm out.
Thank you. Well, then there was All
roads lead back to the big be in here.
I would never go into the lip balm
business because it's so competitive.
The only deal I'm looking at is giving
you $300,000 cuz I really think you're
sharp. I really do. I want to show this
to my retail distribution partners, but
I don't want you to fall in love with
that too fast. Sure. Because I I really
want to focus if we're going to do this
deal on this rorowaz thing because
you've proven you've got enough gasoline
going here that we can make the flame
bigger, but I want 20%. A lot of work,
you know, I want to get my money back
one day. So 300,000 for 20% is 1.5
million. We'll end the year doing almost
having netting 7800,000. So you're only
val two times that. And you're saying
the only thing that I'm going to be
really using the money for is pouring it
on marketing. So why can I not go get a
loan for 300,000, spend it on marketing,
and then absolutely, you know, I'll be
I'll be right there and keeping all 20%.
What I will say is I know lip balm is
not the traditional business, but like
you said, if you guys like Kobe, want to
bet on Kobe, you know, this is one of
those things I would love to for you
guys to be a part of. I would add one
thing though, you could do that or you
could do it the way I do it and there'd
be a big difference in yield because you
don't have the advantage of scale. What
we do is consolidate our buys across all
of our companies and buy at a fraction
of what you're paying because you're
just Kobe. Not that you're a bad guy,
it's just you don't have the buying
power. Just between you and I, that's my
deal. You don't have to take it, Kobe.
Make a decision. I understand. So, you
wouldn't do even 300,000 at 10%. No. No.
Uh, I'm not going to give up 20% of my
company today. What would you give up?
Um, I'd be willing to take more money.
um for I think 300's enough for what
you're doing. It's a big ask actually
for what you've got. But if I stay at
300, you won't meet in the middle
between 10 and 20. That's 15.
Tough decision. I know.
15% off. It should be painful, Kobe.
Those are great deals. Cuz I'm I'm
suffering like an animal right now about
the 5% I just gave up. He doesn't want
to suffer like an animal, too. Yeah. No,
me neither. Um, pain both sides. Pain.
I won't do that.
I appreciate it. Thank you, Kobe.
Congratulations, guys.
So impressed by you.