I first of all I strongly believe that
every kid uh every child should learn
coding. We should actually teach them
coding in school in the same way that we
teach them physics and geography and uh
you know literacy and math and whatn
not. Those are all fundamental skills.
Coding is one such skill because
software is everywhere and in fact our
day-to-day is dominated by software
already. You can't really live your life
travel um wake up in the morning without
software anymore. And I think as as
humans it is crucial to not only be in
readonly mode but also be able to create
uh things ourselves or at least
understand how how creation is done on
these devices. My name is Thomas and I'm
a developer. I've been developing uh
software since the early 1990s and today
my role is mostly being the GitHub CEO
leading uh the largest developer
platform uh on this planet.
I was born in uh 1978 in East Berlin
when Germany was divided into two
countries. So I was on the on the
eastern side uh in Berlin in in a suburb
called Matsan. I grew you know had a
normal childhood um but was fascinated
by technology remote control cars uh uh
you know little computer games. Uh in
1989 the wall fell and and that opened
up you know a whole new world to me as
an 11year-old. um obviously from from a
toy perspective um getting access to to
Lego and and Mickey Mouse but also uh to
uh to computers and so in the early 90s
um I bought my first computer uh 64 and
after um university um I went to
technical university in Berlin I
actually uh went into the automotive
industry uh I started working at uh
Mercedes back then it was called Dameler
Chrysler working on driver assistance
system uh for for the S-Class and I did
that uh for a while and then switched to
the supplier side to Bosch uh uh which
is you know a large automotive supplier
amongst amongst other things and and
there uh worked you know on parking
systems and it was in 2008 uh that two
things happened. One is I finished my
PhD thesis but also Steve Jobs showed
the iPhone SDK. Everybody wanted to
build apps um and and at the time only
Apple could build native apps and I
thought this is this is cool. I got to,
you know, build apps myself and I got to
get into that space. And so I quit my
job at Bosch uh at the height of the
financial crisis amongst all things uh
in late 2008 and um reconnected with a
friend um from from university and um we
just became you know two freelance
developers building apps uh for the
German market. So mostly agency work or
or subcontractor for for larger app
projects. I think in in 2009 and 10 we
built around 30 apps. That work on
building apps um for for for mostly
German customers um German enterprise
customers media and and automotive and
so on got us the idea of of building a
platform for mobile app developers. And
so we um together with three friends
Stefan Andreas and and Michael we
founded a company called Hockey App
which was a platform for mobile app
developers. you could distribute your
beta builds and um collect uh error
reports, crash reports and feedback and
those kind of things. And so we built
that startup you know the platform for
our own you know freelance business
because we had that painoint that we
wanted to solve uh for ourselves. Um
because it was before that you would
send you know a build uh over email you
know to to a project manager um in
Berlin or so and then the project
manager would take that build and send
it to the customer and explain to them
or you have to you know drag and drop
that into iTunes and connect you know uh
uh the dock cable and and all these kind
of things. since we made that way easier
which made our own life easier and I
think those are some of the greatest
startup ideas when you're using it
yourself uh uh day in day out and then
improving it um based on the feedback
that you're getting from your own
customers. So we basically started
building out the the hockey app business
while we had the the contracting
business and they were companies um both
about the same size and um when
Microsoft came in in 2014, we thought
they would only buy the hockey air
platform and the product business and
and leave the contracting business alone
uh given there were existing customer uh
contracts and and what have you. uh but
in fact Microsoft bought both companies
uh the the subsidiary the product
company and the the mothership the the
contracting company because the
contracting company had a number of iOS
and Android developers uh that were a
hot commodity uh in 2014 and and hard to
hire um certainly you know at at startup
rates and so Microsoft actually took
over both of those companies and uh a
fun funny story is today of these 11
employees seven including myself work
for GitHub and so different paths Um uh
they all got to Microsoft and then from
Microsoft into GitHub. You know coming
from a small company of of our size
based in Germany in Stutka Germany,
southwest Germany. Uh moving you know
halfway around the world I moved with my
wife and back then two very young kids
uh to Seattle that alone was a big
change. And looking back now um 10 years
later and we moved we moved in in early
2015 it feels all like a blur like
things moved so fast and sometimes I
don't even realize how we did all that.
Our startup was very small and
bootstrapped um for the whole time. So
we never took any outside investment uh
until Microsoft acquired us and at that
point in time I think it was about 11 or
or 12 employees. a still very small
team. all of all of engineers, you know,
building building the product together
and in some ways you know my role today
as GitHub CEO um is very similar uh in
that you know um my developer skills uh
my understanding of code my um you know
empathy for for how software developers
work helped me both with my you know
internal team of about a thousand uh
engineers and with our customer base
which are also all software developers
or those that aspire to become software
developer And so I think you know a lot
of the you know my passion for software
development is actually perfect you know
for me being being the GitHub
CEO I don't think I've seen anything
more exciting and and and changing how
uh we think about software development
in my in my 30 plus year career as a
software developer. You know, when I
started coding in the early 1990s, uh
there wasn't even the internet or I I
certainly had no internet access and so
I had to figure it all out all out all
by myself with with books, with
magazines, um going to computer club in
the community center kind of hoping that
somebody will be there. Um if we fast
forward to where we are now is that it's
so much easier to get into into software
development. you can, you know, just
write a prompt into Copilot or or Chat
GPT or or similar tools and it uh will
likely write you um um you know, a basic
web page um or a small uh application, a
game uh in Python. And so AI makes
software development uh so much more
accessible um for anyone who wants to
learn coding. And on the other side of
the spectrum, it makes developers so
much more productive. Most uh developers
that uh work on a project have way uh
too much work to do. uh they have long
backlogs um of their own ideas of
customer feedback, you know, uh things
that they're hearing from their managers
or from the market or what they're
seeing at competitors. And so almost any
software project that has a certain, you
know, age um has way too much work on
the innovation side, but they also have
what we call technical debt. Uh you
know, legacy code, things that have, you
know, been created over over months or
years that need a cleanup, that need
what we call refactoring. And so
engineers constantly balance those two
backlogs. So having something that
brings the effort down and makes them
you know 10% 20% maybe even 50% more
productive is is completely changing uh
how software developers work. the role
of GitHub you know in this in the first
uh let's say you know five years of the
age of AI um given that we started
working on GitHub copilot in uh June
2020 right after uh GP3 uh uh was was
first shown to the world is that we want
to be you know on the forefront um of uh
AI code generation we want to provide um
tools to developer to be more productive
and more happy uh when when writing code
because the reality is the dream I think
for most developers that start their
their journey um uh as a programmer is
that they have an idea in their head and
they're trying to find a way how they
can can get the fastest from that idea
to an app or or web page or service,
right? Like the challenge is not that
developers uh uh don't have enough
ideas. The challenge is that you take
that big idea and you have to break it
down into small building blocks. And as
you're working on the first block or the
first module or the first class or uh
micros service, whatever it is, you're
you're realizing that this this idea
that you have is so much more complex to
implement than than you thought. And so
from what became a weekend project, it
becomes a month-long or sometimes
year-long project. And many, you know,
apps that, uh, I wrote as a teenager and
I know, you know, many of my friends and
and my employees wrote never get
anywhere because you you ultimately
realize it's much more complex than you
thought and it's not worth spending the
time on it. And in in the world that we
live today, you can always, you know,
download an app from the app store or
find, you know, some online service that
does the same thing. So, I think AI
helps us, you know, to realize the dream
of taking an idea and implementing it
much faster. And you see um some of the
early signs of that where very small
startups sometimes you know five
developers um and some of them actually
only one developers uh uh believe they
can become million uh if not billion
dollar businesses by leveraging all the
AI agents uh that are available to them
and maybe building their own uh to to
write code uh to write software much
faster. Now the flip side of that is
that you know uh I don't think we're
anywhere close to a world where you can
just write a single prompt and say build
GitHub and then an AI agent builds all
of the features of GitHub um or even
just the very basic primitives like
repository storage you know git storage
and uh issue tracking um because the the
decisions um that we as developers as
engineers as product managers have to
make to build a complex system like
GitHub you know thousands if not tens of
thousands decisions um there's the
simple ones, right? Like which
programming language, which which open
source framework, which cloud to use or
do we even use a cloud, which operating
system and and so on. But there's the
much more complex decisions of how you
architect the system, you know, are you
building a monolith and or you building
microservices? And getting to a point
where agents can make all these
decisions and write an app that actually
is a viable business, you know, finds
product market fit, has a great user
experience, and and ultimately generates
both revenue and profit. uh because any
business at some point has to get to the
place where they're making profit and
and return that profit to the to the
founders or shareholders that I think
we're we're quite far away and so we
need uh engineers uh to do engineering
stuff. They they need to exercise their
craft and uh apply systems thinking and
design and and and build really great
applications.
I think the unique thing about GitHub is
its size and both the love uh that
developers have for you know our brand
um for our mascot um the octoat or we
call it internally Mona um and um the
reputation uh that GitHub has created
for itself um since the very early days
since the I remember the early launch of
GitHub and and meeting um or seeing um
Chris one of the founders speaking at
RailsCon in in Las Vegas in in 2009 and
then signing up for my own account and
and started using it. I I was excited
about using GitHub and now we are in in
2025 and there are still many people
that uh love GitHub but you know what
what comes with love is also that you're
not holding back your criticism and that
we have 150 million users and uh on the
platform and so there's at least you
know a million opinions of what are the
things we should invest on and what's
working well and and what's not working
well and what's the one feature that is
important you know to that set of users
while it's not important uh to to me and
and my product leadership team because
we have you know our own uh strategy and
decisions to make. So filtering out the
signal from the noise and I don't mean
noise in any negative way just so much
feedback that we're getting. I remember
when we when we did the acquisition in
2018 and I joined GitHub and afterwards
um we sent an email to 10 GitHub users
and say hey we we're looking into a new
project we would love your feedback. I
think we got nine responses of exciting
users saying if you want to I want to
provide feedback. If you do that in many
other companies and startups you get one
response and the one response is kind of
like well I have like 10 minutes time to
to give you some feedback. There's just
so much um uh uh information that's
that's coming back to us um on on social
media and our platform in email and
support tickets and so on. The second
piece you know that comes to mind is
that GitHub um for the longest time has
been a company with a very strong remote
culture like long before co uh the
GitHub founders started hiring um
developers uh sales folks support folks
all over the world and today I think
we're one of the largest remote only
companies where all work you know from
our homes or from you know hotel in in
soul um or from from wherever we are and
so a lot of um our culture is focused
around GitHub as a platform form which
obviously through open source encourages
um uh asynchronous uh collaboration uh
and then tools like Slack um um and and
video video calls um uh that we use much
more heavily internally than we're using
email like like old school uh companies
do. And so when I wake up in the morning
especially here you know in Seoul uh
which is like lots of time zones away uh
from from the US uh where about 80% of
our employee population is is that I
wake up to 30 40 Slack messages plus you
know uh uh hundreds of channels uh with
with conversation and then figuring out
you know what is actually important for
me as CEO what what to react to what can
I snooze uh for a while and what can I
just ignore that that's the you know a
big part of my job but it's also so
exciting because you know, I can be here
in South Korea um at at this event and
and still still run the company. And a
lot of, you know, what we do on a
day-to-day basis doesn't actually matter
whether I'm here in Seoul, or whether
I'm in Berlin or whether in I'm in New
York or anywhere else in the world. And
and I think that's for for many hubbers,
how we call our employees. A really
strong part of our culture that we are
remote company. Uh it's not related to
the pandemic. It's a choice that we made
of how we want to run the company. you
know how we select GitHub as an employer
and ultimately how we believe we can be
successful. I first of all I strongly
believe that every kid uh every child
should learn coding and we should
actually teach them coding in school in
the same way that we teach them physics
and geography and uh you know literacy
and math and whatnot. Those are all
fundamental skills. Coding is one such
skill and it just has taken us too long
to actually realize that because
software is everywhere. Um hardware is
also everywhere. We carry we carry both
software and hardware with us uh through
our day. And in fact our day-to-day is
dominated by software already. You can't
really uh live your life uh travel um
wake up in the morning without software
anymore. And I think as as humans it is
crucial to not only be in read only mode
but also be able to create uh things
ourselves or at least understand how how
creation is done on these devices. That
doesn't mean that every you know 18
19year-old when they leave high school
become a software developer. In the same
way that not every uh uh kid that learns
physics or or chemistry in school
becomes a physicist, right? Just because
you learn those fundamental skills
doesn't mean that you decide for
yourself that that's the career path to
take. So that's number one. You you got
to you got to learn coding. I think
number number two is you got to use AI
to do that. And and you know whether
it's here in Korea or in Germany uh most
kids um uh and in fact you know most
most people don't speak fluent English
um which is the primary language of
software development. And so it
democratizes access to technology and
that's true for many other uh things in
the world. And so having uh an agent
available uh that answers you any
question but also lets you you know
realize your dream building your dream
uh is incredibly exciting. And then the
third thing you know for anyone who is
already a software developer or wants to
you know develop their craft is you got
to keep you got to keep rehearsing. You
got to keep training. Yeah. You got to
keep learning. There's you're never done
with learning. If I look back 30 years
of what development looked like back
then and what it looks like now, um I
would have been, you know, um very
behind if I hadn't constantly read blog
posts, um uh literature and and tried
out things myself. So I think those are
uh as as crucial as they were in the '
90s, they are still crucial in 2025. You
just have so much more access to
information uh to become, you know, top
of the
field. The obvious answer is that I most
enjoy using GitHub Copi, right? like
that's our product. Uh it's our baby. Uh
we're working on this day in day out. I
often, you know, uh see features long
before the world sees that. And and the
flip side is also true that I often
don't actually know what's shipped
versus what is, you know, in in preview
or in in internal ships. And so I'm
daily excited about what we're building
there and I'm using a lot of that myself
as I am at heart a developer. And
sometimes it's very simple, you know,
asking it to to write me a quick script
that that downloads, you know, ids of
all our repositories um from our API.
And in the past, I would have gone, you
know, to our API documentation and
figure that out all myself and probably
would have taken me like half an hour to
to get to, you know, a shell script that
does that. Today, I just ask Copil and
it writes me the script and it works
within within minutes. Um, and I think
actually that's the one of the true
superpowers of AI. Whether that's
learning to code or exploring the world,
you have um an assistant available to
you that has infinite patience. You
know, it doesn't judge you. Um, it will,
you know, chat GPT or co-pilot never
tells you what what a stupid question
is. It always gives you an answer and it
even accepts when you tell it it's wrong
or it needs to, you know, explore the
topic a little bit further. You know,
you have seen uh the prompt examples
where by telling it to outline its
thought process, it actually gets to a
better answer. I love using it for my
blog posts and PowerPoint presentation
to just uh generate some images and and
play with that. Um I'm I'm really bad at
using Photoshop and and and drawing
myself, but I'm I'm really creative and
I can write prompts and and figure out
how to rewrite the prompt to make the
image look more than uh more more
closely to what I had in my head.
There's, you know, tools that we're
using like teams copilot to summarize
meetings, especially when I I'm on
business trips like that. Um, where I
miss a lot of the meetings that happen
uh in on the west coast and west coast
time zone. Just getting a summary,
figuring out other action items for me.
Uh, same for summarizing emails. Um, uh,
you know, using something like reclaim
AI to to manage my calendar. Those
things are making me more productive.
And I think the really exciting thing is
that there's always a new tool to try
out and see is that how far along that
journey is AI and how much more do we
still have to do as an industry to
actually get to that to that dream of of
having an orchestra of agent uh that
that we're controlling during our
personal and in our professional lives.