Hi sharks. My name is Jen Lawrence and
I'm the owner and founder of a website
called newwagstore.com.
I'm here today to offer you the
opportunity to invest 100,000 for 10%
equity in my business.
Hi Sharks. My name's John Bennett. I'm
Jen's life partner and I'm the numbers
guy.
I didn't grow up with much. One of the
things I looked forward to was going to
my great-g grandandmother's house on a
Sunday for a roast lunch. After the
lunch, my grandfather would give us a
cup of tea. And I didn't particularly
like the tea, but if I drank it, my
grandfather would read my tea leaves.
When I was 17, he gave me a set of tarot
cards. And he said, "These cards were
given to me when I was not much older
than you by an old gypsy lady. She
handed me the cards and she said, "Keep
these and one day you will give them to
somebody who will share them with more
people than you could imagine." And
those cards went on to become the
cornerstone of my website.
In 1999 when I created my website, I
started with a dream, a hobby, and a
passion to create the very best
spiritual and guidance website on the
planet.
I now receive over 600,000 visits a
month. I do 2.2 million readings every
month, and that equates to about 6
million page views every month.
So, from humble beginnings, I've turned
my dreams into a reality. I have an
almost completely passive income, a 90%
profit on my business, and I have earned
over $1 million,
or which one of you can see into the
future and realize the true potential of
newagtore.com.
So, what I'd like to do is just give you
an idea of what the website looks like.
Okay.
So, if I go into the tarot section,
we've got about nine different options
to choose from on the readings. And from
here, I can either pick my cards or I
can allow the universe to choose them.
So, you don't read, it's automatically
generated.
That's correct. It will connect you with
your higher self and you will take from
it what you want.
So
over the last three years, can you give
us the numbers?
Last three years have been fairly
constant.
Okay. So is it is it 100,000 bucks a
year, 200,000 bucks a year?
About 140,000
per year for the last three years.
Per year for the last three years.
After paying for all your expenses,
where are we at? Uh
108,000
um per is your profit. Is our profit
Can you explain how you earn the
revenue?
So the way that it works in its current
format, the website is entirely free.
All the readings are free. However, I
generate my income in one of two ways. I
have Google ads on my website and I also
have an affiliate system where it's a
sign up system that I get a kickback
from that one as well.
How much time per day are you on this
site supporting it?
About 2 minutes a month. 2 minutes a
month.
Yeah.
Why aren't you taking some of 108,000
bucks a year and actually turning it
into a lot more?
It It's actually been run as quite a
lazy business.
It's 2 minutes a month. It's a fantastic
way to demonstrate how light touch it
is.
And now we want you to come and drop 100
grand into it rather than taking our 100
grand into it. I I do have some issues
with I don't go for the whole spir
spiritual thing. I think it's a lot of
hocus pocus.
[Music]
I'm out. Thank you very much.
So, isn't the risk that if for some
reason Google decides not to pay for
Google Ads or changes their model Yes.
that your revenue stream would cease
immediately? You're completely right,
Janine.
One of the reasons that we'd like the
money is I'd also like to introduce a
paid reading and they would be charged
at $5 US.
So, you would then do the reading
yourself?
No. Still be automated.
Jen, I'm really disturbed. As a
scientist, I'm just sitting here
flabbergasted that in this modern age,
people are going to this site making
life decisions that are really serious.
And it's an on an automated slot machine
and it really upsets me.
How much do Australians spend on hope
which we call betting
to say that dreams are possible or hopes
or difference aspirations. I just I just
think that that's actually a little
naive.
The reality is I'm not going to be your
ideal business partner. I'm struggling
with the ethics of it.
Okay.
So I'm out.
Okay, talk to me.
Yes.
Yes. There is a lot of people in this
space. So tell us what else is going on
in the space.
The spiritual industry worldwide is
worth billions of dollars. The model
that we're looking at is not that
dissimilar to her main competitor's
model, which in 2011 with a suite of
five other.coms was sold to a Japanese
publicly listed company for $17 million
US.
I'm involved in a bunch of online
businesses and I've made a lot of money
out of them. Mhm.
You've done well to kind of sustain it
and build this community,
but I think I've based my life on the
fact that, you know, if it is to be,
it's up to me.
Yes.
And I don't really, frankly, want to be
involved in a business, which in some
ways gives people an out on backing
themselves.
I'm sorry, that's just a personal
decision.
Yep.
I'm out.
I actually one of these people that do
believe that there's people out there
that has very very strong intuition. Now
whether that means they can see the
future or they can see goes I I don't
know but I do believe that people do and
so I take that really seriously and
people take it very seriously. So as
soon as it goes down the path of paying
I just don't feel comfortable about it
but I wish you all the very best and
well done for what you've achieved to
date. But on
there was one
Nami.
[Music]
I happen to have met the woman who
founded horoscope.com.
Oh, that's cool.
What an amazing entrepreneurial journey
she's had.
Yeah.
Her exit was the greatest return on
capital invested probably in
Australian.com history.
You have a $1 million valuation on your
business.
Yes.
Which at your present earnings is
actually 10 times the valuation which is
actually very high.
I'd be far happier
with a $100,000 investment for a 20%
stake in your business.
You came in looking for 100,000 for 10%.
If you accept the offer, you're going to
pay twice as much equity.
Can I speak to John about it?
Yeah, sure.
I'm very transparent. We're not going to
walk out. I'll just have the
conversation right here in front of you.
Does that mean the business is only
worth 500?
Yeah. Yeah. She's valuing the business
of 500
and Nomi gets 20%.
So each month I pay her 20%.
So we lose 20% of our current income.
Okay.
For the $100,000 investment.
Right. Okay. Right. I think that sounds
good. Am I supposed to ber?
I'm not going to b I love you. I love
you and Janine and I would absolutely
love to work with you on my business.
Excellent.
Congratulations.
What can I say?
Thank you so much.
Congratulations.
Oh, love.
Thank you.
And congratulations.
Well done.
How to meet you. Thank you so much.
Thank you so much. Thank you. Yeah,
we'll see you soon.
I'd have to say I don't think that
valuation was that bad for an online
business. However, I do accept that you
will bring her a lot of value. So, good
luck to you.
Well, I have to ask, did you see that
coming?
I did do my tarot cards beforehand and I
did get a pretty nice reading. So, yeah,
it was good.
What then does the future look like for
you now?
The future looks very exciting.