hello my name is Jerry Daly this is my
wife
Kate we're here today hopefully to
secure an investment of £80,000
for that we're offering 20% Equity of
our
business a little bit about
me about two years ago I had a heart
attack and I had to have three major
heart operations I thought I was going
to die at one
point so I asked myself what would I
like to leave for my
wife and I always knew that she fancied
my bum and my kiss she said I had
kissable lips so I copied a cast of my
kiss and popped in the post went down
and had successful operations fit as a
fiddle
now but when Kate got home and found it
that was where send a kiss by Benji
evolved and here here it is the finished
product after a couple of years of hard
work this kit will enable the user to
recreate an exact replica of their kiss
each kit contains enough materials to
actually recreate two kisses so it's a
perfect gift for a couple it can be
bought and given as a gift in itself or
you can buy it and recreate your kiss to
give to somebody that you love although
this box looks very much as though it's
aimed for the Valentine's Day and this
one is there are other boxes in the
pipeline with different labels so it's
suitable for every occasion and just on
Valentine Day in this country alone 2.4
billion is spent that's on cards
chocolate flowers and lingerie and we
feel and think that this product can
find a space in that
market thank you if you have any
questions we'll be happy to answer them
thank you very
much it's an emotional pitch by husband
and wife team Jerry and Kate Daly who
needed £80,000 to develop their novelty
lip casting kits send a kiss they're
offering the dragons 20% in return
Richard Farley wants to know more about
the progress of the business so
far I'm Richard hello Richard H Richard
I Like Your
Enthusiasm uh this strikes me as one of
those kind of unusual products which
which really needs to be tested to see
how it's going to go so can you tell us
about your sales to date Yep this this
product is so new we finally put it out
to the market two months ago and what we
decided to do was to find out would the
public purchase it so we booked up um
the NEC festive Fair it's a 4-day event
and we sold
603 in the four days and that was just
wow yeah it knocked us backwards people
are paying their hard earned
cash and how much do they do they sell
for
$4.99 yeah it's the recommended retail
price can we have a look at a couple of
the would you like a sample product as
well take the kisses
over Jerry and Kate have got off to an
encouraging start with their kids but
new businesses like this can spell high
risk for investors theop fetus needs to
know more about where the investment
would
go so I'll give you £80,000 of my
children's hard earned inheritance just
tell me what you going to do with it
well the first thing I would want is the
injection mold machines injection
molding machines to do what to recreate
these boxes we own the tool we own the
right the copyright design the Bo and
that box is unique to Benji okay but you
can't go manufacturing every single
piece yourself no granted we could ship
them in it doesn't it doesn't
necessarily make sense because if this
is successful you won't be able to
manufacture them yourself no anyway so
how much is that going to cost um the
injection mold machines are about
£20,000 okay so there 20 grand worth of
Machin you need two but I'm just going
to save you £40,000 straight away
because the last thing you should even
contemplating doing is doing injection
molding that's somebody else's job right
the margin someone's going to make out
of that if you're doing volume isn't
worth talking about so forget that don't
even go there right let somebody else
worry about the health and safety
aspects of
that theop fetus has roundly condemned
Jerry and Kate's plans to spend half the
£80,000 investment on manufacturing
their packaging themselves rather than
sourcing it elsewhere Duncan bantine is
ready to have his say I don't think it's
got a fantastic shelf life you know I
don't think in 5 years time we'll see
res selling very well there might be an
no item for a few years then you can go
to do other things things but you make a
great living out of it and I wish you
the best of luck so I'm out okay thank
you Jerry and Kate's enthusiasm for
their product hasn't been enough to
convince Duncan bantine to invest will
Deborah miden see things
differently unfortunately I think in in
terms of scalability it's just not
something I'm going to be interested in
but you absolutely should walk away
today taking encouragement because it is
a good product and with your enthusiasm
behind it absolutely it's going to work
and you you'll you'll get a great life
out of it but not one for me so thank
you but I'm out I think everyone's
really pleased to see such an
enthusiastic couple you know and it's
great to see people who really enjoy
business rather than just doing it for
the slog and the money and the whole B
it's not just about making money is it
you and as we said your only your only
thing for you to guys to watch out for
is that you don't get too carried away
you know but yes great product and uh
wish you the best of luck I'm out for
the same reasons as guys a fantastic
home bus and it's best without spending
too much money too quickly so I wish you
luck but I'm out as
well three dragons in quick succession
have now walked away from the deal they
all like the entrepreneurs but they
can't see an opportunity to make money
for themselves Jerry and Kate's last
hopes now lie with either Peter Jones or
theopus great story by the way thank you
um quite heart rendering really and
obviously I'm not punning but it is
quite quite an amazing story um a very
different idea yes which is why I was
quite struck by it however I want to try
and look at the opportunity and to try
and get real money out of this you have
got to sell a huge amount and build an
infrastructure around you and it's not
something that really excites me
although the product itself really
excites me and I think you've done an
amazing
job I match your inspiration I match
your driveing enthusiasm keep Focus
going but I can't invest because I can't
see the return in the short medium term
good luck thank you thank
you Peter Jones is out only theopus now
stands between Jerry and Kate under
failed investment bid in the
den Jerry K let let me tell you where
I'm on this um I think it's fantastic I
think it's great you actually need very
little money I don't know what your
financial situation is and how much
money you've got available to um uh
Market this but I'll tell you what I
have noticed is that t two people have
got so much enthusiasm and energy for
the product that what you might lack in
cash you've more than make up in being
who you are thank you now I'm going to
tell you I'm not going to be investing
because I don't think it's a business
for me this is really much a lifestyle
business that you could do incredibly
well for yourself so I'm going to say
something weird here I'm going to say
I'm out okay but I'm also going to ask
you to contact me because I might have a
very very good excellent contact to get
this product into stores very very
quickly for you if you can produce it
thank thank you very much thank you so
that's where I
am theopus has ended Jerry and Kate's
hopes of investment but in a den first
he's softened the blow by offering to
help them get the kids into the shops
and Peter Jones has a surprise for the
couple too one thing I'd like to do is
is give you 50 for one which would be
the first sale on Dragon's Den so I'd
like to pay £50 for one anyway cuz I'm
sure Tara and my other half would love
to receive a kiss with that thank you
very much thanks very
[Music]
much thank thank thank
you for