welcome to pitch. Tech where Innovative
startups showcase their technology in
the heart of silon Valley we'll pitch
their solution to a panel of esteemed
investors hi I'm uh tah n I'm co-founder
of storm Ventures we've raised seven
funds for a total of $1.2 billion we've
had 12 unicorns companies such as
maretto Vado uh I'm John Willie so I'm
now a three-time Founder I also teach at
Stanford I teach cs22 24g which is one
of the most popular classes in Stanford
about building uh applications using
large language models pitch. Tech is
dedicated to highlighting startups that
use disruptive Technologies to forge
Innovations let's meet the innovators
shaping the future of
tech pitch. tech is where bold startups
ontech domains get gamechanging insights
from Top VCS Tech domain instantly
signals you're all about Cutting Edge
Tech and Innovation building a tech
startup build it on dote
good thank you guys this my journey has
been from the UK all the way through San
Francisco we're very grateful for the
opportunity that that's that's come to
us we're buzzed about this hi we're
humble works I'm here to tell you about
a problem that is costing the world
around a trillion pounds my background
is in sustainable design and renewable
energy to help with this crisis I pulled
together the team that I thought would
be best fit to solve this there are
1.3 billion information workers around
the globe that are sitting at their
laptops hunched over as they're working
remotely we're going to focus on 145
million remote employees that are in the
UK the EU and the US 88% of managers
don't believe their remote work teams
are working as productively as they
could be here's how we solve this
problem by moving during the course of
the workday we can unlock 17% more
productivity and drop sick days by 25%
how do you move during the workday and
stay productive we've built an ecosystem
an Adaptive ecosystem fully sustainable
sophisticated feels right at home or
works at the office that allows you to
move from position to position and stay
productive it's all well and good as
promising managers CEOs the 177%
Improvement in productivity can we prove
that yes we can 17% Improvement in
productivity is captured by and measured
using the humble Works app our goal for
move to measure is to then create a
report the reports going to be buffered
and anonymized so individualized data
isn't available but will be presented to
a manager who then understands where the
information or the work gaps are between
him and his Workforce and at some point
over the next year all goes to well all
goes to plan we plan to create an AI
manager to supplement and to possibly
replace managers in some cases to have
entire teams being managed through an AI
dashboard and our Revenue model is to
charge
£119 per employee in year one employees
will get the full humble work Suite full
humble Works Suite includes the standing
desk the workstation the Rochester and
humble Works app to help you track
movement as you progress from one point
to the next year two will be the manager
report that's now going to show you the
granular data that we've gathered
gathered in year one and give you live
real-time feedback on how you're working
and optimize your entire workday by year
three we'll have the app the manager
dashboard and environment scan used
through the existing camera on your on
your laptop by year three we're planning
to take on the insurance industry it's a
fragmented industry that needs work with
our granular data that we've gathered
and the root cause of the health issue
being sitting down all day leading to
all of the other issues will teach us
exactly where those Health preventative
indicators will come from this is the
saving in year one compared to what
people usually spend right now per
employee right we will save employees
employers 1,400 year 1 1,680 year 2 and
2,600 year 3 here's how we'll do that
they're currently suspending around
£750 per employee in health insurance
loss in productivity and loss in sick
days are all the mitigating points that
we're going to bring to the market and
Save in in all of those costs across the
board can we do this can we pull this
off with just the standing desk alone we
generated a million in sales at the end
of 2023 just the standing desk by itself
and at that point we pivoted and decided
movement was the bigger play at hand
thank you for your time really
appreciate it if you raise the money you
said2 million uh what are you going to
achieve and by when so in year one we'd
like to build the um AI manager
dashboard and the AI manager dashboard
would take the data from year one and
build an entire framework for how you
should be working and all of that data
is then going to be presented back to
you as a full breakdown of where where
you should be at the end of to we would
like to have the environment scan built
in well what I'm trying to figure out is
if I invest today will next round be
like a double or triple the price
otherwise there's no reason for me to
invest today right let's imagine you
invest today in two years from now the
data that we would have gathered from
movement that nobody else is gathering
from how people are working from home
will put us in a position where the
following round that we go for will be
5x what we're aiming for now just saying
collecting data will be enough to get 5x
the price that's to me like feels like a
really different business where it's
like okay let's spy on the SP spy on the
employees like make sure that they're
kind of like being productive and
working we have uh desks that move up
and down they are standing they don't
use what you say and yeah and I think
that well usually what typically happens
is that uh you know we got the ones that
have the the memory and everything like
that you can just push a button it
immediately go to the next setting
pretty much every single person they
either keep it up or they keep it down
they're not moving it up and down you
know all all the time I mean this kind
of gets the other part of the problem
which is like well like you're trying to
change people's behavior yeah right and
like it's going to be like oh and then
you know how do you do it in another way
that it's going to be like that it's
going to be accepted by the by the users
they going to be like you know is it
like the nag screen that's going to come
up and say like hey it's time for you to
to to get up and walk around or is it
like hey I mean because I think it would
be if you just give hey I have the
options of like putting my desk up or
down I have options of putting it my
laptop on know higher or lower uh I mean
the the stuff that I've seen is that
people I mean often people aren't aren't
doing that which is I mean it's part of
the root of the problem where it's like
okay people have bad posture because
they don't even realize like like
necessarily they have they have this bad
posture but then also like you don't you
don't um you know it's challenging to be
like the kind of Nag wear whatever
that's going to be like oh well well the
camera shows that you're slouching why
like why why why don't you set up
straight stuff so what what are what are
your thoughts there brilliant question
and I'm glad you all in fact the um the
house we were kind of uh joining and and
we're staying with um have a hack house
and they have standing desks we have we
all have standing desks we don't use
them and in fact I'm I'm going to say
something that's that's probably going
to sound controversial but standing
isn't the answer to go from sitting to
just standing it's recently been proven
that you'll burn a few more calories but
it's not solving the problem which is
why we pivoted in 2023 towards movement
and towards creating behavioral change
by benchmarking using the humble Works
app once you understand where you are in
context of a leaderboard cuz that that
will be part of the next step and how
you've performed the metrics that you're
now playing with or the switches you're
now turning up and down are going to be
or the ones that are uh available to you
is mood move and productivity so what
our goal is is to show you over a period
of time as a baseline here's where you
are and after a few weeks it takes 21
days and so what's the time period I
mean like in terms of like hey I
implement this like at what point am
going to see the ROI our goal is to go
into a company and to propose a 25% roll
out to their work from home stuff right
to find the teams that would be
reluctant resistant or the teams that
would jump on and say yeah I'm I'm up
for this the early the early adopters
all the way through the ones that can to
be relaxant right and the app is going
to set a baseline over three weeks it's
going to set a Baseline and the the
Baseline for that app would be here's
where we are before the humble work
suite comes in and allows us to move
from position to position here's me
sitting down hunched over my laptop like
everyone else in those 1.3 billion
information workers right
and then three weeks later we introduced
The Humble work Suite from that point on
with within three months our goal is to
show productivity Spike whether it's a
few perc or goes all the way up to what
we're promising at 17% there's going to
be a marked difference in productivity
so maybe we could talk about like what
the current status is you know how many
units are deployed how much data are you
getting per month right now all that
we've just completed the the the full
build so the entire humble works is
bootstrapped so built it from scratch
and at the end of 2023 I pivoted away
from just selling standing desks by
themselves we focus on building the tech
building the full suite and use the uh
so you're right now in the process of
getting the data and all that right now
absolutely so right now in the process
of Market penetration and and and and
adops to encourage movement uh many of
our some of the meetings are we just
walking meetings we just walk around the
block so that that's why I'm not sure
this you know app or chair will would
make a difference no of course see see
imagine this as this point where
nobody's done this before up until this
point everyone's very easily said I'll
spend £3,000 on a an expensive ergonomic
chair that'll go up back will go in and
that's it and nobody's really embraced
this idea of what if we change this the
the entire status quo if we change the
dynamic and we we built this homogeneous
way of working where all of my employees
are now working in the same way if I set
up an office I wouldn't allocate and
just throw a budget out and say right
you can have a sofa if you'd like you
can have this sort of chair you more
than the office would be fair sterile
and look quite homogeneous with a
similar setup along the way thank you I
appreciate it I think today's Q&A helped
me understand the gaps um the linear
storytelling and um the presentation of
the pitch that can then mitigate the
gaps you would get towards the the Q&A I
feel like I answer the Q&A as best as I
could uh but possibly having more uh
tangible and statistical U evidence at
the Q&A would have helped because it's
almost like you have your appendix ready
and your appendix could then validate
the rest of the the questions there and
then so possibly having an appendix and
helping shape the framing the pitch in
in a structured order that would help
the dot te is is just this absolute uh
logical next step to have um a um an
easy way for people to understand it's
not a standing Des company anymore it's
now a technology company and this is
where we're going and dotech shortcuts
that process or I imagine hopefully
shortcuts that process are people going
oh that's humble Works they do standing
desks no they humble works. Tech and
they must have a tech site to this what
is that tech oh there's an app and now
there's a manager report and now there's
uh AI bills into it I found that uh uh
the quantitative uh benefit
to be a little questionable what I mean
by that is uh uh um his product is just
starting to get deployed right now and
as a result he doesn't have a lot of
data back yet and so he can't say
because of his product we get these
benefits instead what he's saying is is
that uh if you do these kind of things
like more Mobility you get these
benefits and the product can do these
things and therefore the product product
will be able to provide and so I I see
logically what he's trying to do and and
if I him I would try to sell too when it
comes to presentation I thought humble
Works was by far the best presenter
right that doesn't sound like an AI
recommendation no that I mean like that
because they was they called us because
they called me that like your system is
crazy customers don't like Dynamic
pricing because it's like wait a second
oh you got you got a different price
than I got when I like when I went you
know went went to for this or like it's
you know there's a lot of backlash
around surge pricing and like these
these sorts of things which ultimately
ends up getting a brand risk
[Music]