[Music]
Hello dragons. My name is Ben. I'm Joe.
And I'm Oliver. And our company is Lux
Collective. We buy and sell pre-loved
luxury items. So we grew up in a place
called Formbby. And when we say that to
people, they automatically assume, well,
you come from a lot of money. But for me
and Joe, that's far from it. One
Christmas, my sister asked my mom for a
pair of £400 trainers.
£400? Why is my sister getting a pair of
£400 trainers when our budget for
Christmas is always
£100? So, I went to my mom and asked why
my sister has a bigger budget than me.
She told me they were from a secondhand
online luxury
marketplace. And I became obsessed with
this website, but I knew I could do it
better. I knew I needed a business
partner. So, I knocked on my brother's
bedroom and it took him about 3 seconds
to verbally sign the contract. So, we
started buying items off eBay and Depot
with clean them up and would sell them
on Instagram for more. We've now amassed
over 1.8 million followers. And last
month alone, we got over a 100 million
views across our main three social media
channels. Since incorporation in
December 2020, we have seen sales
revenue exceed 8.5 million pounds. We
are here today to ask for £100,000 for a
2% equity share in our company. What's
it called the company? Lux Collective.
Lux Collective.
Thanks for listening. I'm going to pass
you over to Ali who's going to give you
a quick demo on how it works.
A rags to rich's tale from brothers Ben
and Joe Gallagher and their colleague
Oliver Miller. Basically, this is our
website. Um, and we drop stock every day
of the week. And that can be anything
from bags, footwear, and accessories,
all from the top designer brands.
They're offering 2% of their designer
goods resale platform in exchange for
£100,000. So, that's more like the
buying side of things, but obviously we
do have customers who sell to us, so
that's where all the stock originally
comes from.
Sara Davies is first up to find out more
about the company.
Right guys, so is the business wholly
owned by the three of you at the moment?
Yes, 100%. And so when you say you've
done uh 8.5 million in sales to date,
yeah, give me the last few years since
you launched. So in 21 we did 2.5
million in sales revenue and a net of
285K. In year 2, 3.8 8 million in
revenue and a net of
255k. This year we're predicted and on
track to do 6.5 million in revenue and
to do a net profit of 420k.
That is very impressive. Thank you. Very
impressive. Thank you.
You're clearly printing cashier in terms
of the net profit of your business. So
you've come in today asking for 100k. It
begs the question why why have you come
here? So the next step for our business,
we want to go into retail like your
Selfridges, your Harrods. We want to
have a store in there. Why? There's a
case study in America of a company very
similar to us who've done the exact same
thing. And I think they were on about
$15 million of revenue in 2018 and 2019.
It went into Nean Marcus. Nean Marcus is
a store in America. And now they're at
$500 million worth of revenue. So we
want to basically do that in the UK. So
why do you want a dragon? because we do
not know where to start at all with with
detail of how to get in.
So just thinking about your strategy
going into Selfridges or a Hower,
how does that match their strategy
working with the brands? So for example,
you're now got a nice store in store in
Selfridges. The brands obviously want to
encourage the sale of new product. Mhm.
Selfridges make good money off the back
of that new product and the new guys
roll into town to encourage their
customer not to buy that new product
when they can buy the same product that
somebody has discarded for half the
price. Yeah. How do you think the
brands, this is the specific question,
how will the brands react to Selfridges
for allowing you to be in that store? So
at the moment, Selfridges actually have
their own thing called
reselfridges, which from my personal
opinion and looking at it is not very
well done. So they are actively doing
it. Well, they're doing it on the back
of working with the brands, aren't they?
I can promise you they would have got
authority and gone to the brands that
they work with and said, "This is our
pre-loved area of our business model.
This is how we're going to really hold
that customer in tight for you, Mr.
Gucci, Mr. that Eve Salaron, you're
coming in as three disruptors and taking
their customer and I think that that's
flawed. I don't think you've got any
chance. And the reason why I think that
that's complete wrong for you to go
there is because I think what you have
and what you've done I think is
fantastic and I think you've got a huge
opportunity to take this to a 60 70
million pound business doing exactly
what you do. But I wouldn't pivot into a
strategy that when you don't understand
how that works across those luxury
markets. Okay? But I think what you have
here you could build upon and I think
you could force yourself into a
situation where a selfridges goes you
could become our pre-loved. I want to
acquire this business. That's an
opportunity that you should be selling.
Okay.
[Music]
So, and so you said 100,000 for 2%. Yes.
So, you're valuing it at 5 million? Yes.
5 million? Yeah. Yes.
So, I'll tell you what. I'll tell you
where I am. Okay. Um, some people in
this den wouldn't get out of bed for 2%.
Not looking at anyone in particular, but
you're offering a a small stake in your
business. Yeah. But to have somebody
motivated to want to get really involved
in your business, they're going to want
to take a significant proportion of your
business. And so, you're going to have
to give away a lot more of your business
if you're going to walk out of here with
a dragon. Okay. Okay.
My personal opinion is you just need to
go and make hair while the sun's shining
and the sun is shining really really
bright and you just need to get your
foot on the gas and go for it. And if
you go for it in a big enough way doing
a lot more of what you're doing, some
big guy is going to come along and buy
you up or buy part of you because they
you are a pain in their behind and you
can scale this business without anybody
coming
in. I'm sat here thinking would I like a
chunk of this business? Absolutely. But
then I feel like you would resent me
because I'd won such a significant chunk
of your business. You'd get to the point
in six months time where you'd be really
frustrated and saying, "Why did we give
her all of that chunk of the business
when she's just told us to do more of
what we're doing?" Cuz that's
essentially what you need to
do. So, I'm going to shoot myself in the
foot and tell you that I'm not going to
invest and I'm out.
Yeah. I I'm I actually think the same.
Um, I'm not going to make you an
offer, but I'm going to wish you the
very best and say that I'm out. But
congratulations. Thank you. I appreciate
that pizza.
Do you know what? I'm going to make you
an offer
cuz I just I just really like you guys
and I think it'd be loads of fun to work
with. I know all the people around your
space and I think a lot of the value can
just be done connecting you with those
people. So I'm going to offer you all of
the money for 5%.
Interesting. Thank you very much. Thank
you. I appreciate that. Thank you. To
me, you're just the whole package as far
as entrepreneurs are concerned. You
know, you're just you just got you came
up with an idea. You you've done it and
you're turning over 6.5 million last
year. I mean, that is phenomenal. No,
they haven't. That's this year. Oh,
that's your projected. Yeah. Yeah. So, I
too am going to make you offer and I'm
not going to make it easier for you cuz
I also want 5% of the business. Okay.
Thank you, Deborah. Thank you very much.
[Music]
And there was one. Yeah. Look, um the
business looks
rosy. However, you get a few bad months,
it could turn. Yeah. And I think you're
going to need some strings pulled.
H to make things happen. And I've got 50
years experience this business, but I'm
not going to give myself away for 5%.
So, I'll make you an offer. Mhm. I'll
give you all of the money, but I want
10%. Cuz I believe that I can catapult
you quicker.
Thank you very much. Thank you. Can we
go and talk to the wall? Talk to the
wall. The window.
A trio of offers for the secondhand
luxury
traders. Steven Bartlett and Deborah
Meden have each pledged all the money
for 5%. Whilst fashion mogul 2 Casilian
has valued his industry expertise at 10%
considerably higher than the 2% that was
originally on the table. We'd go to four
to three. Go to four. Okay. Will the
young entrepreneurs be as impressive at
negotiating as they are at producing
high
profits? Uh
uh thank you for all your offers. I
right we really appreciate it. Um so
like when I was 19
um I kind of like didn't really like the
direction my life was going in. So like
I decided like I need to start working
on
myself and um I started listening to
your podcast even and like the
conversations you've had with all these
people really helped me get back on
track and live a like I never thought
I'd be in this position now showing you
guys my business that has turned over
whatever. Like you've helped me out a
lot man like I appreciate it. Um,
can someone help me out? I think I think
we prefer I think we would prefer to
work closer with Steven. Fine. The
difference is you're getting eight years
of experience with me getting 50 years.
It's fantastic experience. Have we got a
deal? I think we have to I think we
would prefer to agree. Well, we would
definitely want to return. I think 5%
for us is too high. Right.
We would do we would do 3%. That's where
we're at, Stephen. And like we would
shake hands on a day at 3% right now.
Can we meet in the middle?
I think 3%'s a good deal.
So, you wouldn't be willing to go to 4%?
Sometimes in the den, you know, some
sometimes in the den want to see a bit
more willingness to negotiate and meet
in the middle and I'm I'm I'm a dragon,
so I'm meant to be like tough guy that
you know is going to like I don't know
throw the money at you tell you to
whatever. But I just I'm in love with
what your story. I'm in love with what
you're doing. I think you're great guys
and I'd love to work with you. So, in
this case, I'm accepting the 3%. You got
a deal? Yeah.
Success for the lads from Liverpool as
Ben's tough stance pays off and Steven
Bartlett pays up. Celebrate. Thanks very
much. Thank you very much. Now they have
their dream dragon. The question is
what's next for the business?
Um, definitely not retail.
It went down like a leather.
I used to push trolley and now I'm
working with Steven Bartley. I never
thought I'd be in front of him in
Dragon's Den. I actually thought I'd be
opposing him on on his podcast,
but it just so happens that this was
first. You absolute soft touch. I know.
They played you like a fil. They had no
negotiating power. Stroked your ego.
Steven, we love your podcast. You know
what? I looked at it and I thought the
ego aside when I do that deal with them.
I would. Yeah, it's a good deal.